<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So am I, but I'd rather die on my own terms. I understand where your coming from, my boyfriend understands and so do my family but they don't quite get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean. I don't want to get better. I miss my Psychosis and Depression. I think I deserve it and I'm not sure my antidepressants are working but my Risperidone is.  I want my cause of death to be suicide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 13:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when people worry about me. I know they do it out of care, but it makes me feel worse for making them worry so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 08:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear that.  
I don't cope very well, it's all I can think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 00:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I understand that.  
Fair enough, my worst track on MK is Rainbow Road. 
I'm not sure, I can't tell what I've been feeling but I have been suicidal for the past few hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so used of being alone that I prefer it, I've always been alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, it's just mindless violence but it's fun.  
MK: Yoshi or Diddy Kong. 
SSBB: Kirkby or Pokemon Trainer 
What about you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 14:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I've heard that about League Of Legends.  
I play GTA 5, Mario Kart and Super Smash Bros online sometimes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 09:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix mostly. My favourite thing to watch is Orange Is The New Black but I'm currently watching Hells Kitchen with my family.
I play PS3, GTA 5, Fallout 3, Minecraft, Skyrim and Skate 3, you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 09:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is, I haven't volunteered and tried a service before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing my boyfriend. No, I was but I got pulled out by my Family.  I used to be into photography and I do like trains, music and video games. I used to be a keen bird watcher too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that goes well for you.
I know but it's hard. 
Not much, TV and consoles and that's it. 
Awesome,  never heard that and Iron Maiden is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 13:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly but my parents still aren't letting me out by myself which is pissing me off, it feels like I've been grounded for something out of my control.  
I can't play that many songs on the piano. 
Slayer's Seasons In The Abyss,  you?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 12:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I suppose. I still can't tell what I'm feeling, and I've still got lack of motivation and focus and still a bit suicidal, even with these antidepressants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 12:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I know I've only been taking these antidepressants for a few days but I still can't tell what I'm feeling, lack of motivation and lack of focus.  I can still get suicidal.  
I'm not very good at the piano lol  
Fair enough, I can listen to anything like Deftones to Saxon, or Shining to Dream Theater. Very wide variety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 23:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, I can spare that as I still live with my parents. 
I like to make stuff up, you? 
What's your favourite Metal Band? 
That song is good but my favorite is Seasons In The Abyss  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 22:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is it? 
The local gym is 30 a month, I can't remember how much it is for a year.  
Yes it does, it's a good instrument to play. 
I listen to mostly all Metal. 
It used to be Slayer, but now I don't have a favourite  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are being all helpful.
Excersize is meant to help Depression,  that's why I'm thinking of going. 
I hope you are well.
Ah I play the piano, mostly Metal, you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 16:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand but some people tend to see the worst and overthink things. I'm sure they will, your nice and friendly.  
Ok that's good,  is the gym helpful?  
Ok I'll keep that in mind.  
Music helps my my family and boyfriend thinks my music is too negative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 09:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you are coming from but I don't want to go to the Hospital again.  
Ok well I hope that goes well, I'm sure it'll be fine but I understand why you are worried :)  
What is it like going to the gym? II might start going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 08:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they'd get very worried abd win;t trust me anymore.  
It's part of the hospital stay but you can have it separtly too.  
What happened if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 19:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I understand but I'm not telling anyone I tried to hang myself yesterday. I am getting therapy but it's not helping anymore.  
That's fine,  I hope the Doctor went well,  I enjoy talking to you, your nice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 15:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to be an immediate danger to yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 14:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where your coming from but I don't know if I'm worse enough to go back.  
You are let out but you need to have a check in to see how your doing and it depends how well your doing. 
Yeah, I'd hate that to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 13:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was effective.  
It was free on the NHS,  I'm in the UK. I stayed there overnight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 13:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what stopped it the first time, but my Psychosis has gotten a lot worse which has brought back my Depression. 
We had a community meeting every day, had a named nurse each day and had different therapy like Art, Group ect and Individual Therapy once a week but I had Individual Therapy twice a week.
The normal stay for that unit was 3 months, I was there for 7 months and 2 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 13:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family loves Spongebob.  
Not all the time but I have told then about that.  
Yeah pretty much, we are having the crisis team round later today to see if I need to go to Hospital again. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 12:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've heard that.  
It's usually my sister who says I don't eat enough.  
Watching stuff like Spongebob,  I only got diagnosed again yesterday.   
I don't know, it just feels that way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 12:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done a lot, it's likely to be very painful.  
I have to be encouraged to eat and do stuff.  
They know, they understand but I don't think they get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 12:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jumping off the multistorey carpark,  it's a 10 min walk away.  I know they will, and I know it'll destroy my boyfriend,  but I'm in so much pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 11:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I know how I want to do it but my parents won't let me out by myself. I tried to hang myself last night but they don't know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 11:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm too scared of what happens afterwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 10:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very well, I constanly want to kill myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 10:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do I.  
I think Psychosis is from bullying, and PTSD is from sexual abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 09:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it wouldn't boher me if I died tommorow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 09:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I haven't been on them before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 09:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been diagnosed with it again. I haven't had it for 3 years. I'm dissapointed in myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 09:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, any Metal or anyone from the Strange Music label I could listen and recommend to for hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 09:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I haven't checked in a while. I'm sorry to hear about your daughter, I hope she gets better soon, 
The Doctor did say my Psychosis is getting worse, and she said I have Depression too. Ok I'll take a look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 09:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to the Doctor, they upped my dose to 4mg and put me on an antidepressant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 09:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I got put into Hospital they thought I was slightly autistic, I used to cut and OD.
My boyfriend has Aspergers and he used to hit himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 09:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't know what I'm feeling most of the time.  
We'll, 3 years ago I got Hospitilazed and diagnosed with PTSD, and eating disorder and the main one is Severe Depressional Episodes with Psychotic symptoms. This has developed into Psychosis which have been getting worse over the last year.
I've been hearing voices and seeing things for 8 years, had feelings of unreality and mood swings for 10 months, and I've been having delusions, lack of interest/motivation/focus, not been able to feel anything, sometimes being extremely quiet, blanky staring and been very suicidal over the past month.  
My Dad thinks it's Depression again, butI'm scared it's developing again into something else.  
I'm on 3mg Risperdone, which had to be cut down to 2.5mg as I was constantly suicidal. My meds are losing their effectivness but I'm seeing my Therapist and Psycharist today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 08:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DBT and Mindfullness worked wonders for my Mum. Look into it, it might be useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 08:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could try to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but not as much as before. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 23:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told them and they put me on suicide watch.  
Well, 3 years ago I got diagnosed with Severe Depressional Episodes with Psychotic Symptoms but now it's just Psychosis but my parents think my Depression is returning.  
I'll try not to buts it's so hard to deal with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 08:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what to think at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 08:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know.I shouldn't but I still feel like a burden,  thanks for the e -hugs, sending some back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't anyway, my parents have me on suicide watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've told them, they put me on suicide watch. My Dad is going to stay awake till 4, then he's waking my mum up so he can go to sleep and my Mum will stay awake. It feels like I'm inconviencing them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I'm serious enough to go inpatient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Told them, they put me on suicide watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their reaction. I told them and they've basicly put me on suicide watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 20:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it'll be ok, I just don't want to be taken to the Hospital again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 20:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'll give it a shot but I'm nervous just thinking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 20:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand but it'll be benifical in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 20:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how to bring it up. I don't think I can keep myself safe.  
I don't know if I want to fight anymore,but I know I need help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I have some advice on how to tell my parents and therapist I've been making daily trips to the multistory carpark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a frequent poster on /r/SuicideWatch and extremly suicidal. I also suffer from Psychosis.  
I think my parents and therapist need to know over the past few days I've been making daily trips to the multistory carpark.  
I don't know how to break this to them, they're already worried about me as it is. Any advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 20:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you try different things? I know it's hard but sometimes you just have to embrace fear :)  
Yeah, I've got that a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I have some advice on how to tell my parents and therapist I've been making daily trips to the multistory carpark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 19:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a frequent poster here and extremly suicidal.  I also suffer from Psychosis.  
I think my parents and therapist need to know over the past few days I've been making daily trips to the multistory carpark.  
I don't know how to break this to them, they're already worried about me as it is. Any advice?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 19:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went there, then had a horrible run-in with a rude guard who was locking up the carpark. I posted in it in /r/offmychest  
I think I need to tell my parents I've been making daily trips to the multistorey carpark near us but I don't know how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This is a garage...you know, for people with cars?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 19:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that. I'm suicidal,  not ignorant. I know what a fucking garage is. You must see me on the CCTV Cameras, pacing about like a feral on the top story...ever wondered why I've been up there the last few days?  
I would've told you why I was up there but your attitude was so appalling I just walked away...fuck you,  you made me feel so much worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 14:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I am but that's because of my Psychosis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 14:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand,  is there any clubs around you that you can join? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 13:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 10:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there must be something. What used to make you happy?  
Do you have any pets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 09:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sorta believe in recarination because of that small bit of energy that doesn't dissappear after we die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 09:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done my research so I know the success rate.  
I'm willing to take that chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 09:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand how tough it can feel, I've had mental heath problems since I was 12, and I'm 20 now, heck I'm even planning my suicide.  
I know it's not that easy, but it might help to think positive and surround yourself with things that make you happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm ready to die, I'm sorry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 08:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my Dad, Mum, Lana and Michael, you all knew of my mental health problems. But I always found it hard to talk about it. These metal health problems, even though the Psych Doctor said we need to find the root of the problem, I think I already know it. I think it's a mix of genetics, what happened to me in Foster Care, upbringing and bullying. I'm tired, I'm never going to escape. It's a day-to-day battle, even with my meds.  
I won't be able to keep myself safe if I carry on, this is getting to the place I was before I went into Hospital.  
I'm sorry for being a burden, and none of this is anyones fault but my own. I should've jumped earlier.  
Those daily walks? Walks to the multi-storey carpark to see if I had the courage to jump off. And I finally do.  
Maybe I'll finally be able to escape. Thanks for trying to help but I just can't be helped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm ready to die, I'm sorry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 08:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my Dad, Mum, Lana and Michael, you all knew of my mental health problems. But I always found it hard to talk about it. These metal health problems, even though the Psych Doctor said we need to find the root of the problem, I think I already know it. I think it's a mix of genetics, what happened to me in Foster Care, upbringing and bullying. I'm tired, I'm never going to escape. It's a day-to-day battle, even with my meds.  
I won't be able to keep myself safe if I carry on, this is getting to the place I was before I went into Hospital.  
I'm sorry for being a burden, and none of this is anyones fault but my own. I should've jumped earlier.  
Those daily walks? Walks to the multi-storey carpark to see if I had the courage to jump off. And I finally do.  
Maybe I'll finally be able to escape. Thanks for trying to help but I just can't be helped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 07:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not that great at helping, but I'm sure people can help you.  
Have you been to your Doctor?
I understand where you are coming from, I'm sure you can learn how to change. There's help availble for everyone, just don't give up yet :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 07:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks you, I hope I can but I'm not sure how without getting drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say around 12. My first attempt was at 14/15. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may not know you, but we are willing to help. Why? Because hardly anyone likes to see people suffer. I know I don't. We do care, and that is why we are willing to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 17:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nearly climbed over the barriers yesterday. I did the first part, got my foot in the other hold and nearly hoisted myself up before I got a phonecall. I was so very close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 15:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what it's like. I got pulled out of College due to my mental health getting worse by my parents and sister.  
I hear voices saying I'm a burden, go jump, don't eat, self-harm, something bad is going to happen ect...  
They always insult me, and the increase of dosage in my medication has made me more suicidal.  
I'm always willing to talk if you need help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 13:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your up to it, hike. It gets you into nature and exercise makes you feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 13:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not depressed, but I have Psychosis.  
I only took 2mg instead of my 3mg, so my voices are playing up and I'm getting mood swings. I'm still suicidal, but not as much as I was on 3mg.  
So far I've watched Family Guy with my sister who made me eat, and I'm halfway through watching a program on cats with my Dad.  I'm tempted to go to the carpark and jump off, I nearly climbed over the barrier yesterday. Let's see how it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 12:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there can be, I'm not depressed but I'm suicidal, though I am on meds for Psychosis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 20:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a PS4, but I have a PC that might run it but I'm a Console Gamer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 13:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you just have to embrace the fear. Or it will subside naturally. I'm doing it soon and I'm nervous, but I'm interested to see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 10:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm exactly like that. I hate being on meds but they should be changing me to injection soon so I can't miss a dose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 22:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be real nervous and excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 13:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm with my boyfriend at the moment,  he knows but I'm not sure he fully understands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 13:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seeing her later today, I don't know what else I can do. I'm worried I'm developing Paranoid Schizophrenia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so paranoid and I don't know what to do. It feels like I'm going even more insane then I'm already am. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 08:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that this is all in my head, but it's scaring me.  
People around me being replaced.  
People poisoning my food.  
Government brainwashing us from the Tv and getting cancer causing lights.  
I suffer from Psychosis, I see a therapist and am on 3mg Risperidone,  my meds don't help with the thoughts but have only had these thoughts the last couple of weeks and it's making me so scared. I had to be sent home from College because I was so scared.  I don't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 22:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, 3mg Risperidone. I absolutely hate it because it feels weird without my Psychosis and my symptoms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 22:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My death is likely to send my mum back to hospital. 
The person who's going to kill themselves after I do is my boyfriend. He used to suffer from Severe depression and anxiety before he met me, and he has said my death would send him back to that but much, much worse. He's terrified of losing me and he has said once I kill myself,  he won't be far behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 12:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only when I break down, which is something which is happening more often recently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 08:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bring it up, they already know because my mum made me send them a text.  
Level 2 Diploma in Animal Care  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 00:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, I'm seeing my therapist on Tuesday. I've never liked taking them, it feels too weird without my Psychosis and my meds aren't helping with my paranoia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I post here at least once a week. I'm pathetic. This time it's my paranoia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 00:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This time it's because my paranoia is tearing me apart. I can't handle the feeling of being watched all the time, meds and food being poisoned,    government brainwashing us from the Tv ect.  
It's affecting my eating, it's gone right down. I'm refusing to take my meds again. I've only been having these thoughts for around 2 weeks and I'm more suicidal then I've been in months. Maybe my parents are right. That my head is so messed up I can't deal with College.  
A few more days of hell and I'm done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 09:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, wearing black all the time and listening to bands like Slipknot, Avenged Sevenfold, Muse ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 09:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a bank account, I'll look into it.  
Ok that's helped a bit.  
My family and my boyfreind, it makes me miserable. They won't let me miss one dose, but I'll figure out how to skip a few. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 08:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for thinking I'm not that crazy, but I also think the people around me might of been replaced.  
I knowthat if I stop taking them, I won't be so nervous about dying, People make me take them but I've got a few ideas to fake taking them.  
I've never tried drugs, I don't know how to get away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 08:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm either going to spend one more week with my boyfreind and jump next week, or I'm going to jump today.  
I've had mental health problems for around 9 years. I'm just tired.  
I was going to do it yesterday but my Dad stopped me.  
I hate myself, and my parents want me to stop College so there's my only purpose of living gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 12:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, this time feels a bit different. This time I'm not letting my boyfriend know of my plan.  
I've been getting so paranoid recently. Been getting delusional, lights causing cancer, people recording me and the government brainwashing us through TV. It got so bad I was shaking on the coach back from College because of the lights. I've only been getting delusions for a week.  
And my Risperidone doesn't help with that, and it's been causing nosebleeds ever since it's been increased.  
Anyway, I think I'm done. Still nervous about dying but, fuck it. I'm doing this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was peaceful, and I did break down ,  it was terrible. I know what you mean,  I do feel better afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 21:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather jump then do any other method. The only reason I considered hanging is cause I was really desperate.  
I know that's a real possibility but I think I'm finally ready to take that chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 19:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean. I'm sitting in a park trying not to break down because there's no place private enough to hang myself,  they could of let me jump on Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 12:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to music. Usually Shining, Slipknot or Billy Talent. Sometimes Tech N9ne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 10:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand how frustrating that is, it's happened before to me but that ended with me in Hospital for 7 months.  
I have but he says it wasn't a waste of time, which it was to me, and that they needed to know for my health. He doesn't know what I'm planning today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 10:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, 3mg of Risperidone,  got upped yesterday. I don't have anyone else to talk to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 10:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to die. I don't even know if I want to get better, because I don't deserve to and it'll feel too weird without them.  
I'm on 3mg Risperidone,  got upped yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tommorow I'm gonna try hanging myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 00:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've came so close. The last time I tried was on Saturday and my boyfriend took half an hour talking me down on the phone from the top of the multistorey carpark. Then I went to A   E that's made everything worse.  
My voices won't stop and I'm so fucking miserable.  
I don't want saving, if I don't do it tommorow I'm going back to the carpark on Saturday. Fuck this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to wait 5 fucking hours in the A   E yesterday because my boyfriend told my parents that I went to the multistorey carpark on Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pissed off at him, I know how much he loves me but he didn't have to get my parents involved.  
They decided to take me to the A   E Department yesterday to see if I was safe to stay at home.  
The whole experience has made me feel so much worse. Hopefully next week I can finally jump.  
Edit: And they increased to 3mg Risperidone which I'm really really not happy about.  
Why won't they just let me die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 18:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will, my boyfriend is coming with me to see if my meds can be increased, I'd rather see them decreased.  
Not really,  the only changed is I'm back at College,  and I moved out to live with my boyfriend and his family, but I'm still going back at the weekend, but this happened last year with the depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 14:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your point of view, however I suffer from Psychosis and have hidden my meds while my boyfriend is at college so he can't make me take them, the next time I'll have to take it is Friday,  I'll be at home then and my Dad will make me take it.  
Some people just don't want to get better. I think the best bet is to talk to his parents and explain what's been going on. They will be grateful that you contacted them but he will be mad at first but hopefully he'll understand that you did it out of concern for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm depressed again and I don't know what to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 12:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, the main thing I have to deal with is Psychosis, I'm on 2mg Risperidone for it.  
Three years ago I was hospitallized and got diagnosed with Severe Depressional Episodes with Psychotic Symptoms,  an eating disorder and PTSD.  
My depression has come and gone since then but it's been very mild, but over the past couple of weeks my mood has been terrible. I've been more snappy,  I've felt down most of the time, I've lost interest in things and I can't motivate myself. My hygiene could be better.
I've lost my appetite and I'm sleeping more and I've got way more suicidal.  
I see a therapist for my Psychosis and I'm seeing her tomorrow so I might mention it then, and I'm tempted to call my Dad and say what's been happening,  but I don't know what to do.  
Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 10:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi how are you doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 10:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi how are you today?
I'm not that good at advice so maybe a friendly chat would help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 10:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to die but I really don't want to live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 22:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the most recent album of theirs is Repentless,  brought out Sep 11 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 22:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, my 2 favourite genres of music is Metal and Rap.
Fave five music artists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 09:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental health problems and stress from College. I'm on meds but I absolutely despise taking them, I get forced to take them.  
And the fact I can't cut is getting to me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 09:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No probs, what music do you like? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 09:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No probs, what music do you like? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 08:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi you still here?
I'm not great at advice, maybe just a friendly chat about random stuff could help. We can chat about anything :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 08:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi you still here?
I'm not great at advice, maybe just a friendly chat about random stuff could help. We can chat about anything :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 07:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey have you tried reaching out to people?  
I know it's scary and I know it's hard but honestly,  once you've got the help you need, your life will feel so much better, trust me it's for the best :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why am I still wasting my time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 07:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter how worse I've gotten, I haven't had the balls to kill myself. I know where to go to and what with, but I just can't do it. I don't wanna live but I don't want to pass my pain onto anyone else, but I'm getting real sick and tired of it now and I think I'm gonna try again before Halloween. Hopefully I'm not a coward for once in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 07:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just get disappointed and sad that I haven't done it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 07:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted Slayers new album. That's it.  
They're my favorite band but I'm still around now so I'm getting worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 07:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi wanna chat? I'm not good at advice so we can talk about random stuff if you like.  
Hope you feel better soon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 06:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's been going on?
I'm sorry I wasn't able to stay up to chat, but we can still chat whenever you feel like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
