<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just tired of the entire democratic party being called liberals, because we aren't. I'm not. When there were Blue Dogs, I was one. Too bad they shot themselves in the foot and made themselves irrelevant. There are still dems who are middle-of-the-road; unfortunately, they've been co-opted by the DINOS. On a bell curve, we are actually the dominant part of the democratic party still, but the radical left and DINOs overshadow us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't that the Coffee Party (serious)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannity is insane. He'd say anything for attention. Talk about a narcissist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has to list all his business interests on tax returns. We want the ones that trace back to Russia and Putin. You would be surprised what a forensic accountant can do with those schedules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With IQs about 90 and severe need to be told what to do because they can't make decisions for themselves, probably never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember - RUSSIA! RUSSIA! RUSSIA! Don't be distracted by trivialities. This is unimportant compared to our President being a puppet of Putin or the country being run by white supremacists. 

I know there are responsible Republicans out there who don't want this either. Please speak up. COUNTRY BEFORE PARTY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On for chrissake -- who cares what taxes he paid in 2005? We care who he's in business with NOW, i.e., RUSSIA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, sorry, but all my links direct to a specific product, so that seller has to deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't get paid when they click your links. You get paid when they purchase something, and then only once the transaction has completed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a liberal. I'm actually more of what would be a Blue Dog if they hadn't destroyed themselves by being TOO conservative. I'm fiscally responsible and socially middle of the road. I can see where we need to rein in spending, but not like this. Not at the expense of the poor and elderly, both groups I belong to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is trollish bullshit. I'm a southern white Democrat, and we are all on the right side of civil and all human rights. We are not a dying breed. The Millenials are going to bring this party back in the South.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This country is on its last legs. I'm glad I won't live to see it fall, and I hope my children get out before it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read about this. This is the real reason they were ALL fired, although it's not unusual for a new administration to clean house. They usually do it slower, though, so as not to cause a logjam in the cases. In this case, this is EXACTLY what Trump wanted -- to stall the case until he can find a corrupt AG who won't prosecute it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only reading a little about politics nowadays, because -- depression and angst -- but if I have to put up with any more of this "He didn't mean/say what he said" bullshit, I'm going to go postal on somebody. WTF kind of idiot is Spicer to get out there and say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even more conservative if RBG dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I was just thinking how absolutely assinine this sounded, and thinking "Every leader in the free world, and probably most of the rest too, are laughing their asses off at this."

I feel sorry for Spicer. How much longer do you think he will last before he walks out and leaks the truth about Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 47%, and they aren't all under his spell anymore. Only 39% of them are. The rest were dems and independents that voted for him as a protest vote and mainstream "blue no matter who" voters who are getting very discouraged right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I've been on it for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were not good people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking or traffic, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for affiliate opportunites for my blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently in the process of monetizing my gardening blog, and I need some good affiliates. I have the major 3 - eBay, adsense and Amazon, but want something I can make better money on. I'd like to concentrate on things like garden tools   accessories   books. Anything on composting, organic gardening and permaculture is good.

Please PM me if you have any opportunities, and I'll send you the link to my blog. It is currently getting around 3,000 hits a month, which will be increasing now that spring is here. I'm registered through Clickbank, so if you have an offer there, let me know as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only pay U.S. citizens, so you have to prove you are one, not just someone who is claiming to be and using a fake SS#.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, they will fail everyone because they don't need anymore workers for that qual. I know it's cruel, but that's how it works. I'd say save up your last chance to do when they are calling for workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making "awful" money? Did you mean "awesome?" I don't want to do something that is awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave notice and left in good standing, and they wouldn't hire me back. They have a policy of not rehiring old workers, so I would think you have slim to no chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son tutored while in college, and he loved it, in fact, he's thinking of doing it again now part-time. 

You can "teach" all day long on sites like Udemy. I intend to do a few tutorials there soon, just to see how it goes. The good thing is that it's residual income after you take the time to set up the tutorial. I hear video tuts sell better and for more money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were you, I'd stick with MTurk and sites like that, where the tasks are simple and quick. It would help with your anxiety, and might be bolstered by your OCD, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I tend to forget about him because you don't hear much about him anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So what recent democracy have they overthrown and replaced with a military junta? 

You didn't answer my question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't his partner quit at one time because he was unstable, and start his own site? Whatever happened with that? 

Assange pretty much IS Wikileaks. I don't see how they could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not even AI, really. I'd rather be spied on by the CIA tapping my phone than have a weapons-ready drone hovering over my house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's o.k. We won't die by then. When it gets bad, someone will do something, just like they did in the 70s and in China just a few years back. Nobody wants to be known as "the man who allowed everyone in America to die of CO poisoning." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what recent democracy have they overthrown and replaced with a military junta? 

As far as I remember (the 1980's is a long time ago), none of this was ever really proven to be the work of the CIA alone, although they may have helped. They did start the whole crack epidemic and all, so there's that. Still, not all democracies are good democracies, and not all democratic leaders are good leaders. Case in point - Trump. Maybe we can get them to overturn his smarmy ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they ever cut it back on? If he keeps this up, they may kick him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that whole story. It doesn't take away from the good things they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a man pay a woman's outrageous fine to the city so they didn't put a lien on her house. It was ridiculous. They gave her a ten-day notice to cut her lawn. She was in the hospital, but called me, and I had someone to cut her lawn. He cut the front and was in the process of cutting the back when the city contractor showed up and made him stop. They cut the exact same lawn (3/4 of which was already cut) and charge 3x the going rate for the service. Plus the city wanted to charge her $250 administration fee. This kind man stood up and slammed $250 on the council's podium and told them they were horrible people to do that to a single mom. Turned out that there was a reporter there, who decided to look into things and found out the contractor was the BIL of someone in city government, and this wasn't the first time he had done this. When it was all said and done, there was a huge scandal, the guy lost his contract, and there was a city ordinance passed that contractors could not charge more than "the prevailing rate" for any service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, all that, but they also bust huge drug cartels and find and bring to justice international criminals. I bet they do a lot more of that than they do what you're talking about. There are many different arms of the CIA. Your scenario is only one. If we put them out of business, we would soon be overrun with international criminals and drug cartels taking over our country right out in plain sight. The CIA gets to them before the FBI needs to, in other words, it keeps them where they belong -- away from the U.S. No, they're not perfect, but I'm willing to bet that they have done a lot more good for this country than harm to it.

Watergate was a long time ago. Let it go. We need to concentrate on Russiagate now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there will be no wall. The GOP will keep Trump in there just long enough to push their agenda through, then they will turn on him and send him and all his men to prison where they belong. Who do you think will be the "John Dean" of the Trump administration? I'm thinking it will be Sean Spicer. He's getting pretty good at double talk and covering his own ass now. I can see him turning on Trump to save his own neck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I truly feel like being locked up for so long has caused him to go insane. He is definitely not the same Assange who walked into that embassy, who was all about justice and doing what was right. He's now all about revenge, and don't tell me he isn't tied up with the Russians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's definitely a Russian stooge. Why else would he want to keep the CIA from doing its job? I truly hate Assange now. He's not a hero anymore, he's just a crazy person locked up in an embassy who wants revenge on the world, but most especially, the U.S. I think they should kick his ass out and let him see what the CIA has on him and how fast he can be "disappeared" like so many other enemies of the state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just breathe! This won't last forever. Just work as hard as you can to win back Congress and take back the White House in 2020. We can undo everything they have done. The world isn't going to come to an end in 4 years, unless, of course, they start WWIII, THEN we are all screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sick GOP is foaming so much at the mouth over trying to get their anti-American, mysogynistic, racist platform passed that they're trying as hard as they can to keep Trump in office as long as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's now officially not just the administration that is racist, but the entire GOP and some complicit cowardly Dems. And the same people backing them are also trying to interfere in elections overseas. I see WWIII ahead, and this time, billions of people are going to die and half the world will be destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends who have found awesome designer framed glasses at Goodwill  and Salvation Army and had new lenses put into them. One even found some that were her exact prescription and in a case, so not scratched all up. She got what would have been a $600 pair of glasses for $20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My huge job is going through 12 years of pictures and photos I've never sorted and decluttered. Sometimes I just want to delete them all. I did go through and delete duplicates created by saving the same file over and over to an external drive, but having to go through one by one with a viewer and decide what to keep is going to take YEARS!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That whole article might as well be in Russian to me. I don't understand a bit of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds good, but the problem is that it's taking up too much counter space and there is nowhere else to put it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son's room used to get so messy, and he would get so upset when I told him to clean it because he got overwhelmed. I told him to take one thing at a time and put it where it belonged, then repeat until it was done. That's the only way to get through a mountain of stuff. One thing at a time. 

I have lupus, and my house gets messy sometimes, especially the kitchen, and especially now that I have such a small amount of counter space. I've been known to take everything off the tabletops and counters and put it into a pile on the floor in a place where I can't ignore it, then clean the table/countertops well. Just seeing those surfaces clean motivates me to go through the pile on the floor. It also gives me space to work. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have rid myself of so many clothes over the years, and now I wonder why I ever had so many. I still could stand to get rid of some old stained things I call my "slouching" clothes, and a few things I never wear. Think I'll do that this weekend. You've inspired me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ETA: Sorry, forgot to say congrats on the declutter success! 

I had a sister like that, only no matter how clean your house was, she could find something to bitch at you about. She chewed out my 80 yo mother once because there were fingerprints on her doorframes. I don't talk to her anymore, but I often wonder what her house looks like now that she is 74 years old and not able to get around well, and I wonder if she feels bad for how she treated her own freaking mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 years old. I'm telling you, millenials are going to save this world. So fucking amazing, they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know videos are good for your site, but overusing them is bad. Whatever you do, please don't make them autoplay or have that little video thingy that follows you down the page. I do everything I can to avoid sites with these monstrosities. I have blacklisted every single site I come upon that uses them, and a lot of people say the same. I love videos, and I don't even mind unobtrusive ads, but these things that attack you when you load a page make me want to scream! I will never put them on my sites, and if it means I make a little less money, so be it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use mine for a few other things besides warming too, like melting butter, softening frozen things. I just used it for softening some homemade ice cream made from leftover smoothie, but I can figure out another way to do those things. I'm going to clean it out and sit it by the dumpster tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have that problem, and I just had to learn to say "No, thank you. I have enough stuff now." Saying no to people who you care about is hard, because they are trying in their way to show they love you. I usually coo over it a bit, saying "Oh, that's really sweet/cute/beautiful/nice/etc. but I'm trying to only take in things I need right now, and I really don't need this." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't room to stack them in my kitchen, sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't live without a toaster oven. Waiting for a good one to come into Goodwill now. I'd much rather have a better toaster oven than a microwave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting rid of my microwave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only use it to reheat things, and it takes up way too much of my small amount of counter space. I didn't have one for awhile, then my friend who was staying with me bought me this one mostly because he wanted it. The ring under the glass broke, but it works o.k. without it, still, can't donate it. I'm thinking of putting it out by the dumpster with a "works" sign on it and letting it go. I'd honestly rather have the counter space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would insult me. I'd rather have them say they gave it to someone else who needed it more, or who especially admired it. If it represents such "a huge financial and time commitment" from you, perhaps you should ask before you gift it whether it's something they would appreciate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better in some ways, worse in others. Search engines grade you not only on how long people stay on a page, but overall on how long they stay on the site, how many links they click and how many pages they visit. I'd say never put over 1200 words on one page without breaking it up in some way, although some say no more than 800 and some say up to 1500. 

ETA There is something called a "bounce rate" that measures visitors who click in and quickly back out. If you have a long article, some visitors will click quickly back out because they don't want to read it all. I've done that too.

You may have to experiment, based on your topic. You are also graded on return visitors, so in my example, someone may leave after reading about varieties of blueberries, then when they get one, will come back to read about how to plant and grow them, then if they get pests will remember the site and come back to learn about how to control pests. This doesn't work for every topic, but it's a pretty standard way to get a higher ranking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I just heard it as a rumor, sorry. I don't feel like it would benefit them much, but Bezos seems to have gone batshit crazy lately, so who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone once told me to always go for higher priced items on Amazon and impulse items on Clickbank. I haven't done anything on Clickbank because they annoyed me with all their spam. 

The way I work Amazon is to write a product review and link to the Amazon product in a line that says "This is the best price I could find online for this product." People love bargains, and they by-and-large don't like to do a lot of comparison shopping. I also relate other items to the item I'm reviewing, like with diatomaceous earth for internal use, I will point out that while DE removes dangerous heavy metals, it also removes essential minerals that are metals, such as iron, zinc and copper, so I link to those supplements. To get them to buy a larger size, I point out that it is also useful in the home or garden to kill insect pests. 

Yes, Amazon commissions are painfully low, and there are rumors they are discontinuing their affiliate program soon, but if you "stack" products like I do, and link to the higher-priced items, you'll make more sales. You need to tell people WHY they should buy an item, not just throw up a link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone once told me to always go for higher priced items on Amazon and impulse items on Clickbank. I haven't done anything on Clickbank because they annoyed me with all their spam. 

The way I work Amazon is to write a product review and link to the Amazon product in a line that says "This is the best price I could find online for this product." People love bargains, and they by-and-large don't like to do a lot of comparison shopping. I also relate other items to the item I'm reviewing, like with diatomaceous earth for internal use, I will point out that while DE removes dangerous heavy metals, it also removes essential minerals that are metals, such as iron, zinc and copper, so I link to those supplements. To get them to buy a larger size, I point out that it is also useful in the home or garden to kill insect pests. 

Yes, Amazon commissions are painfully low, and there are rumors they are discontinuing their affiliate program soon, but if you "stack" products like I do, and link to the higher-priced items, you'll make more sales. You need to tell people WHY they should buy an item, not just throw up a link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone once told me to always go for higher priced items on Amazon and impulse items on Clickbank. I haven't done anything on Clickbank because they annoyed me with all their spam. 

The way I work Amazon is to write a product review and link to the Amazon product in a line that says "This is the best price I could find online for this product." People love bargains, and they by-and-large don't like to do a lot of comparison shopping. I also relate other items to the item I'm reviewing, like with diatomaceous earth for internal use, I will point out that while DE removes dangerous heavy metals, it also removes essential minerals that are metals, such as iron, zinc and copper, so I link to those supplements. To get them to buy a larger size, I point out that it is also useful in the home or garden to kill insect pests. 

Yes, Amazon commissions are painfully low, and there are rumors they are discontinuing their affiliate program soon, but if you "stack" products like I do, and link to the higher-priced items, you'll make more sales. You need to tell people WHY they should buy an item, not just throw up a link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Professional blogger/writer here. Most people only have the attention span to read about 600 words at a time, so put your most important material in the first 600 words if you're wanting to give information. By breaking up long articles in to pages, or even serial blog posts (part 1, part 2, or even different related topics) the mind does a "reset" every time it reaches another page, and starts again on the 600 word limit. Still, after a number of pages, the mind may have all the information it needs, and just not read the rest. This is why it's important to "front load" the most important info into the first part of an article. 

For example, I once wrote a series of articles on blueberries. I could have put it all into one large article, but instead, I broke it down into four 600-word articles on choosing a type and variety, how to plant, how to care for them and pests and diseases. I did this because some people are only looking for one of those topics and don't want to scroll through a 3,000 word articles to find the info. If they can't find what they want quickly, they'll click out and go elsewhere.

On a blog, how long a person stays on the site is just as important as the fact that they click on your search link. You don't want drive-bys, so you give things to them in bites with internal links leading to other bites.

As a professional writer, I think conciseness is the most important thing to learn. Say as much as you can in as few words as possible. I start out free writing, just letting thoughts flow, then I go back and tighten up the copy at least twice, also reading for spelling and grammar. Breaking long articles up into smaller, concise bites will help keep people on your blog longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't fall for that. Lyricists make big money. If you are really good, get an agent and register yourself as a lyricist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I did it a couple of years and bought a car with the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. She put her kids first. Now, with the money she would have paid for rent, maybe she can start a savings account for emergencies. I think this is wonderful, and I applaud her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who has been in this situation, she isn't overpaying. She probably gets back everything she pays in (aside from SS, of course), plus Earned Income Credit plus standard deductions for herself and the kids. I had a couple of years where I got back more than I paid in, but not by too much. It also may be her way of saving, by not claiming her kids than getting it back at the end of the year. I did that too, because money  in a savings account was too tempting to spend. Believe it or not, a lot of low-income people do this. It's stupid in a way, because no interest on your savings, but at the low rates they are paying for savings accounts nowadays, it's not that much of a loss, and you can't spend it on frivolous things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it odd that they closed your account for no sales. I've had my affiliate account for years and made hardly any sales, and it's still in good standing. What kind of website do you have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, use a pseudonym or don't have a byline at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG! I would have been very tempted to curse that person out! I'm so sorry you had to be subected to that kind of bigotry. 

I do feel like freelance editors fleece clients sometimes. That being said, I've had editors make a piece factually incorrect and requested that my byline be removed because I refused to have my name on such garbage. That usually got their attention. Only once did I have a person refuse to correct the piece or remove the byline, so I did a total rewrite of the piece on my own blog, corrected the errors, and noted that it had been made factually incorrect by an editor and the client refused to remove my name, so I wanted to correct the errors. Then I sent them a link to my blog post, and within hours, they had removed my byline with the understanding that I would remove my post.

You have to be a badass sometimes in this business. I do not let clients abuse me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for free courses on Coursera. Maybe learning more will get me higher level, better paying work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else sometimes feel like they should re-study English, or is it just me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to sometimes get the most nitpicky editors, and TBH, some of the things they say about my writing deficiencies are upper-level English (I'd say Master's Degree or better) that are way beyond what is expected for most online projects. 

I once had a HS algebra teacher who taught us from the HS book and gave us test problems from his first-year college algebra book. He didn't seem to see the difference in complexity, but there was enough so that half of the class was failing, and the curve was outrageous. No one got an A and only one boy got a B. I failed or just passed every test, and finally just stopped doing them at all, just put my name on them and turned them in. I made a C for the course. That's how big the curve was.

Anyway, what I'm saying is that I feel like I'm being given 8th grade work and graded on a graduate level. Wondering if anyone else has noticed this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just posted about getting fired, but I never did any work for them, so it's understandable. I have a feeling they lost the Microsoft contract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more like the academic survey websites that get posted here occasionally.

I love doing surveys at night when my brain is fried from writing all day. I make barely anything, but it's fun to see what academia is researching and it's $60-$100 a month I wouldn't have otherwise. It's all in your outlook, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be a great job for expats in cheaper countries to make some extra cash, but it's less than minimum wage here in the U.S. Still, it's all relative. If you need a bill paid and have no work available, you'll work for anything. I've done some pretty low-paying work to pay the bills. I have no "high horse." Sometimes I ride whatever horse is saddled up until I can get out from under. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else get dumped by Appen Crowdsourcing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got this email this morning. I never did any work for them, so not a big deal. Wondering if it's the end of the contract with Microsoft, or if they are not doing crowdsourcing anymore, or maybe they just dumped me for being inactive.

 Hello,
 
 Thank you for your interest in working for Appen as an Independent
 Contractor on the Crowdsourcing project. Regrettably, we cannot move
 forward with the contracting process. If you are due a balance, it will
 be processed in the next payment cycle.
 
 Action Required:
 * All Appen documentation is confidential as per the NDA signed with
 your contract. Please destroy all Appen and Microsoft documents from
 your email accounts, your computer's hard drive and any hard copies you
 may have printed.
 
 Thank you for your time and interest in Appen opportunities.
 

We wish you the best in future endeavors,
The Appen Crowdsourcing Team  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. Shared it with my other writing group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband (God rest his soul) was born on December 24. Until he met me, he never had a birthday party. We started celebrating my husband's birthday on March 1, the only month nobody else in the family was born.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they aren't hiring writers right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continuous Improvement Return

This might help you
http://www.marketing-dictionary.org/CIR+Planning+Process </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask for customer retention and tell them that you can't afford it, and if they can't give you a lower price, you'll leave. Works for me every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this every year for my internet service as well. Last year, I got dropped from $57 to $53 for a $75 service. I simple told them I couldn't afford $75 and asked for it to be shut off, told them I was moving to another company that had a great special going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never buy anything from China online. Had a friend who thought she had found a great deal on seeds from China, and ended up with weed seeds. The company refused to answer her messages, and finally closed that ID and opened under another ID. After a lot of hassle, eBay finally refunded her money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunshine kills odors. You can put the cushions out into the sunshine for a day or so to get the odors out. That will keep your roomie off the couch until you can have a talk about the BO problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just going to suggest this. You can also use it on any porous surface, such as ceramic tile or wood floors to remove smells. Our maintenance team here at the apartments uses it on tiles and walls all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like pickled beets, just buy a couple of cans of beets, drain them and put them into the juice for a week or so. I learned the hard way that you have to add red food coloring, or they beets turn a yucky brown color, but they taste just as good if you don't mind that.

I'm also going to try this recipe for making bread-and-butter pickles out of old pickle juice. I had another recipe for this, but can't find it now.
http://www.oldfashionedfamilies.com/the-very-easy-and-never-ending-jar-of-pickles/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In FL, you can do it all through a paralegal if it's amicable, even custody. You do have to go to a hearing if there are kids, but if not, nobody has to show up to the hearing at all. My ex got his first divorce (working on his second now - so glad I didn't marry him) through a paralegal service for about $50, I think. No kids involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they are still pretty much the cheapest store in town, although I'm seeing Save-a-lot's prices going down on some things since Aldi came to town. SAL is under new ownership, and they need to stay competitive. They are now trying to be a "hybrid" store, with low-priced food and lower prices on name-brand food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! I used to buy canned goods there because they were so cheap, but no more. What happened was when everybody started shopping dollar stores for food, they had a captive market, so they raised prices. I just saw where they have lowered a lot of prices on food items lately, around here it's probably a reaction to competition from Aldi and the new super WalMart, because before, they had no real competition in this neighborhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's still a great deal! Cheese in our regular stores is even $2.50-3.00 on sale. It's ridiculous. I love cheese, so I was thrilled at Aldi's prices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. I've eaten some crazy shit when I was broke, including lots of eggs, homemade biscuits, and grits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check that out. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We use d/b/a (doing business as), but that requires using your real name, and I'm not sure if we don't also have to pay for the d/b/a alias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They appeal to writers at the lower end of the scale who want security of payment. Mills are easy. You don't have a be a quality writer and you always get paid. My problem is when quality writers set themselves up on mills and work for well under 10cpw, and consider that good money. 

I use mills to fill in when there is no other work, but to me, that's what they are there for. Even a little money is better than no money at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I used to bake a lot, I froze eggs in ice cube trays and stored them. Now, I maybe eat a dozen eggs every two weeks, sometimes less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't eat that many eggs, so I don't worry about it. I can get them for $1 for 18 at Dollar Tree and usually $1 or under the large eggs most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you have health care. I'll bet you your higher prices aren't even as much as we pay for health insurance.

My son lives in Seattle, and his grocery prices are twice mine too, so it all depends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
