<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4692</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  nefarious

Huh? I am just trying to further the discussion because it is interesting... especially since most of us exist in a 9-5 world (that benefits the larks). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [downside](https://flowingdata.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/06/lisa-simpson-graph1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... when all the data is averaged across a population, the trend is that night owls exhibit more of these traits (i.e., #s 2-4 in your list) than morning larks. You would be considered an outlier in that sense. But we cannot all be outliers... from a statistical standpoint, this is simply impossible :P... I see your point, though, which is - I think - that we are all complex and multi-faceted, and might not always fit neatly into categories. But this isn't synonymous with being an outlier. These types of statistical analyses take into account all of these individual nuances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 18:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeppers - the link has been shown in several studies. Also, night owls have been found to be better at [inductive reasoning](http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/if-you-want-to-get-ahead-be-a-night-owl-8547115.html) (which "is linked to innovative thinking and more prestigious occupations").  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that yes, night owls (vs. morning larks) are at greater risk for mental disorders, however, night owls (vs. morning larks) have also been shown to have higher levels of general intelligence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 16:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 16:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not completely... night owls (vs. morning larks) have been shown to have higher levels of [general intelligence](https://www.psychologytoday.com/blog/the-scientific-fundamentalist/201005/why-night-owls-are-more-intelligent-morning-larks) and be better at [inductive reasoning](http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/if-you-want-to-get-ahead-be-a-night-owl-8547115.html) (which "is linked to innovative thinking and more prestigious occupations"). 

The [downside](https://flowingdata.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/06/lisa-simpson-graph1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 05:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had pretty severe bacne when I was your age - considering the age, it is likely hormonal. I was prescribed 75mg/ day of Spironolactone by my dermatologist. I also began using a mild laundry detergent and wearing a new, clean T-shirt to bed every night (no exceptions). I also applied 5% benzoyl peroxide lotion (from drug store) every night before bed (tip: get white sleeping t-shirts as the peroxide can bleach fabric over time). In the mornings I washed the area with Spectro gel as my last shower step (to wash away any shampoo/ conditioner) and applied some benzoyl peroxide lotion. My back is completely clear now. Honestly, I think the back acne was mostly hormonal and the Spironolactone did most of the work. You/ your parents should book an appointment to see a dermatologist regardless. Best of luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I think it would be a lot of fun to do, too. Did your girlfriend use something like http://www.livingdex.xyz/ to track her progress? Right now my boxes are organized by type so it will take some time to rearrange... we also just bought a subscription to Pokemon Bank so that will help. I just started playing X after finishing White... would it make more sense to go back to White to start catching for my Living Dex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 15:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great answer - thanks for clearing that up for me! I guess that also means that seeing a Pikachu wouldn't complete the entry for either a Pichu or Raichu. I'd have to breed/ evolve to do so, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shiny Charm question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 14:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this has been answered before, but I have been Googling and cannot find a definitive answer. In order to get the shiny charm, do I need a complete living dex? So, for example, will I need a Pichu, Pikachu, and a Raichu (3 pokemon), or will I just need to evolve 1 Pichu into a Pikachu then a Raichu (to have all 3 entries)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 11:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a couple people giving them away for free in KW. Google "kefir grains kijiji kitchener" and a few posts come up. Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 23:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, just for privacy. Had some bad experiences on the internets before... can't be too careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 15:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After buying a Japanese copy of Pokemon White, and trying (and failing) to breed a shiny Vulpix, I wanted to move on and MM for my favourite Pokemon, Pikachu. I caught a modest Japanese Ditto, traded it to my White game, and bred it - holding an Everstone - with my Raichu brought up from Diamond. After ~30 eggs, this little one hatched. It has a modest nature, and although it only has "decent" stats all around, it has "fantastic" potential for speed. I just finished EV training it in Special Attack and Speed, and let it evolve into a Pikachu (http://i.imgur.com/IkRvaGJ.jpg). Couldn't be happier! :oD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modest Pichu, my first MM shiny (only ~30 eggs)! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 15:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought a Japanese Pokemon game off a kid for $10 and have been trying my hand at MM for a Vulpix. Got bored (~300 eggs) and was taking a break zooming around the White Forest in Pokemon White when this little fellow appeared in a random encounter! The irony. Brave nature... so thinking of evolving him into Gallade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random encounter shiny Ralts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 06:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
