<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's more to it than money though. The guy has terminal lung cancer, and wasn't expected to survive 2016.

He's not going to be interested in squeezing a few extra dollars right now, nor does he have reason to be scared he'll be a victim of a terrorist plot, so it's likely his twisted view of the world comes from somewhere more visceral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it as a practical implementation of Maxwell's demon. That'll make you feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still alive? It's been 5 hours since you posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google is bringing virtual reality to its Chrome platform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm nominating the whole of the [Q Society](http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/inside-the-far-right-q-society-explosive-dinner-where-muslims-are-fair-game-20170210-gu9xo8.html).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably tired after the Q Club dinner.


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/inside-the-far-right-q-society-explosive-dinner-where-muslims-are-fair-game-20170210-gu9xo8.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the far-right Q Society's explosive dinner, where Muslims are fair game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mostly summarise and explain it there, but the summary misses a few interesting aspects. I've blocked it out below and bolded the key guts of the idea.

1. all of the chemical components of the atmosphere, mostly nitrogen and oxygen, but also carbon dioxide, water vapour and methane etc absorb or reflect different frequencies of light depending on their shape and size.

2. Light in some frequencies are strongly absorbed (and sent back down) by come of those components, notably carbon dioxide and methane, which is why they're called greenhouse gases. The frequency that's absorbed covers most of the infrared range of light spectrum 

3. There's a narrow range of frequencies that aren't absorbed by anything, so light at that frequency just goes straight through. **That range is between 8 and 14 m, and is called the infrared atmospheric window.**

4. Everything emits infrared when it's heated, and most materials emit a wide range of infrared energy, depending on how big it is and what it's made of.

5. These guys realised that **glass beads emit infrared based on their size, so they made glass beads between 8 and 14 m,** which absorb energy from both outside and inside, then emit it in those frequencies.

6. They then put a reflector under the beads so most of the IR would go in one direction - up.

7. ???


8. Profit.


https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Infrared_window </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just privatisation. AEMO is at the root of most of these failures, and should be investigated by an independent (eg, not LNP controlled) entity.

They're consistently favouring higher cost fossil fuel plants over renewables, and making operational decisions that cause failures in regions with with high renewable components. Given the frequency and impact of these decisions, it's increasingly unlikely they're not commercially or ideologically motivated.

This whole country is in desperate need of a wide ranging anti-corruption body. Institutionalised theft is just so deeply endemic and growing so fast it'll take a massive effort to stop it already, let alone if it becomes more entrenched.



http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-02-09/aemo-orders-back-up-power-station-at-pelican-point-on/8256594


http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-02-08/rooftop-solar-growth-could-fuel-big-power-price-hikes-uwa-report/8249748

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, you're wrong about that. The conservative acquaintances at work and other dens of iniquity I frequent are lapping it up.

To anyone with sense, it's empty juvenile posturing, but the LNP's core demographic sees it as strong and clever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's time to nationalise health insurance. Private industry competition clearly isn't working to create inefficiencies and reduce costs, so it's time for government to step in and take control.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The LNP is hilariously corrupt over coal.

Trumble's been shirtfronting Shorten in parliament over it, and even Morrison got into the act, though that one backfired.


With the government upbeat after a Mr Turnbull's aggressive pivot, and buoyed by the South Australian black-out, Treasurer Scott Morrison produced a lump of black coal in Parliament to taunt the opposition over energy.

"This is coal. Don't be afraid," he said waving it about in contravention of the standing orders.

"There's no word for coal-a-phobia officially but it's the malady that's afflicting those opposite."

Ministers then handed the hamburger-sized piece along the frontbench although it stopped abruptly when the pregnant Assistant Treasurer, Kelly O'Dwyer, refused to handle it.


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/turnbull-government-sharpens-attack-on-labors-clean-energy-20170209-gu9h5l.html


You really couldn't write a comedy this funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> increasing the margin of theft in a store will only force them to raise prices and slash resources more to keep the same profit levels.

Aldi have opened between the Woolies and Coles in my suburb, and sell better tomatoes for less. Other overseas companies are also looking at Australia's overpriced grocery duopoly and seeing fat and lazy incumbents who're ripe for a fall.

Colesworth can try to keep their duopoly rents, but they'll be empty wastelands if they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the article. It actually discusses that:


After donating a reported $250,000 in cash, and the same amount in technical services, to the Trumps inauguration parties on December 28, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella condemned the ban in an Q A with employees. He said, There is no place for bias or bigotry in any society, in any context. Thats where we start from. We will always as a company stand for that diversity and inclusion.

The question inevitably arises**is it possible for a company to stand for diversity and inclusion and donate money to a guy who is making good on his racist campaign promises?** Of course not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Kicked in $250,000 for Trump's Big Party Before Speaking Out Against Muslim Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Melbhenge' sun spectacle wins fans in Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should feel sorry for Trumbler. He's been reduced to throwing his own dead cats onto the table.

I mean, fair enough that the media are talking about this instead of the plan to cancel unemployment benefits for anyone under 25 years old, but what's the point of having a pack of dogs if you have to bark yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, though I suspect it's skewed by very small numbers of expensive properties moving.

Anecdotal, but I moved out of Floreat (coastal suburb) three years ago. That house is now back on the market for nearly 200k less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's all it takes to trigger Trumblethinskin, he's going to need a stage for his stand-up comedy routines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Western Australian dolphins using blowfish to get high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Greens should be chasing them over David Gillespie's eligibility to be an MP. That will really throw the cat amongst the pigeons.


http://www.canberratimes.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/david-gillespie-a-turnbull-government-minister-under-constitutional-cloud-20170206-gu6kf2.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's crazy they're allowed to do this. 

In WA, the Libs have refused to release documents about billions of dollars of infrastructure spending. They were ordered to release them by the tribunal, took it to court and lost, and are still delaying the release.

http://www.watoday.com.au/wa-news/wa-election-2017/show-us-the-plans-libs-move-to-defer-tribunal-hearing-over-secret-roe-8-docs-20170207-gu7nec.html

The ministers responsible should be suspended until they comply with the tribunal order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Just Shattered a World Record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WA is already experiencing big drops in property prices. 

This is true, and it's accelerating rather than leveling off. In my suburb, median house prices fell by 17% in the past year, and 9% in the last quarter.

There will be a substantial number of people who bought in the past three years who'll be on zero or negative equity by now. The consequence on the market is already visible - without equity to trade on, these people are essentially trapped. They won't be upgrading as their families grow, which will drag the market down even further.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the Senate inquiry into the TPP? The government will pay about as much attention to any source they disagree with.

Look at Brandis ignoring a court order to release his diary.


http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2017/02/07/tpp-inquiry-report-be-released </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the ones into watersports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this stage, Turnbull's best chance for posterity is to go for a long swim at Cheviot beach. 

Or any Melbourne beach, at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From 2003:

Last weeks conviction and jailing in Australia of two leaders of a rightwing populist party on trumped-up charges of fraud has set a dangerous precedent for use against any political movement considered a threat to the parliamentary order. After a protracted political and legal witchhunt, secretly orchestrated at the highest levels of the Australian government, the criminal law has been manipulated to trample over basic democratic rights and imprison the founders of an opposition party.

Former MP Pauline Hanson and a co-founder of her One Nation Party, David Ettridge, were each sentenced to three years jail without parole under the Queensland Criminal Code. As a result, both are barred for life from standing for parliament. Their alleged crime arose from registering Pauline Hansons One Nation as a party under that states electoral laws in December 1997. They were accused of supplying the names and addresses of 500 members whom a court later ruled to be merely supporters.


https://www.wsws.org/en/articles/2003/08/jail-a29.html


By comparison, assault of elderly, blind, disabled, pregnant, or mentally retarded person 2nd degree with a firearm carries a mandatory 2.5 year sentence in NSW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open source Amiga DVI/HMDI graphics card ready for pre-order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Try Raspberry Pi's PIXEL OS on your PC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Into a cup?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leafy suburbs of the wealthy world face growing danger from wildfires, experts warn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not very good advice.

TFA actually says:

The applications deemed Medium/High Risk will be posted in a follow up within 60 to 90 days, after reaching out to affected **banks, medical providers, and other developers of sensitive applications** which are vulnerable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomi Reveals Details About Octa-Core Pinecone CPU Using 10nm Process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 76 Popular iOS Apps Confirmed Vulnerable to Silent Interception of TLS-Protected Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ubuntu Linux's Mark Shuttleworth talks Zesty Zapus and Unity 8. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Brandis should be going to jail, not London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomi Redmi Pro 2 Will Have 6GB RAM and 4500mAh Battery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Jack Outback, the 'most interesting' Australian revealed by new global research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vodafone Rigged A Race Car With A Virtual Cockpit Using Phone Cameras And 4G </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk tweets tunneling image (but whose tunnel?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather be pragmatic about these things. 


If I was having a serious discussion about their actions or behaviours, and intended to appear credible, I'd use their correct names or titles. Since this conversation is idle speculation, I see no need to maintain formality.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Restore my liberty' says Julian Assange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's the only problem I have with this whole concept. 


There's a whole collection of laughables, Poodle, Potato, GHunt, etc would be eaten alive if they even put their hands up.

The only real contenders seem to be the Mad Monk, Asbestos Julie and ScoMo, all of whom are so toxic it's hard to see anyone who'd back them.

Still, who knows? Desperation is the raw material of drastic change, so we may see a left-field candidate from their right wing...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have two bets happening. 


One deadpool for the date, another wager on who'll bring the knife. I'm backing April 13th as the day, and ScoMo as the man with the red right hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a find, but several years ago, some Kiwi friends of mine in Australia invited me to a hangi in the bush behind their house. They had a steel bedframe to load the food onto, and a few lengths or railway track to heat up and put in with the rocks.

We started digging it at about 9am, and coincidentally, someone opened the first beer about the same time. The ground was really hard, so we got the food in late.

We all kept drinking all day, then sometime after the sun went down, decided it was time to dig up the hangi. We all wandered into the scrub, platters and shovels in hand, but couldn't find the food. Some claimed they could smell it nearby, but we never found it. We ended up dining on microwave pizza and sausages.

TLDR:

If you go metal detecting in the Australian bush and find some railway track on an old bed, that's probably my dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds more like a coffin table than a coffee table. Any bodies in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia's a big place. I reckon there's plenty of us here who've earned that right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "bleeding-heart lefties".


Um, no. It's a mainstream opinion. Do try to keep up.


http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/01/opinions/bannon-trump-coup-opinion-ben-ghiat/

http://www.news.com.au/world/north-america/is-the-us-in-the-middle-of-a-coup/news-story/ab0ece5c5b27b004b0b203fcce435a92

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/president-donald-trump-executive-orders-actions-likened-military-coup-historian-expert-fascism-ruth-a7558831.html

https://www.thenation.com/article/trumps-cabinet-is-a-coup-waiting-to-happen/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, they're one of the most widely respected chipmakers on the planet!

Who else would you go to for a high-end ARM chipset? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qualcomm don't make AMOLED screens, so it'll be down to whichever manufacturer Google chooses for the screen.

It's worth noting that AMOLEDs scale resolution/power better than normal LEDs, which need a more powerful backlight as pixel density rises, and they tend to get about 30% more efficient every generation. 

I'll withhold judgement, but there is a discernible improvement in the crispness of images on a QHD display over a 1080p panel, so I'll take it if there's no serious compromises to get that resolution.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. 

Laws aren't made for normal people. We know how to behave, not to steal, not to hurt other people, all the usual stuff. 

Laws are made to hem in people who want to stretch the boundaries of what the rest of us recognise as right and wrong. They're drafted to be do that job, and to be clear to everyone what's intended, but they're as porous as a net to someone skilled in reading and writing them.

Globally, there's been a trend towards politicians and governments crossing those boundaries while remaining within the letter of the laws. We, the people, recognise that what's happening is wrong, but they point at the law and say "we're entitled".

Trump is taking that trend one step further. He's giving direct instructions to the military. He's issuing laws without consulting the State department. He's ignoring the conventions and controls that are intended to rein in his office, and he's getting away with it. In a year, Americans will be bowing at his altar. https://www.gpo.gov/fdsys/pkg/FR-2017-01-24/pdf/2017-01798.pdf



The rule of law is basically a consensus - we all follow it because it makes for a more level playing field, and life's better for most of us if we do. 

When someone in power decides they'll just do what they want, there's no more level, we're of very shaky ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll need to be a bit more specific. There's a lot of options for us to choose from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Trumble will get down on his knees and pray to his Trumpy Holiness on the National Day of Patriotic Devotion?


https://www.gpo.gov/fdsys/pkg/FR-2017-01-24/pdf/2017-01798.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speak a little Spanish, if you feel like practicing.


Hola, mi aerodeslizador est lleno de anguilas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laugh all you want, but what's happening is essentially a coup.

Trump is dumping centuries of precedent, ignoring policies and conventions intended to restrict direct control of the country, and by doing so, abandoning the rule of law. 

Duterte did something similar in the Philippines.

Governments all over the world have been gradually implementing tools to monitor and take control of their populations. What's happening now is that there's someone in a position where they can test the limits of the "checks and balances", and who's arrogant enough to try.

It'll be interesting to see if they still work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Donald Trump executing a coup on the United States Government? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labor is against the tax. It'd raise about $5 billion a year, so the big mining multinationals are investing in a giant smear campaign to make sure "anybody but the Nationals" gets elected.

WA Nationals Leader Brendon Grylls has proposed charging Rio Tinto and BHP Billiton a $5 rental fee for every tonne of iron ore they produce, up from the current rate of 25 cents a tonne, which was set in the 1960s.


http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-11-23/wa-unions-slam-wa-nationals-mining-tax/8051650
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, and I'd never stand in the way. If I need to vote on it, I'll vote for gay marriage.


But it's not my fight, and I'm not interested in joining it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull is famously aggressive. It's possible he finally remembered where his balls are.


http://www.smh.com.au/good-weekend/gw-classics/raging-turnbull-20140904-10c7ye.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nationals will be interesting to watch. 

The mining companies have been running a massive ad campaign against them because of their tax plan. Its catchphrase is that the taxes raised will go to NSW and Victoria, while the jobs will be lost in WA.

It's a brutal attack on Brendon Grylls and the Nats here, far in excess of any of the other political parties' efforts. 


http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-02-02/wa-premier-slams-mining-lobby-campaign-against-grylls-tax/8236114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm married, and don't see why gays should suffer as well.

That's why I'm against it.*

^*Not ^really. ^It's ^just ^not ^very ^important ^to ^me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far he seems to be reasonably sensible, though given his expressed values seem a long way out of step with PHON, you'd have to ask why he's there.


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/meet-one-nations-replacement-senate-candidate-peter-georgiou-20161104-gsi1xy.html


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except he quit PHON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brandis being rescued and rewarded with a lucrative High Commissioner's job in London, instead of being prosecuted and sent to prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you still have the lunchbox?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Pixel 2 Rumored to Have 4K Screen, Quick Charge 4.0 and Insane Low-Light Camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Food to Sofas: How Open Source is Changing the World Beyond Software </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple wants to put more mobile hardware into Macs, but isnt abandoning Intel yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap journalism. They misspelled "ruining". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Turnbull? Is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, agree with all of that. If we had a strong, forward thinking government, we'd be well-placed to benefit from the chaos that's about to ensue.

Another missed opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a little more complicated than that, but yeah. That, and Churchill's treachery, was the main reason future Australian governments turned away from Britain and looked to the US for military alliances.

http://www.pacificwar.org.au/battaust/Britain_betrays_Australia.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't think that was ever an option. But there was no need to publicly over-commit to what was inherently a dirty political deal the way they did. That's what sunk them so badly.

There was always a significant probability that it would unravel. Planning for that, and having contingencies for it, is just basic sense.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest shock about this whole incident is how deeply unprepared the Australian Gov't has been.


What did they think was going to happen?


I expect laziness from Turnbull. He's basically been phoning in his performance as PM, and Hockey as Ambassador likely didn't do any preparation, but there's packs of advisors, DFAT, a supposedly capable Foreign Minister, the whole rest of the Cabinet.


Didn't ANYBODY stop to think Trump might behave like Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hungry enough to suck the pus out of the inside of a leper's leg.


Western Australia. Drop by for dinner sometime... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole situation reeks of cover-up and deception.

Turnbull says his donations to the Libs have been "regular and generous".


Asked at his first major speech whether he would reveal the donation before the next disclosure, the prime minister said: My donations to the Liberal party have been regular and generous and I would encourage others to do the same.


But there's nothing in the AEC records of donations from him any year in the past decade.

The requirements are:

Donors must disclose donations totalling more than the disclosure threshold made to a registered political party. From 200607, third parties (including associated entities) who incur political expenditure in excess of the disclosure threshold are also required to lodge an annual return.


http://periodicdisclosures.aec.gov.au/DonorSearch.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one are you referring to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of those things are already available in the Android ecosystem. 

Android AR/VR is widely available, works well and is inexpensive. 

Even in device convergence, Apple's borrowing more from Linux than innovating.

Look at the [latest version of Unity](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0ahUKEwjnhZrgrfDRAhVhl1QKHVvrDsUQyCkIHDAA url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DHYxpjpT9Q-Y usg=AFQjCNEYokjX4sHbY3wjhgWlUpBx-dw3EQ sig2=tjUapJipbfhkRJSKXM2JiA bvm=bv.146073913,d.cGw) - it has more convergence that Apple can even imagine right now!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the /s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 09:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another advert on /r/Australia. What a surprise, and it's from the most habitual spammer as well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have already [refuted that claim](https://www.reddit.com/r/australia/comments/5qd23z/infrastructure_australia_says_tax_land_not/dcyj00o/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull says his donations to the Libs have been "regular and generous".

Asked at his first major speech whether he would reveal the donation before the next disclosure, the prime minister said: My donations to the Liberal party have been regular and generous and I would encourage others to do the same.


But there's nothing in the AEC records of donations from him any year in the past decade.


The requirements are:

Donors must disclose donations totalling more than the disclosure threshold made to a registered political party. From 200607, third parties (including associated entities) who incur political expenditure in excess of the disclosure threshold are also required to lodge an annual return.

http://periodicdisclosures.aec.gov.au/DonorSearch.aspx

So what gives? Has he been donating as he says and not disclosing, or is his donation claim just posturing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's plenty of models generated by paid-for studies that show corporate tax cuts lead to job and wage growth. Some of them even have peer reviews.

Analysis of real data from countries that have reduced company tax, instead of from models with carefully chosen assumptions, shows that there's no correlation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them weren't old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, do you consider Bernardi to be charismatic and well-spoken? He thinks he's the chosen one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch experiment with 'Tinder for orangutans' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The modelling can suggest whatever it wants to. Reality disagrees.


A study of US corporate tax rates from 1948 to 2010 found that:

The top statutory corporate tax rate has been falling since the early 1950s. The top corporate tax rate was 52 percent throughout the Eisenhower administration17 percentage points higher than the current top rate of 35 percent. U.S. GDP grew by almost 4 percent annually in the 1950s compared with a 1.8 percent growth rate in the 2000s. 

On the surface, it would appear that more robust economic growth is associated with higher corporate tax rates. Further analysis, however, finds no evidence that either the statutory top corporate tax rate or the effective marginal tax rate on capital income is correlated with real GDP growth.

http://www.epi.org/publication/ib364-corporate-tax-rates-and-economic-growth/

Likewise, it won't attract more investment:

New research ridicules the Prime Minister's claim that cutting the company tax rate will boost foreign investment, pointing out that almost all of Australia's foreign investment applications already come from countries with much lower tax rates.

The analysis by the Australia Institute finds that 97 per cent of the applications to Australia's foreign investment review board come from countries with lower company tax rates. By value, 71 per cent of applications come from countries with lower rates.


The Coalition's tax cuts for business will return very little to the Australian economy for the cost to the budget. "All of this raises the question  if Australia is already successful at attracting foreign investment why would we give tax cuts to foreigners?" said the report's author David Richardson, a senior research fellow at the self-described progressive think tank.





http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/cutting-company-tax-wont-drive-investment-australia-institute-20170130-gu1kuy.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSW will do it's bit to ensure wealth continues to be distributed upwards.

A leaked Treasury document reveals NSW's land titles registry is earning $130 million for the taxpayer each year as the government comes under pressure to ditch its privatisation plans.

http://www.smh.com.au/nsw/leaked-nsw-treasury-document-reveals-billions-to-be-made-by-land-title-registry-operators-20170201-gu2wed.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The modelling can suggest whatever it wants to. Reality disagrees.

A study of corporate tax rates from 1948 to 2010 by the same author found that:

The top statutory corporate tax rate has been falling since the early 1950s. The top corporate tax rate was 52 percent throughout the Eisenhower administration17 percentage points higher than the current top rate of 35 percent. U.S. GDP grew by almost 4 percent annually in the 1950s compared with a 1.8 percent growth rate in the 2000s. On the surface, it would appear that more robust economic growth is associated with higher corporate tax rates. Further analysis, however, finds no evidence that either the statutory top corporate tax rate or the effective marginal tax rate on capital income is correlated with real GDP growth.

http://www.epi.org/publication/ib364-corporate-tax-rates-and-economic-growth/

Can you please stop evangelising these tax cuts? All they do is increase inequality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been the savior of millions of Australians.


Probably why the government wants to crucify it at 33.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've got that already, in theory at least. Nothing's happened.

I mean, really nothing - we could have elected a bag of sand for all the effort we've got from him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Samsung Galaxy S8 and Apple iPhone 8 Should be Worried by Huawei, Oppo, and Xiaomi Smartphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull has commented on the issue. He issued a joint statement with Foreign Minister Julie Bishop titled, "Turnbull government secures US exemption for Australian passport holders".

As it turns out, that statement was untrue, and the US Embassy has since said there are no special rules for Australia.

http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/australia-has-not-been-given-a-preferential-exemption-from-donald-trumps-us-visa-ban-20170201-gu2yck.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And giving $50 billion for multinationals to sequester into tax havens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good dead cat to throw on his Brandis-concealment appointment  last week though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gets $522,0000 a year, plus extremely generous entitlements, as well as being able to give his businesses a substantial tax reduction. Not to mention the influence he'll be able to bring to his future investments.


As well, if he outlasts his predecessor by a few days, he'll also get a generous pension, and plenty of job opportunities with the multinationals he's "encouraged" during his time as PM.

Not a foolish investment, if you're prepared to exploit the opportunity.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you picture yourself sitting between Dutton and Birmingham? 

You might need to practice taking money from people who have almost nothing, and giving it to people who have almost everything. That kind of skill takes years to develop.

I have no doubt the banks will be surly when you request the loan... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but once they've bought their job, the ROI is great. Cabinet ministers get $336,599 per year from you and the rest of us when we pay GST etc. 

Even if they only last three years, they still get a million bucks each. 

It's a steal - you should buy one for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest LNP donor was Paul Marks.

Mr Marks is a controversial figure, closely linked to Turnbull government MP Stuart Robert. Mr Robert was sacked from Mr Turnbull's frontbench last year after being accused of using his ministerial office to open doors for Mr Marks and his companies in China.

It seems Mr Marks made a good investment. Thanks to Robert's corrupt actions, he'll have "earned" well over the $1.3 million he gave to the LNP.

Looks like cabinet positions are relatively cheap as well.

Cabinet ministers also contributed to the flagging Liberal campaign, including Immigration Minister Peter Dutton with $50,000 and Education Minister Simon Birmingham with $20,000. Finance Minister Mathias Cormann gave $29,000 through his fundraising vehicle. 

http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/malcolm-turnbulls-multimillion-political-donation-to-liberal-party-remains-secret-for-another-year-20170131-gu2pnm.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She went beyond using the law to defend her client. She manipulated court administrative process to delay hearings until the mesothelioma victims were dead.

It was acknowledged as clever but viciously unethical, even at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean, so he doesn't have to discuss Brandis being sent to London? 

Do you think he'll mention that the court order to hand over the diary is still being ignored, but he's rewarding Brandis with the high commissioner escape plan anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now what makes you think I shun it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're rather intense. You must feel very strongly about Windows 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I? How strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treasury is politicised, and highly unreliable, but even their models show after-tax wage growth in the long run (10 years) of less than 0.3 per cent. In the mean time, other taxes would be needed to replace the lower corporate tax rate. In other words, the best outcome for workers is that for the next decade they give their money to the gov't to give to corporations in the hope nobody'll change the rules in the mean time and take that minute pay rise back off them.

Meanwhile, channeling the same amount of money into education and training would generate an order of magnitude more growth sooner.

And that's putting the best case for corp tax cuts forward. Verifiable reality suggests that's wildly optimistic.

The reduction in top tax rates appears to be uncorrelated with saving, investment, and productivity growth. The top tax rates appear to have little or no relation to the size of the economic pie. However the top tax rate reductions appear to be associated with the increasing concentration of income at the top of the income distribution. The report notes that tax rates were at the highest when growth was at its peak, and that the reduction in tax rates has not had any discernible impact on the types of investment that lead to growth.

Conclusion of a study of tax rates since 1945 by the US Congressional Research Service, a nonpartisan entity associated with the Library of Congress that does academic quality research to answer difficult policy questions. 

https://fas.org/sgp/crs/misc/R42729.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to anyone involved in the recent W10 upgrades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forcibly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 10 Mobile is basically dead, and this proves it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not use Dutton first? He's not much good for anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP originally suggested the pirates would "steel" nuclear material.  The typo has since been corrected, leaving my formerly witty comment as a sad and stranded non-sequitur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull has never really had any principles. He'll express opinions, but those ere even less binding than Howard's "non-core promises". 

After all, in 2012, Turnbull said that American politics were profoundly dysfunctional, and in reference to the staggering budget deficit and public debt said that whats depressing about the debate in America is that so much of it is actually just innumerate. In particular, Turnbull was scathing about the Republican idea that the budgetary situation could be improved by cutting the taxes of the wealthy, calling it  just bizarre. In 2017, that idea is the centrepiece of his budgetary policy.

It's not so much that he's indecisive, just that his goal, as always, was to win, for himself, for his prestige, for his posterity. Once he won, and propped the trophy on his shelf, he promptly lost interest.

What we see from him now is not so much indecision as disinterest. He just doesn't care.

Morrison wants to reduce taxes for business. "Sure Scotty, whatever". Tudge wants to install a remorseless robo-biller in Centrelink. "No worries Al, I'll back you on that". Dutton wants to add the acronym for "Service Specialist" to the collars of Border Force uniforms. "Fine Tater, do what you want".

He's not being corrupted by power. He has been corrupt his entire life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think they should iron them instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paging /u/SavannaJeff

 Free trade deal with US has hurt Australia: ANU

The US last year clocked up an $US11 billion ($A14.6 billion) trade surplus with us thanks to the US Australian Free Trade deal we signed 12 years ago that also was a stinker.

As the Australian National University's (ANU) Thomas Faunce reported, that deal was a major contributor to the 80 per cent blowout in the cost of the Pharmaceutical Benefits System, which has put enormous strain on the federal budget.

According to the ANU's Crawford School, that pact has hurt Australia every year since it was signed, with $57 billion in lost and diverted trade in 2012 alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quite liked working with them, after a while they get to know you and they're a friendly bird, but they spook easily so you've got to be careful with them.

Yep, and not have anything shiny. Or dangly. And don't ever take food from your pocket to feed them, unless you want to deal with 40kg of emu leaping around with its head tangled in your pocket after it tries to sneak a snack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adolph Hitler 1922:

"If I am ever really in power, the destruction of the Jews will be my first and most important job. As soon as I have power, I shall have gallows after gallows erected, for example, in Munich on the Marienplatz-as many of them as traffic allows. Then the Jews will be hanged one after another, and they will stay hanging until they stink. They will stay hanging as long as hygienically possible. As soon as they are untied, then the next group will follow and that will continue until the last Jew in Munich is exterminated. Exactly the same procedure will be followed in other cities until Germany is cleansed of the last Jew!"

Hitler 1939

Europe cannot find peace until the Jewish question has been solved. One thing I should like to say on this day [the sixth anniversary of his being appointed Chancellor of the Reich] which may be memorable for others as well as for us Germans. In the course of my life I have very often been a prophet and have usually been ridiculed for it.  Today I will once more be a prophet: if the international Jewish financiers in and outside Europe should succeed in plunging the nations once more into a world war, then the result will not be the Bolshivization of the earth, and thus the victory of Jewry, but the annihilation of the Jewish race in Europe."

For decades his message was the same. The end result was entirely predictable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 12:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day you'll get tired of saying that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. 

From 1933, Germany was enacting legislation to marginalise Jews. In 1935, the Nuremberg laws removed protection and restricted economic participation. The Kristallnacht pogrom was in 1938, as was the legislation enforcing different identity cards, names, and passports for Jews.

Even earlier, since the 1920s, Hitler had been talking and writing about exterminating Jews. in Mein Kampf, he wrote that the: sacrifice of millions at the front would have been prevented if twelve or fifteen thousand of these Hebrew corrupters of the people had been held under poison gas.


His, and Germany's, intent was clear and predictable, even before 1939. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which part of Perth are you near? 

If you can get to Girrawheen, go to Banh Mi Vinh Tau. There's plenty of other Vietnamese cafes around, but they're reliably good.

Also try pho if you feel like a sit-down meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Install motion detection cameras around the house. You can use Alfred or similar apps on old/discarded Android phones if you want to keep it simple.

Keep a daily log, and take notes a after each incident, if there's no incident, just note "no incident". Keep it somewhere secure, at work, for example, or encrypted online it you're tech aware. It'll help when you apply for the restraining order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to read this before asking that kind of question.


http://www.abc.net.au/radionational/programs/rearvision/a-history-of-australian-budget-surpluses-and-deficits/5446434

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to Vietnam, and eat banh mi at least once a week.

You can trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, agree with all that. We're taking in 10% less taxes as a proportion of GDP than OECD average, and our tax base has been falling steeply since 2008.

We also have one of the highest ratios of tax levied at federal level in the OECD. Most places have a wider distribution (state, local, etc) of income sources.

The combination of those two things, shrinking income, and an over-concentration of spending power at federal level, is making reform impossible, even in regions that aren't ideologically limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we all know that. But that's the job they've been paid to do. They'll keep trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever makes it to the top will blame Turny's leftist weakness for the looming economic failures and insist a huge tax cut for business is the only way to resolve it.


I'm betting just before Easter, with the holiday preoccupation taking the edge off it. What day in May are you backing? The first Monday, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade the melting pot in for a meltdown pot. It's all that's needed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably should go there and see what's happening for yourself. It's not what you think it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
