<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translation: "We didn't have enough time to program it to work well, so we gave up and just disabled P2 mapping." This is the lazy way out. If we can hobble together third party programs to get it sort-of working, there's no reason they can't fix it on their end. Now with the release of Rev 2, they have more time to get this ironed out.  Get to it!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo Switch touchscreen utilizes TouchSense haptic technology that simulates "touching physical buttons" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arc System Works, PLEASE fix the button mapping for Rev 2 on PC! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Arc System Works,

In Revelator, why is it not possible to map player 2 buttons on keyboard, without using a third-party button remapper and gamepad emulator? Why can't I play using keyboard for one player and stick for the other? Why am I forced to use buggy third-party workarounds so I can play the way I like?  It was fine in SIGN, so why can't they get it right with Revelator?  Please, PLEASE fix this issue in Rev 2!  

Sincerely,

a frustrated PC GG player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's some pretty fucked up images there....should put a warning next time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Chipp so surprised at, Baiken's had huge tits since X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally fine with a reasonably price DLC update.  It would be infuriating if it were only available as stand-alone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm salty alright. I'm never getting back those 51 seconds wasted watching this totally uncreative video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically, with a provocative name like that, people post unexpected/skillful plays that overcome the odds.  You just posted massive skytoss rolling over an inferior zerg army.  What were you thinking?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/1F6fgLC confirmed DD tier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's Baiken action! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. So it's not just a battery and a little microchip with a radio antenna anymore?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God-like rebuttal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rare but it does exist. When I was in Beijing during the Olympics.  It was beautiful while it lasted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intriguing, if true.  Let me know if you ever find that source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was very rude and uncalled for, also against the rules of this sub.  Reported.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are essentially saying that because many studies are dubious, we should totally disregard all studies, which is ridiculous.  I'm not a Ph.D., but I'm a graduate student in molecular biology.  There will always be bad science; that doesn't make science worthless.  An academic should constantly seek out additional and more robust data, and use that information to justify his worldview.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with luminarium here.  Why should a "decent" person feel revulsion at another person's harmless fantasy?  As luminarium stated, we have no business policing thoughtcrimes.     
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Both should be banned, or both should be legal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care.  I personally am not into this stuff.  I just think others should be allowed to be.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair points.  I presented the assumptions that support my belief, but it was more an invitation for discussion than a rock solid argument. While I do believe it should be legal, I agree there is a lack of good evidence on both sides.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't fully convinced either, but I gave him the delta because he was the first person to actually address my question and give a potential, albeit unlikely, way this could be pro-consumer.  I think he would agree that collusion is bad for consumers, but he's arguing that net neutrality does nothing to prevent this; in fact, it may even encourage collusion since they all feel threatened by a common enemy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it matter if it "looks" like a real child or not? If it's not a real child, it's not a real child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's saying that it should be okay to depict fictional characters that don't resemble real individuals, but it wouldn't be okay to depict actual people.  Like it would be wrong to depict a 14-year old version of Britney Spears, but it would be okay to depict some made up fictional character.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably not any different.  Maybe he believes we should prohibit violence in video games as well, for the sake of consistency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want them : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lowko actually showed that going corruptors doesn't really work against skytoss, since the protoss player can easily toss in a few void rays.  He posted a video showing that rapid expansion and mass hydra before the Protoss can get critical mass of carriers is the best counterplay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $90 for an AC ADAPTER??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHERE YOU AT WHERE YOU AT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like they had a sofa on stage solely for these 3 seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HD rumble 
IR camera
NFC
Gyroscope

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually quite reasonably priced considering it has better specs than the nvidia shield and the fancy tech in the controllers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I'll believe it when I see it in stores.  Box art mockups always look better than the actual retail units.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real reason you will buy Breath of the Wild (   ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a less blurry look at our lovely lady

https://gyazo.com/473371f580c7c09a6fc4f514880a3388 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Breath of the Wild trailer goes pretty well with the music from Chrono Cross </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried setting the new Breath of the Wild trailer to the music of Chrono Cross </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 06:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely the colors. my girlfriend and I would love to have our own personal joycons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hilarious and provocative analogy! this sub is awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a really interesting argument I've never heard before actually.  Right now, the big ISPs are united by a common enemy, the FCC.  But if the FCC stopped regulating them so heavily, ISPs would increasingly butt against each other as they expand under reduced regulation.  Thanks for giving me another way to think about it, if not completely changing my mind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, I could see it as gateway to more abusive/dangerous fetishes.  But I think there are a lot of things we permit that are clearly more dangerous, particularly depictions of violence in mainstream entertainment.  If animated child porn is a gateway, violence on TV, movies, and games is practically an invitation.  But you can have a  for this explanation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is interesting. So you are saying that Comcast could charge data hogs like Netflix and pass the savings to consumers?  So essentially Netflix would be paying part of my internet bill?  I feel it's theoretically possible, but wouldn't the far more likely outcome be that Netflix increases their prices? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Animated and illustrated child pornography should be legal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that animated and illustrated depictions of underage sex (i.e. hentai) should be legal. My reasons are as follows:

1. Unlike real child porn, animated child porn is a victim-less crime. No real children are harmed in its creation or consumption.

2.  There is no academically-accepted evidence that the viewing of animated child porn increases sexual deviancy or other criminal tendencies. 

3.  It provides an outlet for pedophiles, preventing would-be predators from committing sexual acts on real children.  

4.  It is often difficult to ascertain the age of drawn characters like those in anime or manga. They may possess child-like features such as big eyes or flat chest, while being actually over 18 years of age.

5.  Prohibiting the drawing of taboo subjects is tantamount to censorship.

Give me your best reasons why illustrated or drawn child pornography should be prohibited.  

Edit: To those threatening me or calling me disgusting: grow up.  I'm not personally interested in child porn, animated or otherwise.  I just think it should be legal. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone who stayed at the J.W. Marriot provide their experience with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which hotel did you stay at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for addressing my question.  I do think that if there was sufficient competition from various ISPs, zero-rating could be a good thing, because then the customer has the choice to use the ISP with the best zero-rated content.  I just fear that often isn't the case, with some territories only offering one viable broadband provider.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> choo choo choo BOOOOM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You had to 2 base all-in to win"

has 3 mining bases </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were a deer or a speeder, yes I would?  Big ISPs are harming consumers; as a consumer I don't have a right to be angry?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just seems like a given to me.  It's obvious that companies aren't charities, that their main goal is to generate profit. I'm looking for someone to convince me that there are tangible benefits to consumers by killing off net neutrality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence my post.  I understand they are some of the most hated companies in America.  I came here looking for one reason NOT to hate them.  So far nobody has been able to provide that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I understand that a company exists to make as much money as possible. But these ISPs keep arguing that their actions are "pro-consumer" What I want is to know is how any of their actions can be construed as "pro-consumer."  How am I going to benefit from the death of net neutrality going forward?  You guys are basically telling me "it sucks for you, you should never expect companies to be nice."  Well I already understood that. What I would like is one reason I should be supportive of their actions, from the perspective of the consumer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Comcast, Verizon, and AT T's crusade to thwart net neutrality is unjustifiably anti-consumer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just one year ago, it seemed like net neutrality scored a serious win when the FCC redefined ISPs as common carriers and imposed new rules to safeguard the open internet. Fast forward to today, and net neutrality is in dire straits.  The Trump administration will likely kill the neutrality rules, Tom Wheeler is going to step down, Ajit Pai will be in charge, and it seems to me like the open internet as we know it will all but evaporate.  Many ISPs now engage in zero-rating schemes, creating an unfair advantage by making their own content free. Worsening the situation, the deployment of meaningful competition has been obstructed time and time again, with AT T and Comcast threatening to sue townships that try to build out their own municipal broadband ISPs or introduce Google Fiber. In short, the internet is going to hell, big ISPs are having a field day, and I feel utterly powerless to stop it.  Are companies like Comcast, Verizon, and AT T truly this.evil?  Can someone please change my view so that I can have at least a glimmer of hope for the next four years?  

Edit:
Thanks for the responses.  I'm not really asking for an explanation of how companies have a right to make money; I fully understand the concept of fiduciary duty.  What I'm asking for is an explanation of how this action might not be as anti-consumer as I believe.  Tell me how the actions of these companies could actually BENEFIT consumers, like they've claimed countless times in press releases.  Convince me that I should be supportive of AT T, Verizon, and Comcast instead of reviling them    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AX 2016 attendees: did they enforce the whole 4-person per room wristband thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At AX 2015 and AX2016, a bunch of hotels were threatening to enforce a 4-person limit per room using wristbands.  They claimed to have staff guarding the elevators who would actively block people without wristbands.  My question is, was this policy actually enforced strictly?  If you have experience with this, please let us know which year and which hotel you stayed at.  Any insight would be appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lament the fall of obamacare, of net neutrality, but I take solace in the fact no one will ever, ever successfully ban porn.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5min = 1.5 years

okie lul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's gotten a ton of money from donations, including from those who've been waiting for him to return to the SC2 scene. If he has no intentional to return, then it could be construed as a scam.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But honestly, I'd say give it up. He has moved on/away from StarCraft and is no longer interested in interacting with this community. He has found a new home in other gaming communities and if he's happy there, then we should respect that decision.

I actually started crying reading this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people are mad that they replaced snakes voice, but I thought Ocelot's replacement was way more jarring.  He went from a snarling eccentric weirdo to a cowboy gentleman, felt like a totally different character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feminism and transgender have been at odds with each other for decades. See here:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Feminist_views_on_transgender_and_transsexual_people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day9 said he was just taking a break.  1.5 years later, it doesn't really seem like a break.  How is it entitled to ask if Day9 still felt the same way as before?  Sounds perfectly reasonable to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Day9 doesn't care anymore, he should just come out and say it.  Don't lead us on for 1.5 years waiting for him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we just going to drip-post everything from this girl now?  Farm that karma! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's our apology from the Protoss whiners who had complained incessantly about DT blink being worthless?  I'm waiting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lowko teaches how to beat mass carriers as Zerg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 09:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question, was Golden actually stream sniping avilo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 09:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are the scans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is silly.  Makeup is part of cosplay.  Makeup that transforms your appearance is part of GOOD cosplay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could we forget
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QghXupHVDC8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol the makeup is so good it made you think she actually looks like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the bara is overwhelming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know if its possible to use 1 keyboard and 1 controller simultaneously?  And is it possible to set the button mapping separately for each? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the guide!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The body of an elite fighting game player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I mean she still looks good but the resemblance to Triss was definitely done with care.  Even more impressed haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOUBLED

That's a funny way of saying the cost was overall reduced by 60% compared to pre-3.8... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucking uncanny.  I'm curious what she looks like normally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mention of the game fixing scandal that did irreparable damage to the scene?  Talk about rose-tinted glasses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PC Players: Is it possible to play locally with 2 keyboards at the same time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend and I want to play guilty gear on my PC at my house.  We are both keyboard players (grew up playing MAME and other arcade emulators).  Can we hook up 2 different keyboards and both play at the same time?  Would we have to use non-overlapping keys between the 2 keyboards?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about? She looks exactly like a Turian to me.  The mandible-like jaw is a dead giveaway.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be nice to new players - Wow /r/starcraft is so insecure, just a desperate circlejerk trying to save a ded gaem LOL

Be mean to new players - Wow /r/starcraft are a toxic group of elitist assholes, no wonder it's a ded gaem RIP

 \ _()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently /r/starcraft is too nice to new players. Come on guys, everyone knows you're supposed to downvote noobs into oblivion so that they don't spoil our great game with their noobiness.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 95% Crazy Shit from WoL #1: Neural Parasite into Vortex Nuke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow that was fast!  this makes a lot of sense.  i play fighting games so i do get the concept of hitboxes.  thanks for the explanation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is it so hard to completely prevent clipping of 3D models in video games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be clear, I know nothing about programming or 3D graphics. Naively, I would think you could just give objects some property by which they cannot pass through each other.  Yet I see some degree of clipping in almost every big studio 3D game.  Why is this so hard to fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg... he wants to eat Noctis??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've got it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Blizzard please do something about maphacking communities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying raise awareness of maphacking and expose these guys who are ruining the game for the rest of us. Though it isn't as rampant as the hots days, maphacking is still alive and well; there are still forums of people sharing private and for-pay maphacks on sites like this:  

http://www.d3scene.com/forum/starcraft-2-hacks/

Here is one guy who claims to have a working one:
http://www.d3scene.com/forum/starcraft-2-hacks/113289-warning-i-am-trying-make-sc2-map-hack.html

I don't know if there is any legal recourse for Blizzard to shut this down.  But at least these guys should be exposed and Blizzard needs to be aware of the situation.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain how it can't be you when the name clearly says "avilo"?  Two users can't share the same name.  Unless you don't actually go by avilo on EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Avilo's videos?  This is a dead on impression.  The humor is derived from the accuracy of this impression.  Impressions are commonly utilized to comedic effect : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 23:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can if you want to be a sheeple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay but my suggestion requires a lot less micro than the OPs suggestion, which is why i think mine is better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not adding an ability, I'm replacing an ability with a more useful one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this is really necessary : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/fCz8PYQEd_8?t=6m20s

Yup seems pretty accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what?  I don't see it in /r/all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you get the joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea is to completely remove the delay between blinking and attacking, so that the DT instantly blinks and deals damage without waiting for the attack animation.  It's essentially the same as the LOTV chargelot buff, which made the charge itself deal some damage.  The high damage is so this can be used to assassinate high HP units quickly, sort of like a snipe.  Finally, this is balanced by the requirement of a target unit to blink to, which further serves to differentiate this ability from stalker blink.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my idea.  Replace Shadow Stride with Shadow Strike.  5 range cast on a single enemy unit.  DT then blinks to the unit and deals 90 damage.  This can be utilized to negate the range advantage after DTs get scanned, or can be used to quickly assassinate high priority targets in large battles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh... got it oops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how he made his username say Avilo when he changes the player vision lollll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lowko confirmed SAVAGE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that most of the universe is composed of dark matter, aka all the stuff they don't have enough RAM to render </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noctis and the gang cosplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTA: Final Fantasy XV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTA: Final Fantasy XV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that we have a problem when even liberal media refute the Obama administration's claims. Color me very disappointed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLAYGUU PLAYGUUGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it kinda humanizes them doesn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sutacurapt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shitttt this is the best mindfuck i have ever seen in sc2. the way he immediately unsieged, got the tanks into the medivacs, and killed those rocks at the last second to block off the ramp....unbelievable micro and decision making.  i dont even care that they got killed ultimately.  still possibly the best play of 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imagine how someone like avilo would have reacted.  stay classy lowko </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 21:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an elaborate forgery.  She stole the digital art and made it look like she drew it by hand.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noctis "pencil sketch" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
