<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that. It only got to me on occasion. My reasons for leaving that line of work were more related to a desire for change rather than burnout or anything like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did all those things, but I just focused on the economics of the funeral work because I figured that was the hardest bit to believe. Weddings are also much more sporadic, as are weekend masses. I've played and/or sang nearly as many funerals as I have regular masses at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cape Verdean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been scammed, per se, but I have been in situations where families try to get around payment by bringing in their own musicians. They can have whoever they'd like play or sing, but most churches provide their musicians with bench fees (or at least the organist). Thus, they were still obliged to pay me for the service whether I played/sang or not. I have mixed feelings on the ethics of that position, but that's the only place where I've ever had payment drama from families. Even then, most don't fight it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disposition is key. A gentle but clear speaking voice, sympathetic responses to attempts at conversation, and unassuming posture all combine to set the right tone for the proceedings. Above all, I felt it was always imperative to give them what they asked for. Other than that, just give them a place to grieve without getting in their way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No horror stories regarding money, no. There have been times when something happened with the check, but those were oversights rather than grievances. Collection was more of a problem for weddings, however, because of the timing of things and the lack of a coordinator at the church in most cases. In general, payment was smooth because the churches set expectations ahead of time regarding payment. Funerals generally have the director there to manage money matters. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't one I've been asked to sing, but that isn't surprising given that it isn't a traditional hymn. I like the tune, but I wouldn't want it at my funeral either. The lyrics are too heavy for my taste.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for teaching me a new word!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stories that Redditors wouldn't believe? I'm sure you've got plenty. 

Stories that I personally wouldn't believe? I highly doubt that. As with your friend, I've been a part of some very unusual moments throughout my career as a church musician. It's a relief to not be part of that scene anymore...seeing how the proverbial sausage gets made has taken its toll on my spiritual life. 

I won't share the worst ones as those are difficult to recount. A weird service I did, however, was a memorial service (non-religious) for a well-known local businessman. They rented out a large hall for people to come and celebrate his life. Cut to the eulogies and five of his family members gently talking about what a difficult man he was and how they weren't exactly glad he was dead, but how they understood if people had mixed feelings about the event. 

Singing "Danny Boy" after that fiasco was a pip, let me tell you. Awkward turtle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...you could fit in well among us. While we would never make a joke like that in the Church, sometimes inappropriate jokes are the way you get through it all. I had a singer whose used to arrive and ask "who's today's contestant?" They were a joy to work with, as you can imagine. 

Still, Sour Ball Girl was a hard one even with that sort of cavalier attitude toward the proceedings. The family were completely shell shocked...no tears, nothing. Just mute people with blank, stunned faces. Plus, the casket was open when I arrived. No amount of makeup can fix the effects of asphyxiation, let's just leave it at that. 

Sometimes, you just get through it by knowing you are helping these people through a difficult time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to have a certain kind of personality for it, I think. It's easier for us than for funeral directors or priests because we just come in at the end. The hardest part is dealing with the family and their raw emotions. If you approach it from a place of sympathy rather than empathy, it goes better. I've definitely had days, however, where I've carried some of those emotions into the rest of my day. Funerals as in the morning so there is a whole day left to ruminate if you let that happen. By and large, however, you just...get used to it? I chose to focus on the technical aspects of the music to help focus my attention away from the body and the grief of the family. It mostly worked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, some days were hard. The key for us was to maintain distance, expressing condolences while not letting in their sadness. It's a bit of a tightrope to walk but you don't last long if you can't get the right balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do a search for most popular Catholic funeral hymns and you'll get a variety of lists. The most common hymns include:

On Eagle's Wings
Amazing Grace
How Great Thou Art
Blest Are They
Be Not Afraid
Here I Am, Lord
Prayer of St. Francis
You Are Mine 
I Know That My Redeemer Lives
Christ Be Our Light
Lord of All Hopefulness
We Have Been Told
Eye Has Not Seen
I Am the Bread of Life

Most funerals I sang included at least one from that list. Most of those hymns have some reference to resurrection and/or salvation. People seem to find those thoughts comforting. 

Additionally, you need a psalm setting. Most people; in my experience, chose either Psalm 23 (The Lord is My Shepherd), 27 (The Lord is my Light), or 103 (The Lord is Kind and Merciful). There is also a mass setting containing sung parts of the mass that must be chosen. Most parishes have a standard setting, so you need to know several offhand in order to avoid surprises (I know 7). 

Lastly, you need a meditation and song of farewell. These tend to be where you get the most variety. In my experience, you find some ethnic preferences among these as well as some standards. Schubert's "Ave Maria" is so popular it's basically a running joke among Catholic funeral singers. I've sung it literally hundreds of times and could sing it on command from memory with no warm-up or warning provided you let me pick the key. Panis Angelicus is another meditation I sang often. Ethnic preferences mostly included traditional hymns or parish-specific favorites. For example, Irish-dominated parishes will tend to have lots of requests for a religious setting of the tune to Danny Boy or another traditional hymn called "St. Patrick's Breastplate". French-Canadians often want to hear "J'irai La Voir Un Jour" or another traditional French hymn. Similar preferences exist for other ethnic groups as well. You might also have a hymn to celebrate a particular family member passing, such as "Mother, At Her Feet Are Kneeling" or a Marian hymn for a deceased mother. 

Most important, however, is checking with the funeral director regarding the gender of the deceased so you use the right pronouns for the hymn. I wish I could say that had never gone wrong before. 

Keep in mind that I'm talking most common here. I've had many funerals that included only hymns from that list and the Ave Maria. I've also had eclectic funeral requests with none of the content listed here. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 11:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a funeral musician for quite a long time. 4-6 funerals a week, mainly Catholic services. I made approximately $40k a year just in funeral service fees. Most people I know think I'm joking when I tell them I did that as a job. 

Basically, I show up at funerals and play and/or sing religious service music. I could do it almost without thinking since there are really only 20-25 songs/hymns that people want to hear at a funeral. You show them a list of suggestions and they get their service music, easy peasy. The tomes where you got an odd request were exciting by comparison. Show up 15 minutes before, leave 10 minutes after, collect your check on the way out. 

It sounds pretty heartless the way I describe it. Perhaps it is a bit. That sort of mindset is needed, however, to have any shot at being able to do the job. We all developed a bit of gallows humor just to cope with the sadness of comforting mourners on a daily basis. However, you cant really know what it's like to do that job until you are actually doing it. I've sung at a funeral for 4 dead kids and their mother who died trying to protect them in a freak house fire. I showed up to sing one time for the funeral of a 20-year old who choked to death on a sour ball. The casket was still open...some regions of the country have open-casket calling hours in the church just before the service. Another time, I sang at the funeral of a woman who had just given birth to her 2nd child. Her family members were wailing and throwing themselves at the casket. If you think you know what I mean by wailing, you probably don't know...it's a unique, haunting sound that creeps into my mind at low moments. 

I call it the best worst job I'll ever have. 

Edit: Thank you very much to the kind stranger who gilded my comment! It's my first time getting gold. I now feel like a real Redditor. I've been replying to people's comments along the way, so feel free to ask questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 09:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't care that you think they are morally bankrupt because they are, in fact, morally bankrupt. They are in power now. That's all they care about. Stop being naive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this statement wholeheartedly. As a professor, the best thing that can happen to me in the classroom is that a student takes the time to thank me or tell me they enjoyed my class. Feedback on our research is often slower and more negative. Student feedback is what sustains me as I wait for reviews on my research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedantry...the last vestige of the poor argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reject your characterization of my comment. On the one hand, you have students of color presenting an argument about a group of people they view as having systematically oppressed their people for centuries. In the other hand, you have you, a person who is upset (or feigning upset) at the confrontational argumentation style these student have chosen. The aggrieved feelings of the first group deserve far greater consideration of the second. I reject your attempt to goad me with a false equivalence through the use of your counter example. The merits of style are debatable and of lesser importance to the merits of pointing out systematic oppression are not. 

As for your edited addition, you are misrepresenting your previous comment. Calling something "disgusting" and "racist, divisive nonsense" implies a certain amount of disagreement with those points. We are in agreement that they are divisive...it's not clear to me that they are all racist, although they probably they are. 

Lastly, you should expect that your statements will be held to a higher standard here than in some other subreddits. I simply assumed you were an academic since I wouldn't expect you to visit this area if you weren't. Your attempt at provocation was therefore treated just as I would treat one of these students' attempts: dispassionately and thoughtfully. I replied because your so-called provocative statement was poorly constructed. In future, you would do better to construct better arguments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how you can judge a presentation on the title. Titles are intended to be eye-catching and, in some instances, provocative. All of these slides certainly accomplish those goals, even those which aren't strictly title slides. Just because you don't agree with the theses (I'm guessing based on your butt-hurt response here) doesn't make them not worth considering or explication. Of course, the support for these these needs to be just as rigorously scrutinized as any other support for any other theses. Aren't we for academic freedom here, however? Perhaps the problem is that we aren't appropriately bothered when "How Muslims ruined NYC for everyone" is censored out of presentations, either explicitly or through self-censorship. 

This isn't /r/politics. We can be thoughtful about such provocations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like he tried to do that, but two women he impregnated had abortions. Does it say anything about him that he can't seem to find a woman willing to bear his child? It's unlikely that two women had their birth control fail with the same guy accidentally...that's a rather low probability event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you will! ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There it is again...willful ignorance and/or blatant obtuseness. It's not a conspiracy theory if one knows for a fact that it is occurring. Your failure to  "buy it" has no bearing on reality. 

Facts aren't debatable...they are facts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to believe you're being deliberately obtuse here. Otherwise, I have to believe your brain dead or a blatant racist. None of these are flattering, of course, but obtuseness at least has comedic value. 

Stick to the Trump pages, in any event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been an underwriter and I'll tell you that this is absolutely, positively, 100% unethical and wrong. Any data which needs to be obtained independently from the borrower needs to be obtained using proper, verifiable procedures. For banking information, this involves either a document procured directly from the bank with the borrower's signed consent or an independent verification of previously obtained documentation from the borrower. Who would even trust the loan officer if they went and verified the information themselves...they have financial incentives to lie, meaning they might want the password to print up information that is overly positive toward the borrower (e.g. Deposits only, excluding certain transactions, etc.).

I would not only involve the bank management above this clown, I'd probably say something to a regulator. Of course, I'm mean...or so my students tell me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have an identical twin? I thought every turd was unique?

Also, Seamus O'Drunkigan called. He wants his potato back, so take it off your real nose and put in the mail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Summer's Eve had a face, it would tell you to stop stealing its thunder with yours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty sad state of affairs when even your dogs find you too dull to pay you any attention. Read a book between reps, son! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get this roast done quickly, folks! I'm sure he has a neighbor hidden away in a pit somewhere who desperately needs some lotion in a basket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like Prince William's mildly handicapped brother who was stolen away from the Palace at birth and forced to live in poverty with Lady Di's chambermaid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tofu Palin?!? That's the legit funniest thing I've seen all week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll tell you...at least from the first list, I found myself agreeing with a couple of them. That tells me something about myself I don't like because, quite frankly, I hate me some Colin Cowherd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 19:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how the cat being kicked seems to be mumbling to himself toward the end. "Goddamned Reece, why can't he just go to his basket like everyone else...stupid jerk...my eye hurts...wait until I tell Mom!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You damn well better have an A! You don't get to be tough and lazy at the same time. I'd still complain, though, because you've essentially been cheated out of an important learning experience by this boob.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 08:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In her defense, she isn't soliciting some random person. This is the father of her child and someone she has a history with. Granted, that doesn't make it alright to be seeking out other relationships while living with a BF. I wouldn't go suggesting she's a pattern cheater, however, given the circumstances. 

As far as the rest of it goes, I think you make a good point. Money and stability can be a very attractive thing for someone in an unstable place in their own life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alas not. It was mainly about the use of accounting as a control mechanism rather than anything as "customer facing" as telonium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 11:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow...I've actually read that article. It was great! Not as great as the Harry Potter series, of course, but excellent as far as accounting history articles go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot believe this is the top comment on this thread. I was prepared to put my own most evil thought here, but now I'm hesitating because it's clearly at least 6 times more evil than anything written here thus far. 

Weak sauce, Reddit!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 08:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go managerial and put "The Bare Essentials: Materials, Labor, and Overhead!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only issue I can see with this channel is that the videos and commentary are from NHK World. If you download their app, you can see a schedule that will tell you when they'll be streaming their Grand Sumo Highlights. Because it's someone else's production, I can see a situation where this channel gets shut down at some point in the future. Kintamayama, by contrast, pieces together his videos and provides his own commentary...much more of a "fair use" than simply grabbing the NHK production.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the implication that anything OP says or doesn't say could potentially be responsible for his mother committing suicide thereafter. Clearly the OP should avoid being needlessly cruel. But I don't see why OP shouldn't seek the comfort of family if that's what is needed. OP is the victim here, not the mother. It's up to the mother to deal with any revelation of her awful actions as she sees fit. Don't put it on the OP to also manage the mother and gee feelings. 

With that said, I agree OP would benefit from a therapist to talk this all over with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 06:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over in YouTube land, Kintamayama basically suggested that Tochinoshin intentionally lost his match to Gagamaru in order to help Gagamaru ensure his kachi koshi. A number of the commenters on the video seemed to agree. I also noticed that the NHK highlights program didn't include that fight in their footage for the day. It certainly looked like Tochinoshin got beaten handily, but he seemed to look that way in some of his other matches. Of course, those other matches were with higher ranked opponents...

Is there some sort of open secret regarding match throwing I don't know about because I'm a relatively new follower of the sport? It seems like throwing a match would be very costly, what with the use of tournament records to seed the following tournaments. I know there were some issues with match fixing in the not-so-distant past, but that doesn't seem to be what's being suggested here (or is or)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply superb writing...superb! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 07:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to echo the other respondent to your comment. Can you give us a sense of how much you got charged for something like this?

Also...CAD file? That means we have to design it ourselves or also find someone to design it for us? Or is this something we could find a source for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry that people like you and OP have to deal with terrible families like this. I think it's fine if people want to distance themselves from family members. Stringing them along instead of cutting ties, however, just seems evil! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other news, a teenage boy from Jamaica Plains died. Cause of death was listed as irony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 06:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earth Sciences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does filtering technology for fossil fuel power plants do more harm than good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 05:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pollution, Particulate Matter Size, and Public Health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Jill Stein! If she wanted to help out the progressive cause, she should have either get her act and her party's act together or thrown her support to Hillary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, this constitutes "theft by finding" in the UK. A homeless person was prosecuted and fined for it recently. What a mess! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what happen here if Kisenosato somehow holds on to win this basho in a playoff? I know it's unlikely, but it's fun to consider. Do the preceding three tournaments qualify him for promotion with a win this week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting. Regression analysis aside, this sort of anomaly should trigger an automatic recount of some sort! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This data is available for a fee through BoardEx. It's rather expensive to get, however, and I believe it only covers board members for the S P 1500.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvote for pedantry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sort of nonsense if infuriating! I'm glad that you got the help you need, but we need our institutions to be helping out those with the sort of help they actually need. This includes travel money if it comes down to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you did the right thing. She may have to suffer some consequences for her actions, but encouraging her to evade the law might have made you a party to the crime. Let's hope, for her sake, she gets some credit for coming forward. 

As far as legal ramifications, she likely is facing some combination of fines, loss of license, and/or jail time. If she had stayed, they'd have gotten her for DUI. Hit-and-runs often gave more severe consequences than the accident itself. Nevertheless, the immediate consequences are likely to be liveable. She'll probably be offered bail so it won't keep her out of work in the short term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've worked at a school like that and we were "asked" to give the benefit of the doubt to the students. Again, a C can't magically become an A or anything like that. But a C+ could become a B- to save a Big-4 placement. I now work at a more selective school...same reasoning applies. 

This fellow thinks he's teaching you a lesson, but he's just screwing with lives if the grade distribution is as you say it is. He should be stopped. Absolutely, 100% bring it to the department chair! If you want to write a note that will have maximum impact, PM me and I'll give you tips and help you craft it. It won't help you now, but it will help you feel like you got some revenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write that letter, OP, or visit the department chair in person. It absolutely will help other students. I can confirm that professors have conversations like this, both formally and informally. A recent faculty meeting in my department saw us talking about discrepancies like you saw here, leading us to agree that all professors who teach the same course would meet and agree on a shared median grade to be enforced by the department. It's true that we can't force each other to grade a specific way without their consent (it's an issue of academic freedom). However, not all professors are even thinking about the real world implications of their grading. Once made aware of it, people have ways of getting very pragmatic. We mostly know where our bread is buttered and want the best for our students. You can't pass people who should fail, you shouldn't turn a C into an A, but you can and should squeak out a B- from a C+ if it'll keep a Big 4 placement. 

I'm curious...did the OP try asking their professor for the B-? I know some professors will ignore the plea, but they might also have been amenable to negotiation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 65% as a minimum?!? No wonder Canadians are so happy and friendly. They have low standards, apparently! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Jesus...the brother sounds like a dish rag, but OP sounds like a complete nutter here! Get some therapy, calm your rage, and stay distant from the family until you've done both! They're infuriating, but that's no reason for violence! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's is actively telling you he isn't going to change. Believe him and leave for both your sakes. You should also get some therapy. There are no excuses for the sort of angry outbursts you report in your post. They will kill any chances you have of building a healthy relationship in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how many law professors are on here. However, you can probably do some research while you wait for an answer by looking at vitas of professors at law schools where you think you might like to work. See what degrees they have, what sort of work experience, and whether or not they did clerkships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that. That doesn't negate my puzzlement, however. Maybe it's because I'm an academic and know that it isn't purely a meritocracy. He's not in academia, however...and perhaps succeeding on his own merits isn't surprising because of that fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kudos to your uncle for keeping it stylish while under the "care" of the US Government! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha...the dangers of my replying while half asleep. 

Nate Silver doesn't have an earned doctorate, but instead has four honorary doctorates. I find that kind of fascinating! Sure, he did his Bachelors at Chicago and studied at the LSE for a bit, but one wonders how he got so much credibility without the credentials? I mean, knowing this doesn't change my opinion of his work...but it's a puzzler.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom adopted rather than risk another girl...going along with that horse shit is all the evidence I need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that...I thought I made it clear that I was grasping for straws. The whole thing makes me want to vomit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this and ponder what sort of monsters Texas lawmakers must be to inflict the sort of psychological damage and personal risk on young LGBT kids. Is there any way this comes from a legitimate place of concern for these kids? I just...I need to think there are still good people on the other side of our politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
