<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even playing through hard I found there to be loads of ammo.

You only need to tap the fire button to make the bastard think twice which should only cost you about five ammo. Most useful get out of jail card for sure when it comes to the alien, as even if he hits you through the fire it'll only knock you over and take away a fraction of your health.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was *extremely* fortunate in these factors:

- I live close enough to London for people out of town to agree when I say i'm from London
- I live far enough out of London that I don't have London pricing (still 2nd most expensive county though)
- I was born into a decent family business
- Left school at 13 and went to work, so have 5-6 years cost free head start on saving
- My parents beat into my skull to buy a property ASAP (I paid 164,000 for a house in my hometown in 2005, and sold it in 2013 for 330,000)
- I then could afford to buy a plot of land, and am currently living in a mobile home on this plot while I build a house as I can afford it.

I appreciate that's a lot of info, but I just wanted to ram home that I am *extremely* lucky, and I am aware of that i'm like more lucky than**9**3% of the population. In any case, yeah I have a very unique position for a 36 year old man. 

TL;DR: I Own.


Edit: wrong percentile haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumour has it that he lost a testicle due to the trousers being so tight. That also helped him hit those high notes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 09:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's movie logic. There is no real explanation for it only that it can do it, further making it more Alien compared to our understanding of science. Which honestly is still the best explanation imho as it gives the creature a degree of mystique that I fear will soon be lost in the next upcoming 3 alien/Prometheus movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 09:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South of London, UK

I own a carpet and flooring business and also do photography on the side. Married, two young kids. 

While I don't spend as much on me as I do my wife from time to time, I'll spend 200 np on a decent jumper. I have a penchant for Brora stuff at the minute (gotta love cashmere) and the last jumper I got from there was 315.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never look at Hollyoaks the same way again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the UK and play usually after work 8pm-11pm when I do. I've never joined an empty table during these times so it seems there are plenty of players. I can't talk for daytime play though as I've never experienced it. 

As a game though even if you have lag it isn't like playing an fps game. Just switch server clusters to US and you'll be golden even if it turns out EU numbers are low during the day (although I don't think they are) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always one isn't there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And **cold** wet t-shirts. 

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the fact than Nick is hanging out on the far right with that smug grin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phantasy Star Online was the shit.

I always wanted the Opa-Opa mag for my hunter :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC:

Pre Prometheus, and excluding the AVP films, yes.

Post Prometheus, we have Guy Pearce playing 'Weyland', although ti could be a totally different Weyland, as Weyland-Yutani isn't a thing yet so it's still possible that Bishop was based on one of Peter Weyland's descendants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 09:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who upvote this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every PSVR headset owner should have this accessory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The jedi and the Sith are two halves of the same whole. I'm cool with there being no Sith as long as there are no Jedi too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf is a thinner gypsy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 08:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again I need to point out that the platform has been out for *three months*. 

Give it a chance, games take time but do what you got to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a game where a table of 8 players may be full for hours so if you're unlucky I hear some people having to wait ten minutes or so for a game. This has never happened to me though, and even when I've started a game I've had it full in under five.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't happen in my house. 

Not unless she wants to be cleaning up bucket loads of poop afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is most like to play in VR would be a full blown mechwarrior simulator, but I'm not sure how that would work on PS4. 

On PS4, resident evil is going to take some beating, but something in the Alien franchise would get a lot of notice from nom VR people I think. 

As far as mechanically, the London Heist honestly made into a 10-15 hour title would work amazingly. Also I have high hopes that Farpoint will be the major system seller here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely get it. 

Provided you learn how the game works and don't start eating a packet of crisps or start playing dubstep down your mic, folks are more than patient, and it's a great way to learn what different dialects there are and how many areas have little nuances in the language. 

You'll find you'll speak far more fluently far quicker than just hanging iut with people from the same town, and most likely meet someone who speaks the same native tongue as you who will be able to help you say the words you still don't know. It's a pretty diverse bunch of nationalities on there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of the way you mean yeah i think it's fine. It's a similar thing divers experience when underwater for any period of time. Some suffer with it and others don't. I'm one of the fortunate ones that don't suffer from this nor the motion sickness. 

Things I'm a little more concerned about is the effect on your eyes it may have looking at something that close up for extended periods, and having the pressure of the unit on your head for that time also. I do find even when trying to put the unit on as loosely as possible that after playing for thirty or fourth minutes I start to get a pressure headache.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where people are getting here time from. 

If he has a PS4 already set up (and has a camera) I was playing games in less that five minutes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you find them my sweet? 

Did you find the ones on the black mamba? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EVE Valkyrie** **6/10**
Fun for a short while as long as you don't burn out on it, but quickly supplanted by RiGS.

**RiGS** **8/10**
My favorite action game at the moment. Fast, with a high skill ceiling. The only drawback is that multiplayer matches often have bots.

**Werewolves Within** **10/10**
The absolute most fun i've had with my PS4. So much fun, after a couple of rounds it feels like the other players are mates and you're sat in a pub having a laugh.

**PSVR Worlds** **6/10**
Great as a demo disc or to introduce friends to VR when they come over. Ocean Descent is great for non gamers, and London Heist is awesome with move controllers and has the best gunplay yet on PSVR.

**Brookhaven Experiment** **6/10**
Again, a good demonstration for people when they come over. Has great mechanics but a smattering of content. Very decent gunplay.

**Until Dawn: Rush of Blood** **7/10**
Decent rail shooter with a surprising amount of replay value if you like to see different paths in games like this, and a good amount of collectibles. It is the cheapest method of getting replayability though. Second best gunplay on the system to London Heist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have PSVR you can hack it using TrinusPsvr on your PC to make steam think you have a Vive or Oculus equipped. I'm not sure yet though if there are any way of getting move controllers to work with it yet though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tip:

Breath in hard, then remove the cigar and then blow out and see if you can choke Frank with your smoke puff :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /Thread.

The more the indies have success, the more likely the bigger companies will support VR with their regular games (like Resident Evil 7).

It will be a long time though before we see any large number of AAA VR exclusive games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm genuinely surprised and happy Ubisoft is still throwing VR stuff out.

Honestly I feel dirty for loving Werewolves Within so much, as Ubisoft has some terrible business practices and I try not to buy games associated with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a Tiger in your area, you'll get a big bag of them for like 1.

I have hidden them everywhere in my house, even my wifes Kitchenaid Mixer (her pride and joy) has not escaped the googlyness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gutted tbh, as it's definitely in my top 3 PSVR games.

Hopefully the staff all find jobs elsewhere, I know sometimes staff get absorbed into other studios under the same parent company so fingers crossed, and hopefully their experience in their new companies will help spread VR compatability in other future releases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While there definitely should be some little guards you can fit into the unit to protect the lenses included in the box when you buy PSVR, provided you stop the unit from being rammed onto your face when putting it on, you shouldn't have any problems.

I feel that there should be an update to the PS4 OS where when it detects the VR unit it reminds you not to place it as close to your eyes as possible, as it also helps to prevent fogging up the lenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you're coming from, but please remember this is technically year one tech. A glimpse if you like into home VR.

I also have two young children (10 weeks, and very nearly 4 years), so I know exactly what you mean about it being a production, but come on. It takes literally a minute to unbox the unit, and plug it into my PS4 in the evening when they go to bed. Hell, when my wife is out I even bring my sons cot into my study so I can play and with the sound down to about 50% I can easily hear him if he cries. There are games that while you can play a similar game with a regular computer or console, take on a whole different experience when in VR. There is really only 3 or 4 games I would say currently released that are actually full proper games and not 'experiences', which I guess may be part of your problem, but the system has been out what? Three months?

Werewolves Within is by far the greatest experience i've had in VR gaming since playing Xorex on the old W Industries machines in the very early ninties. Resident Evil is a prime candidate for this too. The game feels *totally* different in VR.

You are entitled to your opinion, but you say it yourself. Time will tell, and I don't think you gave VR enough time. Hopefully you'll get to try some more games in a few years when the tech has been embedded into the industry for a short while and we begin to see more games like Resi that can be played both ways, allowing VR users to get some proper games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got banned a few weeks after release from Archeage as TRION classed this as third party programs which as against their TOS. 

Bullshit reason I know, and that doesn't necessarily say that will happen here but i'm just putting it out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> clearly is a multi player PVP game

No, it isn't clearly a multiplayer game, and even that component still has some pretty major flaws. It's not a bad game, but considering its one of the most expensive games on the platform it is still pretty shy on content, that is why it gets a lot of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood that last line, because she isn't Ripley, and she knows she isn't Ripley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to avoid spoilers here, but great username Rookie Killer ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Nobody has played it yet. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instantly the Genie spawns a little dwarf whos name is "I knowingly, consciously, and of my own free will under no duress" who you best keep happy as you'll die when this little guy chooses :P

These genies aren't to be trusted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rejoice. 

And stake a claim on some celebrity chefs small holding like Hugh fearnley whittingstalls home which has a massive farm next to it and try to cultivate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling bullshit on this. This looks more like a probable features wish list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do I, but even though I sit close to the screen, I can't read some of the text in games when playing them in 4K. Battlefront for instance, the waypoint markers are almost non existant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, while you are *technically* correct, most people from Britain under 50 would not say 'cheerful' when asked what the primary meaning of the word 'Gay' would be :P

Anyway, Technically correct is the best kind of correct :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to bitch about reposts but this was posted literally several hours previously to this post, to this sub, with a different title. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/TheDepthsBelow/comments/5ml581/what_is_that_thing/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Brett is standing in the equivalent to the air conditioning unit to the Nostromo so it's cold condensation that has collected and started dripping that he is bathing his face in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still waiting for my codes and I bought mine the day before release day :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have similar complaints about battlefront too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the single player missions are connected by an overarching story (a pretty basic one) making it a campaign  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is called single player mode

In the quiet words of the Virgin Mary: Come again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak directly for them as I'm a rom, but there are Irish down my road and at my kids school and nursery. 

Generally speaking from what I've seen is that the teachers will try at first and then give up on them somewhat when the mum starts rocking up to school in her nightdress and juicy couture pink dressing gown and basically using the place as day care. I want to be clear here that this is not a blanket statement. The parents that show engagement tend to help their kids in school and be proxy they perform better and then the teachers seem to be more helpful with them. It's the ones that fit the stereotype i see being left behind, and I believe that largely is due to those parents not wanting them to learn too much and risk being influenced by the gorgers. 

So in short the ones that show interest seem to get help, and the ones that fit the stereotype tend not to. This is just my personal observation though. 

As for promoting and supporting our cultures, we will learn our cultures via our families. If schools want to support us in that, truancy laws need to change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not called practice mode either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seriously underestimate the potential of VR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I bought it recently in the sale along with werewolves within, I really enjoyed it but I've only played it once due to having so much fun with werewolves within:P

How did you get the tracking to work 360 degrees for your weapon?? I have to use the circle button to flip myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is literally 90% chatting and looking at folks. Make your family wear headphones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the only game I bought used, and I paid 25 for it which I feel is about the right price. I made a point of not buying it new so I could play it while CCP didn't get a whole bunch more money for another copy sold. While I do want to support the platform, I don't want to encourage this kind of behaviour from developers and publishers. The PSVR user base is older than the stock PS4 and rest of the console bunch, it'd be nice if the half ass production tactics didn't fly with us here on this platform. 

Many reviewers have said how light on content it is, and while the multiplayer is alright, I still prefer rigs as a multiplayer game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not called a training mode is it?so what would you call the single player missions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the crux of this argument is that Eve: Valkyrie tried to pass itself off as a AAA title what with its price and marketing, which you get a very, very small amount of content for that price. 

Had it been 20 new it wouldn't seem to be anywhere near as bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your point, but there isn't anywhere near the teamwork, variety of class-ship, maps, plain old fun, party play in Valkyrie, that there is in overwatch. 

That's not to say Eve: Valkyrie deserves to be hated, because it does have its moments. It just is very, very disappointing in that with a couple of months work, they could have fleshed out the single player a bit more, and gave the multiplayer depth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The system has been out for literally 3 months and I get the impression you expect there to be a library for itequivalent to the rest of the PS store for regular PlayStation games. 

Give it time, this is the first time this tech has really existed for general home use and most developers are really only experimenting with VR at the moment. Let's see what happens over the next few years. 

Anyway, Resident evil is out in a few weeks and that really is the first real AAA title made with VR in mind. As you say you've been spoiled somewhat but bare with it. This is basically a new system launch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tips I found:

- Keep the box and store your headset in it when not using it and not on one of those stands. Keeping the lenses free of dust is really important. 

- if you wear glasses try not to smoosh them to your face by sliding the unit all the way into your face as this can also severely damage the lenses. 

- although hard because when you get it you'll be itching to play it, try to start off with short play sessions first of like 20 minutes before taking a break. I never had an issue with motion sickness but several folks I have loaned the unit to have said that repeated short sessions really helped them play games like Scavengers Odyssey without throwing up by acclimatising themselves to it over a period of time. 

- There is a sale on right now IIRC on the PlayStation store. Get some games while you can. 

- While possible to play move games (motion controller) in a small space, you really need a 3m square area to flail around when playing games like Brookhaven Experiment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah same situation for me, just don't squash your glasses onto your face and there is no problem. 

Little foam protectors would be a nice addition though, if only to make the system somewhat consumer proof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a pain in the ass having to wait but ultimately it should be a good thing for the medium. 

If the units are selling well, games should also sell well which will then promote more developers to make some VR games and push the envelope. I love playing VR games and I really don't want the medium to fail, so remember to buy your games new and not second hand ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reward is the social interaction and the comedy that ensues. Honestly I've had more fun in the first few days of owning it than any other game in recent memory. 

You could indeed go play the game with friends, but then you'd get to know people's tells etc. Playing with new people everyday keeps the game fresh and engaging. Also having someone new face palm as they say at the start of a round 'I'm the saint, what do I do?" Is hilarious, particularly when it turns out they are the turncloak and it was all a sham :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The excitement I felt the first time I wasn't a villager... The first time I played the game my first like 8 rounds or something I was a villager. 

Then being a werewolf after was fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I REALLY wanted to try this when it came out on steam using a VR headset but didn't want to drop 800 on a headset. 

Now I have PSVR and hopefully I'm going to get the chance! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an industry you could never imagine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe, my stamina lifting track is [Raw Power](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AFi338RFfNw), busting out a super set of clean and press, and prisoner squats is amazing to this rhythm.

If i'm going for PB's I normally go cheesy like [Arnold - Luke Million](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qJdMjRHRLfg) for the pre lift pump :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In hindsight it was a bad idea for me. I have an 8 week old baby at home so game time is pretty limited at the minute :P I still haven't tried battlezone and some others although I've had them installed for a while. 

I keep getting pulled back to rigs and werewolves within :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's pretty cool. 

I listen to this one but the original is my go to cardio track.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just leave this remix here:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nd77RcjjprU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck snakes.

I spent like 100 on VR titles a week ago after getting my PSVR
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be frank when a bouncer queries you, not being a fucking dick about it normally works in your favour. 

Ask how their night is going. Crack a joke. Whatever. Just don't make their night harder for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hung Jury from the Y2 dead orbit vendor is probably the closest there is to an OP right now, but good luck getting the same roll now that the condor has stopped selling it like that. 

That would be closely followed by Treads Upon Stars, the rockets McDickface strike loot. I managed to get one iirc with explosive rounds on and firefly which while I prefer hung jury still makes for an amazing scout rifle. It's just a shame I rarely use it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pair of move controllers. 

I just found Brookhaven a far superior game so far. Maybe I need to spend some more time with Rush of Blood, so I'll spend some more time with it this week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 03:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Rush of Blood listed many times, but I really don't get it's appeal. Sure it's fun and all, but after playing the first 5 levels of it I didn't see anything that made me think it was sop much better than anything else.

Did I miss something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the wake of Carrie Fishers death, a petition has been made for Disney to officially induct Princess Leia into the annuls of official Disney Princesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 03:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allow me to plug 'Victorian Pugs' here. 

Longer faces, longer legs and a straighter tail, they resemble the breed how it was several generations ago. The kennel club doesn't recognise them, but they are a far healthier breed and a far less inbred unhealthy breed than the current pug.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only difference really is that the rear 60 degrees or so is difficult to aim at due to how PSVR camera detects the move controllers. This is solved quite neatly by being able to press the circle button to flip yourself 180 degrees and face back letting you quickly check behind you so it's slightly easier from that respect. 

Honestly though the game is definitely worth the 15, I'd only to watch your mates crap their pants on the first wave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it make and weird noises? I remember seeing a video where the lyre bird could imitate chainsaws and even a camera with a motor drive flawlessly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it will be removed shortly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Packets of salted peasants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still haven't played a game where the match was entirely populated by players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... I've been playing since Boxing Day and don't remember pulling any off. Be right back :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Digital store should still have deals until the 6th. 

Honestly though if you have any hope for VR to be adopted, buy the titles from a store and not second hand. The tech will stagnate if there aren't enough sales behind it to make it and enticing prospect for developers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same problem. All I did to fix this was wear my glasses and position the headset one notch further off my face. Try it from when you first put the headset on and hopefully it'll work for you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence the basis of it's appeal to 90's me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and then blame younger Carrie for partying so hard so she would then look like shit. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but essentially headhunting talent is how the best business become better.

It works for government departments also </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  level 59 Tamer here

My condolences. 

I got to soft cap but found that I couldn't be competitive in any form unless I wanted to spend 24/7 in game, or a couple of thousand quid and I just kept getting owned by Sorcb1tc4 H4r4mbe or someone similar. Then I'm told Tamer is the weakest class by several different sources and then couldn't face levelling a second class again. 

The grind is real and I just couldn't face it again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why people poo poo the nes classic. 

It's like saying buying a car out of the showroom is shit when you can build your own with a little know how for a similar cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 10:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't skip any of the story content in FFXIV to be honest. 

While it isn't the greatest story in the series, Squenix seem to be focusing on one well told story per expansion instead of a single massive over arching storyline, and so far they've been pretty damn good. Plus, the way the game approaches classes (one character can do everything) there isn't a need to level up alts replaying the same story content over and over so it doesn't outstay its welcome. 

If you're remotely a Final Fantasy fan I would definitely recommended the game, as the bulk of the players I came across while playing shared my love of the series and it's good to chat with them. 

From a purely mmorpg perspective, it's very competent but is most definitely a theme park mmo (good or bad depending on your preference). The crafting system is fairly enjoyable too with a small mini game to play during crafting. 

As far as tips for a newcomer:

- Research what job you want to play before hand. The game has both classes and jobs, and a character becoming proficient in several classes opens up a job for your character (Summoner, Gladiator, Black Mage etc). This should be the number one tip as levelling classes takes time, and levelling one up that doesn't effect or cross class into your chosen job is annoying. Some classes have skills that can be slotted in other jobs too, you should look at what ones are available for each job. 

- When you get to flying mount zones the game requires you to travel around each zone and collect aether currents (basically forcing you to see the entire map before flying). It's ok collecting these while questing, but it's a pain getting them afterwards. Try not to miss them. 

- dungeons are often required to progress the story, queue for these asap as sometimes the wait for the less popular ones can be pretty lengthy. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got PSVR, so the only thing better than this would have been an alien isolation sequel announcement with VR support :P

And some man diapers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I agree with you.

I dip my toes in PVP in games like Destiny in small bite sized chunks. Every few months theres an event in Destiny that lasts a week that makes me thirst for the grind, but by the end of that week i'm so mind numbingly bored of it, I can't look at PVP for a few weeks, and then return to games like ESO or something.

What I really want from my next mmo though is a game where the focus is on the 'RP' of the mmorpg. Less stats, more getting a group together and *doing* something together that doesn't involved repeatedly running a twenty minute dungeon 5 millions times farming tokens.

I know people look at it with rose tinted goggles, but I really think the reason why UO was so popular was that while it had a dedicated PVP population, there was a large RP dynamic too. People hired other players to help them transport goods etc. They'd take over bridges and charge tolls etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 09:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When those teeth long and sharp, play your bones like a harp, that's a moray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 09:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suede shoes should work, but I always find that boat shoes tend to look good with chinos of any colour. They aren't *very* dressy but I guess that isn't required when talking about chinos.  

This kind of thing: http://www.orvis.com/orvis_assets/prodimg/7A3AL2FH.jpg?01AD=3zXscHyQHDWEHq1eEhFvdMqNwB9X97JrTkWmb8y9KgTxlBMtE6QgwFQ 01RI=A2F7AB18E5D9007 01NA=na

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your son my mother?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 08:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice easy going track. This is the sort of thing I could lose some time to while on a long drive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know i'm flogging a dead horse when saying this but...

Disney will literally become my god if they grab Whedon and the surviving Firefly cast and make a similar show with similar tone set in the Star Wars universe.

Seriously, Star Wars firefly needs to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But your picture is of a actual Computer program in the films lore so technically is software anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looked like an animated human, and not a human if that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A'Jorah Hai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 11:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't work unless you're carrying a bullwhip and a hat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 09:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was making a point in another thread where Rogue One gives entirely different context to that scene. 

She's basically just giving sass to Vader now. That also chimes with how angry sounding he is in that scene. 

It does also make we wonder if Disney are now trying to plug that Vader knew Leia was his daughter. I mean, can you see anyone else giving Vader sass, *and surviving*?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 09:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure a shot from the Death Star is not going to be survivable for most folks :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 09:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I felt all the characters were lacking characterisation. I think they had too many characters for instance, while their scenes were fun, Chirrut, his friend (Base?) and the pilot all didn't really add anything to the story and their screen time could have given the other main characters more fleshing out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 09:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hanging from the ceiling, behind swipe, cut in half move Vader did was incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 08:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You summed up my thoughts exactly. 

None of the characters had adequate backstory save for Jyn, and certainly none of them felt like they went through any kind of character arc. The movie felt like a bunch of action sequences with some exposition thrown in between and every now and then a bonk on the head "look! You're watching Star Wars! Here's another reference!!"

I don't understand why people are raving about the film. I was really underwhelmed with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Rogue One makes it secretly seem that he knew Leia was his kid too.

Do you honestly think Vader would stand for someone giving him sass like that?.. diplomatic mission to alderaan my ass... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty underwhelmed. 

Maybe it's my fan goggles making it less of a movie than it really is but most of the characters were pretty throw away. I only felt that Jyn had adequate characterisation, and possibly Cassian. The rest could have been cut and not been missed. I feel the films biggest flaw was having too many main characters. Sure some are interesting (Chirrut and Baze), and K2S0 could have really done with more screen time seeing as he had some of the best lines in the film.

Everyone is cheering the CGI of Tarkin and honestly, it was terrible. Every time he's in a scene it just totally broke my immersion. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying, they are ultimately fun *wonderous* films, but I just want to see how despicable the greatest cinema movie villain could be :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really REALLY hope we get to see that cut one day. 

I feel Disney may have put he brakes on it to make it *slightly* more family friendly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an option for backers to have the Pryme version free of charge, but doing so forfeits your option for a refund. 

I hear those that did choose this option are still waiting for those 8 year olds introductory science kits to become advanced enough so Mark One can use it put the water detecting cup together, which may take quite some considerable time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 08:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meaty mushrooms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck snakes.

Spent 25 silver dust LAST NIGHT on an ornament :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using a 980Ti and it's not playable for me at those settings. 

I can reduce them down and have the game look good like it, but max setting sis a stretch for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a balding fat 36 year old man, I have encountered this. I think it also has something to do with how good looking you are, as most of the men I have spoken to about this have been fairly... pleasant looking I guess? Lean, nice hair etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I have a penis and I am a pervert."

This statement is how I am made to feel when I take my kid to soft play on my days off from work. 

Seriously though, yeah I like sex, I did some at some point hence I brought my own kid there. But why do you think I'm a weirdo just because your kids are sexy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While that's not true, I understand the mentality. I am not confident that we will get another main entry in the series that will 'feel' like metal gear without Kojima.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good write up. 

Out of interest what's the consensus on Mr Pickles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always laugh when people say Destiny is dead :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea it was available for VR. Does it room scale??
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda irrelevant though. Droids can quite easily be rebuilt. C-3P0 was rebuilt in empire remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 07:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck sake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 10:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's still pretty accurate taken in the context of No Mans Sky lying bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 08:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like how everyone believed Anakin would "bring balance to the force" by defeating the sith, when he did that by murdering and bringing the Jedi down to similar numbers to the Sith, effectively balancing each side to equal quantities?

(This is secretly my hope for Luke's storyline in the sequel trilogy, that he won't want to rebuild the Jedi order) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 08:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my favourite rickyism :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 08:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye,

By the old mods, and the new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To rile him up. 

An agitated opponent makes mistakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 12:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive me for not checking and also trying to not put click situ titles on my posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 10:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 1 year "Did these games release this year?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar thing happen to me, only it was spread around town that I was gay because I turned her down, which to be frank kinda hurt me. 

Then several years later she falsely accused someone of rape, so I stopped hurting and started feeling like I dodged a bullet there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy sanity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This advert about a polish grandpa learning English to go and see his grandchild will leave some dirt in your eye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping he becomes the anti-Luke, showing what would have happened to him had Luke joined Vader instead of resisting the dark side. 

I want Kylo to go full ~~retard~~ dark side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
