<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long would it be to take effect and how long a fatal OD take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys sing about all sorts of self-destruction, including suicide, and they are DBSM, a sub-genre of Black Metal.  
They sing in Swedish and English, and the band name is Shining.  
One of my favorite bands ever.  
[Hail Darkness Hail](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BGY31niv_kk)    
[Claws Of Peridation](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ah4cs4f-gks)  
[Tillsammans r Vi Allt](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iULz19Cc7yw)  
[Fullstndigt Jvla Dd Inuti](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x5WpA6pQneM)  
[Frtvivlan, Min Arvedel](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KSNLnDH6tjA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, do it a couple times a week.  
It really helps me to de-stress and calm down, and it helps me to be less suicidal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents have mentioned me going back but they haven't made me, they think I could do with it but don't need it.
My boyfriend who knows more then them keeps saying about it as he thinks I do really need it but he knows I'd rather not, so he keeps pointing out the benefits but not actually telling me to go back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't give a fuck about my scars, they aren't that noticeable, but someone did notice like the 2nd day of College.  
Cuts, I like to keep them hidden, unless I'm alone or too hot, but they are on my legs at the moment and I never wear shorts anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to post my shit on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the weed that would induce bleeding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do tend to use this one to do research, and most of the time theres no anti-suicide messages, people think it's hypothetical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still enjoying this one, the questions are interesting to say the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends. Thinking about it is normal. Like nearly everyone has had those thoughts. What really matters is how you think.  
If it's "I wouldn't have to do this/worry if I was dead" or if it was "I don't want to deal with life anymore" That is normal and non-worrying.  
If you are beginning to figure out methods, plan it, doing research, now THAT is worrying and then you need help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good, I liked the different setting.  
Was being careful as I didn't want anyone to see but it was good, felt more peaceful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough and oh yeah, just jogged my memory.  That's still pretty painful. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 13:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it was around 6 for me, it's hard to deal with, and thank you.  
One of the guys might be in the same College but I haven't seen him yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 11:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no such thing as a perfect suicide method.  
There is always going to be that few percent, even if it's only 1-2% and you are always going to need materials, unless you are willing to explain this to me, I'm going to say that's never going to be possible :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 11:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you record this though?  
Unless it's for documentation or proof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give me that face :P 
Yeah I've found some good sites now, got some good info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I have, and I've been sexually abused by more than one guy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Various stages of healing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much eucalyptus oil is fatal and what is the efffects of an OD? Why is it fatal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 13:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not College, apart from the fact that one of the guys that abused me might be here but I have't seen him around yet, and I already took a year off.  
It is a bit, not great at budgetting which I need to learn.  
Parents - it's alright, nothing that bad, they are just overprotective and can take things the wrong way. 
And I have tried solving them before, for many years, and many treatments. Nothing is that effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be alright </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't to it at home as someone is always home, and there is nowhere to hang myself on my bedroom, I'd prefer trains as it's instant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know about that D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 08:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah alright, what's the other factors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I want it to be more secluded, and trains seem the best method IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, and I have to have a rucksack for college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought it was longer then that and fair enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College has already started here, and that would give them a fright and a half :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far does the drop have to be?
How long will it take them to die in both methods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, and this College has pretty big grounds and a dense forest/arboretum. The only people that really go in there is for 1, possibly 2 courses, and that's only in certain areas for 1 and the other sticks to the path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does hanging work? Info needed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like some info on who different types of hanging works and which one is the most effective, and how people do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want someone to troll?
Troll me, I don't give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want someone to troll?
Troll me, I don't give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want someone to troll?
Troll me, I don't give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want someone to troll?
Troll me, I don't give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While walking around the College Grounds, I found the 2 perfect trees that could be good for hanging. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only problem is one is right next to the path, the other one doesn't look strong enough but I haven't tested.
And I have no rope, and no money to get some, getting paid next week.
But I don't know when is the best time to get the rope, and how to get it to my room without my parents getting suspicious or finding it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it's a bit stupid and it's one of the most effective coping method I've had! I've done it on and off since age 12. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharpener blade, always used these. I've also got a Stanley blade which I nicked from My Dad's Stanley knife but I've never used one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 19:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a Kik group? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 19:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: No-one made any remarks and I was able to change my jeans before my family saw and I got a new blade :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I relate to this so much haha, 21 here but I'm in College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, and if something doesn't look right or it may be infected they will give advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad I'm at College and have no way of getting any and my bus is in 10 minutes FML xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends what I'm in the mood for really. Can be Slipknot or Shining, or could be a Dark Lotus or Insane Clown Posse song. 
Do you think the guys from ICP would be impressed if I carved the hatchet guy onto my leg and sent it to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not even that bad, this is the most effective coping method I have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they don't like anything different from normal.
I tend to post in /r/selfharmpics and I like looking at others,  I find it interesting and it has helped with urges and what would happen if I cut that deep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me laugh.
We so edgy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh it was quite a lot of cuts in the same area so it could of been that, I do tend to go deep, I just do lots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is I did put tissue there afterwards and kept it in my pants 
I'm more annoyed that I lost my blade .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the worst things about cutting is stains. Now I have to be in College with that and I can't find my blade again :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 14:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thighs before lesson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 14:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 08:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How effective is DBT?
I've only really heard good things about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 08:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright thanks that explains it, I can be like that at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 07:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I don't know the difference as I've only heard of the grandiose one.
What's the other one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 00:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Castor plants?   
What climate and where could you find them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 00:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How toxic is Rhubarb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 00:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way. If you want more understanding by people that think like this, /r/sanctionedsuicide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also untreated.  
Look at distraction techniques, mindfullness, and find a hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying, if you need to talk to someone ASAP, there is always /r/r4r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not on meds, I was (Zolotft and Ripsersonde) and it was very effective. Then I got better and got discharged, but stopped meds cold-turkey.  
There are many different ways to go about this. I tend to just listen to music and go for walks, but I hardly eat and I do self-harm.  
My Mum is in treatment but came off her meds sometime last year, therapy had been a godsend to her, she useses techniques used in DBT and Mindfullness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is really not accurate, I have no sense of self-worth or self-esteem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there really no cure for it? :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 20:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why hello there.
Are you following me to make sure I'm not infringing on creative property? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 13:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm out of treatment at the moment,  dyspraxia can cause some hassles with speech and coordination and social skills hut I'm managing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 11:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 here! 
I have Dyspraxia so I was born with it, but I also have BPD and C-PTSD,  both diagnosed at 20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it go, any coping methods that worked for you?
I wouldn't say I'm really that self-sabotaging. I have my moments when I snap at people or I'm a bit grumpy, but I wouldn't say it was serious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but I'll feel like I'm admitting defeat or I didn't try hard enough, I've been in therapy for 4 and a half years, and in April I got discharged.
It's only been 6 months since I've last went. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested, but I'm in the UK.
Is that a problem? 
If not, send me a PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad that I'm taking it out on the people around me, and would like to stop it, and I dont like getting upset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I stop snapping at people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 23:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what to do, I'm getting worse and it's making me grumpy and snappy. I do not like being snappy, as it could draw me into an argument and I'd really like to avoid that instead of getting in one and getting upset over something stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! I like looking at them, they are intersting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never done drugs, smoked, and I don't drink.  
I did go through a phase when I was 16 drinking a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 11:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to go straight to the Police and explain EVERYTHING.  
He has raped you, that's a crime, and he has the evidence which is the images on his phone, which would be classed as child porn.  
You need support and to talk this over, and if you don't feel comfortable going to a professional, there is subs on reddit, one of them being /r/ptsd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said that that's the most likely one, he put on my discharge paperwork PTSD with other symptoms caused by trauma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few just before shower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 13:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can BPD be left untreated? When should someone seek help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 11:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed back in April, along with C-PTSD, got offered Emotional Regulation Therapy, but declined and got discharged because I was doing really well. Fast forward a few months, getting moodswings, getting easily stressed for no reason, hardly eating and losing weight, suicidal and self-harming, along with my C-PTSD symptoms. 
But the thing is, I'm ok most of the day. But my boyfriend keeps on mentioning therapy when I don't think I need it. He said that I am ok most of the day, but at the same time, I'm not.  
I just think I can handle this by myself but he knows I'm gonna get stressed with College but I should to deal with this by myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 09:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what to talk about, this has happened many times before with people. It's even more frustrating is that he knows that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This song is us lot :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 03:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 03:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need to do it, do it. Your body, your choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's happened, or if I've just switched between laughing and crying. It's weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, after over a month of saying no every time he asked.  
He would not stop asking and I thought if I let him, he wouldn't mention it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How likely is the chance of dying from that?  
What happens if they survive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that's what I'm doing research on atm, doesn't help that my bedding is white. I got a Stanley blade but I don't know how well that would work.  
I'm soo hardcore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It helps me get less stressed and nervous, it's a distraction and a way to relax for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it's to do with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How deep could a Stanley blade cut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one on here or the one on /r/PTSD ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't if I was you, might explode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you actually hit stryrofoam and what have you used? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this and was curious if it would go that far but I have no idea how it would work https://imgur.com/edkbkNS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 00:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I don't tend to take care of my cuts.  
I just let them bleed then wash them off in the shower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sorta feel it is, I forgot to mention in my main post, is he knows I've been made to do stuff before and he knows I have PTSD, I should of carried on saying no but at the same time I've tried doing that before and the guy just wouldn't stop so I thought it would make him stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people don't know the meaning of the word no. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It shall be a battle to the death!
I shall be using a Tant,  the same sword the samurai used to commit seppeku,  it shall be easier to kill myself after so I don't get caught! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a part of your countries mental health team ain't gonna do shit,  you know nothing about me   
Come fight me irl faggot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did this on the train today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of weird or extreme ways to self harm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 11:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolwut  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sat with my feet on my Mum, I like having my feet played with or stroked when they are in her lap but I'm very nervous she's gonna lift up my sock and see them fresh cuts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't very impressive,  I've only just started self harming again. But I'm very nervous they are going to see.
And I'm thinking of more extreme ways of self harm other then cutting.
I wanna try bloodletting but I don't know what to use or the supplies.
I also wanna try chemical burns, like bleach or sugar soap, my Dad's into DIY so we got some liquids and my Mum is on a lot of prescription pills, and I got some string from an old hoodie. 
Oh,  and I weighed myself and I'm 53.4 kg (8 stone 5) and that is the lowest I've been in a while, I am really happy about that :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I swear this is the 3rd time in 24 hours I've cried and it makes me feel weak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why this is, but I'm hating it. I had a really good time away with my boyfriend, might of gotten a bit clingy when he had to leave to get home, but otherwise since then I haven't been that good.  
I cut myself again ,tried looking for pain killers but couldn't find them, and I've hit my arm with a hammer and the back of my head on the wall.  
I feel like I'm spriling hard today and I can't take it. I just really want to die and I feel terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you haven't found it yet, /r/depression  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little cuts on my foot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! I love Lifelover 3  
Shining is the best DSBM out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I really need it. I just tend to feel really bad or guilty and I will sometimes shake. I used to shake loads but I hardly do it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not tell anyone,  apart from Reddit and sometimes my boyfriend. 
I really don't tell anyone when anything is wrong, he can sometimes tell.  
I'd rather just not tell anyone and I tend to cut or not eat to manage my feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 10:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to date quite a bit a couple years back, but that of might been because of my other diagnosis.
I'm in a 6 month relationship now, and he knows a lot about my mental health.  He's alright with it, but he does feel sorry for me and he is trying to get me back to therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not, I did but then I got better so I got discharged but then my mental health has been going downhill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else feel really guilty or ashamed if you want sex or afterwards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have C-PTSD from various sexual abuse. 
Me and my boyfriend have gone down to Falmouth for a few days, and we have been doing a lot of fun stuff, including dirty stuff. As I'm too embarrassed to initiate this sort of stuff, he usally does it but when I feel like I want to do something like this or afterwards, I just feel really bad for wanting it or I just feel so guilty.
I don't know why, I just do. It doesn't happen all the time, mostly when I start or iniate stuff.  
I always shake a little bit afterwards too but I'm ok with that these days, it's just I hate feeling bad about asking for sexy stuff.  
Anyone have any ideas about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death by falling would be way quicker, be a whole lot of pain. Frowning would still be painful. There is a website called www.lostallhope.com that will have more info if you go to the suicide methods they will have more info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this in the realm of suicidal self-mutilation? 
I'd understand if he was saying about cutting the vein in his throat or something like that, but all he is doing is cutting off the tip of his finger 
I know he might lose a lot of blood, and as long as his finger doesn't get infected and he takes care of it, he will be fine, but it will still be painful as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 08:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get up the courage to do it. I really hate my survival instinct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny pathetic cuts from a sharpener on my little finger, and I broke my 10 month clean streak from cutting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's roughly weekly, but I did it yesterday and tonight. 
It used to be every day, a couple times a day, but it depends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidently left a wrapper for a sharpener by the toilet, and my Dad asked me about it. Luckily they belived me when I said I found it yesterday in my bedroom while sorting through some stuff in my room. But I hid the blade in my iPod case, and I threw out the sharpener which still had another blade in, and some pills. I regret it ._. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 21:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am haha and it's just helpful, I don't like drinking and I can't get any drugs. 
We each have our different coping methods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 11:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's stress, I tend to get more chest pains then headaches due to stress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 11:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what you think her reaction is going to be.  
If she is likely to be understanding and supportive, then tell her.  Judge on what you think her reaction is going to be by looking at her reactions to other stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 11:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't drink or do drugs, I self harm in other ways, my favorite method being cutting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might find this subreddit helpful: /r/sanctionedsuicide
Pretty much all of us think life is pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good to have people to discuss it with, who are non-judgemental and open-minded about this and won't tell me to get help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 09:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really annoying, or when you think you are going to do it and chicken out. Or get stopped. WTF.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 09:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was 10 months, now it's been a few days. Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
