<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Buying] Books and Oriental/Persian Carpets or rugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Books - first editions, good condition, modern authors

Carpets - Persian/Oriental, only hand made.

Let me know.... am interested in buying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need to buy some typewriter ribbons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old vintage style red/black... anyone know where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New SteemTV - aims to bring you the best in decentralised, uncensored media. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe, was joking.

Lots of magic going on in Barcelona though traditionally - some of it in that link! 

Run for your lives! (Just make sure you don't fetch a priest - that never ends well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you're right. I guess in the same way Steiner might have been. I was thinking I'd put her more into a religious grouping but you could be right... I don't think she was practicing in the sense some of the others were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S S is cozy??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experts believe mysterious aluminium object dating back 250,000 years 'could be part of ancient UFO' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes?? This is exactly the sort of woo-woo irrationalist nonsense that always has me exiled to the vile vortex of oblivion. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are holding an objectively indefensible opinion and my personal faith has nothing to do with it. An atheist can look at scripture and come to the same conclusion as me.

And yet they don't. And nor do Biblical scholars. And of course I can tell your faith position from what you reply. So maybe it *does* have quite a lot to do with it. 

It's your job to support your argument and show that my position is incorrect.

Yep. And it's your 'job' to look at where I've done that instead of obfuscating by repeatedly asking me to do it in the hope it might look like I have haven't. 

In fact, it's you who disagree with what I've said. But - being a literalist - you can't just say that. Some degree of **Wrongness** must be ascribed to me. By you. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how you developed your labeling system, but when you use it to distract from the fact that your position isn't defensible it's easy to see it for what it is. 

It is defensible though. It's just not defensible to *YOU* and people like you - atheists and other people who think they have 'the Truth' basically.

It depends on what the benchmark is. I might think Einstein's Second Theory is not defensible - I may even have lots of clever comebacks and support from a peer group who think exactly as I do who all agree with me. 

But unfortunately, Nuclear Physicists may differ. But look on the bright side - this is Reddit! You can shout that you win and that I can't defend my position all you like! You might even convince yourself!!

Sad thing is though that it doesn't matter - at the end of it all you're just a believer. And believers are very often believers because - say it with me - *their position isn't defensible*

How about acknowledging that you had a misunderstanding of the subject.

Yeah, sometimes have to do that. This isn't one of those times. I don't even have a misunderstanding of YOUR misunderstanding. I understand where you're coming from exactly.

If you still think I'm the one who is mistaken please show me why.

If you are capable of seeing why prove that to me first. If you can then we can do something. I've already provided links and evidence you've ignored.

Are you asking me to repeat my mistake?

Otherwise, I'm sure I'll see you around. 

Not if I see you first! Ciao Bella! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labels! The fangs come out.

Science does deal in labels it's true. It describes things and calls them other things: 'dog', 'cat' etc. It can even label ideologies and attitudes like 'literalist' and 'creationist'.

But here's the thing: if you don't like the label, it's no good foaming at the mouth about it... just don't behave like the demographic... then you won't get labelled. Quite simple. 

This is what I do. I often get labelled as a 'lunatic religionist' but then I simply show how this is not true: how I do accept facts, I am prepared to debate. How I do accept things like evolution etc. 

Of course there *IS* such a thing as a lunatic literalist religionist so I can't blame anyone for assuming I am one.... but then you know all about lunatic literalist religionism I think. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to try an prove it. Again.

Nah, I don't play the game that is so fashionable with fundie atheists and fundie Christians.

I think you guys should get a room but it's not my scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put atheists in there too and I'm in. We could do a kind of Reality-TV Roman Coliseum sort of thing.

Definitely has legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Eton to Edinburgh: Muslim life in harmony  in pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Witchcraft in rural Portugal in pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone made (or know of) a successful online Voice Coaching Singing Tuition site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a client who is a voice coach and wants me to advise/set one up. Is it a viable idea?

Would be essentially selling lessons that are pre-recorded with an 'elite' plan for 1-1 Skype.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on at Psg de Gracia train station? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems the cops have shut it down I heard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you respect yourself in the morning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but I don't k ow if I would watch and entire movie of a chick stuck to a bed...

Depends - so many factors..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 10:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these aren't strictly Occultists are they? Blavatsky and Fox sisters. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 10:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So you say, but so far none of the arguments that you have tried to make hold any water. 

With you.

Other's mileage may vary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 10:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong way of doing it imo. I am religious and agree with their position in that case - but they alienate a lot of people with this approach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's presenting himself before God, not inhabiting heaven. Coming off the street and approaching the manager of an apartment building doesn't mean you reside there, or that he would even let you.

He is in heaven. No responsible theologian has ever argued otherwise and they have even evolved arguments to explain it. They could even be correct. They don't deny it though as you do. 

Here is one such:

https://gotquestions.org/Satan-access.html

It's true that Satan doesn't get a whole lot of mention in the Old Testament, but when he does his actions are most certainly destructive and evil.

The link I gave previously gave example of where angels and King David were called 'Satan'. 

In fact, this naming is quite rare and quite late - confined mainly to the latter part of the Bible and certainly not always evil or even destructive as you say. Can provide a detailed breakdown. 

 An adversary can be in opposition to good or in opposition to evil. We see in the Old Testament that Satan attempts to thwart the good.

Actually no, he attempts to TEST and lead to the good. In Job he is an instrument of God. God is the driving force and this is explicitly stated: God *allows* him to do certain things temporarily as a test for Job. In the hope Job will come through. 

I don't see any incompatibility between the Old and New Testament's accounts of Satan.

Yeah I got that impression. But there is a lot of it and all serious theologians address the incompatibilities. You might not be a theologian - and that's fine - but you need, as a believer, to stand in relation to them as one would to a Nuclear Physicist say, you don't need to BE one or even understand it but you do need to accept that they are the ones doing the research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that God's interaction with Satan in the Book of Job isn't some sort of raging altercation doesn't mean that they aren't arch enemies.

It kind of does mean he isn't exiled from heaven though right?

Can you explain what you mean by the 'Christianising' of Satan?

Sure. Originally in the Judaic sources he was not a counterpart of God in the sense of being an evil polar opposite but rather was utilised by God (as in Job exactly) as a testing figure. The Jewish sources see Satan as an 'accuser' or 'Stumbling block' and in no way a personification of evil or even necessarily morally evil. 

This is interesting material here:

http://bethelbooks.com/wayoflife/24/

This chapter and the next one look at the references to the devil and satan in Scripture. We shall see that they are not the same thing, and that the words are used differently in the Old Testament from the way they are used in the New Testament.

And it gives interesting examples such as this:

The word satan is a Hebrew word which simply means opponent or adversary. When it occurs in the Old Testament, it is usually translated into the English word adversary.

Sometimes the adversary was an angel or a godly person. 

For example:    

an angel is described as a satan in Numbers 22:22    

David is described as a satan in 1 Samuel 29:4

None of these uses are compatible with the Christian 'Prince of Evil' locked in an ongoing Good vs Bad war with God. This is a Christian overlay onto earlier Judaic tradition. The Islamic traditions return to the Judaic sources and are more in line with the original conception.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he has a different name Iblis but is more of a direct connection to the Judaic version bypassing the Christianising bits in many ways.

You've got to think the 'Christianising' aspect is not Biblical - he is a very different character in the Bible than in the dogma.

For example in the book of Job (1:6) he is actually in heaven, chatting with God. 

 Now there was a day when the sons of God came to present themselves before the Lord, and Satan came also among them.

 And the Lord said unto Satan, Whence comest thou? Then Satan answered the Lord, and said, From going to and fro in the earth, and from walking up and down in it.

Note that reference to the 'Sons of God' too.

So what is Satan doing in heaven here? Why is God greeting him so nonchalantly and not at all like some arch-enemy or someone who is exiled. Actually they end-up making a bet of a highly dubious nature. 

Edit: got carried away - meant to say, yes, I agree with your participating in the Christian mythos point. It's exactly that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judaism and Islam - in both he is a very different figure and not evil per se. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely agree. They're some species of troll for sure.

And another thing: kids should just be allowed to get on with being kids - I don't agree with any religious or occult stuff being put on to them before they can decide what's a fit for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An after-school Satan Club could be coming to your kid's grade school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Spain has such major opportunities with cities like Madrid and Barcelona, like guys, come on, get that tech industry, get that Silicon Valley. Encourage research, I think it will increase productivity overall.

Hahahhaha no, sorry... I shouldn't but....hhahahahahahaha I just can't help it...

Sorry :(

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIGHT HALLUCINATIONS WITH IVAN SMAGGHE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is link about the machine:

http://www.theransomnote.com/musings/interviews/light-hallucinations-with-ivan-smagghe/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, is a true saying. 

Some mystics and magicians are believed to know this name... apparently it can make you do 'weird stuff' lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well 'most beautiful' is subjective I guess. But there are some great poets in Classical Persian.. Rumi, Khayyam and Hafiz are kind of obvious but check out Saadi and Attar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, will check it out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already know that. 

Some people say they are mythological imaginal constructs and residues of early human entheogenic pseudo-archetypes and as such have no contingent existence (or if you're an atheist 'woo woo bollox' I think is the phraseology) but even if this is true, I still find the spirits far more intelligible, rational and generally more real than their human counterparts.

And the girl ones are mega-hot too! Fucking mind-blowing when they get all hot and bothered lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We kind of all know who's at the bottom of this really though don't we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I'm with you... but then again there's not much that doesn't get me seriously consider giving up my British citizenship.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese Man Claims He Can Predict a Womans Future by Fondling Her Breasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese Man Claims He Can Predict a Womans Future by Fondling Her Breasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 12:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese Man Claims He Can Predict a Womans Future by Fondling Her Breasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 12:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of Persian / Farsi lessons or teachers in BCN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 11:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is says ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand by statement. It was not wilfully offensive but if it was I would stand by it also.

I see no need to apologise for an opinion I sincerely hold and which I expressed with no intention of offence. 

I can only suggest - yet again - that we chill and have a laugh as no-one has offended you and all that's really happened is you disagree with my opinion and my mode of expression. That's unfortunate - but you need to realise being offended isn't an absolute. We can get past it.... or not. My preference would be to move on, life's too short but ymmv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it matter though?

This is an Occult forum. I am not naive enough to think that implies some sort of kinship or brotherhood but it SHOULD mean something else: that we hold ourselves different to the standards of 'the normal world'. And I do. 

I don't know about you but if one is going to assume that following some Occult path is just a variation of the local 5-a-Side football on a Sunday morning then what's the point? I said what I said. Fine. You got offended. Also fine. But you know what? You don't get to put your offence on to me - because *this is an Occult forum*. If we're in some other sub maybe... but them maybe I wouldn't say it there.

I say it here because I SHOULD be able to say what I like - and so should you btw - with at least **SOME** sense that people reading have transcended the ordinary pleb in the street. That they have developed **SOME** sort of detachment and **SOME** sort of thick skin and yes, **SOME** ability to pull things back, master oneself and be in control. And some sort of insight too into why people say what they say. 

Now I am going to assume - this being a sub about what it is - that people here can do that. I am going to think you can... I'm not going to treat you like some boring soul-less cog in the machine because *YOU'RE HERE* so I owe you that. Which is why I don't owe you an apology.

I am being myself. If you want to redress the balance insult me in your worse terms and we'll be equal.

Be yourself. And don't take offence. And don't expect me to expect 'taking offence' as a value - I don't. If I did I'd join the Church or some other 'moral' institution. 

We're free. It's all good. If you need to 'get even' somehow I'll sit back for your worst insults and then we can have a laugh but I'm not worked up now and won't be then... just saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can do conflict in a face to face - life sometimes goes that way.

But it's not happening now and you're the one not chilled and I am. Fine but if you want to kick back then we're good. Maybe even have a laugh.

Anything else just jog on and deal with it. You've got the problem not me. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Chill your pants man. It's all just opinions... of no matter.

Thoughts flow through us.... no need to identify with them or project your own on to others. 

Relax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Scientific method was invented by Muslims though so in lands previously in the Islamic Empire there was that basis - which is another factor. You can clearly outline a backwards movement here as you can in Islamic nations generally. 

I don't think that's coincidence. 

Especially these days - look at Iraq, it's been chaos for 15 years. Leaving aside the rights and wrongs of the US invasion, if it had been rebuilt - perhaps on the Dubai model - with (say) Arab money and turned into a Leading ME city it would have taken maybe 5 years and  I can guarantee you that if any Islamist tried to mess that up the people themselves would deal with that - because they have their aspirations and something to lose. 

Now they don't. Which is because someone wants it that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you're right. I'm thinking more of the hardcore materialists but yes, should have qualified it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might try it. Things chaotic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People who think that science and magic are mutually exclusive are ignorant.

I'd rather say this:

*People who think that science and magic are not mutually exclusive are not magicians. *

Nothing in magic can be reproduced under lab conditions. In science things need to be reproduced. 

A Reductionist Materialist could never be a magician for example and Science is often (not always) the first tool of Colonial oppressors. And, yes, those two things have a hell of a lot to do with each other. 

Which is why it is the colonised countries that are not provided with education.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate them. They ate my Buick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have no idea what you mean by this.

In that case it doesn't matter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... thank God we're not ignorant and better than the uncivilised savages right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a web developer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have another business which is also home-based that is my main one or else cash-flow might be a problem.

The issue is not so much the business but the publication of books which happen at certain times in the year so it is a bit feast and famine. But over the year it is generally a profit - just not regular. That's the main issue.

Another one is that certain big authors (Murakami for example) are on 2-year cycles so you could sell 3 or 4 books of his (say) for around 2000 each but it only happens every two years or so and there are very, very few authors in that bracket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes but mostly it works out ok. I am in Europe and deal mostly with US customers because collectors there are more interested in UK first editions (which I mostly deal with) than US ones because they're rarer. Print runs are typically far far less. 

So shipping to US includes insurance mostly because US customs have some some hardcore rules about shipping. Shipping to Europe sometimes I have to take a hit on shipping to be competitive but you can sometimes build this in, depends on how hot the book is. 

EDIT: should say that in this business trust is everything so if someone knows you pack well, don't rip them off and can find good stuff in perfect conditions then you have a loyal customer and a relationship... if you can get some of these who are hardcore collectors then they will actually ask to pay more for insurance many times. I would myself when buying a book off a dealer as I sometimes do.

I have a customer who purchases a certain author who's new limited editions are always 1500+ when released minimum. They are always happy to pay 100+ shipping and insurance - which is about the rate from Europe to US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get all that. 

My point is that his observations *WOULD* apply in an internet-age or any other information age given that the receiving audience (ie members of society) were the same and a constant. 

I don't think they are. I think they have been 'adjusted'.

Btw, you might (or might not) enjoy this new Adam Curtis documentary if you can get BBC:

http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p04b183c?ns_mchannel=YT ns_source=bbc_iplayer ns_linkname=description_link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.... ok! I'm kind of chilled but mission accomplished! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I'll leave you be.

I'd appreciate it. The odd thing is - seeing as we're on the subject of paranormal issues - that my crystal ball tells me that your response would have been the same (or worse) had I gone into greater depth.

In fact the knowledge that a self-appointed Goon Squad exists and whose main mission is to self-aggrandise themselves by swaggering their bollocks against the subject matter exemplified in my post - and you're exactly the type I was thinking of - is the very reason I was reticent to do so. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get the right ones. Now I just order direct from the publisher if they are doing signed editions but I used to trawl around second-hand and charity shops. You can find some gems there but is getting harder and condition is not always ok. You need to know a lot. 

Also Ebay used to be good for sleepers - there are some books that look really cheap but are not. But that's not so good now either, most people know these things.

What I tend to do now is to look at really small publishers, get sent proofs and read a lot in my genre. If you find a small publisher with a small print-run of a book that you think will go massive then buy copies - especially if you it's the author's first book... if he becomes a Rockstar in the next years then you're on a goldmine. 

Exception to this is big authors with fanatical fans: Murakami would be the main one I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just from home. I thought about a physical shop sometimes but it would not be cost-effective for me.

I just order books that I know I'll be able to sell for at least 75% and which I know for sure will sell but there's no way of predicting actually when. 

Shipping is the major expense because you can't expose yourself to sending non-insured/custom-packed and signed-for on a book costing $100 or more and not everyone wants to pay higher amounts of shipping on books below 50.00 I find. Above that they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. Given the OP's question was this:

Can anyone come up with a sequence of events that led to Robert Wone's death? **Rational or otherwise**?

Your reply is unquestionably motived by either illiteracy, irrationality or personal bias. Probably all three. Unquestionably. 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YIKES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you study MM in depth and you also study the current media landscape do you not see any dissonance? 

Or, put another way, if you think MM was writing today do you think his analysis and theories would be exactly the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf? What's that monkey doing with his right paw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. It's been superseded. It's en ex-maxim, gone to join the choir invisible. No longer extant.

These days I'd go with Robert Anton Wilson's *"Reality is What you can get away with"* - with the caveat that now that means absolutely everything as we've all signed over every last scintilla of our critical faculties to our anyone who feels like fucking us up the ass. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Occult Ritual that went wrong and was covered up by making it look like a sex-related incident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah - that needs updating I think for the Post-McLuhan era. Maybe something like *the message is the medium* ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HyperNormalisation: A new film by Adam Curtis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well porn is about money and not sex. Can't serve two masters as some guy once said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've got a point. Maybe you didn't like the way they expressed it but that can't nullify the point surely?

Or does it? Seems strangely ironic if so - if one possesses a mind capable of making those kind of tangential leaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I am. I sell books from home on ABE and Biblio. Sometimes used but always rare, collectible - always first editions and mostly signed. I have a niche of Hypermoderns and Limited Editions. I tried normal used books (ie not collectible) via Amazon but could not make it work. Might be different for you though. 

My advice if you're going into bookdealing at home would be to find a niche that you can get passionate and know about - learn all you can about this all the time. I'd definitely recommend looking at modern firsts though. The margins can be very high if you know what you're doing. Get a hot author signed first in mint unread condition and you're looking at 75% plus mark up straight off the bat. 

Typical Booker winner (mugs game to predict this though) if a short print run and little-known author can be bought at 20 Euros (say) and goes for maybe 100 or more. Wolf Hall I think now is 300. I bought a few of them but sold them when they were at 100. 

I know of recent books that have hit 2000 Euros or more. You really need to know what you're doing though. Happy to answer any questions. Here's an interesting link by way of illustration:

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2372555/JK-Rowling-250-signed-copies-The-Cuckoos-Calling-crime-novel-unmasked-author-refuses-profit.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any rational Conspiracy/Paranormal Pods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 11:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a contradiction in terms but I guess I mean meeting the following characteristics:

* NO Right-Wing, White-Power BS (50% ruled out right there)
* NO BIGFOOT, Ghosthunters or mentioning the word 'EVP' (can't stress this enough)
* Rational take but no materialist debunking
* SOME actual research
* No ALIENS

Is it possible? If not who wants to join me in starting one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conspiracy theorist Max Spiers found dead in Poland days after texting his mother 'If anything happens to me, investigate' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 10:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 10:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, kelseyaida, thanks for this... I'll head over now and check it out! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True Crime Garage - best True Crime out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Nick, it's very helpful, thanks. I'm going to digest it and think about some of the key points as they impact my situation.

Just briefly touching on some:

-Results: yes, I have for myself. Am not sure yet how to extrapolate that to a client. Not sure how this could be proved other than relating the experience - my present work/financial state is not a result of manifesting.

I'll have a look at your site and maybe I might ask some more things. Thanks a lot for taking the time to give this considered reply.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to make the transition to that too. Thing is though I have the feeling I'll have to jettison my client base to do it and rebrand... is a big step.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @ /u/RomaNorgy and /u/guster-von - I'm a traditional personal coach but am looking to transition maybe to an LOA coach specifically.

Just wondered: a) if there is such a thing b) if it could work as a practice and c) any tips you might have about shifting to this.

All help appreciated thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 14:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been reading a brilliant and very helpful PDF by /u/MoreToCome/ (not sure what it's called) where he says this:

Once you no longer truly care if your desire is met or not, you open the door to manifest whatever you wish. 

And then gives the following example:

After I received... I became attached to the money all over again out of a fear of having it run out. I tried to control it by keeping a tight grasp on it......

The interesting thing is - I had to learn to DETACH before I could receive the money AND I also had to DETACH again after I received the money (in order to be truly FREE of it). Ive realized that overcoming ones attachments is a process that continues throughout ones life. Ive also realized that it applies to everything in life (not just money).

This seems to me the key to it all and where many (or me anyway) go wrong. 

My question is this: How DO you detach? What is the process?

Anyone have any tips, hints or methods?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any LOA coaches here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 14:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or anyone know of one? Be much appreciated, would like to ask some questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 09:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry friend, but the things you are writing here explicitly contradict what your religion says. The Qur'an says that religion in Allah's eyes is only Islam and that whoever follows another religion it will not be accepted from him and they will be the losers on judgement day.

It never ceases to amaze me - I literally find it mind-blowing that we have come to a position in society where someone could even make such a statement without any self-reflection or embarrassment. **THIS** is exactly why I say what I do about atheists (and fundies) and why I will not retract it.

1) An atheist has no problem, not just telling a believer they're wrong (no problem with that) but telling them that *they do not know the facts about their own religion!* and the atheists do!

It would be as if I said that atheism demands one goes to church on Sunday and then - when corrected - feel no shame, embarrassment or need to even take it on board - I just keep repeating it and tell the atheists continually what atheism is!

2) And after all that.... they STILL get it wrong!

Those who believe in the Qur'an, and those who follow the Jewish scriptures, and the Christians and the Sabians,- any who believe in Allah and the Last Day, and work righteousness, shall have their reward with their Lord; on them shall be no fear, nor shall they grieve. 

Qur'an 2: 62

As a side note good for you finding a religion to convert to, however the religion you converted to does not afford the same privilege to people converting away from it, that's why ex-muslims are closeted and afraid to speak about their lack of belief.

Nope. They are afraid to speak about their lack of belief because totalitarian fundie extremists might kill them. 

This is what happens with totalitarian fundie extremists who are 100% convinced they are right and who have 'The Truth' which is why I oppose the same tendency in atheists where a similar 'we have the truth' BS prevails.

As to apostasy in the ideology and practice of the Prophet and Qur'an. Here is Sura 4:137. 

Verily, those who believed and then disbelieved, then believed and then disbelieved and increased in disbelief, never will Allah forgive them nor will He guide them to a right way.

Question: how is it possible to believe then disbelieve and then believe and disbelieve again? If your argument is correct then that wouldn't be possible. They'd disbelieve once and be dead. 

This one seems pretty self-explanatory  2:256:

There is no compulsion in religion. The truth is distinct from misguidance.

And again, to the varying races and peoples - 5:49:

To each of you God has prescribed a Law and a Way. If God would have willed, He would have made you a single people. But Gods purpose is to test you in what He has given each of you, so strive in the pursuit of virtue, and know that you will all return to God 

No record anywhere of Muhammad ordering the death of an apostate or saying it should be so and it's certainly not anywhere in the Qur'an

















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But surely if you're a Muslim you believe "There is no god but God. Muhammad is the messenger of God."? How can there be other "equal" paths for those with other gods and other prophets?

Muhammad is one of over 100,000 Prophets according to Islam. All the other religions come also from God. This just says he is 'A' Prophet. 

Allah is just the Arabic word for God - it is used in all other religions in Arabic and if you wanted to say you disbelieved in God in Arabic then Allah is the word you'd use. It's not a name.

Qur'an itself says Jews, Christians and others will 'go to paradise'.

Honestly don't see the problem here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I know you're wrong. Let's digest.

No, let's not. We're on different paths. It would be a waste of time to try to reach common ground... I'd like to but we both know it's not going to happen don't we?

We're not speaking the same language. We'll only confuse each other. 

As Muhammad said "Go in peace, you to your way, me to mine..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many other religions have you studied? How many Holy Books have you read?

Christianity, Gnosticism, Judaism, Qabala, Zen Buddhism, Zoroastrianism, Thelema, various occult groupings.

Why did you decide Islam is the best? 

Read again. I said I did not and do not evaluate on 'best' as I believe all equal paths to God. Just depends which is the one for you. 

Did you only read the Quran or did you also study the Hadith and Sira?

All

When you found out that Islam mandates chopping hands off thieves, stoning adulterers and executing/punishing apostates, what did you think?

I thought "Holy fuck, some fundie morons will have a field day with this?!!" and laughed. I didn't realise they'd be atheists then. That came later.

What did you think about how women are treated i.e. receiving half the inheritance a man does, not being allowed to marry non-Muslims like men are, and not being allowed to marry more than one spouse like men are? 

You seem to think I'm an atheist... are you sure you realise I'm a believer?

It's like a Xian asking you "how did you feel when you realised you needed to accept Jesus as your personal saviour?"

How would you answer?

Do you think it's equality to not even give women the choice and give the burden of providing on men, while claiming that because the men are breadwinners, the womens lack of freedom is justified?

Can you sit on a chair when the chair hasn't any?

Bonus points if you know the reference without Googling!

Btw, at this point I should say don't worry, go with this... it's just fun. You already won - happy to let you win. It means so much more to you than me so you should have it! 

View the rest of this as a victory lap!

What about apostasy? The Sunni madhabs say execution is the only way and lots of material has been written on this with support from lots of big scholars. Do you reject them all and feel you understand Islam better?

I kind of see the maniacs in the religion as the same as atheists to be honest - both are kind of fucked up and both have this overwhelming need to be right - and to prove others wrong. Both are kind of stupid and irrational and both suffer from a kind of cancer that makes them stupid. 

So in Islam - yeah we have these fuckers. Hard enough to deal with them without dealing with the atheist version too.. but yeah, to me the same kind of scumbags in general. 

They both need to be opposed. It's a cancer.

How about the history of Muhammad himself? He is an eternal role model so when he does unsavory things do you think the excuse "oh well it was a different time!" is acceptable at all? Unsavory things like marrying Aisha when she was 6, ordering beheadings, engaging in banditry and raiding caravans as revenge...how about insulting polytheists and calling for their extermination while only tolerating Jews and Christians as second class dhimmi?

Well of course he didn't marry Aisha at 6. Atheists love to say this but that's why I say they are stupid and worse, liars... this is a classic example actually - let's break it down:

1) it's not true and can be proved not true from hadith

2) atheists should know this but they don't care - Strike 1

3) when you prove it to them they ignore it -  Strike 2

4) Then they lie and carry on saying it  - Strike 3.

So really, who can take them - you - seriously? You're not a researcher are you? If you don't know this then that's just lame. If you DO then you're a liar.

Does it really matter which? 

To me no... others may vary.







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I note the rest of your post is a personal history, and not a description of the methodology you used in evaluating Islam.

I think you're wrong. Read again... no matter how much it must pain you. Try to evaluate the words and think how someone - not you - might experience such a thing and describe it. 

If you can do this... ie put your bias aside, I think you'll see you're wrong about this and in fact I described the situation perfectly. 

Just not how you wanted or how you would have done it. 

I'm **exactly** like the OP - why don't you ask him and compare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, let's talk about that: how exactly did you come to the conclusion that Islam is the best religion?

I don't think it is necessarily the best. What does 'best' mean? It is part of my path at this point in my life - there's been others.

All religions are paths to God. Or paths away from God.. depends on the attitude of the person.  So is atheism by the same token. 

I don't really go by what's 'best' as they're all true. Better to ask if the believer themselves is 'true' - far more informative. If they are then it's ok... if not then there'll be trouble.

I think you mean how did I find it? Brought up Evangelical Xian, didn't see any coherent logic in that but still had experiences of "something else" which I didn't feel any need to fit into any bracket... later when I read about Islam I realised it was more or less what I already believed so was not really any transition at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly the smug arrogance of Muslims to have found the ultimate truth 

I know... bastards!! We all know it's **ATHEISTS** who've found the ultimate truth! WTF?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also wouldn't be a Muslim if you weren't raised a Muslim.

I would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 00:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same as the OP - more or less - and am a convert. Not born or raised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 00:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you write speeches for Trump?

Actually yes! How did you know? We can count on your vote right? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **You:** One of the more eloquent ad hominems I've ever come across. 

**Me:** It's a low-effort off-the-cuff throwaway tbh, but then it hardly needs to be more.

**You:** That level of bravado for something as lame as this...just sad

That's your level of debate? You can't decide whether it's eloquent or lame?

And you have the effrontery to even venture an opinion about matters re God, life, death when you don't even know what - or how - to think?

You don't even know your own mind - or you change at the whim of some lamer on the internet - and you think people can debate with you about **GOD**?

How's that? Better? ;) I can do worse too lol


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Something is there...well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 21:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you in a forest laughing with no-one to hear you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's meant to be a joke btw... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 














. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Not so sure about that. There's lots of ways of clearing the mind... the state of emptiness is the thing. Can get there many ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please enlighten me.

I don't think that's possible. The journey to enlightenment can only begin (and end) with the individual. You'll have to find your own way there... or not.

Also please respond to my post. Would you try to convince your dying friend his delusions were exactly that - delusions. Would you cause your friend incredible pain for no gain?

I would never - not there and not here either - set myself up to be the arbiter of what is delusion. If I want that I know of many Fundie mosques I can go to and listen to how they alone 'have the truth' - and if that makes me lose my faith I could become a certain type of atheist and believe the same thing. 

So, no, I don't know what delusion is, I am not the judge of it and more, I actually think your non-belief is fine for you. You're 100% right in all your views - for you.

And I am 100% right in living my life in a way that precludes me ever telling you you're wrong, delusional or in error (might say irrational though lol). 

So no. Would say to my dying friend 'you're 100% right'. I'd say the same to you btw actually if I happened to be at your deathbed - and it would be true in both cases. In my opinion.

Yours will differ and that's fine too.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additionally why do you choose to come to a forum and discuss your debate? 

Because the cool atheists I meet here remind me they are not all assholes and that humans are basically good and we CAN make a connection even if it is only 1 person in 100. 

Because there are so many fundie idiots in religion and atheism these days (it is, as you say about religion, a Cancer) that I need reminding constantly that not all are like that. I don't need it from the religious side as I am religious and all my friends are cool but I DO need reminding from the atheist side from time to time.

Because those 1 in 100 that I meet are worth so much more than the other 99 and many become ongoing friends I can discuss and have great exchanges with elsewhere. 

Why do you come here.... oh wait, no need to answer that one. I think I know. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why intentionally ignore this?

But why change? Atheist half-baked arguments and general irrationality cause me excessive intentional pain all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The answer to a fool is silence" - Sufi saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deep topic, you make some good points. They tried to sell this MS you refer to a few years ago. Caused a big scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 14:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we should perhaps not veer off the issue for fear of getting lost in the woods. You'd be safe - I am virulently anti-racist - but I'm more worried about me.

I don't think actually that one can retro-fit today's standards, even if they are advances (perhaps especially then) on to the past always. Some people are always doing their best, even if they fall short, and some people are always scum. We can't really always conflate the two. 

Besides, Burton is a classic target as an "Orientalist" but I don't in any way buy into critiques of Orientalism. Well, some ways, but it goes way too far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 14:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, if you don't think everything is material - and therefore  contained in a Rationalist Materialist paradigm - then you're not a Rationalist Materialist!

You're just like me! Be afraid, be very afraid... mwahahah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the Victorian Burton had some Victorian views. Might be a deal-breaker for some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worse than that.

God tells them they will die if they eat the fruit. The serpent (nowhere identified with Satan) tells them this is not true and they will not. 

It turns out that it was the serpent telling the truth and God who was lying. Not sure anyone can see a way round this. 

Other problems for literalists:

* Tree is 'knowledge of good and evil' - why is this a bad thing? It isn't saying evil doesn't exist at this point... just that KNOWING that is bad. See next point too.

* If they were naked before eating the fruit and that was no problem why would it be a problem after? Surely the problem after that they only THOUGHT nakedness was wrong and this, in itself, must be a wrong thought as they were naked before and it was ok. 

* Snake is cursed to crawl on his belly thereafter. What did he do before? He was a snake... it's what they do. 

* Who were the other people in the other lands mentioned when Cain was exiled? At this point there is only Adam, Eve and Cain in existence? 

* An oldie but goodie: Where did Cain and Abel get their wives?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's another one while we're being poetic... famous Muslim thinker [Ibn Arabi](http://www.ibnarabisociety.org/articles/treasureofcompassion.html)

O Marvel! a garden amidst the flames.  

My heart has become capable of every form:  

it is a pasture for gazelles and a convent for Christian monks,   

and a temple for idols and the pilgrim's Kaa'ba,   

and the tables of the Torah and the book of the Quran.   

I follow the religion of Love: whatever way Love's camels take,   

that is my religion and my faith.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, never been that many people of our world-view it seems. In some ways people need certainty. I can see why - not so easy to live in a kind of grey/liminal area.. but that's where the magic is. 

Richard Burton was Welsh I think (the actor) but it's not him. This one is the famous Arabist and linguist. 

English explorer, geographer, translator, writer, soldier, orientalist, cartographer, ethnologist, spy, linguist, poet, fencer, and diplomat. He was famed for his travels and explorations in Asia, Africa and the Americas, as well as his extraordinary knowledge of languages and cultures. According to one count, he spoke 29 European, Asian and African languages.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Francis_Burton

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manifesting and Tech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Building on the idea that you need to form the desire, focus on it and 'let it go' into the universe, I've been experimenting with various forms of tech to help with this. 

So far results have been spotty but I am still tweaking the system. So far I've tried Lucid Dream devices and Binaural Beats (both don't work as far as I can tell), Float Tanks (some limited success) and Hypnagogic Light Machines, one in particular.

My method is this: 

* Decide on desire for testing purposes - something trivial "Will see Yellow Butterfly" or whatever
* Meditate briefly on desire to 'fix' in place
* Have a session on the device keeping the desire in mind and at culmination of the experience 'let it go' consciously and say goodbye to it.

Early days yet but some encouraging results. I'm trying to get something replicable and statistically significant - at least to me.

Anyone else tried anything like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Appreciate it.
 
It's a low-effort off-the-cuff throwaway tbh, but then it hardly needs to be more. 

You should see me when I slip into even First Gear though. Sadly, it's hardly ever necessary here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious people are saying 'No'.  Couldn't make this stuff up. 

They spend their lives wittering on about 'Truth' and how we need to actually be loyal to it while berating anyone who believes interminably while they have **NO PROOF**

When the postulate is that they **HAVE PROOF** they decide to shut up!

Bizarro Genius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "people we typically want to convert"

Hmmm, question was to atheists. Have to assume this is an atheist answering..

*Note to self: file under: WTF3567a Casebook 22*

* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes unfortunately you are right...Or maybe it has to be accepted...No way to persuade them. After all, if people fight about non-issues it is probably blocking them form causing more harm around real problems.

The thing we need to realise - and I think most sane rational people do - is that the closed-minded atheists and the closed-minded religionists are the same thing. They both are convinced they are right and can't assess any other factors than those that support their world-view.

The 'Truth' in a spiritual sense (and religion is by no means always the same thing) is something quite other than belief or doubt or proof.

I can only quote Khayyam:

Some look for truth in creeds, and forms, and rules;   

Some grope for doubts or dogmas in the schools;    

But from behind the veil a voice proclaims,    

"Your road lies neither here nor there, O fools. "

Or perhaps Richard Burton:

All Faith is false, all Faith is true:   

Truth is the shattered mirror strown   

In myriad bits; while each believes   

His little bit the whole to own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 09:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly. so there is no need for us to prove Abraham was a real person.

For us, no lol! 

Hardcore religionists and atheists have a lot invested in the prove he was / prove he wasn't pitched battle though... so I guess there'll still be tickets for the fight on sale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't speak to the others but can comment on the Sufism aspect.

It's true to a certain extent. In some Orders there are stages one achieves via exercises, interaction with the Sheikh etc which are connecting with one's "Inner Jesus", "Inner Moses", "Inner Muhammad" etc. 

They are not sequential or hierarchical but states of being one 'stands in' when you reach that point. The figure of the person in the 'real world' is an archetype of a certain attitude.

Moses leads out of long-term exile, Jesus is compassion and forgiveness, Muhammad resists and fights against overwhelming odds etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all comes down to that doesn't it? Whether everything is contained in a Rationalist Materialist paradigm. 

I don't think it is. This study seems to me to be founded on that assumption so - for me - it's flawed from the start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for first generation converts only. If you are born into a Muslim family then I have no problems believing that you can have genuine religious experiences.

I was not born into a Muslim family. Far from it. I had never heard of Islam or knew anything about it when I had certain religious experiences that did not fit into any framework I knew of. Later when I encountered Islam I saw they fitted into that framework.

But at the same time - religious people refuse to believe that people fall out of religion.

I don't deny that. Happens all the time. I know people it's happened to.

Religious people think that apostates and deserters must have an ulterior motive.

Again, no. I have observed several cases of this and can explain it to my own satisfaction. 

I'll give you an example in reverse to illustrate my point. When I first left school and went to college I was in an 'atheist' period. I wanted to be one, was heavily into nihilism, existentialism and stuff but still could not rid of myself of what you might call 'religious experiences' and perception of the existence of God. I reframed this in a drug-subculture context and basically took huge amounts of drugs for a couple of years. My partner in crime was the college Rock Star who was kind of a mentor to me - introduced me to the coolest books, music, people etc. We went to some amazing gigs and hung out. Went to India and Middle East looking for gurus etc. 

Later, after college I heard he'd not only become a born-again Christian (this is not a surprising trajectory btw) but he was a Pastor with a huge Church. Here's the kicker... I am religious myself, I sought him out (not with my Muslim hat on) and guess what? He is not only not in the least remotely like the person I knew - not even half the person, he's a boring conservative with no fire - he is not remotely interested in concepts of God, religion, philosophy etc.

This a person who when he was an atheist I would stay up with all night discussing whether God existed. Now he is not even interested in telling me he thinks God does. 

My point is this: when he was an atheist before he had life, passion and fire. If he were to become one tomorrrow *he would be no different than he is today* except he would have no faith. 

De-conversion is just (imo) the final admission you have nothing. But that does not mean there IS nothing.

I know many practicing religious people right now this moment who are 'atheists'. They certainly have no religious impulse or experience - though probably it is not for me to judge it. 

How can they desert God when they have already experienced him? 

As above.... they never did. Some do, some don't.... it's actually quite rare. I'd even agree with you if you said 90%+ of religious people don't and you then levelled the usual criticisms atheists have AT that 90%+. 

I just can't agree with the 100% figure and that seems non-negotiable in these discussions... that's the nub of it. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God and stuff may be 'going on' anywhere they want.

So a belief in God may come from 'elsewhere' and therefore not be within the parameters of the research. It could, in fact, not apply in the case of God and beliefs relating to God and therefore religion.

It is therefore an irrelevant survey. Thanks for clearing that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree there. Of course, "God" and stuff might not be 'going on in the brain'.

Of course you might think it could only be... but it ain't necessarily so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuts both ways doesn't it? If that's the case (and maybe it is) then neither you nor me - I'll say that again neither **YOU** nor me - have any right to any opinions on it at all.

I'd settle for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Here's the thing dude: people can be very different, people can have had very different life histories, and (what you could guess from that) people could be in very different situations.

Preaching to the choir dude. Maybe this better directed at your fellow-travellers

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really agree with this research - not just because many highly analytical people believe in God but because this:

They do the opposite when thinking about the physical world, according to the study.

I actually don't. I can't know what anyone else does but for me, there is no compartmentalisation like that. The thought processes of thinking about anything are the same more or less. That's not strictly true as the feeling of belief in God is not (for me) subject to all of the same assessments, it just 'is' but in the way other things 'just are' - sense of self for example.

I een tried to be an atheist once, I was quite into it and heavily invested enough to read everything Nietzsche ever wrote (still love him) but nothing has ever shifted that perception of 'God'. 

Which could be something else of course - but it's not in the normal run of things so why not?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kind of is a Hack Job though. 

There are literal contradictions in it within the same chapters even. It is impossible to believe one is literal without denying the other.

And that's before we even get to modern discoveries which prove certain statements incorrect. 

It would be impossible for an attentive scribe to not notice this so that would be a definition of a hack to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually agree with this. Most of it. 

The fact that there *could* be massacres is indicative of the pluralistic society. Not that they are a good thing but in the sense that if there is prejudice now in the US against Muslims (say) that is because it is human nature as you point out, and the fact that the US is a multicultural society. 

These things, unfortunately happen in multicultural societies and will probably go on happening. They don't happen in monocultural societies because there is a monoculture. 

I don't deny these happenings - I just dispute they are evidence of an Islamic attempt at monoculture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The early caliphate spread through war, though. There is no denying that - you can't say they took a Mormon approach and sent pairs of young people around with name tags nocking on tent doors, right?

Yeah lol. I guess not.

My point is that the *State* or Empire spread and Islam was just the State religion. The two are not synonymous... and aren't even now. A Saudi State looks very different to a Turkish, Syrian or Iranian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly, history disagrees with you.

No you disagree with me. 

Just gave you some reasons against it. But you're not going to address them are you?

This is exactly what happened to Jews in the early part of the spread of Islam. Many converted because they would otherwise be second-class citizens or even exiled from their homes!

Reference?

Why would they need to do this if the Charter of Medina prohibited this? 

I'm talking about how religion spreads through force.

Yes, and you're trying to put all religions under one huge umbrella ignoring any specifics that would impact the situation in practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. But my point is that this does not work within an Islamic context.

Do you think this template above was also used by Islam?

If so then you need to address how they circumnavigated these issues:

1) The injunction against converting Jews, Christians and others

2) The non-necessity of doing so in a theological sense as these groups are held to be believers. In other words they're going to heaven - what else is there to do?

If they DID get round those two factors we need to address these two issues:

3) How exactly did they do it?

4) Did it fail? It must have done as their are very large non-Muslim communities in all countries in the Islamic Empire. 

5) How can we explain #4 (ie 1400 years of non-Muslim communities) in the light of your template above. It does not seem to fit.. clearly NO further generations converted. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, fair enough. I don't recognise 'what Arabs did to pagans' any more than I recognise 'what US did to Shintoists' in Japan in WW2 (actually most of the victims of the US there were Christians oddly but you get my point I hope).

It wasn't a question of trying to convert pagans. It was a question of Muhammad calling on them to convert if they wanted to. Qur'an is pretty clear "No compulsion in religion", no forced conversion and if people want to reject the Message they can do what they like and God will judge.

Not as a result of this call - but for other political and financial reasons - pagans and Muslims ended up at war. 

So 'what Arabs did to pagans' does not really matter in the context of this argument as it had nothing to do with the spread of Islam - particularly as it happened before any Empire-building and in the home city of the tribes involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So whatever you want it to be at any point without stating it or involving in any degree because you're not remotely interested in discussion only being right.

Ok got it.

I was afraid of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that there are still minority communities in the Islamic world doesn't mean the Islamic world didn't spread by force. Did they not conquer the territory in the first place, and establish Islamic dominance?

Well that's different. If your argument is that the *Religion* was spread by force then my previous counter-arguments apply.

If you are instead arguing, as you seem to be above, that the *Civilisation* (you won't like that word but work with me for a bit) spread that way then I would ask you this:

1) How is that different to every other Civilisation or Empire that ever existed? It's kind of how they spread.

2) Do you have an example of an Empire or Civilisation that DID NOT spread this way?

3) Are you against all such Empires and would you criticise them all in the same way? If not then why single out Islam? (If you say 'religion' here we're back to Square 1 and my counter-points, yes, this is a Flow-Chart)

I'm not arguing Muslims went door to door forcing conversions.

Seems very clear then you're arguing against the normal mode that Empires are formed by then yes? You're basically opposing Empires and the way they develop?

So why Islam specifically? Why not list Roman, Greek, Persian, Austro-Hungarian, Russian, British....

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you are getting it. 

If they converted people - by force, peace, cupcakes or free porn - then how is it possible that there are massive **UNCONVERTED** communities throughout the Islamic world?

Let's try some metaphor.. that could work.

**YOU** You eat all the cookies.... look, that's what you do, there's none left... you eat them

**ME** what are these jars of cookies right here? How could I have eaten them????

**YOU** would 'destroyed' work better? 'Eliminated the cookies' - is that better? How about DISAPPEARED the cookies? Stop arguing semantics!!

**ME** Yikes..... *runs for door.......* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a tip: just repeating 'by the sword' on continuous loop as a means of non-thinking or addressing the points raised isn't really making you look that good and it certainly isn't making it true just because it's repeated *ad infinitum* like a talking parrot on methamphetamine.

Constant repetitive slogans and brainwashing may have conditioned *you*, but just because you're a victim of the process does not mean you know how to effectively apply it on others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you really so unsure of your ideas that you can't argue anything without straw manning your opponent's position?

No, I am so completely sure of **YOUR** position and how you will respond - there are only a limited number of responses in the playbook after all - that it does not matter what I say. 

There is a strange freedom in it. If one does not fall into the trap that anyone will listen or that we're actually exchanging views. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you mean 'Research pre-Islamic Arabia' as you probably know that I already know about it, being Muslim and all.

What I think you mean is *'view these issues through my own atheist filter'* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you prefer to die rather than to (fake to) change your religion?

We're not talking about what I think. We're talking about what atheists **TELL ME** I think.

And one of the things they tell me I think is that religion is a cancer that would indeed make me want to die in this way.

They tell me how suicide bombers can't wait to die to get to those virgins. 

So - now you tell me different.

Which is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of those prices at the top might be inflated and overpriced, ABE gets like that but, depending on condition, it's got to be $70/80 plus I'd say... maybe more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only speak of what I personally experience - that's a good tip btw, you could adopt it usefully - and as I have not met any I can't say.

If I do though I'll be sure to tell them you said their religion was forced on them through violence and no-one ever chose to adopt it.

In a way though, this is very transparent. No atheist actually **CAN** believe anything other than religion is forced on someone because to believe it is a choice, or to believe (and this is what really freaks their pants) that there could be an actual thing called a *religious experience* is something they cannot comprehend. 

And as they are also convinced - like any good fundie - that they alone are right and have 'The Truth', what other option is there? It's the only thing they *can possibly* believe.

But as to it being rational, analysed, thought-out.... alas, no.

It's Pavlovian knee-jerking at best. And maybe not even just the knee  if you get a gaggle of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.abebooks.co.uk/servlet/SearchResults?an=idries+shah sortby=1 tn=oriental+magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 12:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.. I'll check it out. Didn't think of a meetup... cool! Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
