<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we had a war about something like this a while back.

It didn't end well for those states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But if you don't purchase health insurance, and you get sick, you will still be treated at the emergency room. Who do you imagine pays for that? Do you think the hospitals just eat the cost?

Most people I've seen who have a problem with the mandate either have enough money to pay for their own treatment or aren't worried about getting sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to buy car insurance for the benefit of other people when you cause them or their property direct harm when driving on public roads.

You need to buy health insurance just for existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yes, Republicans obviously benefit more at this time because they are the party with the most power so they do it more. But my point is that even if the most recent districts were reverted, Democrats would still not be a majority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rule, Britannia! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fuck how is this funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but the districts are the same and its unlikely there was much change in demographics in 4 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that's not true. [Current districts cost the Democrats only 9 seats](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2013/02/17/redistricting-didnt-win-republicans-the-house/?utm_term=.915a1fec3001), far below a majority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nation had a choice months ago and chose not to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, custom flair incoming bitches.

Dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come on and Slam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they could easily be classified as "enemies of the state".

The 80s called. They want their foreign policy back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No better than Vox or Salon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Whoever, owing allegiance to the United States, levies war against them or adheres to their enemies, giving them aid and comfort within the United States or elsewhere, is guilty of treason and shall suffer death, or shall be imprisoned not less than five years and fined under this title but not less than $10,000; and shall be incapable of holding any office under the United States.*

Last I checked we're not at war with Russia. Idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither obstructing justice nor treason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lying is unacceptable for anyone, especially the President of the United States. However, Khan is disgracing his son's memory by telling outright lies in order to score a few jabs against the President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know when Trump does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you mean they cut the election with heavy blows, no. Hack has only one definition, and what Russia did sure isn't it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It sure looks like Khizr Khan lied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is not holding a hearing anything but a "no"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to consent. They obviously did not. I don't see what's so hard to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair he was nominated in November of '87. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the President's Constitutional responsibility to nominate justices. He has the only standing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You heard the man. NEVER! Come 2040 John Roberts will just be flipping a coin for every case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still a rubber stamp if it says "no."

That's literally the opposite of what a rubber stamp is. You obviously have no idea what you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it will send a message it's okay to refuse to even hold hearings for a president's nominees.

Is that not okay? Honestly asking. The Senate was just acting on their powers laid out in the Constitution. They are under no obligation to confirm a nominee if they don't like them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Senate acted on their powers specifically laid out in the Constitution. They're not a rubber stamp for a President's nominee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Senate acted on their powers specifically laid out in the Constitution. They're not a rubber stamp for a President's nominee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie can still win, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Obama won and the Republicans should have shut the fuck up and affirmed his(quite reasonable) nominee.

Couldn't the same also be said that Republicans won the Senate (more recently than Obama's reelection), and Obama should have nominated a more conservative judge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you don't like it that doesn't make it stolen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *airhorns* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we end this "hacked the election" meme? It's quite literally "fake news". No voting machines were compromised, no vote totals were altered. Honestly, if Russia was going to hack the election you'd think they would have had the sense to make Trump win the popular vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am aware of what soft power is. I asked you how China intended to one up the US in that department. As you said, the US is the world leader because of it, and I would hope their position is rather stable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how exactly does one "soft power" their way to be the world leader over the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Current estimates predict China's economy will overtake the US's in 2026 at the earliest.](https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2016-us-vs-china-economy/) And that's only if they drastically institute economic reforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  nations to look to the remaining stable economic powerhouse

That's the thing though. Even *with* Trump at the helm, the US is still far and away the most stable and largest economy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please. China is in no position to take on anything close to "world leadership". Maybe in 50 years or so, but the US will remain the sole superpower for the foreseeable future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Spaniards gerrymandered Florida's state lines 300 years ago /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As they should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a legitimate president.

legitimate

adjective

ljidmt/

1. conforming to the law or to rules.

Trump received 270 electoral votes through legitimate elections held in all 50 states and DC. He's a legitimate president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> England and Scotland shared a Monarch for over 100 years before they were formally joined by the 1707 Acts of Union. What immediate political differences were there before and after the Union? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AS A REMINDER, THIS SUBREDDIT IS FOR CIVIL DISCUSSION.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rainbow Nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh get over yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make him illegitimate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drumpf

IS THIS THE END OF THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wawa is love. 

Wawa is life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they've even joked that their entire careers have been in an effort to get Clone High back on the air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok then. Well let's go through it all.

1. Trump-Clinton: Literally nothing has come from this Russia "scandal". They didn't "hack" the election. No voting machines were compromised and they released true information. People made informed choices.

2. Bush-Gore: The Supreme Court didn't "appoint" Bush. Literally no asked-for outcome of the Florida recounts would have made Gore the President. Also don't see what states rights have to do with that...

3. Reagan-Carter: This has been [pretty thoroughly debunked as a conspiracy theory](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/October_Surprise_conspiracy_theory), and both houses of Congress (Democrat majority at the time) concluded that there was no evidence. I guess we should be thinking of pizzagate as true to, because that has about the same amount of credibility as this does.

4. Ford was confirmed by Democrat majority houses of Congress and his Presidency was in accordance with the legal line of succession as defined in the 25th Amendment and the Presidential Succession Act. "Illegitimate" my ass.

5. Nixon-Humphrey: Nixon did undermine peace talks, but that doesn't change the fact that Humphrey would have won were it not for millions of racist Democrats voting for George Wallace. 

That entire rant is just a bunch of conspiratorial nonsense and complete ignorance of the laws of the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DEUS VULT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How in earth does gerrymandering matter in a presidential election? You can't gerrymander state lines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this may be the dumbest thing I've ever read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the Goblet of Fire deleted scenes. They just sing the Hogwarts song.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Virginia celebrated the birthdays of Civil Rights leader Martin Luther King Jr. and Confederate generals Robert E. Lee and Stonewall Jackson on the same day until 2000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the relations between European kingdoms and the Crusader States? Were they independent nations, or were they more akin to what we would consider to be colonies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any Muslim nation consider invading Western Europe (England, France, etc.) as retaliation for the Crusades? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to photograph the effects of Superman's new power...or they'll never believe me!

The original "pics or it didn't happen." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

...

...NAIIIIIIIIIIIIII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SKIDDLY BOP BE BOOO BOP, JACKY BABY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sMqQOGTshak/hqdefault.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SKIDDLY BE DO BOP, JACKY BABY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. You're forgetting about the Finders Keepers Statute of 1888.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Make America Chart Again](http://images.politico.com/global/2012/10/121001_3_ross_perot_reuters_500_605.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MATCH MEEEEEEEEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LBJ is rolling in his grave at that comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "HARRY DID YAH PUT YAH NAME IN THE GOBLET OF FIYAH?!?!?!?!" he asked calmly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I'm just saying that this article from 1996 now has an option to share on social media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.theonion.com/article/nation-suddenly-realizes-it-never-had-worry-about--54323 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that there's an option to share that to Reddit and Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND THANK YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lin-Manuel is GOAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C H A R T S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2018: After the passage of several bills directly targeting California's immigration policies, California elects a very liberal Governor promising an independence ballot proposition should Trump be reelected in 2020.

2020: After several of his policies successfully being enacted, Trump is reelected in another close election against a Booker/Harris ticket, once again losing the popular vote. Trump ramps up many of his policies, and completely cuts off federal funding for California's sanctuary cities. In response, the Governor vows to have an independence referendum by the end of the year.

2021: At Trump's second inauguration, a bomb goes off on the National Mall, killing dozens. Members of the [Yes California](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yes_California) movement claim responsibility. The Governor condemns the attack. Trump is livid and tells the Governor that should the referendum take place he will take action to stop it. The ballot proposition takes place later that year, with "Independence" winning by a wide margin. Both Trump and Congress declare secession to be illegal, with Trump vowing to send the army to stop it from going forward. California's Senators and Congressmen stop attending sessions of Congress in protest.

2022: The Governor is reelected in a landslide and declares that secession shall move forward. Trump sends in the army to stop them. Trump's popularity soars as he vows to "preserve the Union at all costs". Several military bases in California are seized, but most stay loyal to Trump. Hundreds die within several days. Many of California's eastern counties declare their intention to stay in the Union. 

2023: Sacramento is captured, and The Governor asks for peace. Trump refuses, stating that "rebellion will not be forgiven". The Governor and most of the government is killed and Sacramento is burned. Trump sends in more troops to occupy remaining rebellious counties. Americans are horrified at the atrocities committed against "their countrymen" by US troops. by the end of the year a "Reconstruction" period is initiated.

2024: Both party nominees run on a platform of ending federal occupation of California. A moderate Republican is elected and vows that California shall be "welcomed back with open arms".

2026: California formally reenters the Union. In an act of unity, the President and his family visit the new capital, Los Angeles. His wife and daughter are shot and killed by a group of pro-independence terrorists. In response, the President declares a renewed federal occupation to "root out remaining traitors". Many Californians die and video leaks of the President personally killing several captured terrorists.

2028: America is tired of 6 years of conflict and a Democrat is elected with a "just let them have it" stance.

2029: A formal treaty is drawn up with [this](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/a/a9/Coastal_California_Map.svg/585px-Coastal_California_Map.svg.png) being a now independent California Republic. White counties remain a part of the United States. Texas, under the guise of "a too liberal President", declares its own secession. America, not wanting to get into another prolonged conflict, allows them to leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. He "came back" 50 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TFW someone calls a monarchy a better example of democracy than the United States.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't thinking having a monarch as head of state and an unelected Upper House qualifies it as "the best". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M'arx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not offended I'm just confused. Are you trying to say Nazis are funny? Or that Trump is like Hitler, which makes him funny?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, how the turn tables... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's not a joke! It's literally just a picture of Hitler! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And would you care to explain why this is "humor"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't *say* anything. What is this even supposed to say? That all of Congress is Nazis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE Drumpf=Hitler???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Unregistered Democrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the Middle East and North Africa become majority Muslim a few centuries after being conquered, but India was able to remain majority Hindu despite being ruled by Muslim empires for similar amounts of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to [this](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Islamization_of_Egypt), Egypt became majority Muslim by the mid-10th century, about 300 years after the conquest, and today is almost 90% Muslim. But India today is 80% Hindu, despite being ruled by Muslim empires for hundreds of years. What accounts for these differences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Twelve Angle Stone, one of the finest examples of Inca masonry. [1600x1082] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They use something to dissolve the cement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screenshot of a tweet.

Political **HUMOR** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sucks, doesn't it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [RFK has a raging clue.](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bd/Robert_F_Kennedy_crop.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK I agree with the sentiment but maybe a quote from someone other than fucking *Trotsky* would be better. He's not really someone you should look to for good ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/LakeLaogai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM NOT TOPH! I AM **MELON LORD!!!** MUAHAHAHAHAHA!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than I expected, but worse than I hoped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a list of everything Trump's done.

- Declared the court system a threat to national security.
- Insisted that his Supreme Court pick had no problem with attacks on the judiciary, in the face of blatant evidence to the contrary.
- Trashed New START during a call with Putin  after putting the phone aside to ask his advisers what that (nuclear-arms treaty) was.
- Publicly condemned a private company for dropping his daughters (increasingly unpopular) fashion line.
- Suggested that publicly criticizing his military decisions is tantamount to aiding the enemy.
- Got angry at his press secretary for being impersonated by a woman.
- Used the executive branchs immense authority over border control to inflict arbitrary cruelty on thousands of Muslim immigrants, create chaos at airports all across America, and sour diplomatic relations with the rest of the world.
- Violated court orders against his travel ban.
- Created a diplomatic crisis with Australia  and threatened to invade Mexico.
- Allowed his press secretary to falsely claim that Iran had committed an act of war against the United States.
- Retained the author of a reactionary screed that likened the 2016 election to Flight 93 as a national-security staffer.
- Suggested that Frederick Douglass is still alive in speech on Black History Month.
- Told a demonstrable lie about the size of the crowd at his inauguration  and predicted that the media would pay a big price for refusing to repeat it.
- Told congressional leaders at a private meeting that he only lost the popular vote because undocumented immigrants cast millions of ballots against him.
- Suggested America might once again have the opportunity to confiscate Iraqs oil.
- Pushed for legislation you fuckers aren't even gonna read this but it'll still get 100s of upvotes.
- Allowed his company to leverage the cachet of his election into a massive expansion of its hotel empire.
- Ordered the Department of Homeland Security to issue a weekly list of crimes (allegedly) committed by undocumented immigrants in sanctuary cities.
- Prepared to radically reduce American funding to the United Nations.
- Signed a bevy of executive orders that were drafted by the White Houses Breitbart wing  and no one else.
- Declared that his election had restored American democracy, in an angry, authoritarian inaugural address.
- Replaced the White House websites page on climate change with a vow to drill for oil on federal lands.
- Defamed a hero of the civil-rights movement in a series of racist tweets.
- Allowed his secretary of State nominee to pledge that America would block Chinas access to its disputed islands in the South China Sea  a promise that, if kept, would almost certainly mean war.
- Named his son-in-law a senior White House adviser, in defiance of norms (and, very likely, laws) against nepotism.
- Called NATO obsolete.
- Repeatedly denigrated Americas intelligence agencies, then leaked plans to downsize them.
- Declared his openness to reviving a nuclear arms race.
- Disparaged the sitting American president, while praising a hostile foreign autocrat.
- Continued to use Twitter as a tool for souring diplomatic relations with the worlds second-greatest power.
- Named a billionaire investor  with an enormous, personal financial interest in deregulating certain sectors of the economy  as his special adviser on regulatory reform.
- Declared the American intelligence community to be inherently untrustworthy, after it produced information that he did not like.
- Said he would continue skipping daily intelligence briefings when he becomes president because hes smart enough to get by without them.
- Said he doesnt know why he should be bound by the One China Policy.
- Signed an Executive Order making anime illegal.
- Invited his adult sons  who are slated to run the Trump Organization next year  to a policy meeting with the leading - lights of Silicon Valley.
- Picked a man who once tried to call for the abolition of the Energy Department  but couldnt remember the departments name  as secretary of Energy.
- Named his bankruptcy lawyer  who thinks liberal Jews are worse than Nazi collaborators  as his pick for ambassador to Israel.
- Issued a decree making Nickelback the official band of the United States
- Provoked heightened diplomatic tensions with two nuclear-armed states.
- Handed the Environmental Protection Agency to a climate denialist.
- Handed the Labor Department to a serial violator of labor law. Although he quit like a loser today.
- Requested security clearance for a conspiracy theorist who claims that the Clintons operate a Satanic child-sex ring out of a popular D.C. pizzeria.
- Questioned the legitimacy of the election he just won.
- Appointed Ben Carson secretary of Housing and Urban Development  despite the fact that Carson has no relevant experience and recently declared himself unqualified for any cabinet position.
- Allowed his D.C. hotel to actively court the patronage of foreign diplomats.
- Invited the manager of his blind trust onto a phone call with the president of Argentina.
- Made Bernie Sanders' subreddit illegal.
- Met with Indian business partners who have publicly declared their intention to capitalize on his status as president-elect.
- Tried to coerce Britain into appointing a right-wing extremist as its ambassador to the United States.
- Berated the media at a closed-door meeting for publishing unflattering photos of his double chin.
- Admitted that his charity was guilty of self-dealing.
- Derided protestors as paid professionals whose acts of free speech are fundamentally unfair.
- Invited the manager of his blind trust to a meeting with the prime minister of Japan.
- Assembled a team of racists to lead his White House.
- Took credit for the fact that Ford will not be relocating a plant to Mexico (which they never had any intention of relocating to Mexico).
- Declared Americas leading newspaper a failing institution.
- Took calls from foreign leaders on unsecured phone lines, without consulting the State Department.
- Referred to his White House transition as though it were the next season of The Apprentice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a list of everything Trump's done.

- Declared the court system a threat to national security.
- Insisted that his Supreme Court pick had no problem with attacks on the judiciary, in the face of blatant evidence to the contrary.
- Trashed New START during a call with Putin  after putting the phone aside to ask his advisers what that (nuclear-arms treaty) was.
- Publicly condemned a private company for dropping his daughters (increasingly unpopular) fashion line.
- Suggested that publicly criticizing his military decisions is tantamount to aiding the enemy.
- Got angry at his press secretary for being impersonated by a woman.
- Used the executive branchs immense authority over border control to inflict arbitrary cruelty on thousands of Muslim immigrants, create chaos at airports all across America, and sour diplomatic relations with the rest of the world.
- Violated court orders against his travel ban.
- Created a diplomatic crisis with Australia  and threatened to invade Mexico.
- Allowed his press secretary to falsely claim that Iran had committed an act of war against the United States.
- Retained the author of a reactionary screed that likened the 2016 election to Flight 93 as a national-security staffer.
- Suggested that Frederick Douglass is still alive in speech on Black History Month.
- Told a demonstrable lie about the size of the crowd at his inauguration  and predicted that the media would pay a big price for refusing to repeat it.
- Told congressional leaders at a private meeting that he only lost the popular vote because undocumented immigrants cast millions of ballots against him.
- Suggested America might once again have the opportunity to confiscate Iraqs oil.
- Pushed for legislation you fuckers aren't even gonna read this but it'll still get 100s of upvotes.
- Allowed his company to leverage the cachet of his election into a massive expansion of its hotel empire.
- Ordered the Department of Homeland Security to issue a weekly list of crimes (allegedly) committed by undocumented immigrants in sanctuary cities.
- Prepared to radically reduce American funding to the United Nations.
- Signed a bevy of executive orders that were drafted by the White Houses Breitbart wing  and no one else.
- Declared that his election had restored American democracy, in an angry, authoritarian inaugural address.
- Replaced the White House websites page on climate change with a vow to drill for oil on federal lands.
- Defamed a hero of the civil-rights movement in a series of racist tweets.
- Allowed his secretary of State nominee to pledge that America would block Chinas access to its disputed islands in the South China Sea  a promise that, if kept, would almost certainly mean war.
- Named his son-in-law a senior White House adviser, in defiance of norms (and, very likely, laws) against nepotism.
- Called NATO obsolete.
- Repeatedly denigrated Americas intelligence agencies, then leaked plans to downsize them.
- Declared his openness to reviving a nuclear arms race.
- Disparaged the sitting American president, while praising a hostile foreign autocrat.
- Continued to use Twitter as a tool for souring diplomatic relations with the worlds second-greatest power.
- Named a billionaire investor  with an enormous, personal financial interest in deregulating certain sectors of the economy  as his special adviser on regulatory reform.
- Declared the American intelligence community to be inherently untrustworthy, after it produced information that he did not like.
- Said he would continue skipping daily intelligence briefings when he becomes president because hes smart enough to get by without them.
- Said he doesnt know why he should be bound by the One China Policy.
- Signed an Executive Order making anime illegal.
- Invited his adult sons  who are slated to run the Trump Organization next year  to a policy meeting with the leading - lights of Silicon Valley.
- Picked a man who once tried to call for the abolition of the Energy Department  but couldnt remember the departments name  as secretary of Energy.
- Named his bankruptcy lawyer  who thinks liberal Jews are worse than Nazi collaborators  as his pick for ambassador to Israel.
- Issued a decree making Nickelback the official band of the United States
- Provoked heightened diplomatic tensions with two nuclear-armed states.
- Handed the Environmental Protection Agency to a climate denialist.
- Handed the Labor Department to a serial violator of labor law. Although he quit like a loser today.
- Requested security clearance for a conspiracy theorist who claims that the Clintons operate a Satanic child-sex ring out of a popular D.C. pizzeria.
- Questioned the legitimacy of the election he just won.
- Appointed Ben Carson secretary of Housing and Urban Development  despite the fact that Carson has no relevant experience and recently declared himself unqualified for any cabinet position.
- Allowed his D.C. hotel to actively court the patronage of foreign diplomats.
- Invited the manager of his blind trust onto a phone call with the president of Argentina.
- Made Bernie Sanders' subreddit illegal.
- Met with Indian business partners who have publicly declared their intention to capitalize on his status as president-elect.
- Tried to coerce Britain into appointing a right-wing extremist as its ambassador to the United States.
- Berated the media at a closed-door meeting for publishing unflattering photos of his double chin.
- Admitted that his charity was guilty of self-dealing.
- Derided protestors as paid professionals whose acts of free speech are fundamentally unfair.
- Invited the manager of his blind trust to a meeting with the prime minister of Japan.
- Assembled a team of racists to lead his White House.
- Took credit for the fact that Ford will not be relocating a plant to Mexico (which they never had any intention of relocating to Mexico).
- Declared Americas leading newspaper a failing institution.
- Took calls from foreign leaders on unsecured phone lines, without consulting the State Department.
- Referred to his White House transition as though it were the next season of The Apprentice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a list of everything Trump's done.

- Declared the court system a threat to national security.
- Insisted that his Supreme Court pick had no problem with attacks on the judiciary, in the face of blatant evidence to the contrary.
- Trashed New START during a call with Putin  after putting the phone aside to ask his advisers what that (nuclear-arms treaty) was.
- Publicly condemned a private company for dropping his daughters (increasingly unpopular) fashion line.
- Suggested that publicly criticizing his military decisions is tantamount to aiding the enemy.
- Got angry at his press secretary for being impersonated by a woman.
- Used the executive branchs immense authority over border control to inflict arbitrary cruelty on thousands of Muslim immigrants, create chaos at airports all across America, and sour diplomatic relations with the rest of the world.
- Violated court orders against his travel ban.
- Created a diplomatic crisis with Australia  and threatened to invade Mexico.
- Allowed his press secretary to falsely claim that Iran had committed an act of war against the United States.
- Retained the author of a reactionary screed that likened the 2016 election to Flight 93 as a national-security staffer.
- Suggested that Frederick Douglass is still alive in speech on Black History Month.
- Told a demonstrable lie about the size of the crowd at his inauguration  and predicted that the media would pay a big price for refusing to repeat it.
- Told congressional leaders at a private meeting that he only lost the popular vote because undocumented immigrants cast millions of ballots against him.
- Suggested America might once again have the opportunity to confiscate Iraqs oil.
- Pushed for legislation you fuckers aren't even gonna read this but it'll still get 100s of upvotes.
- Allowed his company to leverage the cachet of his election into a massive expansion of its hotel empire.
- Ordered the Department of Homeland Security to issue a weekly list of crimes (allegedly) committed by undocumented immigrants in sanctuary cities.
- Prepared to radically reduce American funding to the United Nations.
- Signed a bevy of executive orders that were drafted by the White Houses Breitbart wing  and no one else.
- Declared that his election had restored American democracy, in an angry, authoritarian inaugural address.
- Replaced the White House websites page on climate change with a vow to drill for oil on federal lands.
- Defamed a hero of the civil-rights movement in a series of racist tweets.
- Allowed his secretary of State nominee to pledge that America would block Chinas access to its disputed islands in the South China Sea  a promise that, if kept, would almost certainly mean war.
- Named his son-in-law a senior White House adviser, in defiance of norms (and, very likely, laws) against nepotism.
- Called NATO obsolete.
- Repeatedly denigrated Americas intelligence agencies, then leaked plans to downsize them.
- Declared his openness to reviving a nuclear arms race.
- Disparaged the sitting American president, while praising a hostile foreign autocrat.
- Continued to use Twitter as a tool for souring diplomatic relations with the worlds second-greatest power.
- Named a billionaire investor  with an enormous, personal financial interest in deregulating certain sectors of the economy  as his special adviser on regulatory reform.
- Declared the American intelligence community to be inherently untrustworthy, after it produced information that he did not like.
- Said he would continue skipping daily intelligence briefings when he becomes president because hes smart enough to get by without them.
- Said he doesnt know why he should be bound by the One China Policy.
- Signed an Executive Order making anime illegal.
- Invited his adult sons  who are slated to run the Trump Organization next year  to a policy meeting with the leading - lights of Silicon Valley.
- Picked a man who once tried to call for the abolition of the Energy Department  but couldnt remember the departments name  as secretary of Energy.
- Named his bankruptcy lawyer  who thinks liberal Jews are worse than Nazi collaborators  as his pick for ambassador to Israel.
- Issued a decree making Nickelback the official band of the United States
- Provoked heightened diplomatic tensions with two nuclear-armed states.
- Handed the Environmental Protection Agency to a climate denialist.
- Handed the Labor Department to a serial violator of labor law. Although he quit like a loser today.
- Requested security clearance for a conspiracy theorist who claims that the Clintons operate a Satanic child-sex ring out of a popular D.C. pizzeria.
- Questioned the legitimacy of the election he just won.
- Appointed Ben Carson secretary of Housing and Urban Development  despite the fact that Carson has no relevant experience and recently declared himself unqualified for any cabinet position.
- Allowed his D.C. hotel to actively court the patronage of foreign diplomats.
- Invited the manager of his blind trust onto a phone call with the president of Argentina.
- Made Bernie Sanders' subreddit illegal.
- Met with Indian business partners who have publicly declared their intention to capitalize on his status as president-elect.
- Tried to coerce Britain into appointing a right-wing extremist as its ambassador to the United States.
- Berated the media at a closed-door meeting for publishing unflattering photos of his double chin.
- Admitted that his charity was guilty of self-dealing.
- Derided protestors as paid professionals whose acts of free speech are fundamentally unfair.
- Invited the manager of his blind trust to a meeting with the prime minister of Japan.
- Assembled a team of racists to lead his White House.
- Took credit for the fact that Ford will not be relocating a plant to Mexico (which they never had any intention of relocating to Mexico).
- Declared Americas leading newspaper a failing institution.
- Took calls from foreign leaders on unsecured phone lines, without consulting the State Department.
- Referred to his White House transition as though it were the next season of The Apprentice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be deep in the cold, cold ground before I recognize RutherFRAUD \#notmypresident \#tilden1880 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1848 was a pretty huge upset. You had Zachary Taylor, a man who had never held elective office, running against not only former Senator, Secretary of State, Secretary of War, Ambassador to France, and House Representative  Lewis Cass, but he was also running against former *President* Martin Van Buren. He was also a Whig when the Democrats had a pretty solid track record of winning. But he still pulled it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using that dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh but businesses definitely need to pay a living wage, though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has done literally none of that.

And since you've moved on I take it that you agree with me that the 14 Points are bullshit. Good to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Put up in the damn gift shop. 

That list is such BS it's not even included in the Definitions of Fascism. 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Definitions_of_fascism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The defense is that it was written by a guy with no academic background a few years ago for the sole purpose of trying to oppose GWB. This list is not taken seriously at all in academic circles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes. The gift shop list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reported for incivility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Presidential_Succession_Act

This should detract from your argument pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it this way.

Imagine the Patriots are playing say...the Browns. In theory, the Patriots *should* be able to destroy them with almost no effort. They have better players, better coaching, the whole 9 yards. But let's say the Patriots have a bad day. They allow a lot of turnovers and give up a lot of points, but they're still ahead by 2 points late in the 4th quarter. Now let's say a referee made a bad call and it gave the Browns the ball, and they were able to score a field goal to win at the last second. Did the ref make a bad call? Yes. Did that bad call lose the Patriots the game? Yes.

But the point is that the Patriots have NO BUSINESS even allowing it to be that close in the first place. Clinton was only up by 2 late in the 4th quarter before the Comey letter hit. That's on her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.snopes.com/mike-pence-supported-gay-conversion-therapy/

Pence never stated that he supported the use of electric shocks or "gay conversion" therapy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hillary will beat Trump in a landslide!"

Gee, where have I heard that before?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but we realized how horrible that was and how it went against all of our values and changed it. We can't just go back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Restricting voting to a certain type of people is a bigger threat to our nation, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 18 years old and US citizen. Those should be the only requirements. A guy with a PhD has the same voting power as the guy who didn't finish high school. A billionaire has the same voting power as someone in poverty. You can't restrict voting to "educated" people. It goes against the foundation of our nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's not, but there are times like these when I think that sub is some form or satire or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. People should at least have a college education to be able to vote. And now that I think about it, you should need to be a man, too. And own land. And be white. 

I don't see how that could possibly go wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impeached for purjury, you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a measure for a new election. It's called "every 4 years." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not have treasonous relations with that government... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people honestly think there will be a new election? Like are people honestly, not sarcastically suggesting that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Honestly if you believe Pence would bring anything close to the human rights abuses in the Middle East I don't know what to tell you. He's a piece of shit but an imaginary "Christian Caliphate" shouldn't be a reason to stop Trump's removal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. I prefer pop teen sensation Brittney Brittney. And her Brittney Brittney dancers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Humor" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I enjoy the discussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California spent on high-speed rail and illegal immigrants, but ignored Oroville Dam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Flynn was appointed by Trump, which means he is a republican problem.

Still a registered Democrat.

So Obama was not president ?

He was, but that's hardly "in charge". I guess there was no obstructionism for the past few years from the Republicans if you think he was "in charge" that whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Won't Chelsea Clinton Shut Up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Flynn is gone

He's a Democrat, so not really helping your case here.

Dems were in charge for the previous 8 years

No they weren't. Lost House and Senate within a few years of Obama's election.

They lost to Donald Trump. /u/eightexamples is right. They've been failing nonstop for the past few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats want to use Flynn scandal to damage Trump. Here's why they'll fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who said it first? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Drain the Swamp" and "Hope and Change" are essentially the same, just marketed differently. Nothing Trump has done has had even a hint of "revolution". Unorthodox? Yes. But a far cry from "revolution". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the end of Trump's campaign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invigorating angry white voters is about as big of a "political and racial revolution" as African Americans coming out for Obama in '08 and '12 was. And hatred of PC culture an "ethical revolution"? Come on man you're just grasping at straws here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but that's completely inaccurate. What has Trump done that is anywhere close to a "political, social and ethical revolution"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump aide sees sexism in Tapper's Conway interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something in [here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Definitions_of_fascism). Also you'll notice that the 14 Points do not appear anywhere on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Implying the "14 Points" hold any merit and weren't written by a liberal non-academic with the sole intention of targeting Bush and is now brought up by people on /r/politics because they have no idea what fascism is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. If you look at South Park over the years many of their classic episodes take right-wing positions.

1. Goobacks (2004): Satirizes illegal immigration. By the end of the of the episode, Stan comes to the conclusion that while immigrants are living in poverty and they are just trying to get by, poor societies often hurt other societies instead of helping them.

2. ManBearPig (2006): Satirizes Al Gore and climate change. Pretty much says that climate change is no big deal.

3. Stunning and Brave (2015): Satirizes political correctness and Caitlyn Jenner, and pretty much says that it's all total nonsense.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eisenhower. Ford. Reagan. HW. Clinton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOP! I can only get so erect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ay deed naht heet her eets bullsheet ay deed naht heet her. Ay deed NAHT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truman, Kennedy, LBJ, Carter. 4 presidents and the Democrats have had 4 failures. Out of the last 4 presidents, one just entered office, one was mediocre, one was a failure and one was a success. To attempt to draw a conclusion based on party is asinine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't "dismiss" them. It's just that terrorism was not on anybody's radar at the time. The world "terrorism" was mentioned *once* during the 2000 debates. It would be like if that meteor that passed by earth last year had hit earth, nobody would have blamed Obama for not acting on that. Bush took the proper responses for the time. This revisionist history about 9/11 is honestly insulting to the victims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 presidents is hardly enough to draw any meaningful conclusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You saying...you want a piece of me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they're making money, but far from what they could be making. BvS was considered a surefire Billion+, but it lost millions from the poor word of mouth. After Suicide Squad, I know a ton of people who aren't going to see Wonder Woman. Surely there'll come a point where the poor reception catches up to Warner Bros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BvS "made money", but it was a lot less than they should have, all because of the bad word of mouth. It made less than $100,000,000 more than Deadpool, an R-rated movie with a hero most people have never heard of. Imagine if The Dark Knight Rises only made a bit more than Captain America: The First Avenger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
