<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5987</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're my favorite kind of nut, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably 9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange is underrated tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sushi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you think people are judged for losing weight for superficial reasons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a wizard, doggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know what my dad's haircolor was until I was about 17 because as long as I was alive it had been a faded brownish color and then turned grey, and he hated getting his picture taken when he was younger so there weren't many pictures of him from when he was young. I found an old photo album and turns out, he used to have fire engine-red hair. He also used to be very pale and accumulated so many freckles that it turned into a tan. So that explained why I'm ghost-level pale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it with offices and this style of poster? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potatoes aren't exactly the healthiest food, they're basically just starch and have a lot of calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you Archer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was funny though, for a brief moment in 2005. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But my boy is wicked smaht! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you google "Christopher Walken" the first thing that pops up right now is a bunch of shitty tabloid articles about him getting a pat down in Atlanta. No wonder he looks pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people in Texas still believe they're cowboys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given all the years of hard work that must have taken, he has the right to not be modest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sshhhh he's cultivating mass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massachusetts is where the wicked smaht ones are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have to peck them then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, they legit just used your picture without even asking? People suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awfully depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even get a message that they made an article about this thread...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really the airlines fault, but I was stuck next to an extremely obese woman who was spilling into my seat and snoring loudly the whole flight. I'm a 5'2 100 lbs female so I don't need that much space either, but she was so obese that she was taking up enough of my seat that I was squished against the side of the plane the whole flight. I don't understand why they don't make these people buy two seats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short people of Reddit, how much weight loss or gain does it take for it to be noticeable to you? How much is noticeable to other people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really something I miss but I recently learned that if you order a milkshake in other parts of the US, you get a frappe (thick milkshake with ice cream). In New England a milkshake is just... shaken milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I know is that they have crabs. Don't go to Maryland unless you want to catch crabs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP just thinks he's clever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of Reddit who have lost or gained a large amount of weight, what differences have you noticed in the way people treated you when you were thin vs fat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transgender people of Reddit who have transitioned, what differences have you noticed in the way people treat you as a man vs as a woman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Manhattan tomato soup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some countries, cheating in school is normal and expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *cops assaulting people. Also airline passengers not being treated like criminals would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay calm and eat something. It'll go away. You definitely didn't overdose on caffeine though, it's pretty much physically impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a person from 1900 traveled to the future, hearing people talk about "the World Wars" would sound pretty dystopian. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much weight loss or gain does it take for your clothing to not fit, and how tall are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBF it wasn't the biggest superpower in the world at the time. The US didn't gain superpower status until the World Wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or woman legos, apparently. Unless the one in the back is a woman? I can't really tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are they opposed to IVF, if you don't mind me asking? I was born through IVF and if it's because they think IVF babies are some kind of soulless demon spawn or something, that would be hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm not really, but I gained a lot of weight (about 30 lbs) from binging constantly over the last year and being super unhealthy. I have a small frame and my normal weight is in the upper 90s to lower 100s, I gained to the 120s and on my frame it made me look like a total fatass lol, even though it's not *technically* overweight. I'm just working on getting healthy again and back to my normal weight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many pounds would be a noticeable weight loss on a non-overweight short person (say 5'2)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19 and my mom graduated in 1979, and my dad in 1977... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zoe Mozert painting a pin-up girl, 1940s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [She wouldn't look out of place on Instagram in 2017](http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-WN1Dfq2hpto/UEn4JEqri0I/AAAAAAAADJA/d3ViWqGi9Ro/s1600/tumblr_lu8724IeDf1qh0yodo1_1280.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, I'm 5'2 and if I'm over about 115 lbs people think I'm overweight, even though you're not technically overweight at 5'2 until you get to the 130s. Although I also have a very small frame and IBS so I get bloated easily. You're most definitely not chubby though, you look very thin (but not in a bad way!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when people spout that "the human body was designed to retain fat" nonsense. The human body was designed to survive and function during periods of famine through burning fat stores, people can generally go with very little food and be just fine. I used to let this crap scare me into eating at least 1200 calories a day even when I'm on a diet, but I'm a generally sedentary 5'2 woman and only need 200-300 more calories than that to stay the *same* weight, so it's not such good advice for me. I'd only be losing half a pound a week on that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd call it disordered eating rather than an eating disorder. Not all obese people have an eating disorder, but all obese people have some form of disordered eating pattern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on like every news channel all day today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We never have more than like a week of spring max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I keep hearing about this everywhere, not just on Reddit. My 58 year old dad was pissed off by it and said he isn't flying United ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really seems like there's this trend lately where flight passengers are treated like both chattel and high-risk criminals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucked up people exist. The real problem is that we do *nothing* to try to prevent this, no matter how many times it happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The future is for rich people, not us poors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like most pools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no no no no that is not ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus most of the eastern US and Canada (until they legalize it at least). We're the only ones in the east to legalize other than Maine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weight would you consider too thin for a 5'2 female? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weight would you consider chubby on a 5'2 girl with a small frame? What weight would you consider thin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because those Republican states are so known for their acceptance of legal weed, abortions, and gay marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically the states that "vote for small government" have a lot more rules policing what you can and can't personally do with everything except smoking cigarettes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was damn easy for me to get alcohol at 16-18, and for me that was last year. If you *really* want to stop minors from getting alcohol you should ban all older siblings and parents from buying it. And anyone who knows someone under 18 honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Percentage of world population living on less than $2 per day [1348x644] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Googled it, it says the last saturday morning cartoon lineup ended in 2014, I don't have cable so I guess that's why I didn't know. But I've never had cable and there were still saturday morning cartoons when I was a kid. It was the only time there were any cartoons for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in 97, we had dial up and tapes until like 2006 (and we weren't poor), and Saturday morning cartoons still exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What differences have you noticed between people born in the early 90s vs late 90s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why but whenever I look at a T_D troll's history a *lot* of the time they post in there. I'm not sure if it's a correlated interest or if it's trolls or something posting there to seem inconspicuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were born in 1995 or later, most of your 20s will be in the 2020s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you consider to be the cut-off birth year between Generation Y and Generation Z? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What generation would someone born in 1997 be considered part of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite was the scoreboard with NE: 3 ATL: 28 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exercise and music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm upset and I eat chocolate it just makes me feel worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you consider to be the cut-off birth year between Millenials and Generation Z? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders walked into a costumed battle at Anime Boston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your city was a candle what would its scent be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try visiting Boston, the first thing people usually comment on when they come here is how clean it is. Although they might just be comparing it to New York which is disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do Southerners love college football? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build the wall! Keep the New Yorkers out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, especially because up until recently we didn't win at things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd be incorrect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The largest wing of the Democrats are moderates, Clinton was one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this scandal be known as Blackwater? Because that's a pretty badass name for a scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure, it just doesn't seem likely to me. I could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommen= oversized child= Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bannon is Ramsay Bolton IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan has an insanely low approval rating right now, even Trump fans wouldn't be happy with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Ryan is third in line after Trump and Pence and pretty much definitely doesn't have Russia ties, we're screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the top left- 

NE: 3 ATL: 28

Don't let the rest of the artwork distract you from what's important here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red. I pushed too hard and now my eyes are bleeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeb! is a foolish guac bowl merchant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically those are for disabled people, it's just that fat people co-opted them. Thankfully I haven't seen this in the wild before, I guess my local Walmart is just classier than the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were Jeb Bush what kind of guacamole would you sell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss JEB! memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2.5 years? damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A true classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You went against your own serious tag, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would depend on what country you're from and what films are considered foreign to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you predict your personal life will be different in 2020? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bostonians aren't friendly enough to be Canadian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the US was started out of a bunch of different colonies that had never worked together and didn't really want to be one country in the first place. The South in particular definitely wouldn't have joined if they couldn't make their own rules (there was that whole slavery thing) and were still borderline on seceding up until the Civil War. Creating a single country-wide government from scratch and getting rid of the state ones just wouldn't have worked.

Personally I'm damn thankful that things are mostly run on the state level, the federal government is a shitshow and most of the other states suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do most of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the largest difference is probably the language difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IBS doesn't mean you're constantly shitting yourself, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People born in 1997 are a century younger than Amelia Earhart, William Faulkner, and Moe from the Three Stooges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee has zero calories. When you don't put anything in it, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunks is a coffee place first and foremost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol her pants have padding in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be Puerto Rico, Canada, or the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There is only one person still alive who was born in the 1800s, a 117-year-old Italian woman named Emma Morano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PSA: Antiques Roadshow is on PBS which is being defunded by the Trump administration. Please donate if you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massachusetts is trying to switch from Eastern time to Atlantic! We'd need Rhode Island, New Hampshire, and Maine to switch too for it to work though really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Googled drug in each US state [650x448] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Remaining JFK assassination records. Most have already been released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about Blue Origin but I'd say there's definitely already a space race of sorts between private companies (SpaceX) and the public sector (NASA). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space Race 2.0? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is Latin America so much poorer than North America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meth is mostly popular in the West and South. It's not really a thing in the Northeast, although heroin definitely is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "providing useful information" do you mean being a pretentious douche? Fuck off, hipster prick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like finding dumb reasons to feel superior to others when they have nothing going for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless there's someone on Reddit who's under 12 years old. In which case, get off Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were born in 1995 or later, most of your 20s will be in the 2020s. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm ok with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of Boston... please please don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can never go to Iceland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exercise and listen to music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single payer healthcare, plus changing pretty much every one of his stances on everything. 

And stop tweeting, act like an adult, start taking personal responsibility for once instead of blaming everyone around him, stop wasting more taxpayer money on personal vacations than he's cutting from the arts and humanities, fire Bannon and everyone in his cabinet, nominate a decent non-partisan supreme court judge, etc etc etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's projecting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
