<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6292</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 02:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it was bad... Even worse, though, she convinced me to try a foursome later. Guy got drunk and pushy, I backed out for fear of my safety. Now-ex-wife ended up with that guy. You know, until he got fired and couldn't give her money anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 01:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my wife of the time - who hadn't done anything with me specifically for some six months prior to this - sat aside and offered little interaction other than encouragement for me to continue with this other person. Technically, it was a threesome based only on the number of people in the room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 01:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viagra laced beer. It sounds like a good idea, for when you drink yourself flaccid, but it would make for incredibly awkward bar scenes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 00:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My self esteem was fine. My confidence in my marriage, however, was severely damaged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 00:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything. I hate repeating myself, and there's only so many ways to rephrase an idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 14:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Providing honest responses to indifferent, cursory questions

. Example: How are you? Can't complain, except for feeling like a cold might be coming on.

People expect me to just say"fine" and be done with it. There's always a short pause in the conversation when this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 06:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost pepper extract  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 06:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her heart stopped. She didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 06:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't sleep... clowns will eat me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 05:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snape kills dumbledore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably going to have plenty of time. From what I understand, they're splitting the last book (geez, again?), so you'll probably have until the end of next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the plus side, you don't know *how* it happens. So there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 02:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bathroom door  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 02:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primrose Everdeen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frequent morning sickness

New parent help

Cancer treatment options

SIDS causes/prevention

Infant casket purchase

Family friendly cemetery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does blue look like? (asked by a blind child) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do these all the time! Let's see...

There are children in Africa who would kill for this!

--to--

There are killers in Africa who would starve for this!

First one that came to my mind, I've got more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, at the moment, my job is getting ready to get officially fired. I get away with redditing by merit of having been removed from all responsibilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick it in the fridge, forget about it, and throw it away in a couple of weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having friends... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP has a good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breastfeeding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try really really hard to not be a dick to people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In soviet Russia, joke laughs at you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money goes to schools that show good test scores. Schools with lower testing students get less funding because they "aren't meeting the standard." travesty, because these schools demonstrate a greater need of support endeavors for the student body development.

Let's help out people who have shown they don't need it as much, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 05:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need an adult!!!

I am an adult!!

I need an adult-ER adult!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nickelback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule #1: Nobody knows the rules, they're just faking it. It's your job to fake it better than anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sonder.

Paraphrasing the definition from memory, here...

The profound sense of wonder caused by the realization that every single other person you ever encounter has a life as complicated as yours, with just as much drama, stress, joy, and woes, in which you play no more of a significant role than they do in yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sit-down dinner. Plenty of time to talk while waiting for the food to come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I normally do with this is a text document. I type one thought, change to italics, then type a response to that though, change back, respond, and so on. Helps me isolate separate thoughts, and track my own worries. Sometimes, things pop up in there that I'd never considered consciously before, but are oh-so-obvious once I typed them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why/phy.

4 hours of intense focus, followed by 4 hours tripping balls. Sounds productive, AND fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many existentialists does it take to change a light bulb?

Once the bulb goes out, how can we be sure they even exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I think this actually makes the phrase I've been using all these years a bit more convincing. Makes people realize that I'm trying, but also just don't speak it well enough to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I maintain and repair a machine which fires massive amounts of energy into the air at a specific frequency, which allows us to identify, track, and manage data about anything from weather to missiles to aircraft, all over the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 04:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible, but very unlikely. I've had one ex who I can claim is still friendly toward me. In my experience, it's either fine right from the spilt, or it'll never happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to take Spanish in high school, but it didn't stick. Later on, I learned an extremely helpful phrase that has seen me through some sticky situations.

*Lo siento mucho, pero no hablo Espanol - no mas de este. Uno momento, y voy para ayuda.*

I'm very sorry, but I don't speak Spanish - no more than this. One moment, and I'll go for help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> April 5th, 2016. Central Texas, USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fido </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distractions work, too. Mindless games or involved books are my go-to's.

If you're really struggling with something there's something else that you could try. It sounds kinda strange, though... Write down your though process, as though "talking" to yourself. I find that putting all my thoughts in front of me as they occur helps keep me from cycling endlessly through them, and lets me analyze all the points a little bit better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookware (pot, pan, skillet, spatula and ladle), dishes (1 bowl, 1plate, 1-2 cups, per person), cleaning supplies (409, scrubbing bubbles, dish soap, laundry soap), clothes (2 pair work clothes, two other sets of shirt/pant combo, as many socks and undies as you want), bath soap (absolute must), paper towels, real towels, toilet paper, and bedding.

Bare minimum, you will need all of these within a day or two, or at least within the first week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find some way to take myself out of it for a while. It can be anything from running to reading a good book to playing video games for hours on end. When I come back from it, usually I've either thought through the anxiety, or have rested my mind enough to deal with it anew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 03:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roses are red, zebras: half black.
If you like the front, you'll just love the back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 06:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure... I was just clicking through tagged games on the subreddit front page, before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I tried this game, it was too slow and unclear for my liking. I lost interest almost immediately.

Now, there's a sense of strategy, of progression, that makes it feel more involved and rewarding than any other incremental style game I've played before. It honestly feels like a text based RTS-style game. Strange thing is, though, that I hate RTS games.

I love this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 16:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

...mostly  #4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started taking notes. It's hard to fuck with personal records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have chosen my words poorly. Those were all examples of what I fill that time with, not all the things I do every single morning. To be honest, more often than not I just play video games for the whole two hours, because it's the only time I'm the only one awake in the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnny Depp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casually walking through a closed door  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, the one I'm writing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 years.

Then puberty hit, and I fell off the wagon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wild Arms 4. Final boss changed shapes at least a dozen times, and I died before I beat it. It was so unreasonably hard, especially since I was one-hitting absolutely everything outside of that one battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I'm hungry*

Hi, hungry! I'm dad.

*No, dad, I'm serious.*

Serious? I thought you said you were hungry?

*Geez... Would you please make me a sandwich?*

Okay... Poof! Now you're a sandwich!

*Daaaad!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That moment when everything has gone to absolute hell, and you're just about to give up, when suddenly something comes to your attention that will completely fix everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daily rinse, which turns into a good scrub the next day if I ever forget. Which is frequent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I'm not pleasant or personable in the morning. This just makes me hate it somewhat less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, get the right shoes for your feet. 

There are many specialty stores that offer a free professional gait analysis for customers. Basically, you walk in, they ask you how you're going to be using your new shoes, and then they'll ask to watch you walk for a minute. Based on your answers and how your feet land in your stride, they'll recommend a shoe type for you - either stability, motion control, or minimalist, and maybe a couple other types I don't recall or know of. Best part is, you don't even have to buy the shoes there - you can go home and hunt down the type you need on the internet. From personal experience, Brooks is high quality and fairly affordable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 08:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make your morning part of your day, rather than just a transition from sleep to work.

Take me, for example: I actually wake up two hours before I have to go to work. In that time, I shower, have breakfast, play video games, watch TV - whatever strikes me. It took some willpower to make that my routine, but now I actually look forward to my 5 AM me-time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 03:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, just trying to help you. I've spent most of an evening browsing for something we could agree on before, but Max shoots something right out that's usually right on the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 03:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to crumple the shit out of eight or nine turns of that single-ply Scott tissue crap. Now I use Charmin, and fold one-two squares with much better results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 03:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too many variables. What are you into? What about her? What are you in the mood for? What do you like? Do you want something deep, or superfluous?

Serious question, though: do you have a playstation 3 or 4? If so, just log in through that and use Max to find a suggestion based on how you answer a couple of quick questions. It has never let me down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because that's the way it is, doesn't mean it's right. Or smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Swamps of Degobah.

Can't find it to link it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Importance is relative. It might seem extreme now, but in a couple of years you won't even remember most of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Formerly military here. I worked on a base a couple of years ago which had a clinic on it. They were so undermanned that if anyone assigned there got sick during non-work hours, we were told to just go to the ER. It was dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 21:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me, but my four year old 

She recently discovered laser pointers, and has come to the conclusion that it makes things lazy. Her exact words: the laser light makes people lazy.

Can't fault her logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 21:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hobo with a shotgun.

It... I... Words can't even.

Look, just go watch it, alright?

Prep for gratuitous graphic unrealistic violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter's birth. I laughed, screamed, and cried my eyes out. It was the most joyously terrifying moment of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 00:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common sense is fairly rare.

The military is not efficient.

No one likes everything you do as much as you.

Reddit doesn't care.

The internet is mostly superfluous data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gilligan's island. 

Gives you the premise, introduces the characters, and is catchy as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Dresden's rings. He has silver bands which store a small portion of the kinetic energy caused by the motion of his arm throughout the day. Then he took that concept, and wove three of the bands together, tripling the potential power. Then he made one for each finger. That's a lot of pow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this is a like, or dislike... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Icebreakers wintergreen mints. Probably the only reason I don't smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird Al, and... Eminem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instant zippers. Like, magnetic, or something.

Seriously, they make magnetic ball bearings, and if you line them up right, they already sort of zip together. Sew that onto a jacket and you've got no-effort zips without the noise of Velcro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rockadoodle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changing Jar-Jar's personality would do a lot to fix all three, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate steak. Like, steak with chocolate syrup on. Accidental discovery, but surprisingly tasty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 05:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrote this before in r/rants, but it seems to fit here, too.

I'm 27, and this year was my first good birthday in roughly a decade. Here's more or less a chronicle of the bad ones.

Year 1: Left home alone on rainy day by parents despite my plans to go to a movie with girlfriend of the time, assigned to wait for a plumber to come fix the house, sometime between 10 AM and 6 PM. Plumber never showed, and the roads flooded between me and the theatre, so I missed the date.

Year 2: While on the phone talking to family about abusive roommate (who I was going to flee) got t-boned (before cell phone laws). Lost my car, but uninjured. Was removed from my apartment, given lack of transportation. Could be worse.

Year 3: Air Force basic training. 21st birthday. Did not go well when the TI found out. What's worse, it was week 2 of 8, so I had that long to go before I could have my first drink (I was a good boy, actually waited.)

Year 4: Was in 2-week Combat Skills training course. Had left then-wife $300 emergency money while I was in there, which she decided to use to take our only car up to Illinois. So, not only was I trapped in the training grounds when we were given free pass to leave, I also had to send her more money ($100) to make the trip back. Somehow, she ran out of money/gas halfway back, slept in a truck stop, and "begged" a random stranger for gas money. I put that in quotes because we're divorced now, and I now have suspicions over past activities.

Year 5: Antidepressants. Don't remember much, but this is the year my divorce started. Was removed from my house on base around the time of my birthday (she spread lies, the military had to act). Spent 1.5 months without any contact with my daughter. Plus side, managed to recover from my situational depression enough to get off the meds, so... yay.

Year 6: Divorce settled, have joint custody. Ex-wife decided to withhold my daughter from me for three months without an explanation. I found out when I went to pick her up from daycare (week or two before my birthday) and she wasn't there. Staff said the mother had told them I wasn't to be allowed near my daughter. I called to ask why, and ex-wife called the cops on me. Never got an explanation, but was later accused in court of sexually assaulting my two year old daughter. WTF.

Year 7: Final custody hearing was actually ON my birthday. Other than the drama surrounding it, it all went well; I won full and sole custody of my daughter. What with the timing, however, I can say for certain that the birthday was particularly shitty, especially since crazy ex and her psycho dad (who had threatened me several times, and was actively trying to end my career) were still in the area and knew where I lived.

Year 8: More or less fine, except my new wife had a miscarriage. We'd planned it, wanted it, got it, lost it. All in roughly a month. Have had no luck since.

Year 9. This year. Stayed in the house. Locked the doors. Had some whiskey. Watched movies. Ate cake. Made every possible attempt to not allow fate to ruin the day or the days surrounding it. Worked pretty well, this time around.


So.

 Be thankful for what small blessings you have on any given day, because as you progress through life the only thing you can really be certain of is that things will only ever get harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 04:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life. It's like everyone is just winging it, and trying not to let anyone else know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 04:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laugh maniacally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 06:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse me, ma'am, but I seem to have lost my icebreaker around here. Have you seen it?

If she asks about it, then something about how much a polar bear weighs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 06:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time you want to buy a video game, put the cost of the game into a savings account first. Then, if you still really want it next paycheck, get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 06:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going with WalMart checkout items...

Combination pen/laser pointer/flashlight.

Any given candy.

Windproof lighter 

Pocket video game. Yes, even the crappy checkout lane ones - video games weren't invented until the 1970s, so it'd be amazing.

Singing post card.

Umm... I know there's more, but I'm drawing a blank.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 03:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suck at my job, didn't get promoted, and got fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 03:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids didn't like their parent's rules, so they threw a fit, broke some stuff, and then claimed that they knew better and ran away. Years later, they began to realize they didn't have all the answers, but were too proud to admit that they needed help.

Source: American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 03:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carefully considering the words you will use before speaking. Presentation of an idea is rather a large portion of what convinces people to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 15:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 27, and this year was my first good birthday in roughly a decade. I'll throw my own little rant in here now... not trying for one-upmanship or anything, just want to show you that it could be worse.

Year 1: Left home alone on rainy day by parents despite my plans to go to a movie with girlfriend of the time, assigned to wait for a plumber to come fix the house, sometime between 10 AM and 6 PM. Plumber never showed, and the roads flooded between me and the theatre, so I missed the date.

Year 2: While on the phone talking to family about abusive roomate (who I was going to flee) got t-boned (before cell phone laws). Lost my car, but uninjured. Was removed from my apartment, given lack of transportation. Could be worse.

Year 3: Air Force basic training. 21st birthday. Did not go well when the TI found out. What's worse, it was week 2 of 8, so I had that long to go before I could have my first drink (I was a good boy, actually waited.)

Year 4: Was in 2-week Combat Skills training course. Had left then-wife $300 emergency money while I was in there, which she decided to use to take our only car up to Illinois. So, not only was I trapped in the training grounds when we were given free pass to leave, I also had to send her more money ($100) to make the trip back. Somehow, she ran out of money/gas halfway back, slept in a truck stop, and "begged" a random stranger for gas money. I put that in quotes because we're divorced now, and I now have suspicions over past activities.

Year 5: Antidepressants. Don't remember much, but this is the year my divorce started. Was removed from my house on base around the time of my birthday (she spread lies, the military had to act). Spent 1.5 months without any contact with my daughter. Plus side, managed to recover from my situational depression enough to get off the meds, so... yay.

Year 6: Divorce settled, have joint custody. Ex-wife decided to withhold my daughter from me for three months without an explanation. I found out when I went to pick her up from daycare (week or two before my birthday) and she wasn't there. Staff said the mother had told them I wasn't to be allowed near my daughter. I called to ask why, and ex-wife called the cops on me. Never got an explanation, but was later accused in court of sexually assaulting my two year old daughter. WTF.

Year 7: Final custody hearing was actually ON my birthday. Other than the drama surrounding it, it all went well; I won full and sole custody of my daughter. What with the timing, however, I can say for certain that the birthday was particularly shitty, especially since crazy ex and her psycho dad (who had threatened me several times, and was actively trying to end my career) were still in the area and knew where I lived.

Year 8: More or less fine, except my new wife had a miscarriage. We'd planned it, wanted it, got it, lost it. All in roughly a month. Have had no luck since.

Year 9. This year. Stayed in the house. Locked the doors. Had some whiskey. Watched movies. Ate cake. Made every possible attempt to not allow fate to ruin the day or the days surrounding it. Worked pretty well, this time around.


So.

I think what you have up there are many minor inconveniences, but all in all there's a fair amount of good stuff going on in your life. Be thankful for what small blessings you have on any given day, because as you progress through life the only thing you can really be certain of is that things will only ever get harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
