<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7095</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 13:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all remember that cat zingano pulverized nunes, yeah? I don't think this is an easy fight for either of em. Don't hate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If chance the rapper isnt on the new record i'll be shocked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save bandit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 05:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah rascals is definitely a very charitable translation of yaro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JK stands for Joshi Kosei. It means high-school girl, but is used most frequently here as short-hand for whats called compensated dating, with high-school girls. Its a shady business, while some are certainly sexual (and as a result, most likely illegal), most guys just pay to walk around and/or hold hands. 

Its alarmingly common here, most japanese people don't blink when they see it. But its a hugely popular theme for JAV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 14:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a dumb question but, do you only want to shoot weddings? Like, not just couples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mickey had mentioned a few times that he didnt feel like he deserved to be on the main card. Punk told him not to talk himself down, fake it til you make it. That if he's on the main card, he deserves to be on the main card and not to let anyone tell him otherwise. Something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, i cant give you any specific details but I know two of my japanese friends got work outside of shuukatsu time by going through headhunters/employment agencies. Maybe try search for them and find a local one? 

Dunno if that helps at all, good luck buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ijime musume means "mean girl" btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering how great cowboy has been at 170, and the fact that Dana wants him to stay there (despite cowboy wanting to go fight alvarez at 155), i think maybe, yeah. But I guess we'll have to wait and see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
