<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9885</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] I had a go at curried vegetable pies, perfect for the cold weather with mash and kale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I just started making cp soap recently too. My most christmassy one so far is chocolate orange with cinnamon which was 10 fold orange essential oil, cocoa powder and cinnamon powder(although maybe cinnamon leaf essential oil would be better) in base oils of
40% coconut oil 
30% shea butter
30% olive oil
And super fat at 5%
It's a great chocolatey colour and the cinnamon and orange has a real festive smell, So everyone's getting a bar of that for Christmas!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of the items you listed the ones I use most frequently (apart from the French press which I only use for coffee so not sure I could add anything) are the food processor and ice cream maker. So here are my tips:
Food processor - I love to use mine for curry bases/pastes, pesto, bean or chickpea hummus, mayonnaise, falafel, quickly shredding carrots for all kinds of things, with a blender too you can have fun with different soups - I made a lovely spicy pumpkin and coriander over Halloween 
Ice cream maker - you can experiment with all kinds of flavours and types, Italian gelato, sorbets, there are tonnes of recipes online I find ice cream really satisfying to make!

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes totally, and the chemistry between them was really believable, great performances all round </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same for me, Room was my biggest tear jerker in a long time, mainly due to Brie Larson's amazing performance I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second veggie chilli on baked potato or sweet potato and daal or any curry really - paneer pea and spinach is great! I also often make a big batch of falafel that I can have as lunches either in a wrap, pita or as an addition to a salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The disgruntled face of someone disturbed mid-nap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 12:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think it's just one of those things that doesn't seem worth it to me, but who knows, I might have another bash if I'm feeling particularly ambitious one of these days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
