<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9822</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1,500-1,700 calories every day, no exceptions with added exercise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm just going to keep at it and see what happens. If in a week or so it's the same thing I may have to shake some things up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triathlon training = lots of running :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ax!!!!!!!!!!!!!! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the BMR/TDEE listed is the recalculated amount as of today...I may try to just consistently get to the upper end of like 1,700 and see where that leads me. My training is just fine (minimal recovery time/good stamina), just the weight loss stagnation is killing me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yeah I was fully convinced like the food just went thru my throat and immediately out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went completely vegan a couple months ago and let me tell you, my asshole was a nuclear reactor for about a solid two weeks. A body not used to veggies has a tough time adapting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stagnant Weight Loss, Advice/Encouragement Needed! - M/23/228 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 14:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello gang!

So here's the sitch. The past month/month and a half I've been losing weight on average at around 2.9lbs per week which I consider a pretty good clip. However, in the past two weeks it has slowed down significantly. We're talking like 0.4 to no change at all. Basically I'm just wanting advice as to whether this is normal or if there is something wrong with my diet/exercise patterns. 

Diet: I am completely plant based...lots of spinach, tofu, etc. I eat at a strict calorie deficit, my BMR/TDEE are 2,069 and 2,771 respectively and normally I'm eating around 1,500-1,700 calories a day. I avoid all heavily processed/sugary foods and do not drink soda/alcohol at all. Yes, before you even ask, my protein levels are just fine. 

Exercise: I workout six days a week with Sundays as my rest day. Two days a week I work with a trainer for an hour doing body weight/strength training exercises. Two days I'm going Capoeira for an hour/two hours respectively. The other four days I am training for a triathlon so lots of cardio. 

Now keep in mind that this is all extremely strict, I am borderline obsessive over fitness at this point. That's why stepping on the scale and seeing no change is frustrating to say the least. I'm obviously going to keep going but I have a good 30lbs to lose and dammit I need it to happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quit punching your boob and love yourself dammit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 15:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO DAMN IMPORTANT. "This is my life now."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 15:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't probably something you want to hear but I'm just being 100% honest. A lot of us really harp on the exercise/diet aspects of weight loss and completely ignore the emotional/mental aspect which is just as important, if not even more important than the other two. 

I like to think of weight loss in a sequence:
1. Get your mental health in order. Get your mind in the right place. See a doctor, get some help and get your mind aligned with your body. You will have a voice in your head saying "I can't do this" throughout the whole process, our goal is to make sure we are mentally strong enough to silence that voice every time. 
2. Once your mental health is in check, you will find it much easier to stick to a diet and avoid binge eating. Trust me. Been there, done that.
3. Once your mind and diet are good to go, exercise simply to supplement your body along the weight loss journey. 

TL;DR: Get your mental health in check and the rest will fall into place. :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 17:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing quite like it, changes your whole outlook on a wide variety of topics from animal ag, the environment, ethics, etc. I'm sure you can attest to the feeling that your body just feels so much lighter. Love it. Keep up the good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Yup the goal is to be at my goal by June!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you get to the end you'll be thrilled you started today. You got this, ain't no thang chicken wang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
