<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During my junior year of Catholic high school I took AP English and was genuinely excited for a higher level of reading and being introduced to more difficult books. I'm not a religious person, despite going to a Catholic school all the way through high school, so I was incredibly disheartened when we began reading our books for the year and the only symbolism that we were made aware of was religious. A few symbols I remember being brought up constantly was the number seven, the number three alluding to the trinity, and how all sacrifice related back to Jesus' sacrifice for us. I have no problem with a book referencing religious beliefs, such as The Alchemist, but when you're constantly forced to dissect a book for themes, symbolism, etc. and really only discussing the religious themes was frustrating. I'm sure not all private schools are like this but mine certainly was and it turned me off from reading until I graduated and got back into it and haven't stopped since! OP, I definitely agree with you and, although my experience was quite negative in high school, experienced firsthand how someone can steer you in the direction of seeing what they want you to see rather than actually seeing it for yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have about 3 journals full of quotes, new vocabulary words, and final thoughts from every book I've ever read and I love going back to reference them. Whenever someone asks me what I enjoyed about the book, I can always look back at some of those quotes I recorded to refresh my memory on themes and certain conversations that grabbed me. It helps me retain what I've read a little better as well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braid, Kingdom Hearts, and The Witness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ask and The Answer, by Patrick Ness

Thoroughly enjoyed The Knife of Never Letting Go and am excited to continue on with the series this week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know! I haven't read much Vonnegut at all so I was excited to receive this one. Happy reading!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, I'd like to wish everyone on this great thread a Merry Christmas/Happy Holidays! I pretty much only request books for Christmas so I'll list out what I received. Looking forward to another great year of reading! 

The Elements of Style - Strunk and White 

The Sirens of Titan - Kurt Vonnegut

Ask The Dust - John Fante 

A Short History of Nearly Everything - Bill Bryson 

Broken Monsters - Lauren Beukes 

The Collector - John Fowles 

The Curious Incident of The Dog in The Night-Time - Mark Haddon 

The Ultimate Hitchhiker's Guide to The Galaxy - Douglas Adams

Man's Search for Meaning - Viktor Frankl 

People's History of The United States - Howard Zinn 

The Time Traveler's Wife - Audrey Niffenegger

Infinite Jest - David Foster Wallace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it tends to be different from couple to couple but around the one year mark couples begin to transition into the "mature love" part of the relationship. This is usually the time where the love bird phase dies out and general routines begin to form within the relationship. This is typically a rocky point for couples because the excitement starts to descend from what it was during that love bird phase where you want to be with each other all the time. Based on what you said, this seems to be the case both physically and mentally for you. A lot of people realize this and, with open communication, tend to try and work through these things in couples therapy or mixing up the routine to spark a little bit of that excitement. I would definitely recommend keeping open communication with her since she has stated that "you seemed unhappy a long time ago." If you truly do still want to be with her, make sure she knows that and that you're willing to do whatever it takes to see you BOTH return to a state of happiness. That's something that you can discuss together but for me I always found that introducing a little spontaneity every now and then always helped (road trips, weekend getaways, various new activities, etc.). Maybe try some of those things and see if it helps. Either way, I hope it works out for you, OP. I'm rooting for ya.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
