<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject155</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they ever have fresh pistachios? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House to be lit in blue for autism awareness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you realize that people weren't supporting Trump because of a remark about banning Muslims from the United States. People are concerned about security, they're concerned about the terror attacks they see occurring in Europe, and they wanted someone in government who would take the issue seriously rather than brushing it off as offensive to discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Ryan screwed up the first attempt at healthcare reform. There will be more opportunities to work on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump ran on certain issues. He was elected on those issues. Now he's enacting policies on those issues. You can gloat about approval polls all you want but don't look too surprised when he wins re-election for doing the things that elected him the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they were real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary is the epitome of establishment politics. She has a public position and a private position. The public position is what she campaigns on, while the private position (which involves doing what lobbyists and Wall Street pay her to support) is what she governs on. Her campaign rhetoric should be completely ignored because it's fiction. She has no intention of following through on it. They are just empty words to make you like her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burger King Kids Club: Where Are They Now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are certain ideas which obviously aren't acceptable. We can't kill people (abortion included), and we can't discriminate between people based on their class or race or any related factors.

I would propose a synthetic virus, transmitted easily and able to spread across the world. Its purpose would be to reduce fertility. If we directly targeted hormone production we could also eliminate things like anger, which is a primary factor in crime and other antisocial behavior. The world could become a much more peaceful place in addition to lowering the population. There may be detrimental health effects though. It would require a great deal of study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a Google cultist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrats will appreciate any vote they can get. Their party is in the worst shape its been in for nearly a century. They've lost control of every branch of government at a time they were expecting to control them all, voters are Demexiting every day, and more Americans are calling themselves Republicans than Democrats for the first time in years in some surveys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada apparently has a big problem with illegals from the US fleeing there because of a fear of being deported from the US. At first the attitude was to treat them as guests but it quickly seems to be turning into concern at how many there are and how long they intend to stay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I predicted, they don't want the truth to come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an evolutionary trait. The people who stood around chatting in the cold died of hypothermia and only the introverts survived.

Source: am computer scientist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Christianity is very different from Christianity in its native region of the world. They have turned it from socialism into capitalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aircraft touches down late and almost overruns runway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats don't want to hear the truth. They want to keep the conspiracy theory alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some very colorful pigeon breeds, although they live in tropical parts of the world. Perhaps this is a crossbreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number of Americans who feel the country is moving in the right direction is steadily increasing.

http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/other/direction_of_country-902.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julia Child has a rather untraditional way to make moussaka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stepping Out, Melania Trump Honors Women Affected by Bias and Abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selena - I Could Fall In Love [Tejano] : (April 16, 1971 - March 31, 1995) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling she is going to want the nomination again in 2020, and as insane as it might seem to normal people, the DNC will probably give it to her if she wants it. Being president is her life ambition. She won't give up after a mere two devastating rebuffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the first time he got involved in this argument he was exposed as quite the hypocrite, living in a high energy mansion while the Republican president at the time owned a ranch at which almost everything was renewable and recycled.

http://www.snopes.com/politics/bush/house.asp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was in the news for a while in February about various wiretapping orders requested and issued. I believe they had some issues getting permission to spy on American citizens so they narrowed the scope of the inquiry to focus only on foreigners who were in communication with members of the Trump team and get the transcripts that way. The story faded out for a while, although this week it was discussed some more on MSNBC.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DdTGnpHR_sk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would cost tens of thousands of dollars in this country. I need to be careful with my bike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Obama administration was spying on Trump and his transition team before they moved into the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have quite good indication that it's related to hormone exposure (and perhaps also hormone mimickers) during gestation. There's a certain percentage of natural occurrence, which is why it has always been recorded in history, and in my opinion there is another percentage of unnatural occurrence caused by modern chemicals, which is why it seems to be more prevalent recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politics? Notice how one faulty study on the effects of sodium was enough to get every restaurant and manufacturer to reduce salt in their products, and yet hundreds of legitimate studies on the health damage of sugar does nothing. I guess there isn't a powerful salt lobby, but there is a powerful corn lobby which wants to put corn syrup in literally everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naturally it would require a fundamental change in perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think a person volunteering for a procedure is more ethical than forcing an unwilling animal to partake in one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxation as a percentage is an idea that people have been conditioned to accept. It does not have to be that way and it is unfair to those who earn more. Why should they pay more money to the government than other people? They are not receiving more in return. If anything they're receiving less in return since they are less reliant on the government's help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is treated more or less the same by the government and should be charged more or less the same in taxes. If the average tax burden is $9118, that is what Trump and other rich people should pay. They are equal citizens and should be charged an equal tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've seen his tax return. He paid ~ $40 million tax in one year, 5,000 times more than an average American pays. He pays much, much more than his fair share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House panel passes bill to audit the Fed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic National Committee Asks Its Entire Staff To Resign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Schumer 'launched into a tirade at former Democrat power-broker's wife because she voted TRUMP' and repeatedly called the president a 'liar' over dinner at an upscale New York restaurant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lauren Daigle - Come Alive (Dry Bones) [CCM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UN monitored Saddam destroying the Iraqi weapons and remained in the country to ensure no other stockpiles were hidden, before being chased out by US bombers without a chance to complete the job. I don't know how the media in the US framed it but in Europe we were shocked at the way the UN inspectors were treated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't seem like a logical concern to me. If we assume that a divine being created life, and life is an incredible experience, why shouldn't that same divine being be capable of creating an eternity which is also an incredible experience? With the ability to create and control anything, such a reality is possible. The idea that one could become bored in eternity implies that there is a flaw in the design of the experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to imagine all of the Democrats voting against him when so many of them have praised him in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you could save a lot of money by growing tobacco at home. I gather it's a fairly easygoing plant, being in the same family as tomato and chili. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muslims believe they are the true chosen people due to Ishmael being the firstborn. They do not have positive feelings toward Isaac's descendants, the Jews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie was a hardcore Russia fan when it was the Soviet Union. He's pretty socialist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see them running the country. Do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm skeptical about the article. I grew up in Europe where almost all washers are front loading. They take two hours or longer to wash clothes and are only moderately successful. The top loaders here seem to work better and the cycle is only 20 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats lost the election, badly, and instead of admitting their flaws  and working to improve their appeal to the voters they blamed Russia for causing them to lose, and then accused the Trump administration of working with Russia. Despite months of accusations, no evidence to support the claim has ever been presented. That pretty much sums it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In both cases it's jealously. People resent the skinny because they don't have the discipline to be skinny, and they resent the fat because they wish they could eat whatever they like and have so much self esteem that they didn't care about being negatively judged by others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact ICE. It might be a regular hangout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shotgun mics people use for vlogging, youtubing, and general non-professional videography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Organic" is another one. Many things are inherently organic. The factory just puts them into two different packages and doubles the price on one of them. It's even worse here in the United States where there is no clear definition of what organic means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rode microphones. They cost like $150. Takstar makes a comparable microphone for $30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America survives because of immigration. The brainpower that keeps the country functioning comes from people who moved here from places which have a decent education system. Education would seem to be one of the most critical areas to fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No surprise there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the real reason. No one wants to watch someone else eat. They need to have their own food to occupy their senses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have to. There's nothing to stop you paying the ~ $50 fee to be married, using a free venue, and having all the guests pay for their own clothes and food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look at the numbers, Republicans control most states. The map itself is almost all red with just a few pockets of blue. I'm sure the GOP does have the numbers to accomplish something like that. Not a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the_donald is Reddit's most active community. Any site that relies on advertising or investment cannot alienate its base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 009 Sound System - Dreamscape

It's the song you hear in about 50% of youtube videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has spent [most of his life](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GPGLQmevlHE) as a Republican but did take a break for a few years during the Bush presidency, as did many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't a secret Democrat. He's just very moderate for a Republican, which is evidently just what the voters were looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasps are similar to bees. They pollinate plants. They also attack the pests that harm plants. Paper wasps in particular are pretty docile. I have several wasp nests on the outside of my house and they don't bother us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I recall he very much regrets that decision and hasn't been able to pick up his acting career where he left off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems reasonable. If you're absolutely confident that there is nothing after death, why would you fear it? You won't experience pain or regret or feel separated from the living. You would experience nothing, no consciousness at all. There's nothing to fear about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not this they. Ryan is hopefully finished now. He can be disposed of and a proper healthcare bill that serves the American people can be drafted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 hours? You should have a degree in the subject you're teaching. Four or eight years of study or practical experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Healthcare is like schooling. An average quality level should be provided to every citizen for free by the government. Those who want a higher quality can pay to attend a private institution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has a relative in politics who can pull the strings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the Republicans? The polls gave Hillary a 98% chance of winning the election. That's the person you would target with blackmail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clothes dried outside should smell good. Maybe the washing machine is full of bacteria and needs to be sanitized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a good step but the hiring process would also need to be much stricter. You cannot have the current teachers who know nothing about the subjects they are teaching, couldn't care less about the success of their students, and sometimes even resent the students and make inappropriate comments like 'if you want to hang yourself I'll give you the rope'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare footage of extinct animals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RyanCare probably won't pass. It's a terrible piece of legislation. Healthcare will have to wait a few months until the issue can be revisited and those of us who are priced out of buying healthcare will have to wait longer before we can have medical care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem isn't so much the allegation, which could be kept secret, but the newspapers that broadcast it before any trial has taken place. Courts should perhaps order such allegations to be kept secret until guilt is proved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does cancer seem to occur in tissue which was inflamed, such as burned skin, agitated lungs, and irritated colon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The implication is Nixonian spying on the opposition party during an election. The speculation began when Hillary Clinton made comments referring to intelligence or classified information that she could not have had access to as a private citizen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Chombo - Chacarron Macarron [Reggaeton] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does this have to do with Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a resident does not guarantee the same security as being a citizen. The government can kick you out at any time for any reason, or no reason at all. If you leave the country you can be denied re-entry for any reason. Of course, becoming a citizen has impacts on you if you try to live anywhere else in the world, such as taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why pay 375k for a glorified apartment when you can get a real house with a yard and privacy for not much more than 100k in Houston? I'm not familiar with mortgages but assuming a 30 year loan, that would be about $300 per month plus whatever the interest rate is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really like Chloe either. She seemed like an extrovert party girl with a lot of problems, not the kind of person who would normally be friends with a shy person like Max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can make a much better Chicago style pizza quite easily. Mix a dough with high yeast content and high oil content. Let it proof for a couple of hours, then roll it out and press it into a greased 9" cake pan. Add the cheese and the cooked fillings, then roll out a top layer of dough. Cover it with crushed tomatoes and spices and some Parmigiano cheese and bake for about 25 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats don't seem to realize that they have no power in the government. The voters took it away from them in the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blogging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This confirms what we've known all along. Foreigners were "targetted" in order to wiretap US citizens. The only incidental thing here is the voices of the foreigners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bots make up the majority of traffic on those social networking sites. Investors are being duped. It might pop like the dotcom bubble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steam Trek - The Moving Picture (HD) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Things Are Made - CDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skatt Bros. - Walk The Night [Disco] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: These fabulous shoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian plane uses entire runway length to get airborne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nazia Hassan - Ankhien Milane Wale (Remix) [Pakistani Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, and even if you did you still need to change the policies in nearly 200 individual countries, most of which are several decades behind us in development and have barely begun their assault on the environment. It's unsolvable for the simple reason that too many of one species exist in the ecosystem. The inevitable consequence is environment collapse and mass fatalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Houston we have ranch style houses with fenced yards very close to downtown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so many people are paying for internet service within range of each other, why not cut it down to one or two accounts and split the cost between everyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left has shown complete intolerance for anyone else. They are focused on dividing the country, which is beginning to fracture. I don't see any point in showing them fair treatment any longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a simple vote. It's been done several times before when one party has a congressional majority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a television is rich in much of the world. Being able to eat at McDonald's is rich in much of the world. Having hot water is a luxury. Indoor plumbing, a microwave, a car. These are all luxuries that most of the world can only dream of. Americans are rich, no matter their place in American society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do not realize that half the world, billions of people, barely has access to food and potable water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poverty in America is comparable to being rich in many other nations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't expect people to change their lifestyle. All we can do is reduce the number of people on the planet to lessen their impact. The fewer people there are the less land is required to sustain them, the fewer forests, habitats and animals are destroyed, the less pollution is generated, the healthier the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress should vote to add a few more seats to the court and stuff it full of conservative judges who will veto anything the Democrats try to do for the next half century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has seven years to go until he's no longer eligible to run again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's no secret that Obama was close with Putin or that the Clintons are close with Russia. Why should they suddenly do a 180? It's all an act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there were a secret relationship between President Trump and Putin he would have no problem insulting Putin because they'd both know it was just theater to fool people. Kinda like how the Democrats act toward Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2020: This time it's personal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alligators are part of the appeal of the park. They're just big lizards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collaboration between parties is how the government of the people is supposed to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 years before it was popular. A true hipster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The metal strip story is disputed. Eyewitnesses claim the fire started before that point was reached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 09:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat eight 300 calorie hamburgers and people would think you're nuts. Eat eight 300 calorie slices of pizza and people would think it's the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I joined Reddit most of the posts were pictures of animals with funny captions and other funny content. Now it's almost all political. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Israel is the Jewish homeland, the only Jewish nation, surrounded by a dozen Nazi countries that want to exterminate the Jews. How can anyone side against Israel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use it to make sandwiches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The federal military budget is the enormous white elephant in the room. It's obese. That is where so much of the tax money is going. If that budget could be cut by half we could implement healthcare and still lower taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 09:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same experience a couple of years ago. I bought a coupon for a local pizza place. The list of addresses clearly mentioned the one in my neighborhood. When I tried to use it a couple of months later I was told it wasn't accepted at that location, and when I checked the Groupon page again the list of addresses had completely changed. Only a handful were still shown and they were way over on the other side of Houston. I contacted Groupon and they refused to give a refund, assuring me that one of those restaurants an hour away from me would be happy to give the discount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. EPA awards $100 million to upgrade Flint water system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or paid to be careless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a strong supporter of the concept of net neutrality, yet we spent 25 years or longer without it in the law and our internet service didn't suffer. It feels more like a hypothetical boogeyman than a literal one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crystal Bernard - Music Box [Adult Contemporary] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The oldest millennial in the world is currently 35 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're selling a service which previously did not exist in the market area, you're performing a good deed. People now have a choice they did not have before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a major business opportunity in providing meals to the elderly. You'd be surprised by how many of them are wealthy, and they are willing to pay handsomely for gourmet food to be delivered to their room and set up for them. Much profit can be made and you get to perform a good deed in the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a harsh penalty for companies which fire a worker in order to hire a foreigner based on the premise that 'no American can be found to perform the job' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Amazon Smile was always 5%. I can't believe it's so low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a matter of choice. People choose the health for their body. It's unwise not to be vaccinated but it shouldn't be forced upon anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cybill Shepherd - Talk Memphis to Me [Jazz] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully expect Hillary to reappear in 2020 and for the DNC to ensure she gets the nomination if she throws her hat in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats became more liberal, and Republicans hold the views that the Democrats were embracing 20 years ago but now consider to be bigoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was difficult enough for a billionaire celebrity to beat the system. They turned the media storm up to 11 to try to make him lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several years ago we learned that tv manufacturers are listening 24/7 to audio picked up by the microphone, transcribing words to text, and passing those logs on to advertisers, who would target the customer with ads in various places, not necessarily on the tv. It's reasonable to assume that the same technology has been in use for at least as long by the CIA to record everything you said within range of a microphone. It doesn't really matter for what purpose such a databank exist, it is the principle of privacy being invaded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
