<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9140</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize I can't "undo" the removed post, but a real life restaurant removing a ban for a fictional character feels pretty oniony to me lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alexei Navalny: Russian Court Convicts Main Opposition Leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chili's lifts lifetime ban on 'Office's' Pam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But without multiplayer, how will a 12 year old question my sexual persuasion, race, or mother's parentage when I make mistake?

If I don't called out, then I'll never learn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm both horrified and better educated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiffany CEO Steps Down - Points To "Post Election Traffic Disruption" and Proximity to Trump Tower As Causes For Disappointing Sales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Brady suspects Super Bowl jersey was stolen after game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to say what we're all thinking: this looks like a bad PS battle lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please say you want them to secede!

Please be that fucking stupid!

On a side note, I love how conservatives are all for state's rights except in liberal states like CA and NY.

DAY 1:
Nebraska, WV, TX...you go ahead and limit the rights of your citizens however you see fit.

DAY 2:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN THOSE COMMIE LIBERALS WANT TO GIVE EVERYONE EQUAL RIGHTS REGARDLESS OF AGE, RACE OR SEXUAL PERSUASION! FUCK THEM! THEY MUST BE SUBJUGATED!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, nothing like a president that says "I'm not responsible if I don't get my way all the time"

I feel like there's a word for leaders that require absolute loyalty and unchecked power. What's that called again? A dictatorship? Am I remembering 5th grade social studies correctly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is why no one will remember your name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only respond to this with the link below lmao:

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=7Dt5Nf7ct5c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO re: ep 2.

I agree with you re: Jedi portrayal but as I said to someone else, knowing Liam can do this left me wanting a lot more.

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=vOoWpTxKJGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that Liam Neeson was bad, but he was not top tier Neeson. I know it's very unfair to compare the material to Schindler's List, but knowing that he can turn in a performance like the one at the link below, I know he didn't give his all.

I'm sure that's the script more than anything, but I had higher hopes.

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=vOoWpTxKJGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Resident Evil 4 chainsaw decapitation is the last time a video game actually shocked me/scared me/caught me off guard.

The first was Resident Evil when the dogs jump through the glass.

The series has gotten a little silly (Chinese spider gangsters I'm looking at you in RE: 6) but the old ones are *classics* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between Liam Neeson's and Natalie Portman's underwhelming performances, and this, it's hard to think about what *might* have been.

I feel the worst for Ewan MacGregor because he brought his A game, esp. in Ep. III.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea if this comment is serious but thank you for the nightmare fuel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is Fox Allowed To Air The Super Bowl When They Don't Even Broadcast Sports In 1080p HD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO there's a shocker!

An uninformed person on the internet is presented with evidence that contradicts their point of view; however, rather than read it, they ignore it and keep talking.

Congratulations on sucking at life!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy killer. Let's start with your last comment. I have no problem with anyone from foreign countries, including Ivana. That said.

It may interest you to know that Ivana Trump had a previous marriage of convenience to get out of her Communist homeland (link 1).

Second, it may interest you to know, that Melania Trump was most likely an illegal immigrant to US in her early modeling days (link 2).

Third, given Trump's blatant issues with immigrants from other countries, unlike myself, I'm forced to mock the inherent hypocrisy of his fondness for immigrant brides from Eastern Europe when juxtaposed with his flagrantly anti immigrant policies.  The most ridiculous way to do so is claim they are mail order brides (as Eastern Europe is known for that since the fall of communism). (Link 3). It is not an attack on his wives, but an attack on him and his policies.

Now that I've explained my joke, a typical no-no, **back the fuck off.**


http://www.cnn.com/2015/08/24/politics/donald-trump-immigrant-wives/

https://apnews.com/37dc7aef0ce44077930b7436be7bfd0d

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mail-order_bride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Stephen King briefly considered a Pet Sematary/IT crossover, he dismissed the idea as "too silly" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part is the purple spoon fighting for equality from the bottom of the colored spoons box.

Fight on purple spoon! The struggle is real! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost it at the caption.  All I hear is DMX in my head shouting.

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=3mvBk8N_YTk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between this video, and the fact he's granted more wishes to Make-A-Wish kids than anyone else, I'm very impressed with John Cena.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we sure that's not the receipt?

Do you get a receipt when you receive your mail order bride? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a chef but father is and I worked as a caterer (changed mind about culinary school at least minute)

This may sound stupid, but use the appropriate heat on the stovetop burners. So many people burn/over cook food for this simple reason.

If the recipe calls for medium heat, then use medium heat. Cooking your omelets with the dial turned to 10 isn't the answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing this puppy made me instantly think of when Gizmo gets wet in Gremlins

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=26rtbuybXss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's got a wicked case of toxoplasmosis coming their way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! WE NEED A BAN OF TODDLERS ON PLANES!

SOMEONE MAKE THIS HAPPEN, PLEAAAASSEEE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire idea of Holocaust Denial is based on the logical fallacy of "shifting the burden of proof".

If I say Mother Theresa was secretly a crackhead, international arms dealer, and you say she wasn't, then the burden of proof isn't on *you*

By entertaining the ideas of morons we falsely equate all ideas as being equal. Trying to prove a Holocaust denier wrong takes the position that their idea needs to be proved wrong, and it doesn't.

Sometimes we need a little less diplomacy and a little more Buzz Aldrin.

http://nerdist.com/lets-all-remember-the-time-buzz-aldrin-punched-a-conspiracy-theorist-in-the-face/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have officially found the real Ned Flanders.

This guy is probably awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I realized that the the age bracket I pick on WebMD has more years above it than below it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eddie Murphy as Okie Dokie in Beverly Hills Cop 3.

The whole exchange with the little kid, but when the kid punches him and Murphy says "Oh you little motherfucker I'm gonna kick your ass", I lose it every time!

I started laughing writing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knows what he did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this what spy craft looks like under the Trump administration?

I know Snowden sold our secrets to Russia and China but surely the NSA can do better than Ask Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweetbreads, foie gras, pretty much any offal.

I'm normally a very picky eater but for some reason I real like offal...it's *really* fucking strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I Had A Million Dollars by Barenaked Ladies

The lyrics sound utterly ridiculous and sappy as the singer lists all of the outrageous things he'd buy his love.

BUT, the end of every verse before the chorus is the line "If I had a million dollars, I'd buy your love."

The singer has someone they love, but that love is unrequited (and they believe only by being rich will things change, hence the final line of the song)

It sounds like such an upbeat song but is one of the most depressing songs I know (That's my interpretation anyway) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sandpaper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't move in with anyone you haven't dated for at least a year

Don't marry anyone you haven't lived with for at least a year

Don't have kids for at least 2 years after marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exaggerated pain.

My German shepherd stepped on a nail when she was a puppy (after digging through my carpet.) She made that high pitched yelp that dogs in pain make, which of course made me freak out (especially when I saw the aftermath).

Since then, any time she experiences even mild discomfort she will yelp the same way because she knows I react.

Scratches *herself* too hard - yelp

Make her stop pulling on leash in park - yelp

Brush against her when opening door - yelp

It's crazy!

TL;DR : My German shepherd is emotionally manipulative! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A ringing phone causing you to be disconnected from the internet.

*GODDAMMIT MOM YOU KNOW I'M USING AMERICA ONLINE!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. Misunderstood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I don't know much about the collective in general, just that a number of them were obviously talented.

EDIT: Also, since you're saying they were doxxed, Are you implying they were betrayed by their own? 

(That's an honest question.  If so, then that is crazy fucked up!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're also lucky enough to have an AMAZING camera! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG not a fucking shocker.

For anyone who wants an excellent understanding of the problems with the Olympics, find a way to watch the HBO sports special below.

There's a reason only corrupt countries are rushing to host them nowadays.

https://www.google.com/amp/wgntv.com/2016/08/08/hbo-real-sports-examines-misused-money-and-influence-at-the-olympics/amp/?client=safari </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharing may be caring...but I did buy two beds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pa. abortion bill to receive speedy vote - but no public input </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest: Sanders says Trump may be right about his voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lady Libertys flame extinguished on New Yorker cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Halts Financial Industry Rule Requiring Investment Advisers To Work In Best Interests Of Their Clients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And your word for "Aunt" is: ciocia

It is pronounced the same as the word for "pussy" in Spanish: chocha

Maybe we shouldn't lean on Poland for spelling and pronunciations rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most impressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Lost continent' found under Mauritius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Treasury Rolls Back FSB Sanctions. 24 Hours Later UN Ambassador Haley Condemns Russia on Ukraine. Steve Bannon loves Sun Tzu's "The Art of War." ...keep your enemies confused, indeed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part of this map is it looks like you are skipping western Penn. by taking an underwater detour through Lake Erie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mint worker convicted of smuggling gold in rectum sentenced to 30 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mario looks like the guy who sells Persian rugs at my local mall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that Singapore announces caning like concert events!

It's almost as if they want the offender's country of origin to plead for mercy, just so they can be like:

*Nah, we're definitely caning his ass* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't this just be called Ninja? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming Soon, sideline reporters being accosted by drunk NFL legends

*Can I get a kiss?*

http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x2iwp0_joe-namath-wants-to-kiss-espn-s-suz_fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conway makes up Bowling Greene Massacre to justify Trump travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY FUCKING SHIT!

That's exactly what my dachshund did when she hurt her spine. How IN THE FUCK did that dog learn to fake a spinal injury!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Amazing Bo Jackson Wall Run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For many years it was the amazing Bo Jackson wall run.

A few years ago someone finally posted it to YouTube.

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Lk3l_L-VJ3w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my knee jerk reaction!

Like, uh, the fake news problem may be much more complex than originally thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Survey of Major News Source Credibility, Farcical Newspaper "The Onion" Viewed As More Credible Than Alt-Right News Outlet "Info Wars" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groundhog weather predictions were the original alternative facts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrested Russian FSB Agents Allegedly Passed Information to CIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a hint: SHE'S A WITCH! BURN HER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite shower thoughts ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans vote to suspend committee rules, advance Mnuchin, Price nominations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fans are fickle lol.  It's his music not theirs!

That said I love Tisto (both now and trance...I just happen to prefer trance as a genre) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same reason Tisto stopped producing only trance: he knew how to make money and stay relevant

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once scientists were able to extract semen from the slumbering elder god Cthulhu, genetic engineering got a lot more interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all fun and games until you try a "Vulcan Mind Meld" without a condom.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A link to the past and super Mario 2?!

Yeah, your weekend is shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like if your local truck stop posted the newspaper on the bathroom walls each morning.

Some people read the news and leave

Some people read the news and write comments on the wall

Some people don't read anything and just write "I fucked Tom's sister and her number is X"

...and some people are there to take a horrid shit  that makes future guests miserable

Yep...that's Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a special place in hell for whoever decided "Bae" needed to be a thing.

Runner up goes to: the inventor of "throw shade" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Jimmy Fallon has been reading my dream journal...again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Priest Tells Anti-Trump Protesters to Commit Suicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rogue group of staffers is tweeting secrets from the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Priest Tells Anti-Trump Protesters to Commit Suicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Parent Trap.

Upon realizing the monstrous plans their separated twins put in place, the parents have their children arrested for conspiracy and extortion.

The kids end up in the same prison as Oz.

The parents sell their story to lifetime and live out their days as correspondents/contributors to nightly news programs about the dangers of having children.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carl Grimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump Smashes Record for Getting Majority of Americans to Disapprove of Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't put the judgment down because your inability to spell check your poem hurts my brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries where Trump does business not hit by new travel restrictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your date is Canadian, asking for their thoughts on Qubcois autonomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chernobyl...my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hollywood's obsession with patting itself on the back at awards shows e.g. La La Land and the Artist.

Neither are very good but they're about the "magic of Hollywood." Better start handing out statues! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO we'll see how long the Gideons stand for that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In  other news, Americans collectively shrugged and said, "I don't think any of us were planning to visit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Starbucks in Halloweentown has really upped their game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL It's possible to beat Snake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call bullshit...extremely unlikely yolk stays in tact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buying anything endorsed by a Kardashian or Jenner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emmett Tills accuser admits: It was all a lie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These 6 charts and a cheeky tweet detail U.S. trade relationship with Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOCKED UP, FIGHTING BACK | More than a dozen female inmates accused an officer of abuse. Documents reveal why N.J. fired him. He was never charged with a crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Strategist Stephen Bannon Says Media Should Keep Its Mouth Shut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kaspersky Labs top investigator reportedly arrested in treason probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why American Airlines Is Getting Rid of Seat-back Screens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump pressured Park Service to find proof for his claims about inauguration crowd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Busted: Feds charge cashier with stealing $9.5 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be my favorite Reddit thread ever.

Learned a little Chinese and a llama meme! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pennsylvania priest sorry for sharing 'fat women' meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's crying because his balls are so heavy from being more of a man than everyone admiring him.

(That's not a wiseass comment. He's awesome. That's all. End of story) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposals to Replace the Affordable Care Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rape of 16-year-old girl reported at KUs McCarthy Hall, home of basketball team and other male students / LJWorld.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not tell untrustworthy Redditors my plans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The end of The Notebook when they forcibly restrain the old woman and the old man starts crying.

*oh how I wish I was kidding* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book, "What's The Matter With Kansas" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That they are probably hungry at that very moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ability to swim in a pool of money like Scrooge McDuck.

Let's be honest. Wish #1 was the pool full of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The script that reveals the original intended ending for A.L.F.

...and the actual Gordon Shumway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: I will send in the Feds if Chicago doesnt fix crime problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HUFFPOLLSTER: The First Ratings For Donald Trump's Presidency Are Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump admin orders EPA contract freeze and media blackout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump tells Detroit auto CEOs environmental regulations are 'out of control' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Is Neil M. Gorsuch? Judge Emerges As Trump's Top Supreme Court Pick For Antonin Scalias Vacant Seat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Promotes Neutrality Opponent Ajit Pai to Lead FCC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kenney signs nation's first city pay equity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New evidence: Was DB Cooper a Boeing employee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy went missing for a few days

We thought he was just young and irresponsible.

His mom called to say he was hospitalized after falling into a brief coma.

...so needless to say, we felt like assholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Machines Could Replace Humans - And Where They Can't (Yet) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK leader admits she knew British nuclear missile flew towards United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jersey GOP official: Will women's march end 'in time for them to cook dinner?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump signs order withdrawing from TPP, reinstate 'Mexico City policy' on abortion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
