<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 09:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're paranoid now but be patient. Just try to go about your life normally because it happens when you're not thinking about it. Your darling will come along, and it's going to happen, promise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 15:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your family is the BEST family I plan on being that family when I have one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 11:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, that means I'm probably late on taking my meds, so I should do that. Or I should have a cigarette or smoke some weed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 11:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this was real I'd say the kid was a born entrepreneur. But, fat chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 10:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word to that from Fairfield County. Small economies like these need the boost so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 00:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks ridiculously photoshopped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 18:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather was adopted by white people because his birth mother, a Cherokee, passed giving birth to him. He was put in a boarding school. He became an alcoholic sometime in my mother's early childhood, and when she was in college, he and my grandmother split. He finished off doing great after he settled on the rez, where alcohol is prohibited, for damn good reasons. 

I now live with an alcoholic mother who is falling apart at the seams after  living through a lot of shit, especially because of how things were left for her native elders. She's done a lot of work for the tribe and wall street in her life.

So, does it matter? Think about how the dots connect. At the end of the day, nobody really knows the half of it when they think they do. This is why I continually give a shit about other people, no matter who they are or when their kind suffered, because in a way pain is like energy, it can't be created or destroyed.

And white people suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 22:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's solely your opinion if you think it's less important than other things.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 03:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 03:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. Everyone's different, no need to jump in with your two cents. Point is, I had a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 03:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because more effort could be put into working with those tribes they have done wrong. Building stronger relationships with leaders worldwide is what should be done, because "reservations" still aren't really ideal, and never were. 

If I saw more government subsidies go towards tribes for compensation generally, it would make up for past mistakes, awful laws made, loss of land to settlers AND allow tribal leaders to decide how the money is distributed. Which would be used for spending most likely on funding for education, infrastructure, etc.

Also, you are just so wrong about the last part. I'm a Virgo, buddy. Sincerity is like white out on paper to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 03:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People that represent a certain position or hold a certain title know they're entailed to those origins and basic roots. Although the people responsible are not around anymore, there is a positional necessity to do good in their honor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 03:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North Carolina! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Cherokee.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU

Also a formal apology indicates you can handle responsibility, and if you cannot own up for a crime or wrongdoing, then that is clearly irresponsible and childish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were a member of the tribe you would want an apology. Something inside you would remain forever angry at people in our past. 

I have relatives that survived the Trail of Tears, that hid in the mountains during that event. It was a long time ago, yet it's not a subject I can easily brush off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please become a public speaker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 16:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depression makes us really incapable of what we used to be capable of. Believe me. This work overshadows completely what actually defines you. Fuck a grade. 

It's not you, it's that society is really really bad at finding out how to deal with us, so they toss us into the same mix of other kids without mental health issues who can move at faster paces, do more work etc. This isn't what the world should be doing, if you ask me. I think universities should have separate, slower-paced programs. Not dumbed down, however, because we are intelligent. 

Depression should be an excuse for someone to leave their life and just go far away, from needing a degree or a job and just go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 14:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you live under a rock? You must have gotten a GED and probably still live with your mom. Pick up a book about psychology. And read it.

And I am quittin liberal arts fuck that place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 07:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHINING? Ignorant jerks like you are the reason the mentally ill don't have support in this damn country. Everyone says, "Get over it, stop being sad." 

Our brains don't work that way smart one. Telling a penguin to fly... 

Whining won't stop, I'll speak up for my community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 21:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus. How soon would you have been able to take an interview about your mass murdering son that you loved at one point, smartass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 21:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly the overwhelmingness from the work loads he had and the obvious difficulties with the asperger's and whatever else was underlying could have been fixed by BETTER SCHOOL SYSTEMS, and not special schools for the actually retarded but PROGRAMS for those with other mental disabilities who work slower/with a lesser load.

I have Clinical Depression, have for two years, and have struggled with trying to find confidence in a liberal arts college with extremely difficult work loads not meant for someone like me. I CANNOT handle the same work loads as someone who is not mentally ill.

I am just waiting for the rest of the country to see that. So was Adam. I just know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 00:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.funnyordie.com/videos/1a13cc888d/drinking-out-of-cups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 00:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nbcconnecticut.com/news/local/Substitute-Teacher-Accused-of-Lewd-Act-in-School-247293241.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Westhill High School substitute charged with masturbating in school hallway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 22:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 18:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarcasm, trouty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 18:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing that people can do is raise the media's attention towards her issue. Those companies never like negative media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 11:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwwwwwwww she loooves you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a problem. What are we, barbarians? Ancient Egyptians? Shit. This is real life. If you don't like what your kids watch, pay attention and switch the channel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a black cat named Merlin. He needs one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 12:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried two so far and one was generic, that one made me crampy, emotional/moody, fatigued, and hungry all the time (all I could think of rn). The first one was great but my insurance stopped paying for it. 

I'm switching again so that hopefully I find one that doesn't make me think I'm pregnant or dying all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 11:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He puts my thoughts into words so perfectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 18:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speculating from the comments, Reddit 3's natural redheads. Yay me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 17:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are already doing this in our skies. If what I'm told is true, it's those white streaks in the skies that you see on occasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 17:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys have a heart of gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 00:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Smith, the price of recreational pot has averaged $400 per ounce since the state allowed fully legal sales on January 1. In comparison, medicinal marijuana has averaged $200 since that time.

Does anyone else seem to furrow their eyebrows like this T_T when they read this? A big gap draws more eyes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
