<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you claim to know that Smith was a prophet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 16:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel I have a pretty good handle on it, given your post/comment history.

Will you tell me your beliefs, explicitly? What do you claim to know or have faith in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 15:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about the testimonies given during Fast Sunday?

Yet I see many who have ascribed to the *LDS Church* proudly touting that they now "know" that Smith was a prophet, and "know" the BoM is true  or whatever the 'doctrine' is. It's rather foolish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it literally contributed nothing, which is why you're getting shit on with downvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 18:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additionally, this was the Great RECESSION, not the Great Depression (thank heavens)

Right, exactly. If there was a true and living prophet in the years immediately before the Great Depression, wouldn't they have issued similar prophetic warnings, much as you think they did prior to 2008?

Are you aware of the Texas Sharpshooter Fallacy?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 17:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any evidence of similar "prophecies" prior to the Great Depression? Correlation doesn't imply causation, a broken clock, etc. etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 12:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read the thread. According to legal precedent, it **is** they're job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Push pull legs, push pull legs, rest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 20:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /u/gzcl, sorry to bother you on such an old post.

I was doing phrak's greyskull variant, but then dicked around with the program, and haven't made real progress. GZCL or GZCLP sound ideal, but I don't know which is right for me, and I'd like your opinion on the matter.

I'm 6'4", 190lbs. I can bench 205x3, squat 245x3, deadlift 295x3. I haven't made an real progress in a month or two, and feel bad about that.

I can go to the gym 3-4 days a week (MT, HF or MWF). Your thoughts would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 16:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the app? Dropdown menu, settings, auto-add weight, then you can toggle them off or change the weight increments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 12:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, where is any of this actually told to a member? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 00:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To leave the church, all you have to do is write a letter to your bishop saying you want your name off the records of the church.

Per Handbook 1, this isn't entirely correct.

The church has no policy to contact you again, harass you, or anything of the sort.

"If members of the stake presidency determine that the bishop has followed established procedures, they ask him to **send the member a letter** stating that his or her name is being removed... as requested."

Oh, and the handbook also illegally makes the person wait 30 days.

"Removal can be rescinded only if the member sends the stake president a written request for the recision within 30 days... If a member demands that his or her name be removed immediately, the 30-day waiting period may be eliminated."

_______________________________________________________

If someone who has "been in multiple bishoprics for many years" doesn't know these hoops or form letters, why should we expect Joe Q. Member to know the contents of a hidden, secret handbook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 20:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I don't like or trust my manager to do things correctly, I'll go over their head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 20:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this person sent the letter to the wrong people. It just has to go to your bishop.

How would the person know that that's the church's "policy"? Anyways, this letter is technically illegal. Once the church receives notice of a resignation, it's **done**. There's no special hoops to jump through. There is legal precedent, see [here](http://www.mormonnomore.com/legal-precedent).

Further, have the congregants been taught this rule they have to jump through? Has this been printed in the Ensign?

Anything else is just bad choices by their local leaders, not a church policy.

Again, so why is the church so damn bad at training their leaders? Because as /u/choose_the_rice points out, it's an endemic problem. It happens to *a lot* of people.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 18:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I guess [this official church letterhead](http://imgur.com/VsAMnoX) is just a fluke, then?

I sure wish TSCC would be explicit in their training to their local leaders. Then these [+116](https://www.google.com/search?q=%22this+is+an+ecclesiastical+matter%22+site%3Areddit.com%2Fr%2Fexmormon sourceid=ie7 rls=com.microsoft:en-US:IE-Address ie= oe= gws_rd=ssl) people wouldn't have issues.

Maybe they could sneak it into the manual for someone to leak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 16:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't like getting called out on my bullshit, either. I feel you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 16:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nor did I give you my personal opinion

Earlier...

damn that's cold

Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 23:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give the lady a simple answer next time.

Right, because joining a totalizing religion like Mormonism is "simple." More information is always helpful. Also, it's a reddit comment. It's one thing if they were face to face and he rattled it all off, but she can take her time and take it chunks at a time. 

links strewn about (ever heard of a hyperlink, bro?).

They **are** hyperlinks. Can you click on it and it takes you to content? Then it's a hyperlink. If you're going to be pedantic, then for God's sake be fucking accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was forced to go to these by my parents and ecclesiastical leadership ~10 years ago. AMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 15:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I've been wrong about that my whole life! Thanks for pointing it out, I appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 21:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister has spina bifida, microcephaly, and mild cognitive impairment. She is Mormon, and recently went through the temple. She will probably never marry. Is she going to be a servant for eternity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 20:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair interpretation, thank you.

What about people who are Mormon, are endowed, are members in good standing, but never marry? They have knowledge of the covenant, but never used it. Would you say they have accepted, rejected, or are in the same limbo as people who never heard the gospel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are you trying to force a specific interpretation?

Of course not, but wouldn't you agree that a direct reading of the text is a good starting point to understanding the text?

It would be contrary to God's mercy to deny blessings to those who never learned it or had an opportunity to receive it.

But that's how the verses seem to read. If they are not married "by my word," the marriage is not in force when they are dead. Therefore, they are angels forever. Therefore, doing proxy sealings does nothing, because they are angels forever. That is the direct and clearest reading, and I am wondering if there is any clarification from other scriptures or prophets. Can I clarify my question further at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 20:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But according to a direct reading of the verses, they're dead, and thus cannot even accept the covenant to begin with.

Is everyone before the 1830s servants forever? Is every nonmormon post-1830s servants to gods? Because they're *dead*, and thus cannot, according to a straight reading, even be sealed in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 19:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that JS just made up the D C, right?

I'm well aware, thank you. I'm an agnostic atheist. I was just curious as to whether or not the apparent contradiction has been addressed by anyone in the Mormon authority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 19:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that was my understanding too. That logic is also used to defend proxy baptism of the Holocaust victims, for example.

But, v16 explicitly states that those who are out of the world cannot marry, because they were not married "by me nor my word," which implies Temple sealing. So, why do proxy sealings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 19:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, literally every married couple before the priesthood was restored? Why do proxy sealings, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 19:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in detail, but I do remember the name from the CES letter. I'll look into it, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 17:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did initially, yes. But I also knew the doctrine that Earth is the spirit paradise/prison, which would mean they're still "in the world." I just didn't connect the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 17:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I breath water at the gym. At least 2 L each session, the weights make me thirsty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 16:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting interpretation, because v15 says "when they are dead, and when the are out of the world." "Out of the world" seems, at first blush, to mean dead. Young's teaching seems to find the loophole in the wording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does temple marriage by proxy jive with D C 132:15-17? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've asked this question a few times, and have never received a reply from those I've asked.

Mormons routinely do sealings and endowments for the dead. However, D C 132:15-17 seems to explicitly bar this as even a possibility.

15 Therefore, if a man marry him a wife in the world, and he marry her not by me nor by my word, and he covenant with her so long as he is in the world and she with him, their covenant and marriage are not of force when they are dead, and when they are out of the world; therefore, they are not bound by any law when they are out of the world.

16 Therefore, when they are out of the world they neither marry nor are given in marriage; but are appointed angels in heaven, which angels are ministering servants, to minister for those who are worthy of a far more, and an exceeding, and an eternal weight of glory.

17 For these angels did not abide my law; therefore, they cannot be enlarged, but remain separately and singly, without exaltation, in their saved condition, to all eternity; and from henceforth are not gods, but are angels of God forever and ever.

This seems explicitly clear: If you are not sealed in the temple while alive, you cannot be married after you are dead. You must be a servant forever.

Has there ever been clarification by a prophet or an apostle? How did they go around this incredibly clear modern-day scripture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does temple marriage by proxy jive with D C 132:15-17? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 16:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've asked this question a few times, and have never received a reply from those I've asked.

Mormons routinely do sealings and endowments for the dead. However, D C 132:15-17 seems to explicitly bar this as even a possibility.

15 Therefore, if a man marry him a wife in the world, and he marry her not by me nor by my word, and he covenant with her so long as he is in the world and she with him, their covenant and marriage are not of force when they are dead, and when they are out of the world; therefore, they are not bound by any law when they are out of the world.

16 Therefore, when they are out of the world they neither marry nor are given in marriage; but are appointed angels in heaven, which angels are ministering servants, to minister for those who are worthy of a far more, and an exceeding, and an eternal weight of glory.

17 For these angels did not abide my law; therefore, they cannot be enlarged, but remain separately and singly, without exaltation, in their saved condition, to all eternity; and from henceforth are not gods, but are angels of God forever and ever.

This seems explicitly clear: If you are not sealed in the temple while alive, you cannot be married after you are dead. You must be a servant forever.

Has there ever been clarification by a prophet or an apostle? How did they go around this incredibly clear modern-day scripture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does temple marriage by proxy jive with D C 132:15-17? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 16:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've asked this question a few times on this forum, and have never received a reply from those I've asked.

Mormons routinely do sealings and endowments for the dead. However, D C 132:15-17 seems to explicitly bar this as even a possibility.

15 Therefore, if a man marry him a wife in the world, and he marry her not by me nor by my word, and he covenant with her so long as he is in the world and she with him, **their covenant and marriage are not of force when they are dead**, and when they are out of the world; therefore, they are not bound by any law when they are out of the world.

16 Therefore, **when they are out of the world they neither marry nor are given in marriage; but are appointed angels in heaven**, which angels are ministering servants, to minister for those who are worthy of a far more, and an exceeding, and an eternal weight of glory.

17 For these angels did not abide my law; therefore, they cannot be enlarged, but remain separately and singly, without exaltation, in their saved condition, to all eternity; **and from henceforth are not gods, but are angels of God forever and ever.**

This seems explicitly clear: If you are not sealed in the temple while alive, you **cannot** be married after you are dead. You **must** be a servant forever.

Has there ever been clarification by a prophet or an apostle? How did they go around this incredibly clear modern-day scripture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 22:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does doing it by proxy jive with D C 132:15-17?

15 Therefore, if a man marry him a wife in the world, and he marry her not by me nor by my word, and he covenant with her so long as he is in the world and she with him, their covenant and marriage are not of force when they are dead, and when they are out of the world; therefore, they are not bound by any law when they are out of the world.

16 Therefore, **when they are out of the world they neither marry nor are given in marriage; but are appointed angels in heaven, which angels are ministering servants**, to minister for those who are worthy of a far more, and an exceeding, and an eternal weight of glory.

17 For these angels did not abide my law; therefore, they cannot be enlarged, but remain separately and singly, without exaltation, in their saved condition, to all eternity; and from henceforth are not gods, but are angels of God forever and ever.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I disagree!!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be interested in this article:

https://www.lds.org/ensign/1981/04/salvation-by-grace-or-by-works?lang=eng </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 22:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, I don't know about that. Grace v. Works has been a centuries-old debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 20:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you get praise for not abusing your children? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 20:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the Mormon church that expects too little of it's members. I would hazard that well over half have no idea that Joseph fucked other men's wives. Why? Because the church outright lies to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, go over to /r/exmormon and find out how many 18-55 year old **lifelong** Mormons don't have a clue about the extent of Joseph Smith's adultery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that information is good, and that he should be fully informed before meeting anyone who's trying to get him baptized. He won't be told about Joseph marrying a 14 year old when he was 37. OP will be fed *the best side* of Mormonism, and will probably be disappointed when he eventually discovers the whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these imperfect people mingling their own ideas with scripture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I follow a church founded by someone who married a 14 year old when he was 37? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from complaining on reddit about this, what can we do specifically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 16:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that life is too short, why waste it being Mormon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 15:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, singles wards are fully of adult children who have been denied any sort of maturity from adults.

Groups of twenty-something men and women who have to be "supervised" by people old enough to be there parents. Activities of "board games" and "movie night with popcorn." Going dancing, but like a middle school dance. Lots of passive aggressive petty gossip and backstabbing, constant name dropping, constant appeals to authority. If you're a man, if you didn't serve a mission, you're lesser. If you're a woman, you'll be awkwardly hounded by naive men looking for a wife.

And then there's the Mormon beliefs themselves!

Three hour church blocks of inane babble. No coffee, no tea, no alcohol. Don't have more than one ear piercing, don't wear tank tops, don't have shorts that go higher than above the knee. Noah's Flood and the Tower of Babel are literal events. Polygamy is *wink wink* "not practiced," but still believed in. Black people are lesser because they were 'less valiant' in the pre-existence. If Native Americans are righteous, then they'll turn white.

Gays are okay as long as they never ever act gay. Women should stay at home and defer to their husbands. If the Prophet says it, the thinking has been done. The Earth is 6,000 years old. Ancient Jews made boats, sailed to America, had a battle of **millions** of people that literally came down to 1v1. 

You can become a God. There are infinite numbers of Gods. Gods are men, women are goddesses "unto their husbands." Oh, and those gods have many wives. A lot is talked about Heavenly Father. What about Heavenly Mother? Almost literally nothing.

Don't do it, OP. What's good about Mormonism isn't unique, and what's unique isn't good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, if only it was for you. Maybe someday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 15:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before you do that, gay folks, check through /u/bhroberts posting history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen! Amen, amen, amen. Too bad /u/blakeoakey probably won't respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 00:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the long and detailed response; I did read all of it!

I don't have a good response, but it has given me some things to think about. I'm pretty impressed that you knew about Asherah, and that they used to be polytheistic.

Thanks again for the excellent response! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 20:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, the Bible has multiple references to lions in the Holy Land

But the Bible has known and documented translation errors, as well as historical errors. Even Mormons say "as long as it was translated correctly." Contrast this to the BoM, which appeared to Smith in a hat verbatim from God.

demolishes these small details which we have yet to unearth.

Small to you, maybe. I feel they are pretty substantial.

If you're interested to know more of these strong positive evidences, just let me know.

I would be interested in what you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting those equivalent bottles back would be $5/can from Coke, so your $0.05 is way too low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the law says otherwise

What law?

"It published the salaries of every one of its employees online, available for the public to see."

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/12/26/public-salary_n_4504871.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your argument is weak if you have to resort to ad hominem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 17:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only testable evidence of the Book of Mormon that I know of is Moroni 10:4.

That's completely wrong. The BoM makes many claims that can be tested. Tower of Babel? Bullshit. Steel? Bullshit. Horses, elephants, wheels, millions of deaths in one big battle? Bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 00:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> price for our errors and sins

Who is judging us on these errors and sins? God. Why can't he just absolve everyone? Bam, done. No need for Christ.

Joseph Smith was such a prophet

Joseph Smith was a con man and adulterer, fraudster and serial liar. 

Book of Mormon is the very valid evidence

If you have no external way to test the validity, then it's bullshit. Many tests given to it in almost every scientific field lead to the same conclusion, bullshit.

Mozart

Mozart wasn't acting on behalf of an omniscient and omnipresent deity. He didn't claim to have divine favor. Further, comparing Mozart to fraudster Joseph Smith is a huge insult to Mozart.

Book of Mormon's teachings concerning Christ

The BoM has what unique Mormon doctrines again? Polygamy? Temple? Proxy baptism? Infinite gods?

mercies

Fucking bullshit. If I have a child I don't get a fucking gold star if I **don't** abuse my kid. It's assumed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the lazy

http://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/supererogatory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then god is an asshole, a sadist, and pretty fucking evil. That god doesn't deserve anything but contempt and scorn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
