<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2082</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have always wanted products that are easier to use. 

When I use Dolphin, I can get inside a game and playing in just a few clicks. The possibility of making a mistake is fairly low. It doesn't cause mental strain. It doesn't need to be learned.

Learning takes time and time is valuable. Every extra minute that I spend learning how to use your program is one minute that I'm not using to play a game or do something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone can start a real estate business. I'm glad that you're doing well, but it's not as easy to avoid payroll tax.

No wrong is being done.

When the middle class has to support the whole system and the rich aren't paying their fair share, it just creates a completely unfair society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 07:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games have different values to different people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 07:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that CC companies take about 2.5%, a 0% cut is probably unrealistic. But if they wanted to show that they support modders and aren't just there to rake in money, they would take a 3%-5% cut. Beth could then take a more reasonable 5-10% cut and it would end up at around 10%-15%. The combined 75% cut showed they were hoping to make big bucks and didn't care about modders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you have point. But if you had the choice for ES6 to either work for free on a community patch, or on your paid mods, wouldn't you spend most of your time working on paid mods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I meant 75% combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they also did something similar with Black Mesa.

Forgotten City is good enough that they could work out a deal to release it as paid DLC IMO. Maybe even give the author some access to the source code. But that would be the exception.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they implement a DRM system for mods? Not saying that people wouldn't crack it, but it would destroy the legal modding scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this contradicts what I wrote. Someone might create an unofficial patch anyway for ES6 if there are paid mods, but I'm sure there would be less motivation/collaboration. We would possibly see many different unofficial patches all trying to grab some money.

I'll paste the Q/A for everyone to see:

"Will the unofficial patch ever cost money if paid mods return?

Short answer: No.

Longer answer: The unofficial patches are a community driven effort in probably the purest possible way. It would be wrong of us to attempt to capitalize on that by suddenly shifting to a for-profit model for these patches. Even if there were to be some super simple way to remove all of the logistical and legal barriers to trying it, we still wouldn't do it. Put simply: It would be wrong on so many levels. So no. The unofficial patches will never cost money. They will always remain free.

If we are involved in the effort to generate unofficial patches for Elder Scrolls VI, those will also remain free." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bethesda would certainly sell fewer copies of their games if users could not freely download tonnes of optional (and some really high quality) content. Skyrim would have came out, been a top seller for a few months like most other AAA titles and then fizzled out.

I think they underestimate that effect. The unofficial patch would probably not exist with paid mods. It wouldn't really work as a paid mod and why make a free mods when others are making money on them? You would just feel like a sucker. Most mods would probably not have been made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be more reasonable if they took 3% and 4.5% IMO. Valve's infrastructure costs are very small and they already made their money on the base game. They support free mods for free. 

Bethesda again has already recouped its money on the base game. Whatever they get will be pure profit.

Asking for a combined 75% cut was greedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a for-profit company. They always want to make more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. They don't want to do any quality control. They don't want to make sure that mods don't contain pirated assets. They just want a cut, and a big one. It was 75% last time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of the problems were/are:

- Valve + publisher kept 75% of the money
- Piracy - Of course, Valve didn't bother policing copyright infringement, so stolen assets/mods.

- Spirit of sharing in the community. Modders share ideas, are part of a community. Having paid mods destroys this.
- Some of the best mods are not paid. Feels unfair to have a mod that took 10 hours to make rake in money, while the Unofficial Skyrim Patch is free.
- Modding will only exist within Valve's walled garden. Valve and publishers will now completely control modding. If they decide to pull the plug, everything disappears. Nexus mods will not be allowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it was illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I guess it's just a matter of making this more obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who gives the politicians money so they look the other way? 

Through lobbying, companies basically bribe politicians so that they don't fix the system. They're not blameless.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the EU is asking for 14B euro. But it's not a done deal yet. Found [this picture](https://assets.bwbx.io/images/users/iqjWHBFdfxIU/i5Y96YnbU8pE/v0/-1x-1.jpg) that explains how it worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be nice if graphics pack were tied to games automatically. It's annoying to have to switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend MOO2 with the [ICE mod](http://moo2mod.com/). You probably won't notice anything at first but it rebalances the game.

2 features of MOO2 that haven't been replicated much are 

1) choice between technologies. You have to make hard choices between X and Y technology, depending on your situation. This makes the game more strategic and interesting.

2) freighters. They allow population and food transfers between colonies but have a certain cost and can be blockaded.

I recommend playing on a small map. In fact, I recommend that for almost any 4x since large maps just end up taking forever and being micromanagement nightmares - and me never reaching the end game. With a small map, you actually can finish the game. 

Graphics are primitive, but it's not so bad once you get used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that nobody ever fixes those loopholes. Companies exploit every loophole they can find in the laws of 10 different countries, and then end up paying close to 0 taxes.

There's an inherent unfairness in the system. The more profits you make, the less taxes you pay because the better you are able to game the international tax system.

It's a bit like once your character reaches a certain level, you can just ignore the rules that apply to everyone else on the server. This is an exploit and should be patched.

Game companies will punish players who aggressively exploit bugs all the time. I don't think it's unfair to blame companies who rush in to exploit every bug in the international tax system. Especially not when they then lobby politicians to make sure the exploits are never patched. In some cases, companies like Apple made special deals with the government - private cheat codes if you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like how Apple avoids paying almost any taxes in the EU or anywhere else. [CNN:How Apple paid just 0.005% tax on its global profits](http://money.cnn.com/2016/08/30/technology/apple-tax-ruling-numbers/)

Until people get serious about this, politicians will keep looking the other way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lead Dragon Age writer, David Gaider, is gay btw. Talks about this topic here: https://unicornbooty.com/gay-developer-david-gaider-never-planned-to-create-groundbreaking-queer-games/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Next Big Blue-Collar Job Is Coding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the netplay part? Were there two people playing the game?

-

The NAND is kind of like the Wii hard drive, right?

Wii Remote Netplay means passing through wiimote data over the internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I didn't think that this was an issue for pressed discs, such as those they were distributed from?

[It is](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Disc_rot). Many laserdisks from the '80s have already degraded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dice roll systems aimed to be "more realistic". A real sword fight will probably be over after the first hit. So the fight happens before that first hit is scored. The "to hit" dice rolls mimic that. It's the fencing match that happens before anyone is hit.

It's generally a fun mechanic in PnP RPGs and it worked fine in older games. 

Would be interesting to hear why people dislike this. Why does it feel wrong to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikipedia lists 70 Xbox exclusive games: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Xbox_games

Most are obscure, like Dungeons   Dragons: Heroes, but there are also the Amped games and Dead or Alive 3. 

Also, Halo on Xbox has unique shaders not present in the PC version!

Xbox emulation will also help in the preservation effort. It provides an incentive to dump roms and build complete libraries. I wonder if anyone has been preserving Official Xbox Magazine demo disks for example... In a few decades, bit rot will have destroy all original disk copies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you do it? Last I looked it was impossible to store select games on a different drive. Or maybe it was just so inconvenient I gave up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds really interesting! Your best videos are when you track down bugs. This one has a funny reversal on the normal pattern. It would be great as extra content to pad out a progress report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue Shogun wrote about this in September:

" After looking through the git repository, it looks like someone fixed a handful of things that I was either too lazy to implement properly or just completely forgot about.  One thing he fixed was my implementation of section loading; a proper solution was lacking and I lazily added what was necessary for a few games just to test it.  I looked through that code thinking "man, I sure hope somebody fixed that", and bam, it was there, lol.  They also did a way with alot of the previous FS stuff.  Interesting nonetheless."

More recently, he said that he hadn't done anything related to emulation in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, this is a new fork being worked on by PatrickvL?

He posted this gallery: http://imgur.com/a/Bzvti (this summer).

Edit: Seems like there are two other active developers (jarupxx and LukeUsher) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only Steam allowed for games to be stored on multiple drives... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The shaders, textures, music, lack of rhythm, no sense of danger. 

Fixing it will probably be hard. They might have reduced detail and density because their level is so huge. So they might need to break up the level into smaller, walled off sections to improve it, which would be a major redesign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't surprise me. 180k owners according to [steam spy](https://steamspy.com/app/298050), which isn't great.

They focused a lot on the graphics, which, IMO, don't really matter for a game like this. I don't even like the new portraits that much but that's just me. The Meklar look like the Geth from Mass Effect. Humans went from civilian to military. The new portraits reflect all the new cliches seen in games and movies.

MOO2 with the [ICE mod](http://moo2mod.com/) is still my favorite 4x game. It plays great with smaller galaxies and it still has many unique concepts, like freighters that weren't copied much. 

At least they kept the concept of having to choose one upgrade over the other for most techs, which is something that most 4X games don't do anymore. IMO, having to make hard choices is what makes games interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the ability to switch skills on the fly. It's a great way for casual players to quickly try different builds. 

But it hurt the long term replayability of the game. It made characters not feel special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true that it's a worst case example and that video actually accompanies a paper (https://arxiv.org/abs/1606.01868). Still, it's interesting to see how bad the AI is that playing a game when the rewards are less immediate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true that AI is developing rapidly, but its abilities are overestimated. See Google Deepmind's AI struggling on an Atari 2600 game [here](https://youtu.be/0yI2wJ6F8r0).

AlphaGo is great but it's a very specialized AI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo needs to get serious about independent developers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the [StarCraft Artificial Intelligence Tournament - 2017 Grand Finals](https://youtu.be/Op6GuDfN2ws). These are conventional AIs that are actually fairly stupid. SCV rush seems to be a winning strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Master of Orion: Reviving the Legend - Making of Newest MOO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just processing power. AIs are not as smart (yet) as they're sometimes made out to be. Look at this AI struggling with Montezuma's Revenge for example: https://youtu.be/0yI2wJ6F8r0 (Atari 2600 game).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Deepmind (of AlphaGo fame) is working on a Starcraft II AI right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation.

I think that your progress reports are good btw. You've put a lot of effort into them.

Keep up the good work. You seem one of the most active developers, along with just 2-3 others. It's always cool to see some progress being made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I loved Human Revolution, and I think that Mankind Divided is worth trying at its current price (75% off on Steam right now), the original game is the true masterpiece.

The new games focus a lot on visuals and setting, while the original was about gameplay and player choice. 

"the game was conceived with the idea that we'd accept players as our collaborators, that we'd put power back in their hands, ask them to make choices, and let them deal with the consequences of those choices." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the future of Deus Ex lies with its past - the untapped potential of Deus Ex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he nailed it when he said that the focus of DX1 was on player choice and experimentation, not the setting or aesthetics. 

A lot of it had to do with the era that the game was made in, where they could get away with minimalistic graphics.

I like all the art in MD and HR. Eidos Montreal obviously has extremely talented artists, but this focus on art took away from the gameplay and player choice IMO. If the game had been built in the Unreal 1 engine with featureless walls and props, they would have been forced to focus on gameplay. That angel is an good example. I stumbled upon it in a random apartment. Why did that person decorate his apartment in that way? It seems that everyone in Prague decorates their apartments in really weird ways. While it's beautiful, I didn't feel like it really belonged. I have to wonder how many hours went into it. It probably took as long as making half a Deus Ex 1 level.

I just played through the original Deus Ex and it stands the test of time. Yes, it does get tedious at times. Some missions are weaker and overly long, like the ship mission. But the main gameplay loop is fun. You have multiple ways of solving every mission, and it's really fun to outsmart the guards and sneak up on them from behind. By contrast, the MD levels feel cramped and the takedown ability just isn't as fun. It feels cheap to be able to take down opponents without having to sneak up from behind. And at the same time it's frustrating that your main limit on this ability is having to wait for your internal battery to recharge. That just forces you to arbitrarily slow down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not free, but Google shoulders most of the costs of developing Android. Also, phones are produced on a massive scale. LG can buy parts from existing suppliers. Nintendo has to design everything and then have it custom made. There's a lot more to the cost, than just the SOC. Most Japanese developers were surprised by how cheap it was. Controllers are not cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you won't get ICOW because only the author is allowed to flip a few version bits.

I wonder if there could be a way to encourage open source mod development through a kind of github for mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't have a controller, or motion controls. Nintendo also has to shoulder the costs of developing all the software.

And is it really sold brand new for $300? That's probably a clearance price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't allowed to see the full report, but I assume that Oculus' experts had access to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with this IMO. It keeps development costs down for Nintendo and other devs. Nintendo has shown that it's possible to make great games on less powerful hardware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also $700, not $300. No one would buy a console at that price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. You guys kind of set the gold standard for progress reports. I like how: 

- you take the time to try and explain everything. (mipmapping was not explained here for example)

- you keep the tone cheerful and even try to be a bit funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't allowed to read it because it probably contained some trade secrets, so it was sealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great progress report as always! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a typo on graph for 5.0-2178 (Simpon's game) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no question that Windows 10 is an impressive piece of software, and quite the most secure operating system ever devised. But it is still very much a work in progresseven the programs troubleshooter needs a troubleshooter. In its current form, Windows 10 demands serious expertise when it comes to knocking it into shape so ordinary users can work they way they prefer. It is also guilty of trampling far too much on people's privacy, by keeping tabs of all their comings and goings. 

Rather than offer incentives, the company has resorted to spreading FUD (fear, uncertainly and doubt) among its corporate customersas IBM did back in the 1970s whenever customers threatened to desert Big Blue for rival suppliers. Since the start of the year, Microsofts corporate users have been warned that, even with security updates, Windows 7 simply does not have the architecture to cope with todays threats. The remedial work needed to recover from malware attacks can only drive up operating costs. The message to sceptical systems managers: postpone the inevitable upgrade at your peril.


Along with additional bells and whistles, [the Creators Update (effectively Windows 10.2) due in April], is said to be more secure than even the current version, while offering somewhat better privacy controls for users. But news that Microsoft has baked advertising into the operating systempushing third-party apps as well as its own software and servicescould be enough to make many a reluctant upgrader have second thoughts.

It used to be that only free software came with advertising; users paid a fee, if they chose to do so, to get the software free of advertising. Microsoft charges top dollar for Windows 10 ($120 or $200, depending on the edition) and now wants to bombard users with sales pitches to bootwithout so much as by your leave, let alone the option to turn the nuisance off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The woes of Windows 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks really good. 1080p video would be nice, if possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's like Skyrim Special Edition, they'll just upscale the low res textures and call it high res. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was very well written. Looking forward to part II. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Those names were hard to remember. ist tvr anyone? How do you pronounce that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, they needed more areas, even at the cost of reducing the level of detail in each area. Part of the appeal of Deus Ex is travelling around the world.

Prague is wonderfully crafted, but this is a game, not a work of art. I don't find sneaking into random apartments that interesting. It's like they poured all their energies into side content while they forgot  to cook the main dish.

The original Deus Ex was huge with really interesting and varied levels. Of course, each level cost a lot less to make back then. You were always kept engaged by the main story and had a clear objective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In ME3, you have the choice between the [Spoiler](#s "control, synthesis or destruction") endings. The problem is that these choices don't really stem from issues that are discussed throughout the game. Also, the ending doesn't really explain who the reapers are or why they do what they have been doing. It's not an interesting choice.

The original Deus Ex has a more interesting choice. You either [Spoiler](#s "side with the illuminati (elite capitalism and surveillance society), the triad boss (anarchy and destruction of all communication networks), or the AI (benevolent rule by a superintelligent AI).") I would have liked to have more choices. These are 3 pretty bleak choices for the fate of the world, and it's clear which one was favored by the game designers. But the choices at least make sense within the game and present an interesting dilemma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's obvious that they weren't able to fully realize their vision in MD, and had to rush the game to completion. They were probably refused an extension or even had their budget cut short by Squeenix.

I wouldn't be surprised if they had planned for two or three different city hubs, just like in Human Revolution. 

But the constraints of AAA development are very harsh. Eidos Montreal is a mid-sized studio. They just weren't able to deliver a huge, polished game, with a next-gen engine and next-gen visuals.

They focused on quality above quantity. Their engine is great and the environments in the game are beautiful, but that probably was done at the expense of producing more content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a post in /r/everythingscience . Sharing anecdotes should be okay. https://www.reddit.com/r/EverythingScience/comments/5qwgs6/children_get_more_satisfaction_from_relationships/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made this post so that people from /r/science could engage in a more informal discussion. I hope this is not against the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children get more satisfaction from relationships with their pets than with siblings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Seems to run at full speed](https://youtu.be/X8vTWDkkm50). More complex games are still a work in progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  when a scam becomes obvious Kickstarter will not help the victims of a scam in anyway, they will not communicate names, addresses or bank details of the scammers

I would have expected more from Kickstarter.

I thought that Kickstarter allowed refunds, but it's not quite like that. I've updated my post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4D games seem to refer to a horror game. It's fairly big. They also have the huge train simulator games where you drive a train. [Link](https://youtu.be/ICPLwRe3Vhs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Especially since Kickstarter basically allows you to ask for a refund if goals are not met.~~

Edit: This is not quite correct. As others have pointed out, it's the backers who would have to take legal action. Here is what the terms of service say:

"If a creator is unable to complete their project and fulfill rewards, theyve failed to live up to the basic obligations of this agreement. To right this, they must make every reasonable effort to find another way of bringing the project to the best possible conclusion for backers. A creator in this position has only remedied the situation and met their obligations to backers if:

-they post an update that explains what work has been done, how funds were used, and what prevents them from finishing the project as planned;

-they work diligently and in good faith to bring the project to the best possible conclusion in a timeframe thats communicated to backers;

-theyre able to demonstrate that theyve used funds appropriately and made every reasonable effort to complete the project as promised;

-theyve been honest, and have made no material misrepresentations in their communication to backers; and

-they offer to return any remaining funds to backers who have not received their reward (in proportion to the amounts pledged), or else explain how those funds will be used to complete the project in some alternate form.

The creator is solely responsible for fulfilling the promises made in their project. If theyre unable to satisfy the terms of this agreement, they may be subject to legal action by backers. "
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I think that none of them use Linux anymore. It was used in the Lindbergh Red for example, around 2007. The Lindbergh Red EX released in 2008 was probably the last one to use Linux. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost all of the newer games are only available in Japan. The Nesica service, which is a bit like Netflix for arcade owners is only available in Japan. 

[This](https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2015/08/japans-gaming-centers-provide-joy-for-the-kid-inside/) is a pretty good tour of a Japanese arcade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that he shouldn't have made it about people. I don't care if writers have a degree in science, or law, or creative writing. 

The main problems  that I see with RPG writing are:


1) Lore is not that interesting by itself. It does not replace a good story. Too much focus on lore is distracting. Information dumps are bad.

2) Not enough editing and poor prose. Writers need to choose their words carefully. Longer doesn't mean better. Companies should try to hire experienced editors to catch mistakes and poor writing. I think this is his strongest argument. He points out several examples of poor writing in PoE, Tyranny and Torment: Tides of Numenera. He could probably also have picked almost any sentence in Wasteland 2 ;) (I disagree with his critique of Shadowrun HK, which has excellent writing IMO).

A bit of a rant, but I wonder if some of these problems don't stem from a lack of reading. Games writers should read lots of books, and not just sci-fi and fantasy. That's how you learn to write.

3) Writers should do more research into their subject. I'm generalizing his point about poor historical research. A game is more interesting when I know that the writer has done research on the time period and/or philosophical ideas presented in the game. However, doing research can be expensive.

4) Good stories are centered around 2 or 3 interesting characters. If your characters are not interesting or memorable, then your story will not be interesting. (This comes from me (and Harvey Smith).)

5) Don't forget humor. (Also comes from me.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that it was almost impossible to crack these more recent games, but it seems that I was wrong. There's apparently a front end and dumps for the Nesica xLive games that run on Taito machines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some also run linux. There was even an Xbox based arcade (Chihiro). Check out [System16.com](http://www.system16.com/museum.php?id=1). It has most of the arcade cabinet systems.

I believe that the games that run on Windows don't work because they're encrypted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks. I hadn't watched the videos. IGN has a few details " Said veterans include Rob Auten (Gears of War, Battlefield), Lawrence Liberty ( Fallout: New Vegas, The Witcher) , Montgomery Markland ( Wasteland 2 and Torment: Tides of Numenera) and in an advisory capacity, Obsidian Entertainments Design Director Josh Sawyer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RPG Codex Editorial: Darth Roxor on the State of RPG Writing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darth Roxor talks about the problem of excessive lore in his most recent article: http://www.rpgcodex.net/content.php?id=10511

"Lore - knowledge or information about a subject, for example nature or magic, that is not written down but is passed from person to person: "According to local lore, a ghost still haunts the castle."

This definition is interesting to us for one reason  information that is not written down. Now consider what the so-called lore is supposed to mean in your modern game  backstory that is dumped somewhere for the player to stumble upon. Nowadays you will even be given a whole submenu where all this is safely stowed away, and which you will likely never open."

"RPGs for a longer while have been suffering from an illness that I would call fantasitis, which has crept a long time ago into pulp fantasy literature, and which mostly entails (badly) copying the Tolkien approach  a fantasy world has to be grand, with a robust mythology, huge geography and history spanning over six millennia, to the point that you might as well forget about writing a fantasy novel if youre not planning (at least!) a trilogy from the get-go."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Who is behind Erebus LLC? The listed collaborators are: "Larry Liberty, Rob Auten, Gordon Wang and Lucia Botta". They have no profiles.~~

~~The Kickstarter claims that Josh Sawyer is a design consultant. Is there proof or confirmation that Josh Sawyer is working on this? Maybe /u/ObsidianEric can tell us.~~

Edit: Josh Sawyer is in the video. Seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It runs fine on my 1060 (6GB).  I have one of the overclocked cards (windforce). I've played mostly SSE though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I was a bit disappointed with PoE1's story and characters. I didn't feel compelled to go on.

[This review by Wolf](https://wolfsgamingblog.com/2015/04/08/pillars-of-eternity-review-yeah-its-pretty-good/) sums up my thought pretty well. 

"Where the game perhaps trips up is by not also opting to emulate the sense of humour its forebearers had. This is a game chock full of doom and gloom, and after a while it frankly became too much. Everybody seemed to be hiding horrible secrets and dark pasts, everybody seemed dire and dreich (Scottish word, look it up) and depressing. And thats perfectly fine, except for the fact that getting through Pillars of Eternity takes around 70-hours or so, and thats quite a lot of time to spend in a world that has seemingly never even managed to invent the knock-knock joke. By half-way through my enjoyment of the deep gameplay mechanics was starting to struggle under the idea of spending yet more time trundling around a place which took everything so seriously. A few changes in tone, perhaps in the side-quests, could have done wonders.

As for the many characters you encounter on your travels and those who will join your party they also suffer from one tragic condition; being unmemorable. Given how beautifully descriptive the writing is when it comes to carefully crafting a scene or detailing the games almost absurd amount of lore its incredibly disappointing to see that the writers so clearly struggled to create meaningful, interesting people to journey with. Their backstories are often interesting and worth attempting to fully uncover, but after spending damn near 70-hours in their presence, more that one would expect to spend with the Mass Effect crew across a single play-through of the whole trilogy, I found that I didnt really care that much about them on a personal level. Indeed, even several hours after meeting a new companion I struggled to remember their name."

[This review by DarthRoxor](http://www.rpgcodex.net/content.php?id=9867) is also very good. 

"Side quests are very disappointing as well, with scant moments of potential. The sad fact of the matter is that the vast majority of them are nothing but shameless FedEx quests. Go there, deliver something, kill someone, as if taken from some random generic quest generator. "

"All the attributes also give some minor adjustments to saving throws, and considering that each defence type is boosted by 2 different attributes, the system simply leads to a very disappointing feeling of sameyness, even among different attribute distributions."

"Options that rely on skills and arent purely for flavour are so rare, you might as well disregard them completely. And even those that do have some effect are very rarely different than just avoiding combat with a trash mob."

"What is even more disappointing is that Obsidian even included short text adventures into PoE that had crazy potential for adding content into the game, but there is only a single instance of one in the game that doesnt feel half-arsed. Otherwise, all text adventures boil down to: 1. Examine [thingy] 2. Use consumable to win 3. Use [athletics/might] to win. 4. Walk away."

"
Which brings us to what possibly surprised and disappointed me the most in PoE  the general writing quality is simply underwhelming. It never reaches any heights, its at best average and at worst abysmal. Everything is overly descriptive, very often just redundant and not leaving much for the players imagination. The majority of texts could easily be trimmed to one-third of their original size, which only tells me that PoE has never seen any editorial work apart from fishing out typos. One of the best examples I can think of is when you first meet Guy McBaddie the main villain, and the game makes sure to tell you at least three times that he is a bearded dude in a ceremonial robe and a fancy hat, even though the description is accompanied by two different illustrations in quick succession."

Also [this review](https://johnswritersblock.com/2015/04/20/pillars-of-eternity-ending-review/) by John Stevenson

"The simple fact of the matter is that the Pillars of Eternity main storyline just never grabbed me. I feel bad that this is going to be mostly a negative review because I absolutely love the ambition on display here. Obsidian shot for the moon on this one and it justdidnt quite get there."

"The sheer amount of information that needs to be conveyed means you get tons of exposition dumped on you a lot. "

"Then theres the backstory youll need to know about the War of Black Trees and War of Broken Stones that lead to the current situation in Dyrwood. Oh and youll need to know about Waidwens Legacy, which means youll need to know about Animancy, which means you need to know about how Souls work in this world, which means you need to know about the Glanfathans

They basically needed to give you a history book to read before playing the game."

"I hate that their huge epic world ultimately becomes a negative to the overall story, but it is. Theres simply so much information you need to know in order to even understand whats happening in the story that at some point you simply stop caring."

The main points are: bland characters, need of tighter editing, and not engaging main story.

I think the main mistake they made was not having a good hook to drag you along the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the trailer. I'll wait for more details on the narrative before pledging. The game is absolutely beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean [clockwork](http://www.nexusmods.com/skyrimspecialedition/mods/4155/) by Antistar? I can't find clockwork tower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the one on the left always the oldest image? Hurricane Matthew seems to have brought additional roads?? I don't understand that one.

My understanding is that these images are not all about climate change, but just about changes to the Earth in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who just started playing... The game is beautiful. 

Compared to DX1, the take downs are not as interesting as the baton IMO. DX1 had great mechanics with the baton/stun prod and crossbow. It's frustrating that my arms run out of power after taking down two enemies.

-Lots of unskippable cutscenes. The dialogue system doesn't allow me to skim through conversations like I'd want to.

To give one example, I did that quest with the guy (Michael?) who has his underground church. I spent longer listening to his unskippable tirade than doing the quest. And I had to pick all 3 options during the conversation for some reason. Why couldn't I just skip it? I got the point already. The actual mission area is very small and doesn't present much of a challenge. I just knock him out and it's over...

That long cutscene at the train station when arriving in Prague could have been much more interesting if they had let the player walk around freely, similar to the HL2 opening sequence.

-Loading times are a bit long. I reload often, so it's annoying.

-I admit that I didn't pay a lot of attention to the story but I find the game a bit confusing. Why do I care about this guy with his fake checkpoint? Why do I need to take the subway to go to that place I need to go? It took me a long time before I realized that's what I had to do.

Compared to DX1, exploring apartments and stuff isn't quite as compelling as being part of a big story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst feature of Windows 10 is automatic updates - and Microsoft won't fix it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also among those who were disappointed. The game is beautiful, but it lacks a "soul" IMO. The characters just weren't that interesting. Harvey Smith, of Deus Ex fame, said that a good story is about two or three good characters, and the PoE characters just weren't interesting. Also, it lacked humor and romance.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is now known as [Artistic Skyrim Overhaul](http://www.nexusmods.com/skyrim/mods/81221/?)

Youtube showcase: https://youtu.be/p95Ir_f0S9w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Games/comments/5p3cnh/joseph_anderson_fallout_4_one_year_later/dcp3537/

I actually liked the video mostly but I lost interest in the part about the DLC. Possibly, because I  haven't played it.

It could certainly be edited more tightly. It's amazing how much information can be crammed in a short time by a skilled editor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many different definitions, but he means a "role playing game", that is a game where you can play a certain imagined character in the universe who makes choices.

He says that there needs to at least be character building and choices about how you interact with the world. 

In Dragon Age and The Witcher, you can make choices that affect the world. You can choose to respond differently to different situations. You can't really do that in FO4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone has some more information on this? Does it run games or prototypes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that Chinese pirates stole mods and used them in commercial games. This sucks.

Also, I didn't know that there were Japanese modders. Is the game popular in Japan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Large companies just ignore the pirates, but I think it's not always so easy for mod creators to do so. They're often working alone and just doing this for the love/respect they get from the community and sense of accomplishment. So, when someone steals their stuff, they do the only thing they can, which is yank out their mod.

Of course, it doesn't solve the problem, but it probably makes them feel less abused and taken advantage of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use 1.5x or 2.0x speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that it would be possible to edit this down to 30 mins or less. I summarized the main points I found relevant in another comment, and it's not that long.

He rambles a lot about Far Harbor instead of identifying a few key points. He also tries to rewrite the main quest story and this is where I stopped watching. It's just too complicated and speculative for a youtube video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 05:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked the [credits](http://www.uesp.net/wiki/Morrowind:Development_Team) and it seems that quite a few people left after Morrowind, including:

- Douglas Goodall - Writing   Quest Design Goodall created the vast majority of the game's faction quests. He left Bethesda shortly after Morrowind's release.

- Ken Rolston - Lead Designer 
Ken is the lead designer for Morrowind and was involved in creation of Redguard. He is one of the fathers of role-playing and has done work for almost every paper system out there. Ken left Bethesda after Oblivion's release.

- Mark Nelson - Writing   Quest Design 
Nelson is no longer at Bethesda, but before he left, he worked on both Bloodmoon and Oblivion.

And if anyone knows people who worked at Bethesda, it seems that there are still plenty of unidentified faces on the development team picture.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that would disrupt their core gameplay. Areas between cities serve as a kind of dungeon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly they've never played Rimworld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NV isn't perfect in that regard either. I remember the first bar in NV has broken mirrors. They didn't have time to clean that up? All the buildings in town are full of broken stuff, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that great writing doesn't sell as well as good graphics. It's much less noticeable.

And a lot of players are just going to focus on the more mindless aspects of a game: "Oh, you can blow his head off!", and not even notice that the story doesn't make sense. The visual and gameplay elements are just so much more noticeable that the attention ends up going there.

And writing a good RPG with a good story is hard. You have to write in choices for different classes and different moral outlooks. You have to write believable characters with different life philosophies. Not everyone can do that and those who do might not ever get hired by game studios because their skills don't really intersect with game development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their "administrative" expenses (SGA) are $1.6B. /u/Steelcap said that "to keep the lights on and keep everyone employed, to keep developing new software and hardware, they spend tens of millions a year." No, just the administrative and R D expenses are $1.6B, the cost of developing software is in the costs of sales. Even if that's only $1B, he's still way off the mark, by a factor of about 100x. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "They're only in it to make money" line annoys me a little. That motivation is why all games get made. It doesn't mean that there isn't any passion behind it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with 4DO? Most games [run perfectly](http://wiki.fourdo.com/Compatibility_List). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick summary:

- Not primarily an RPG. RPG aspect is not core. It's like the feathers that have been glued back on the chicken. The chicken is Explore - Loot - Craft.
- Quests not written by writers, but by level designers, artists, etc. Quests have no depth. Just a simple idea. No consequences. No non-violent alternatives. No ties to the lore. No ties to other quests. Many quests are illogical. Bethesda doesn't explore its ideas - they're just simple fetch quests in the end.
- Some quests are more elaborate, but no branching dialogue. Rewards for dialogue options are caps. USS Constitution is the only quest with stat checks. It should have been just one of many good quests, not the only one.
- Impossible to ask clarifying questions. 
- Dialogue system is pathetic. Dialogue mod shows that most answers are the same - or just the same line rewritten. At that point, why not go fully scripted? If there are no meaningful choices, why pretend? 


- Skyrim: More work is put in the environments than in the stories or characters. 
- None of the recent Bethesda games are really RPGs. There needs to be character building and choices about how you interact with the world. Bethesda either doesn't know this or doesn't want to admit it. Afraid that RPG fans would be angry if they dropped the pretense of being an RPG completely.
- Admits to liking it anyway. Exploring the world is fun.
- Nice vertical design in the city. Great combat arenas. Combat has been improved, but still simple and shallow. Having something like the nanosuit from Crysis would be awesome. Power armor is cool, but clunky plus ticking of fusion core means that he won't use it.
- Ideas for upgradeable options similar to the words of power from Skyrim: Could have had an upgradeable stealth Pip-Boy that explain the ridiculous stealth ability. Or upgradeable suit with cold resistance. Or augmentations that you could pick up from synths.
- On very hard, enemies are insane bullet sponges. Don't drop enough ammo. Leg enemies can have less HP than normal ones.
- Perks: Should have been separated between combat and non combat. Non-combat perks shouldn't cause enemies to level up. 
- Survival mode sucks. Contrary to Dark Souls, death can feel unfair. Repetition is not fun. Also, crash bugs. 


- DLCs have a ton of untapped potential. Far Harbor has creative enemies. Goes on forever about FH. Quests are deeper. Better than main story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked this quip:

"Bethesda designers are proud that people sometimes can't tell radiant quests from scripted quests, but they've got it backwards. Many of the scripted quests are so dull that they appear to be radiant quests." (not exact words) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm referring to Cost of Sales + SGA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nintendo has an opperating cost in the tens of millions

I think you're a bit off the mark: https://www.nintendo.co.jp/ir/pdf/2016/annual1603e.pdf It's about $4B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making games and competing for exclusives is also really expensive. They've decided they don't want to play that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also not working so well for Sony and Microsoft. The PS4 is a success at around 50M sold, but the Xbox One is lagging behind. Even 50 M is [not that much compared to other consoles](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_best-selling_game_consoles).

Traditional consoles are not a bad business, but it looks like the market is staying stable at best, not growing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
