<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject983</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for ways to progress as an intermediate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 03:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I would rate myself an intermediate player, and I feel like I've hit a rut in my development.  I mainly play metal/prog metal, so a lot of my skill has developed around that. Right now I know all the pentatonic shapes (major/minor), all the modes, chord/arpeggio theory, etc, so I feel like I have a good theory background.  I also make sure to practice finger style and picking.  Right now I'm working on learning the modes of the pentatonic scale (see: http://www.frettedapprentice.com/modalpentatonics/). I can currently hit 99%+ on most of the metalish/hard rock songs on Rocksmith.  I honestly don't know what to practice.  I've been working on exercises from Alex Websters freestyle metal bass book, but I've been doing those for a while so I'm starting to lose interest.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was not the brightest child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 03:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eric Johnson does a lot of open voiced triads, where one note will be raised an octave, and so it will be played over four strings with one muted rather then playing the closed triad over just three strings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I'm writing it is one part is going to be purely harmony with chords, and the melody voice is going to "emulate" counterpoint by basically playing both counterpart voices.  We have to write it for two instruments, so the harmony is for guitar and the melody is for piano.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 19:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Within the diatonic system in the picture, is to cool to extend chords/use inversions? Ie if I'm in C major, could I use a FM9 or an FM add9 instead of just a simple F chord? And could I use Em/B instead of just a simple e minor chord?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 02:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the picture! Thats exactly what I was having problems understanding.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 02:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traditional music theory class.  I've covered all the stuff you mentioned like counterpoint, how chords are constructed, basic scales and diatonic stuff, etc.  We have barely touched chord progressions though, the only things I know in that regard is half and authentic cadences. I have no idea how to construct a chord progression other then it should have the I chord, V chord, and maybe a pre-dominant chord.  The problem is I have no idea how to pick pre-dominant chords and and I dont know any rules that govern pre-dominant selection.  For example I-vii(dim)-IV-V-I sounds weird to me, but I have no idea if that is just my personal opinion or if there is some rule of chord progressions I'm violating.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about starting songwriting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 01:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my music theory class this semester our midterm project is to write a duet.  I'm pretty sure I'm going to use C major for my key(no sharps or flats makes life easier), but I'm completely lost at how to start writing the song.  I have no idea how to come up with a chord progression, should I be starting with the melody then harmony or vice versa? I know a bunch of music theory stuff, I just have no idea how to take all of it and craft it into a song.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just mainly concerned with the fact that they said the original preamp signal had to be in line with the circuit. If I have a different preamp generating the signal you're saying I should be fine?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Peavey Classic VT 50 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 21:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now for my guitar amp I'm using my dad's old Peavey Classic VT 50, which is a hybrid amp with a solid state preamp and 2 tubes for the power section (I want to say 6L6s but I'm not sure).  Mines the version with on-board reverb and phaser.  My question is in regards to the preamp out and preamp in sections on the back of the amp, which is basically an effects loop.  If you look at the manual found here:

 http://assets.peavey.com/literature/manuals/80343001.pdf 

it basically says that the preamp out signal must be placed inline with the devices added.  I was wondering how accurate this is, and was wondering if it would be possible to run an external preamp into the preamp in section on the back of the amp while ignoring the on board preamp.  If I were, for example, to get  a Pod HD500, I would like to just run it into the preamp in section to bypass the on board preamp.  This would give me a lot of flexibility, as I play everything from classic rock to high gain metal.  Right now I tend to set the amp into a clean tone and do any shaping I want via pedals, as the preamp gain on the amp creates a pretty muddy sound that leaves a lot to be desired, but I don't have many pedals so right now my tonal range is kinda limited.  If it was my own amp I would just plug it in and test it, but seeing as its my dad's amp I don't wanna do anything to it that could mess it up.  Has anyone had success running something into the preamp in jack on one of these amps while not placing the preamp out signal in line?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 21:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the proof that the rationals are countable the one where you draw a number table with the integers listed on both side where one represents the numerator and the other the denominator, and then you zigzag through the graph skipping repeated numbers? Our teacher never gave us a formal proof for the rational numbers being countable, just showed us the table and how the proof would work if done formally.  

I don't think the second thing is assuming what we need to prove, as we need to prove the union is countable.  We know each set is countable as a given, and so if you sum a bunch of countable elements you know that the result must be countable.  That still leaves having to deal with subtracting the intersection between the sets though, so it isn't assuming what we need to prove.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fundamental Mathematics] Union of a sequence of sets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 20:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a quick question about one of my homework problems, and want to see if I'm on the right track to solving it.  The question is: "Given that a sequence of sets 'a1, a2, ..., an' is a sequence of countable sets, prove the union of these sets is a countable set."  

The way I'm currently approaching it is to say that the cardinality of the union of the sets in the sequence is the same as the sum of the cardinality's of the individual sets minus the cardinality of the intersection of all the sets.  We know that each individual set is countable as it is given, so the sum of those individual sets must be countable, as we are summing positive natural numbers.  

The part I'm hung up on is proving that the intersection of these sets is countable.  And my other question is will this be sufficient by itself, or will I then have to prove that there is a bijection from the union of sets to the natural numbers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot about that, good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably go to bdubs if that happens, since they're bound to have at least a couple TVs playing the Hawks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best bar to watch sports games at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 19:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackhawks opener is Thursday night, but I don't have comcast down here so I can't see the game.  Where would the best places to watch the game be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 20:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, time to start drinking.  Goodbye Leddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I fixed that as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just got it to work, I forgot you cant assign strings with = and had to use strcpy instead   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
warning, almost no comments.  All the issues I'm having are in the mainloop method starting at 179.

for some reason i put an old revision in.  This should be the correct one: https://gist.github.com/anonymous/5ca80a7f7982b4873810 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 03:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after switching to strchr, I get the following valgrind error:
==65332== Invalid write of size 8

==65332==    at 0x100000F5C: mainloop (shell.c:233)

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???
==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==  Address 0x104804000 is not stack'd, malloc'd or (recently) free'd

==65332== 

==65332== 

==65332== Process terminating with default action of signal 11 (SIGSEGV)

==65332==  Access not within mapped region at address 0x104804000

==65332==    at 0x100000F5C: mainloop (shell.c:233)

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???

==65332==    by 0x10001763F: ???


Here's a link to the code segment I'm using for it: https://gist.github.com/anonymous/aa33cb3bcec00c85858c
Line 233 from valgrind corresponds to line 15 on the gist
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C] trimming \n from a c string </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 03:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one of my assignments we need to build our own shell, and I get the users input with getline and store it into a char* originally set to NULL, so that the buffer is dynamically allocated by getline.  The issue is I need to trim the \n, but all the methods for doing so use a char[] and manipulating stuff with [strlen - 1] to swap positions, but you can't use array notation with a char*.  I've tried copying it into a char[] with strcpy, but then valgrind starts throwing up invalid reads everywhere.  It works on the surface, but I'll lose a lot of points on grading because of the memory errors.  Is there a way I can simply trim the \n from the original char* w/o creating new strings and dealing with copying shit everywhere?

please ignore any random formatting issues
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 20:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was originally having trouble proving it by induction, which was why I asked as I wasn't sure it could be done.  I took a break from the problem and went back to it, and it was actually pretty trivial to prove.  I figured it would be better to be safe then sorry. My professor hasn't mentioned anything about proving associative and commutative properties so I think I'll be ok on those.  Thanks for your help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about proving a summation form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 19:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for my HW for my math proofs class we start out with summation notation and need to get it into a reduced form, IE 1+2+3+4+...+n = n(n+1)/2.  The thing is my homework question states give the summation and then find and prove a formula in terms on n, and I'm not sure if I need to provide additional proof.  

The question I'm working on in summation notation is sum(4i-1) as i ranges from 1 to n.  I've gone step by step and reduced it to the formula n(2n+1) by taking it from summation notation into the n formula form.  First I took it from the sum to 4*sum(i) from i = 1 to n minus sum(1) as i = 1 to n, and from there took it to 2(n)(n+1) - n, and from there finally to n(2n+1).  My question is, is showing this process enough to prove it, or do I need to go in and prove it via induction for the n+1 case?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 23:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like my bass a lot lower when playing with a pick.  To high and the angle just feels weird for my wrist.  But I agree for finger-style.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideas for drinks with a date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 18:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I wanted to meet up with a girl for some drinks, what would be a good choice in terms of the environment? So far I've been to Red Lion, Brothers, and White Horse Inn on my own time, but they seem to blast music all the time and it's hard to have a decent conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 19:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.carvinguitars.com/products/BR515 or http://www.carvinguitars.com/products/BR510

I personally have the 2x10 version and it kicks ass.  The parametric mids + 9 band graphic EQ really lets you play whatever you need to from the amp.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 05:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about the nut through.  Depending on how the E string is setup you might need to file the nut a bit if you get a really thick string </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 01:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you link to the program website? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 05:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another good one is the Joyo flanger, if the behringer is out of stock everywhere. Mine was $30 USD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 02:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to go under to anesthetics and get knocked out when I get my wisdom teeth out. FUCK THAT SHIT   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 05:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Praise be to Gaben.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 02:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I'm thinking of getting a Sansamp and running my signal chain sansamp for DI, then running to my pedalboard then into the bx500. I could then use the built in DI in the carvin as a post fx DI to the board, as it is just the pure sound coming in and not affected by the tone or gfx eq, and then using the preamp/gfx EQ to adjust the amp for stage mix w/o affecting the FOH sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 01:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok that's what I thought. I'm just confused about the "major" arpeggio I was taught, as it included the 7th as well. Would that make it the major 7th arpeggio and not the major arpeggio?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 01:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer:  I'm just a metal enthusiast, not a gigging professional by any means.  

Your bass should be fine.  the only thing holding it back is it is a 34" scale length, which means the low B string will be a tad loose.  35" is ideal for a 5 string.  However, bass is a 5 string with a 34" scale length, so its not too big of an issue unless you're trying to get an extremely low action, as the shorter scale length means less tension, which means the string will vibrate more in the middle so you need to a have a higher action to compensate.  In terms of upgrades the bass is probably last on your list.  

Right now your number one priority should be amps/pedals.  I am by no means an expert on metal bass, but I have a tiny bit of experience so I can offer my input, although I feel more comfortable talking about pedals as compared to amps.  It seems like you're interested in what I would call more extreme metal, as compared to Metallica or Iron Maiden.  Some people might suggest the big muff pi, but in my opinion that won't be beefy enough, you will want a dedicated overdrive pedal.  A lot of the touring bassists will use something like an Axe FX and actually blend use guitar amp models to get their crunch for their tone (Paulo from Trivium, Nolly of Periphery for a couple examples), but that would be too costly for you. The sansamp DI box has a pretty decent drive channel based on what I've seen on youtube, so you might want to look into that, plus you get the DI to boot.  I'd look into the para drive model, as the adjustable mid range will be essential for using it in a metal band, as compared to the presence and blend controls on the regular.  Something like the Boss Bass Overdrive or MXR bass overdrive might suit your needs, watch some youtube videos or try em out and see what you like.  It seems like that bands you linked to weren't maxing the drive channels, just adding a bit of grit to the tone.  

I don't want to say to much about amps because I don't feel like I know enough in this category. What I will say is don't skimp on wattage, especially if you are not going to be using XLR/DI lines.  I personally have the carvin 510 combo amp found here: http://www.carvinguitars.com/products/BR510

The really nice thing about this amp is the fact that it is their BX500 head mounted to what is essentially a rack mount on top of the cab. So if you decided to switch to a rack unit, you can remove the head and affix it in your rack, as it already has the mounting unit.  Or if you decide to get a fullstack, you can remove the head and use it with the new cabs. The main things I like about the amp are the adjustable DI level so you can adjust it as needed to run to FOH, active/passive switch with a -10db pad for active basses, and the parametric midrange EQ gives a lot of midrange control.  If you decide to go with a combo I think that these choices from Carvin are awesome, but if you decide to go with a traditional halfstack maybe laying out what I liked will help you choose an amp.  I really don't know much about amps because I got this one as my first one, and don't see any reason to upgrade it unless I get to the point where I'm playing gigs where 500w isn't enough.  I snagged mine from 300 USD used as well, so you might be able to find a steal on the used section of guitarcenter or your local craigslist.  

Lastly a note about buying used:  it's fucking awesome.  Its a great way to try out a bunch of new stuff.  Guitar center is awesome because of their 30 day return policy.  So if you get something and don't like it, you can return it and its like it never happened.  Craigslist is great because sometimes you find awesome steals, but the downside is no return.  Unless your planing on going on tour, buying used is a great way to get some good gear at a cheap price.  Ex:  Boss bass overdrive $110 new vs $50-55 used.  MXR Bass compressor $190 new vs $100ish used.  

Hope this helped a bit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 00:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What amp and bass are you currently using?  You say you use whatever cab they have there, so I'm guessing you have your own head.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 00:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an Ibanez SR305.  I pretty much use exclusively bridge pickup only.  Mine has a blend knob so I could move in some of the first pickup if I wanted, it just gets a much fatter bass tone with just the bridge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 00:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question about arpeggios, which I'm working on learning right now.  Back when I played guitar I was only taught the major arpeggio.  However, when they taught it to me it had a 7th in it as well, ie with your example it would include the B note below the octave.  I know that technically an arpeggio is the notes of a cord played individually, so would I have been taught the major 7th arpeggio instead of the major arpeggio then? Its throwing me off because I know a bunch of triads from guitar, but I'm not sure if those would be considered arpeggios if the notes were played separately.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 04:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're more into modern metal, run a MXR fullbore metal into a clean channel. I found running it into an amp with high gain in a solid state preamp muddied the tone, while running it on clean kept it crisp. I didn't have an OD pedal at the time, so I can't tell you how that would affect the tone. I think it would sound better with preamp gain if it was a proper tube preamp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 23:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want to do it with a metronome and you do it to make sure the timing is correct. Doing it this way ensures you hit the chord change right on the beat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 17:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone keeps saying progressively speed up, but I say progressively slow down. The main problem here is that your fingers don't have the muscle memory to make the change, so trying to go fast doesn't teach your fingers anything. By progressively slowing down slower and slower, you can really focus on what your hand needs to do to make the change and focus on building the muscle pattern. This strategy was taught to me by my drum teacher and it's really effective. You won't see results in a day, but one to two weeks in and you'll see some great improvement. Slow is smooth, smooth is fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 18:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would toss the Phase 90 before the OD/distortion.  Other then that looks pretty solid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 23:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the bx500 head myself. Highly recommend, can get some great sounds out of it. I'm a huge fan of the graphic EQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunlop gator grip. I was using .58s before but I picked up .72s today and I think I'm in love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really an artist, but Drake from Drake and Josh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 19:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about getting shogun 2 or Rome 2 from total war series. Thoughts or recommendations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 19:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just say this. I never thought I would like turn based until I tried x-com.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 19:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the bar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 16:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't understand how to integrate F along the boundary curve.  All the examples we did in class + the ones in my textbook are in 2d, so I'm not sure how to parametrize the boundary curve, because in the integral of F dot dr, the dr becomes (dx/dt, dy/dt, dz/dt).  Do I just ignore the z component and treat it like a circle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Calculus] Help with Stokes and Divergence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 05:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having some problems with assigned questions to answer for my calc class.  

1)  Verify Stokes Theorem by computing both integrals, the range of integration is z= sqrt(4-(x^2 ) - (y^2 )) above the xy plane and F = 2x-y, yz^2, zy^2).  Computing via Stokes was trivial, I have no idea how to approach the problem by doing the surface integral though.  I tried parameterizing in spherical coordinates, but converting the vector field to spherical got extremely nasty. 

2) Verify the divergence theorem by computing both integrals for the vector field F = x^3, y^3, z^2 over the cylindrical region x^2 + y^ 2 for o = z = 2.  Here when I computed by the div theorem, I got 279 pi, but when I did it the long way I got 243 pi.  Ive got back and checked my work multiple times, but cant figure out where I went wrong.  For the triple integral, I got my divergence to be (3r^2 + 2z) {in cylindrical} and my limits where {theta = 0...2pi, r = 0...3, z = 0...2}.  

For the long way I parametrized in terms of U and V, getting r(U,V) = 3cosU, 3sinU, V U=0...2pi, V = 0...2.  ru cross rv turned out being (3cosU, 3sinU, 0.  my final integral was 81(cos(U)^4 + sin(U)^4) with the U and V limits listed above.  If anyone has any clues as to where I went wrong I would appreciate the help   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 22:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would get rid of the era restriction-I find it much better to have the higher quality units.

Logistics: Get rid of the 85 cost choppers and either bring in cheaper ones or more trucks.  If you one those choppers gets sniped it will hurt.  

Infantry: Drop the RBS 70 Stringers and pick up a card of SAS. Higher HE, bigger squad size, better training (elite vs regular).  Only downside is the lower range, but I think the other benefits are much better.  I personally would take the UK Gurkhas 90 over the Hudou-ren, but the Hudou might fit better with your play style.  Both are good choices, mainly personal preference here.  

Support: Drop one of the mortar cards. Not only is it slightly overkill, but you don't have any SAM radar AA.  For mortars I would suggest checking out the French Serval.   It has a low range but a ridiculous fire rate of 17 rpm. For Radar AA my go to is the 90 cost US one.  High range and accuracy make it a great pick, just place it towards the rear of your AA net to keep it out of harms way.  I would also recommend swapping out your artillery for the Swedish BKAN.  

Tanks: Looks fine.  

Recon: Looks pretty good.  I personally always run 5 cards of recon, I like having the depth and flexibility to run some more aggressive scouting, but its a matter of personal preference.  
Maybe consider a lower cost helo.

Vehicles:  Consider dropping the M163s and picking up an IFV with an auto cannon.  I've been messing around with M163's and haven't found a great use for them yet.  IFVs with auto cannons are fantastic infantry killers and are one of my go-to units.  I would recommend checking them out, you may find you love them or hate them.  If you take off the era restriction I recommend the ASLAV-25. 

Helicopters:  I would drop the bushrangers and pick up the US UC-1H heavy hog.  In addition to having a similar rocket launcher, it has the frag launcher which is a great way to deal with pesky infantry units.  If you can free up some spots I'd also recommend taking another card of AH-1s.

Planes:  Here is the real weak point of your deck in my opinion, for one key reason.  Sub-par air superiority fighters.  Look into taking something like the F15 Eagles or F16 Block C from the US, as they have longer range F F missiles vs the semi-active ones on your craft.  Your bomber/AT selection is up to you, but I found that running the F111C made it an instant target for my enemies and it always died very fast, because they would go out of their way to target it.  Consider maybe taking some napalm as well.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 21:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primal fear is amazing. I recommend alive and on fire, and king for a day from their 2014 album. Seven seals is another great song closer to blind guardians sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 01:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No radar AA? I could not run a USSR deck w/o my BUKs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 02:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why no tanks under 50 cost in the mech deck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for those of you with on bass pre-amps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 04:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you guys set-up your eq? Do you run with your on-bass cut and do your eq on the head and roll up the highs and lows when you need them on the bass ,or start with them maxed on the bass and roll them off when necessary? Or do you start with the on-bass pre-amp in the middle and use them for minor adjustments?  Just curious about the different ways people go about getting the tone they want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melodic death metal: Children of Bodom, follow the reaper. Exceptional album.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 20:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything by sabaton. I like playing 40:1 while playing as the polish army or into the fire while doing napalm runs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 18:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you get by with only 3 cards of recon on that USSR mech deck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 18:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of fighting an armored red for deck, maybe try mechanized as well. Would be less tanks but metric shit-tons more infantry and vehicles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know voices by disturbed and bring me to life by evanescence both do as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 17:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sultans of swing - dire straits  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 22:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long do you recommend spending on each page before moving on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 18:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...you're telling me I could have been using the book of Cain to identify my old rares instead of individually clicking and discovering each one!?!!??!? *facepalm* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 17:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I was clearing torment 1 ele prison rift extremely easily, then ran into a pack of soul lashers, and they were literally impossible to kill. Two of the affixes were illusionist and health link, and it seemed like it linked the illusions health with that of the main champs, so they never died. The other possibility is that I somehow got two packs with almost identical affixes (all of them had illusionist/health link/jailer, I don't remember the other ones).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 01:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My for sure legendary at the end of act 5 was a worse amulet then a rare amulet that I still have from 60. It's just disappointing, because the amulet was part of a set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you guys doing with your blood shards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 00:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 14:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I died like five times to those damn flamethrowers :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A really fun song to learn is peace of mind by Boston. The lead part with distortion sounds great and the solos aren't too difficult, and the acoustic sounding rhythm has a great chord progression. A tad difficult for the first couple songs you'll learn, but definitely a good one to work towards. 

EDIT: LEARN HOW TO HOLD A PICK PROPERLY!!!!!!!! I took four years of lessons when I was younger and grew to hate guitar, because I was holding the pick between the tip of my pointer finger and thumb, and my teachers never corrected me. I got rocksmith a few months ago and learned I has been holding the pick wrong all along. After learning the correct method, I've been having a blast playing and now I can do strumming patterns without wanting to go cry in a corner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> System of a down is a lot of d drop c or e flat drop d flat (on mobile so can't do fancy symbols). Aerials and toxicity are d drop c, BYOB is e flat drop d flat. BYOB is a great song to work on alternate picking and speed in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking for a trashy china the Wuhan 12" China is fantastic. It's like 25 dollars and it's one of my favorite China's. I also have an aax mini 12" China. It sounds pretty good, but it's very bright. I tend to use it as more of a crash/accent cymbal, and do any riding on my wuhan. Both have pretty short sustains, can be good or bad, idk what sound you're going for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say moving the accents, how are you changing them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 13:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went up like 30 paragon levels, plus leveled wizard, barb and dh to 60, giving me one max lvl of each class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 20:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More guitar/fret based knowledge  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like the bell. Using the tip of the stick gives a nice sound for lighter rock, while the neck (The part below the tip that fans out to the shaft) of the stick gives a very full and cutting sound for more metal/core music. I'd play it for yourself, I like it but that might just be because it blends well with the music I listen too. I don't think the bell would work for jazz that well, but I would probably want a dry ride for jazz anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know of a good theory resource website? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried looking in the FAQ, but was only able to find the YouTube series on basic music theory. Basically what I'm looking for is a website that has all of the scales (major, minor, pentatonic, etc), chords, barre chords, arpeggios and other such items. I used to take lessons when I was younger and have been playing a lot of rock smith lately, but I've been looking to improve by getting more of the technique and theory down that I have forgotten over the years. All I remember are the basic cords (a-g major, a couple of the minors too) and the pentatonic scale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally love my 20" A Custom Medium Ride. The only area where I can maybe see it falling flat is dynamics at low levels, but it would depend on the music and sound you're going for. I know you said you had tried the 20" A Custom ride, but I would recommend checking out the medium version. Great ping when played near the bell and a nice wash when played near the edge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to progress through books like Stick Control? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 23:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently working on the books stick control and 4-way coordination, and had a question about progression. Is it better to move forward at a snails pace and really master each page at a time? Or to move forward somewhat quickly, exposing myself to more variety and then continually repeating through the book. 

I ask because I've seen some people say they've worked through the book in three months while I've spent the past 4 weeks on the first three pages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 23:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot of people recommending stick control, which is indeed a great book. I would caution against purely working from that book alone, however. If you spend all your time on the practice pad you could easily become bored and give up all together. If you get a book on limb independence and spend some time on the kit with it in addition to stick control, you will probably see more growth as have more fun. 

If you do pure SC, you'll probably end up with amazing chops but be stuck on quarter notes for the feet. If you do all limb independence you'll probably be able to bust out some insane linear groves, but the lack of technique with the hands will quickly put an upper limit on your progress. If you do both, you'll be well on your way to being an excellent drummer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 23:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend 4-way coordination for a book on limb independence. I think mine was $7 on amazon with prime shipping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 19:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get to practice my drums whenever I want!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 21:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well for example I use my whey as a post workout supplement, but I really enjoy having some chocolate milk in the morning. Instead spending an extra $60 on more whey for two months, I spend $20 to get some BCAAs to take with my chocolate milk. There was an article I saw by Lyle McDonald (on mobile so I don't have link) where he examined protein timing, and came to the conclusion that having large amounts of leucine was the key factor in muscle growth. This basically allows me to get the most out of the protein in my chocolate milk. I used to take four scoops of whey a day (2 scoops for 2 shakes), but after taking the second shake I always got a massive headache. Cutting out the whey and using alternate forms of protein such as chicken with BCAAs has gotten rid of the headaches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 21:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could also supplement with free form leucine which is found in BCAA powders, and use any form of protein you like  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO NOT GET UNFLAVORED BCAA'S. That shit is literally the worst stuff I have ever tasted. I just got some grape flavored stuff and it's incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 05:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently level 5, and just played a game where it was me and two level fours vs six level fourteens. Total bullshit other then that pretty fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 06:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times should we loop the bass track for the submission? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 17:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mines more like a logbook/journal combo. I keep track of what drum rudiments I should practice that day, all my exercise stuff, a section for upcoming dates, chores, hw and fun stuff I have planned. I then have a section at the bottom for any random thoughts. Ever since I started my performance in school has gone way up, plus it's helped me cut down on my gaming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 16:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Children of Bodom is a better example of melodic death metal. Look up the songs lake Bodom or Blooddrunk for examples, on mobile so I don't have any links  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 01:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just the angle of the camera, but I've noticed indie rock/gospel/jazz drummers tend to have their crash cymbals more parallel to the ground, while metal/metalcore drummers have them on a steeper angle. Any particular reason for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indie rock drummers, what is your setup like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 00:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my friends has asked me to join a indie rock band they are starting as a drummer. Right now I play metal, and my current setup is too large and complicated to set up every time we would gig. So I'd just like some ideas on what should remain in my kit. Right now I have a pearl export kit, with a 22" kick, 14x5 snare, 10",12", and 13" rack toms, 16" floor tom, 14" a custom hi hats, 16" aax studio crash, 14" a custom crash, 18" a custom projection crash, 20" a custom medium ride, sabian b8 pro 10" China splash, 12" aax mini china, 14" wuhan China, and 8" apx splash. I also have a cowbell and mounted tambourine. 

Also, if any other drummers have gone to indie rock from metal, if you have any tips or tricks, or other things I should focus on, I would love to hear what you've got.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 21:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to say ATG front and high bar squats. And yes to being able to overhead squat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 16:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I can do ATG and high bar squats fine. The weird thing is I can squat 135 front squat pretty easily, but 135 on low bar is pretty much my max  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 07:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I build up the core strength to do squats with proper form? I can leg press 500lbs for 8+ reps, but my core starts caving at 135 lbs on squat. I haven't been able to break 135 with proper form for the last two weeks. Running Lyle mcdonalds generic bulk, so I'm squatting 2x per week 3 sets of 5. Are there some good supplemental exercises I could add to help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 23:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Activists complain about lack of diversity at mass grave  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 23:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. She got pregnant and had a kid within a year of graduating high school  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 06:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy johns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 17:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep improving technique, learn more metal songs, and possibly joining an indie rock band  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 08:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like it because it lets me position my toms in a lower position. I could mount the toms above the bass drum, but they would be much higher and have sharper angles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 19:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to nephalem trials? Those randomized dungeon runs were the thing I was most looking forward to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 18:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good idea. I'm finishing up my linear algebra course right now, and all throughout the semester my prof was showing us examples of how to use the concepts we were learning in diff eq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 23:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started going gray at 15. I'm 20 right now and rocking it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 05:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never EVER buy mint chocolate. Tastes like ass. Dissolves great though   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
