<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In A Zen Sense, Why Aren't Animals Enlightened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to me they don't concern themselves with much and pretty much take life as it goes, so why are they stuck in Samsara? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Aren't Animals Enlightened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to me they don't really concern themselves with much other than what is necessary. Why are they stuck in Samsara then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Zen but that sub's filled with so many trolls I can't get anything of substance out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Like To Imagine Zen Started </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Bodhidharma comes into China, sees a Daoist*  
Bodhidharma: "Hey, what are you doing?"  
Daoist: "Uh, nothing"  
B: "Why?"  
D: "It helps me accomplish things"  
B: "Like ending suffering?"  
D: "Uh, sure?"  
B: "Cool ty" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one seems shorter than the rest, is it the full text? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Translations of Chuang Tzu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read the Burton Watson translation and found that pretty good, however it's very expensive for ebook. I've found some cheaper ones, one by David Hinton and one by Martin Palmer. Are either of these good or any others that you guys would suggest? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Toe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 06:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why you were downvoted for this. This is all true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Later forms of Buddhism draw extreme distinctions between Buddhas and arahants, but in the Nikyas this distinction is not as sharp as one might expect if one takes later texts as the benchmark of interpretation. On the one hand, the Buddha is an arahant, as is evident from the standard verse of homage to the Blessed One (iti pi so bhagav araha samm sambuddho ); on the other, arahants are buddha, in the sense that they have attained full enlightenment, sambodhi, by awakening to the same truths that the Buddha himself realized."  
-Bhikku Bodhi, "In the Buddhas Words" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a Bodhisattva in Theravada Buddhism means that you are a future Buddha. Buddhahood is not something that is all accessible like in Mahayana, so not everyone can be a Bodhisattva. Arhats are also considered to be just as enlightened as a Buddha in Theravada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both models of the s8 will have the edge display, however looking at some of the previous leaked images the curve seems to be the same on the front glass as the back glass, similar to the Note 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Assistant works more like an AI where it's more conversational. It can learn about your habits and recall pieces of the conversation from earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~But it is indeed a bulldog statue. I feel like it would make more sense for it to be a buddha statue or for the title to be "I thought she said buddha statue" and have it be the bulldog.~~  
  
EDIT: I GET IT NOW  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While righteous anger and retribution can be immediate fixes for a problem, it will not get rid of the existence of such a problem. For example, if there is someone bullying you and you fight back, a majority of the time the bully will stop bullying you and might even stop bullying people altogether. However, there are still going to be bullies, this was not fixed. Compassion on the other hand will stop bullying altogether. Teaching people compassion from a young age and throughout their life will eliminate poor ways at their roots. If someone is bullying you, attacking you, etc., the Buddhist way would be to be kind to this person, offer them help with whatever may be bothering them, show them what is good. There was a story a couple months ago about a black man who decided to become friends with KKK members. He would go to their meetings, have knives and guns pulled on him, have horribly racist things shouted at him, but he did not act poorly back. He sought to be nice to the members and treat them like who they are: regular people who just don't have correct knowledge. Because of his kindness, 200 members left the Klan. Not because he asked them to leave, he said he didn't do that, they just saw his kindness and realized that that is what is wholesome. Hate and retaliation does not have the ability to succeed like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly to have faith that the Buddha knows what he is doing and to inspire others to have that faith as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's where they're wrong. Because of the fact that we are void of Self, we don't die. It is merely a body that does and we mistake that to be us. Therefore our experience then is going to be very similar to our experience in life since nothing really changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - The newer "Touchwiz" experience. I'm craving Samsung features with a smooth and good looking UX.  
- I'm a sucker for the edge screen, they feel so nice to use.  
- Better battery life. I'm planning on getting the regular s8 since I miss one handed phones and don't need bigger than a 5.8" screen, and it only has a 200 mAh lower battery than the Note 4 but a significantly more efficient chip.  
- I'm definitely going to miss the s-pen though. I remember hearing rumors that the s8 and s8 plus were going to support it since there's no Note 7 anymore but I haven't heard that rumor in a while.  
- Looking forward to using a phone with an actual finger print scanner. The Note 4's scanner is terrible and awkward to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get Gold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, let's see...  
  
Avalokiteshvara is the center of the circle on the right.  
  
Amitabha is the red Buddha in the circle on the left.  
  
Bhaisajyaguru is the blue one next to Amitabha (may possibly be Akshobhya, I can't tell what's in his hands).  
  
I've never been good at telling the wrathful deities apart. The most popular I believe are Vajrapani, Mahakala, and Yama.  
  
Uh yeah that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously you've never read the Platform Sutra if you think there's a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a few rocks and make a tiny rock tower somewhere on the desk. Throughout the day be mindful not to knock it over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd you theme the notification shade and the settings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing people talk about this on the other Android subs so I think it's just a problem with Gmail at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pixel was stated on release to have 2 years of software updates and 3 years of security updates, same as all Samsung flagships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you're thinking about the s7, wait til the s8 comes out; it'll lower the price of the former. LG phones are good and cool and flashy but suffer from instability. If you're looking for the easiest transition from IPhone to Android get a Google Pixel. If you're looking for the vast possibilities Android has to offer, get the s7 edge or  s8.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For every person that is born many other beings have to die for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's doing what?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Am in Possession of the Rarest Pepe of All Time, the Market is Safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago I drew a Pepe in a notebook without looking. I closed the notebook and it is forever in my closet. It has never been seen by anyone nor replicated in any way. This will never lose its value and in the case of severe market crash this may be used to respark the economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to explain to someone what the color blue looks like. Explaining enlightenment is similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when the S6 edge plus came out I thought "if this design had an s-pen that'd be the perfect phone" ;~; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Vans shoes for toddlers aren't called Minivans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because drugs make you realize things that aren't often noticeable much like spirituality does, however the realization that drugs provide are usually meaningless and are dressed up as being significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read "In The Buddha's Words" by Ven. Bhikkhu Bodhi. It's an anthology of the Pali Canon (the basic texts in all schools of Buddhism as well as being the central texts in Theravada Buddhism) with commentary and explanation by Bhikkhu Bodhi himself. It's a very long read, and the suttas can be at first a little annoying to read (there's A LOT of repetition) but overall it's really good and very informative.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon Security Update? Any Issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I received a notification for what I imagine is a security update last night. Anyone install this yet and are you noticing any problems? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are rumors that it will support the s-pen though since there's no new note for people to use right now. Definitely it won't come with it or have a dedicated space for it but I'm hopeful for this to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you let me know the name of this book please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! This sub has kind of become my go to for everything so I thought I'd ask here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah the plus is just the replacement for the larger "edge" variant but both models have edges so it's just the plus. There's still a Note 8 coming out in the fall with what's looking like the same naming scheme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Four Noble Truths are arguably the only thing the Buddha ever taught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I understand it's not meditative since I meditate every day but like you said people dress up experiences as meditation so I was just wondering on his behalf if any of you guys have ever experienced something similar. Thanks though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I said haha but he wanted me to ask around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Friend Had A Strange Experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as advice, the guided meditation is not strictly Buddhist. There's meditation for pretty much whatever practice you choose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got pretty good answers for the rest of the questions. In response to the app, I recommend Insight Timer. It's a timer with a lot of features and a very minor social aspect. It also has a log to keep track of your meditation and generates statistics to help you develop your meditation. It also has guided meditation.  
Wish you luck on your journey!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea but if you read the reviews everyone is there because of problems with their Note 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
