<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6768</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're gonna love it! Great city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago: "hold my beer"... http://trib.in/2oDWBbY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely safe for work. Unless your organization is against boring photos of girls in cardigans and hipster hats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would do her taxes because I'm a CPA, and they were due yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smothering delicious fried foods in salty gravy shouldn't be a thing. Screw Canada. Hockey blows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a local school with an adult program. One night a week, 8 week courses... Something more convenient for working adults.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toastmasters... Public speaking applies to all majors, and you can continue to be involved after college. Great organization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go with the MSA. Makes you infinitely more marketable, and allows you to teach at the college level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 150 credit hours is typically a baseline requirement for the CPA exam. I'm sure you'll need a certain amount of coursework in different disciples of accounting as well. Check out the specific requirements of your state before making a move. They will want to perform an official transcript review of your credits prior to examination (they will point out deficiencies in your education)... you don't want to come up short because you decided to study Thoreau.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe the Milwaukee Brewers' Famous Racing Sausages is the greatest of all MLB sideshows. And, this shirt rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's CPD... He's lucky to be alive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
