<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4049</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 23:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually got my hopes up in a totally heterosexual way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 20:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 20:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please explain to me why... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 20:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you had to leave the door open AND the glass storm door open? That's like an invitation for bugs to come in. I don't understand why you considered this the first option used to "cool off". 

We have A/C and windows with screens. If you wanted more air fluctuating throughout the house, you should have just opened up the windows. 

Now, we have a bunch of flies in the house, having an orgy in our living room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 00:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I love winter!

Every year for the past ten years, I would go outside at night on the first day of winter break during or after it snowed and just stand in one spot (it was usually right outside my front door) and listen. I wasn't listening for anything particular, I just loved how winter could make everything so quiet. And no matter what time of day, it was always so bright, because of the snow illuminating everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 20:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say that all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 18:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never catching cases, why they faces look so e-m-o? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 00:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's sounds so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ate chicken...a lot. 

Grilled or breaded, boneless or not, dipping them in Ranch, Honey mustard, Marinara Sauce, hot sauce. Sometimes I would order pizza with chicken on it. Chinese food would always have chicken in it of course. I would mix chicken in with everything, fruit, salad, you name it. I even ate leftover KFC on Thanksgiving. That was a sad day for me, I ate the chicken in my parents laundry room so no one would see me. I honestly had an addiction to chicken. All that's over now of course. 

I really love bananas now. I just hope I don't get as attached to bananas as I did with chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 20:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this is reddit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I saw that there were pics leaked online of Jennifer Lawrence and several other celebrities (that I'm not all too familiar with) I got excited. I think Jennifer Lawrence, Ariana Grande and Kate Upton are hot and so are the celebrities that I do know.

 When I seen the pictures I got 'ready' but for some reason I didn't want to. I think I was more curious than anything. I realized that these pictures don't really mean anything. I mean, I could put my hand over the face in the picture and they just become another woman from /r/gonewild. Oh and I also prefer video to pictures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 01:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf and I are both 20.

I'd like to have sex at least every other day, especially since the relationship is quite new, but we both have things we're busy with all the time and we never really find time. Sometimes we hardly see each other. 

I wish I could give you advice but I'm not sure if I can. I'm not that experienced with relationships. And I'm sure you wouldn't want advice from a 20 year old guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 22:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only told my parents what happened in the video and they asked me the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 08:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I feel like she tries this whole 'slut persona' thing to come off as edgy. 
 I'm not sexist against women comedians. I just don't like Amy Schumer as a comedian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't like The Simpsons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really got into the the show.

 I'm sure I would of loved it as a kid but I loved Cartoon Network and Adult Swim. 

I also had a strange obsession with Old t.v. shows like Cheers and Three's company.


I'm 20 btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to take a note from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 07:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was a 1v1 with Syndicate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 01:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm depressed, I can finally admit that to myself. It doesn't make me feel good that I realized this. It feels as if I never got the weight off my shoulders, but just added more. And it is almost enough to pull me down, but I'm trying to keep my head up. In High School, I would get stressed really easy. The school work was sometimes hard to understand and whatever mistakes I made, I took to heart. The stress was so overwhelming that I would shut down. To make myself feel better I would play my Xbox and talk to friends. As the work got harder, the more I played around. It got so bad that I almost didn't care for school anymore. After graduation, I had no direction in my life, and I hated that. I'd ask myself, "Why? Why would I choose games over living my life the way I wanted?" Instead of trying to change that and move forward, I went back to my old ways. Doing this over and over, I started to regret the fact that I didn't take school more seriously, the fact that I could of gone to a better college. I always had the potential to do my work thoroughly, I just couldn't handle stress like others. And now, I'm just depressed, spending most of my days regretting the same thing since I graduated. I don't talk to family or friends that much anymore but I try to keep a smile when I'm asked if I'm okay. I use to hangout with friends and workout and actually have a job, now I sit in my room nearly all day, watching Netflix or Youtube, losing myself in someone else's life trying to forget just for a 'little while'. I barely have friends, I have no job, no car, I hate the school I go to, I rely on my parents for help even though I don't want it, I have problems dealing with my emotions and I don't have any real direction in my life. I know I could easily fix all of this, but I'm nervous, scared and confused. I feel alone and I need help. I'm not happy here anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 03:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 15 and I had a lot of Greek Mythology books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 00:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TimeSplitters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 02:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was awesome. I mean if one thinks about it, sure it seems *bad* because it's really not the kid's fault, but you wouldn't have done it if that woman would've raised him better.

 You're definitely not a bad person, every person has had their bad days. I only see this as sweet revenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 08:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No more outlets to lick I guess..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 04:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 03:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take the last word if it makes you feel better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 01:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to you, I'm a high school student, so I should be out on break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 21:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you had better things to do? It seems like the more I reply, the more I realize you really don't have much going for you, which also explains why you're so unpleasant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 19:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 18:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good God... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 18:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that maybe what I said got to you. I guess it can't be helped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 08:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't patronize me. I said one word. Honestly, from what you've said so far, it seems like you're the type of person that likes to be right, even if it means making yourself look like a complete dumbass. How could you possibly think you're right? Is it because this post was reposted somewhere else? Do you actually have full proof /u/OB1FBM's post was a repost instead of the other way around? And even if the other person that posted this original post and said, "I'm the actual OP, that post was a repost!" would you a believe him?

Let me ask you this, why are you doing this? This post was 4 months ago, what's your purpose here? All I wanted to do was see the most upvoted stuff on Reddit and I see your obnoxious comments. You putting other people down because someone called you on your bullshit. I don't know if you've heard but over 50% of the reddit posts are usually reposts and /u/OB1FBM's post is legit. You would know this if you were here when it was originally posted, also somewhere in the comments, someone put up a JPEG showing that he was on the banned list for sharing these pictures on Reddit. I think maybe you should spend a little more time 'investigating' before making such foolish assumptions such as this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 04:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 21:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That, or most of us aren't morning people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks awesome, I was thinking of getting an Op tat but I'm not sure what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 02:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an awesome album. The different poses in the pictures and the added gifs makes this one of the greatest albums I've seen on gw in some time. You've satisfied quite a lot of redditors, including me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 22:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Japanese poem "Tomino's Hell" creeps the hell out of me. People say that if you read this poem out loud bad things will happen like getting sick or even dying. After I read the story,  I stubbed by pinky toe on a door frame and that was enough to terrify me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 22:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait..how did you get this? I'm for certain that I didn't see this before...what the fuck is going on?

Edit: Oh I see the second link, nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 11:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously can't do this without getting hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 11:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if Wikipedia says it's okay then it must be safe...I'll be back :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 11:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must have been a traumatic experience, I'm sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 01:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 09:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're doing a great thing driving people, but were you nervous about giving strangers rides? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 20:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you do when you have to use a public bathroom?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 19:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe it or not this still works to this day. Whenever I would get bored, I would go to website source codes and just look them over on my laptop. Well one day my classmate comes over and says, "holy shit..how did you get there!?" I responded,  "I just right clic..." but before I could fully explain myself he already asked me if I was hacking. I just said that I was looking over source code because I liked to, I understood the code. I told him I wanted to be a Web Developer. 

He just walked off. A week later and everyone and their grandmother thought that I was a hacker. Everyone around me started acting disturbingly nicer to me. It was really weird. As the word spread more and more, I was approached by campus police, I explained my situation and they believed me. Not a big deal. Now just for fun I like to go on Hacker typer (a fake hacking website) and scare the shit out of people from time to time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 09:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had..I mean STILL have the same problem. After I got out of high school, a lot of my friends moved on to different things as well as I did and I found myself more alone than ever. My every day routine was, school, work, gym, and homework. And I'll admit, I loved it for a short while, but the daily routine was boring so I tried to see if I could contact my old friends. Most of them were busy or didn't respond at all. Still feeling lonely I decided to sign up for  a bowling league (I'm not suggesting bowling and I'm also not an old man just in case you're wondering - I'm 20 btw) now you may not like bowling so the thing I suggest is try to get involved with something, a sport, club or volunteering. You'll have fun and make friends I'm sure of it. Then once you get over some of the anxiety you get then it'll be a bit easier to approach other people randomly. Signing up for that bowling league helped me make more friends and I'm much more happier now.


Edit: If you still go to school, I have more advice if you'd like to hear it? Anyways, I hoped that this somewhat helped you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 07:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I look at this, I feel like there is a secret message in it. Like there are short simple words spelled wrong, yet bigger words are spelled correctly,  there's also black in some words and numbers for example,  the "6 6 6" has two black sixes and one red six.

I would like to think there's a secret message in this, otherwise I think I've gone crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 22:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have this problem myself. Earlier this year I got into a car accident with prior back problems, I thought I was ok from the accident, I was clearly wrong. When I visited a chiropractor,  he told me my pelvis and hip were out of place and a bit twisted and that my left leg was a half an inch shorter than my right. After being adjusted several times, the lower part of my back and body are almost back in place, but I still have leg problems,  especially in the morning, it's like a sharp pain in my lower back shooting to my calf. I hope I get fixed up as well as you did.

Oh and I forgot to mention I'm only 20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a picture...go bitch about this on Facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 20:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's a baby raccoon, they end up carrying diseases but they aren't born violent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 08:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best thing you can do is just give good advice, whether you think he was diagnosing her or not doesn't necessarily mean it was arrogant. That's what you perceived I guess, either way there is no reason to get upset, it was just an opinion and I'm sure not all of us think she is depressed that's why other people suggested other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
