<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6817</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont. There is no way for anyone to claim you have bitcoin when its in your own wallet. 

Also, you dont have to pay taxes on a gift. You were supposed to pay taxes on the gambling but those were lost. Tell the IRS "I win" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That Former VP Joe Biden has been caught on tape molesting the children of Senators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cabin in Colorado for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At that point, watch carefully, because there may be a way to move to the side that you prefer (and "double down" on that side

Can you explain this further? How would I turn 10btc into 20btcu? Wouldnt that mess with the 21M cap?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erdogan tells off Merkel for using phrase 'Islamist terrorism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god i shorted table salt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft is BEGGING Trump for exemption from the travel ban, they dont get that their H1B Visas are next! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 

You worked hard. 

You had terrible luck and still overcame it. The extreme majority of people in your situation never would have bothered, that is why you shouldn't be happy paying so much in taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> earnings call at 330 PM EST </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im not sure what paper trading means, can you explain briefly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he claims its because of terrible sales in Asia and the headphone jack basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods, are we allowed to talk about the retarded trader in r/wallstreetbets? The one betting on AAPL to tank today? 

I am very curios about this subs opinion on the matter, you seem a lot more intelligent than that trading sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The policy is not based on race or religion. The largest Muslim countries aren't even included (Indonesia   ksa for example)

Its relevant because you guys dont bitch and moan that I cant move to Canada should I choose. instead you freak out over some kid from Iran who doesnt get to go space camp.

How many Christians (ie legit refugees) did your boy Obama bring in from Syria? None.

Im not even white btw, I just dont like when you people keep shit-talking them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we need to let in every person who wants to come or we are as bas as Saudi Arabia. Have you ever tried to move anywhere besides the US? Do you have any idea how hard it is in almost all countries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> off the total bill for 90 of them i believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which western nation committed human rights violations? If you have any info on this please share!

Oh, you meant America enforcing our sovereign law, never mind... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING: President Trump reaches agreement with LockheedMArtin to reduce F35 cost by $600,000,000.00 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldnt have to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF? I love stoning rape victims now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought USD was divisible by 9 decimals... Isnt it better than BTC that way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we need to meme this into REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen If President Trump got on board with funding the backlog of rape kits in America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are almost half a million untested rape kits in the USA, it would be an objectively *good* thing to test them and throw the criminals into a deep dark prison.

The second benefit is forcing CNN and JigglyHuffPo to claim its somehow bad since it will cause more illegal immigrants to go to jail.

This isnt Saudi Arabia after all, we aren't supposed to let this happen here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Biden Making Children Uncomfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confirmed: President Trump is going to tax or withhold ALL remittances to Mexico until they pay for The Wall! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In regards to getting your guts sucked out of your asshole by a pool drain... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was rewatching Season 7 Episode 5 and thats how Frank explained his brother Gino's death to Dennis   Dee

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND 2015 AND 2014 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really should lighten up on yourself. This anxiety is caused by you elevating your mindset and lifestyle. Just because other people have more than you, you cant be satisfied with what you have accomplished?

Why get a phd in medicine if you wont even be the one to cure cancer? Should every NFL player quit if they wont go to the superbowl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I broke my mouse and couldnt upvote any more Donalds so I just posted another one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UBI is a retarded pipe dream that will never work. If there arent enough jobs, we should have less people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt you hear? Everyone is going to make "art" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your model in Exhibit A is accurate, where does that put the price in 2-5 years? Can you post a graph like this one just for fun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 tick

What does that mean?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wouldnt happen that fast, would it? 

they would need time to sell, cash out fiat, wait for wire deposits, buy the gear, set it up and then start mining

Unless they thought 800 was the peak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have them sit with you and buy one of those reports from creditkarma that shows you a full breakdown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely positively. I make enough that I dont qualify for any subsidy yet the premiuims are obscenely high for a family of 4 in NYC. 

Me and my wife both work full time. We are thinking about having my wife stay home so we dont make as much and will stay in a lower bracket. 

Fuck all of you who say this is fair. I hope you get aids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a whiny fag. You have 300,000 friemds in here right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should expect all the Chinese exchanges to start imposing trading fees, they were making a fortune off leveraged trades/interest fees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, its more of a problem for skirt steak due to the shape. Think about it, it comes in a long thin strip. If you didn't know much about steak, wouldn't the most logical place to start cutting be across the skinniest part? 

The majority of people cut the wrong direction btw, I try to educate everyone i eat with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave the fat.

The trick for skirt steak is to cut it against the grain! I learned that from Alton Brown. Its so weird how that simple knife cut takes skirt steak from tough leather to tender goodness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2 Terms, the media covered less of Obamas scandals than they did in 2 weeks of PEOTUS Trump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who spends a fortune on forklift maintenance every year, this is going to cost Gazillions of dollars to keep operational. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.businessinsider.com/brutal-conditions-in-amazons-warehouses-2013-8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They treat employees like shit and hurt all the smaller local businesses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trendy Millenials hate Walmart buy are die-hard Amazon customers even though they are exactly the same. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
