<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2779</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 13:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Few questions.
You had a single harddrive in a Raid Configuration?
This might be silly, but many people have done the misstake, are you using the video outputs on the motherboard or on the GPU? silly mistake, but easy to do. 
If you have a video output on your motherboar, try disconnecting your GPU and use the internal one instead. 


If you get your PC to POST - go into bios and restore defaults. 

Feel free to ask questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 15:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May you tell me why? 

I don't see a reason behind this. It's better they know why i might have bad days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long did you take your medication before you noticed a change with how you felt? And how long until you were off the meds? 

Thanks for your help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 23:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a good explination, thank you.  And yes.. Most people i've told have just Said "but you seem so happy". Yet they never really see me, i've been living Alone for about 5 years. 

Thank you for answering, take care of yourself, you lovely Human 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 14:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of files are we talking about? Is it Microsoft office files, like excel, word? 

Those files tend not to be infected, viruses tends to create new files on hidden places of the computer.

Plug the USB in your infected pc, only transfer the files you **need** to your USB. Plug it into your fresh, clean pc and follow the instructions [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/techsupport/comments/33evdi/suggested_reading_official_malware_removal_guide/). Make sure you run them on your USB and not the harddrive, since the harddrive should be clean already. And run the searches a few times even if it says it's clean. 

I'm not sure if anyone have mentioned it in the comments and I don't have time to read it all. But disconnect your Infected PC from the network and internet so the virus wont transmit whatever info it has gathered. 

If you have any questions or if I explained something badly, just ask and I'll try to explain it in a different way. 

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 22:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well...](https://gfycat.com/FormalNaturalBluet)

All credit to /u/Your_Dads_Stroganoff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's common, uncommon or weird. But I like the muff to be hairy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use big pillows and have a friend willing to build them with you. Always better to build with someone than to build it alone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully kindness and friendship. I care about everyone, even the strangers on the internet.

Hey /u/Obiblog, you're awesome. 3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always tell people to have backups of their computer and such. I dont have anything I can't get from the internet on my pc. 
And most of the information is in the cloud anyway. Or at work. 
(I work in IT) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 16:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh if he's a computer teacher he Should know about logs and the like, and even if it was you. It was ITs fault you had admin tights

Edit: Rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 11:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be happy. 

???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 11:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/HighQualityGifs

/r/GifTournament  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 11:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 14:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its an .exe file, just run it and when its Done you can just delete it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 01:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bud! Much appriciated! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 00:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May i ask where this is from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
