<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7382</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put some pepperonis in it I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leviathan or spriggan. Wouldn't use way of fire or the other one you mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious how it stacks up in VMA for burst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very old deltia at that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good observation/tip homie, +1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pacific rim?! Man I give that movie 2 thumbs down. I thought it was gonna be 2 Asians licking eachother's buttholes not robots fighting space lizards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noxious doesn't provide a spell debuff. I'm asking if it would remove that debuff by applying noxious over pierce  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, they absolutely don't stack as they both have major breach. But the override of the skill over the other is what I'm inquiring about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [discussion] Noxious breath/Pierce armor, Debuffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all,
  
I had someone in my raid group last night urging me to not run Noxious, as it overrides Pierce Armor. Can anyone shed some light on this so I don't have to test it later? This was the only time I've heard this.
  
I've heard of similar debuff skill stacking issues, with ele drain/pierce armor. 
  
Regardless, your thoughts and expert opinions are appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is the impasse I'm currently facing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OBJ, Demerius Thomas, Crabtree, Edelman. Pick 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to help me decide between Crabtree and Edelman. I'm gonna have to flip a coin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some grand assumptions there, bubs. And no I frequent The Intercept and glance/bounce between all the major shitty MSM sites. It seems you're pretty heavily entrenched in CNN as your main source after reading this thread and your posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking lots of kool-aid, fam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the treasure hunter passive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks a bunch alcast. PS I'm starting to hear a lot of random people in Xbox NA talking about your builds these past few weeks. Nice work posting such great content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey that's nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pepperidge farms members </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the far eastern side of wrothgar. 
  
I've heard of peeps getting through it without CP in vet...but these folks have run it countless times and know exactly where things spawn when, and what mechanics are avoidable. 
  
Try it out and see what's up! The difference between difficulties from normal to vet is astronomical. 
  
Tbh I 'got gud' by shedding blood sweat and tears in that arena. First compete was at 300 cp. could have been earlier if I had known my build better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha nice bro. I had a feeling you of all peeps on here would be aware. 
  
I'm still waiting for the skin, got twins down to ~3% the day before it was broken. Obviously haven't gotten past first boss since. F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your reasoning for thief always being better? I feel like once you get to 80ish percent crit the shadow would provide so much more of a dps increase. I don't have a dps parser so you're my connect to real numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twelve deep just got 2 completes in vMOL this past week. Turns out you just need to be able to beat first boss with 7ish people. And get lucky that the 5 who DC'd aren't integral to the fight. Ducking ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't make a heavy tbs set fam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I got my jeep stolen from there last year!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to play this trial on Xbox. Ffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 16:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master bow sharp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 23:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love ESO. It's an amazing game. I've been playing since its launch in Xbox and have learned so much, made tons of friends, and really progressed in this game and all of its difficult content.
  
The day before the patch that broke minor slayer and vMOL I almost had my first complete with my group. Brought the twins down to 3% and shortly after a few more tries, we called it a night.
  
Please fix this soon. It is absurd this hasn't been addressed (really addressed, not just telling us 'soon') we bought the game, we are subbed, we purchased the content and the content is broken. Fix it please. Should have been fixed over a month ago. Why hasn't it?
  
Sorry if this has already been asked, there are already over 350 comments at this point.
  
We should be the ones deserving the apology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space litter removal. Think of all the debris and shit floating around up there; and how much there will be with more ventures into space.
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upside? Some dodge chance. Downside? You lose one of these aether/twilight/spc/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 22-24k tempers. Rip indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eso Econ sim is very strong on xbone. Sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice response. To add- you can get under and behind that waterfall. There's a little cave that 2 people can sit in. Pretty much dead center of the waterfall. Neat little space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's to my understanding that the zones will be a lot like wrothgar and the other dlc zones. Scaling people up to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm personally on the fence about it. I see both of your points and totally agree that melee should absolutely pull more dps than ranged. 10-20% more IMO. That being said I do think a nerf was warranted, keeping in mind the TG patch where flurry cast time was reduced, the weapons weren't compensated accordingly. Now I do think this nerf was a tad heavy-handed but like you said, in the end it will still be on top.
  
Buffing VMA staves would've made content for everyone too easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main thing with viper is that it's a "surprise burst"
  
A lot of times people don't see it coming and get rekt if my other dots tick simultaneously. Dizzying-poison inject-random viper proc- bye bye! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run that set up on stam sorc and dk. It's nasty good. Dueled some friends for a few hours the other day and won out almost every time. I run it with either serpent mundus or the shadow depending on what I'm doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, it mathematically harder now. It definitely stung getting a cuirass of glory on my first complete, though, so I'm ok with the change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've got it all. What I need-ish now is a precise inferno (I have sharp) and a sharp maul (I have the sword and axe sharp). So I'm done if I want to be. Probably 50-60 clears total... Most before the guaranteed drop change a few patches ago. I've had the most luck with the weekly rewards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gold sharp VMA flame staff.... Wait for it..... In the weekly rewards mail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are essentially worthless for trading after the time window... So why would you even charge? Maybe a tip sure... But if you didn't need it then what's the point?
  
That's what I don't understand about bop trading. If you don't need it, and someone else wants it, give it to them. Otherwise it's not ever being used in your bank.
  
I understand selling the item only if you actually need it for a toon. I sold a precise moon dancer sword for 100k because I legitimately wanted it for my Templar alt, but a group mate needed it for his main to complete the set. I still think I overcharged him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 14:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's killed one of my end game trial guilds. Caused a few people to take a hiatus. This with the minor slayer bug really pissed me off. I'm still pissed off. To add... A couple days before 'they broke it' my group and I got the twins down to 2% and promptly ended the raid night... Had we gotten through that part the skin would have been mine. But it's not, and won't be for who knows how long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it 160?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't done normal, just V. Haven't acquired any gold jewls. Those used to exist when they were pvp rewards way back when. Correct me if I'm wrong someone.
  
Also I think the Jewelry drops on the last couple rounds before final boss fight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DSA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aayyyyyy I got ze joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who you callin yops, pal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard Chillrend pronounced, children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nerienth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed an opportunity with Georgia... Cumming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 23:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say I didn't specify, in regards to the parent comment, that dual wield gives you higher base values than a destro. What I'm getting at is it doesn't matter what 1 hand you use, in overload mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twin blade and blunt passive for swords increases damage done, not base values. A dagger is as good as an axe and sword, in overload. Go test it out and get back to me with your findings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weapon type doesn't matter when in overload, just the trait of the weapon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you help me place this call? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just telling it like it was told when I heard it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The food at the stripclub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to stripclub last night, they had a special on the burgers and dogs. My buddy Ray ordered the burger, I ordered 2 dogs. 
  
After our topless 'waitress' walked back into the kitchen, I caught her slip a frozen party into her armpit. 
  
When she came back with our drinks, I asked "WTF, why is that in your armpit! And why is it STILL in there?!"
  
She told us it was to defrost them.
  
I told her to cancel my order of 2 hot dogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Clinton is elected president... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be the first time two presidents slept with each other... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just telling it like it was told to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Trump is elected president... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will be the first billionaire to move into government housing after a black man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anamorphic projection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's attached to yo rod muthalicka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VO shoulders and boots go well with most everything. I really like the shoulders with DC med chest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah same here. VSO hm isn't bad at all if everyone can avoid the meteor. HRC HM is insane, need to find a better strategy for that then what we've been doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early as a month late as never  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, hopping in there on my stam sorc in about an hour. You do HM yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Which trial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this idea. It's ridiculous and hilarious. I don't see why this couldn't twerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 18:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen one in the chest. Got a sharp fire in the mail tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gotta be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only take the SPC proc when no other allies are in range of the SPC buff. Human PC's get priority. Saw this in action last night on vAA. Pets are everywhere now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 20:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My RNG sucks pretty much always... But I did get the skin on my fifth~ try. Now I didn't use it as much. Spiderkith rulez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your thoughts on infused for MSA 1 handers? I'm assuming it's still weaker than precise or sharpened but the increase in enchant is pretty significant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloodspawn in spindle clutch has been used as a metric to figure out your DPS. Divide his health by your time to get your avg DPS number. Tbh I think the fight is too short for some classes to get their justice. I hear the add before the braziers at manticore in VSO is better for testing as he has much more health and hits like a wet noodle. You need a tank with vigor to hold aggro, and a stopwatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scathing performs better in trials than TBS, FYI. There's some vids online proving it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the main- 65 days. On the 2nd main 12 days. And then there's 3 which are slightly less than that. 
  
Scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll still see a significant dps increase using VMA weapons with any trait over non VMA weapons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could've/should've stopped at 'button.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. I'll expect an update in a few years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minor slayer isn't working whatsoever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
