<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8653</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to hear this! Nothing gives a greater feeling than playing around and roughhousing with my kids. I used to have problems with these kinds of activities before but now I tire my kids out. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. I know right thank God! Anyway, I was just following the format sent by the mods. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing your thoughts! Very much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sound advice! I'd keep your words in mind. Many thanks! That's why I love it here in Canada because people are so nice and polite!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm a Freemason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense now that you put it that way. Thanks for the insight! It's the season now so I might give it a try. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm the only child so I suppose there's something in me that does things for the applause. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid advice. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for taking the time to share your thoughts. I very much appreciate the kind words. I am currently very much obsessed with Muay Thai!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm just privileged to have a lot of computer access today because my twins are sick and not in day care. I just put them to sleep just now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would sometimes- depending on the strain. Indica from time to time gives me the munchies but I'm more interested in moving around than eating nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Filipino living in Toronto. 3 of my 4 kids were born here. We would love to visit Thailand one day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was also stuck in the "I'll start tomorrow" loop. What changed that was when I made my Movember day 1 video and published it on my social media pages on my business website. From that point on, there's no turning back.

why you smoke marijuana 10 mins before working out?

I'm about 10 minutes away from the gym. I find that I'm more in tune with my natural body rhythm if I'm "high". I find that I can skip rope better and I can focus more in technique and power. 

Do smoke only before workouts or are you a recreational user?

I smoke in small amounts (like a bowl per session) throughout the day. I roll joints and enjoy it with my neighbors on Friday nights. MJ helps me with my PTSD and, previously, chronic pain. 

Are there benefits to smoking before exercising?

I'm burning plant material so first there's the risk to your lungs. As for benefits, marijuana affects people differently. It makes me mentally and physically active because of the feeling of motivation that I get from it (it's hard to explain, but I feel it in my chest and my stomach, like a feeling of excitement of some sort). I prefer Sativa in the morning and Indica for night time. 

I hope this helps. There's no shame in asking questions. ;-)

edit: fixed formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can, so can you! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SMOKES! That's an awesome transformation my friend! Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To a lesser degree, I was like that too because of my planar fasciitis. It got so bad that I was supposed to be on cortizone injection treatment plan. That was before I did my Movember diet gimmick coupled with intense physical workout. I used to wake up early in the morning and be in such pain that the few steps that I have to take to get to the washroom becomes a journey to Mordor. I still get the occasional pain on my foot but it's nowhere near as bad as before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words! Much appreciated! Maybe I'll do another video next Movember. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I nerded out on Muay Thai so it became more of play than chore. I love it! A little bummed that I missed my training today because my twins are sick and I'm on daddy duty. Maybe I'll sneak out sometime tonight when my wife and our eldest are back home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha! I like your comment! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cut my carb intake (mostly rice) in half and that helped. I still snore but it is now mild and I don't wake up in the middle of the night gasping for air anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With [these things](https://www.google.ca/search?q=acupressure+ball+plantar espv=2 biw=1366 bih=599 source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwjciNCIj9LLAhWG1CYKHTp0CIMQ_AUIBygB) and a lot of stretching. All the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear you're doing the right thing my friend! Keep going! Stay strong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do kabayan, kapuso, kapamilya LOL! Ask for a free tryout class! New in TO, where from originally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL! That's an awesome thing to say. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. But I was diagnosed with severe sleep apnea. I couldn't believe it when my doctor told me the amount of times my brain would wake up within the span of 1 minute. It was crazy. I almost died on my sleep twice because I choked on my own tongue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words! Agreed! Exercise and sunlight combined is the Way, the Truth, and the Life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words! My legs used to bother me because I'm short at 5"7 and they looked too round. When I joined Muay Thai, it turned out that it's [easy for me to develop leg muscles](http://i.imgur.com/kf71bSY.jpg) and now I'm so proud of them that I'm in danger of getting obsessed! LOL

edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't lose hope. Stay focused. "If you're going through hell, keep going!" - quote by one of the greatest minds during the great wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't do Cheetos munchies but man could I eat Honey Nut Cheerios like an animal. I could graze on Cheerios with milk from morning till night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words. I appreciate it! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's impressive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words! The conditioning was hell I'm not gonna lie. But the soreness is overwhelmed by a greater sense of well being that I feel after each workout. I strive to be consistent and not miss classes. The more stronger you get, the less painful the routines become and with proper nutrition your recovery rate will speed up. There are high kicks in muay thai but lower kicks is more powerful and can do more damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. My wife and I joke around a lot about our past immaturity. Can't wait to spar with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was younger, I would smoke and then watch TV and eat junk food or simply hang out with friends and do nothing. I discovered later on that being a couch potato causes me great grief and anxiety because life will catch up with you if you're living your life slow. I simply switched from smoking and watching TV to smoking and just listening to my body. The best time to listen to my body I find is when I'm doing something productive such as cleaning the house, making art, or working out. I used to get anxious thinking that people judge me when I'm high- but that was because I used to procrastinate when I'm high. Now I have better control and I don't give a hoot about what people think.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never tried canned anchovy. Now you got me curious. I would eat tuna in moderation because I read somewhere that the bigger the fish and the longer its lifespan, the more mercury will accumulate in its body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any tips on finding a good gym and what to look for?

If the gym have kids and they treat the kids well, that's a good indicator that you have a good and well balanced gym. [Here's our head instructor doing pad work with my 6y/o](https://youtu.be/Zhx1QqRYL0Y). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love sardines! I did the 30 day sardines diet because I kept on telling my wife and kids that I like it so much I could probably eat it everyday for a month. They challenged me and I accepted.

edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh trust me. The cops got involved a few times. We were in a bad situation before. We still attend marriage counselling. Now we're more mature and respect each other a lot more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I've been hearing a lot of good stuff about Krav Maga as of late.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not really working that well.

How's your diet though? For me that was the toughest part to change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is with a social environment like the gym, it trips me out haha.

I see what you mean. I go to the gym, nod to people and show them a smile, and then I get to work. I can't say I don't socialize but I keep to a minimum and I focus on what I was there for. That way I don't trip out. :-)

Edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you will! :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going public with my intentions and crazy antics did a lot of help too. Thanks for the kind words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try good quality sativa my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thank you for sharing that! True words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sativa for daytime, indica at night. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your kind words and sound suggestion! I smoke sativa throughout the day to keep me alert and some indica at night to help me relax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never too late! Like what Winston Churchill said "If you're going through hell, keep going!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't really explain it... It puts me in the moment or in the zone so to speak... I get to feel my body better. I hope this helps. I can elaborate more if need be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if I confused you and other folks here. I no longer need the CPAP machine and my wife is happy to report that my snoring is now manageable. I haven't been to a sleep study since my transformation so I can't really tell if I still have the apnea. I'm feeling great in the mornings though unlike before so I think I have apnea defeated but perhaps not 100%. Thanks for suggesting nasal pillow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if I confused you and other folks here. I no longer need the CPAP machine and my wife is happy to report that my snoring is now manageable. I haven't been to a sleep study since my transformation so I can't really tell if I still have the apnea. I'm feeling great in the mornings though unlike before so I think I have apnea defeated but perhaps not 100%. Thanks for suggesting nasal pillow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I no longer need the machine but I really appreciate the concern. Sorry for the confusion! Before my physical transformation, it was so severe that I would choke on my own tongue. Now even the snoring is down to minimal. 

edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear that! And thank you very much for the kind words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I do. I don't use it. Can't sleep on my side with it. Air leaks. Tried different masks already. :'-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing your thoughts! I tremendously enjoy the psychological benefits, I'm really happy seeing the physical changes too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! If I can do it, so can you and anyone else. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thank you for that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your comment my friend. Working on getting more sleep! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change your thoughts, change your life! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I did so much damage to my body when I was younger that I felt that it was too late. I mean I was on Lipitor before I hit 30s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your comment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, tell that mods. It's their own wording. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  35 with a 15 year old. 

I know right. Bums her out when people think that she's her mom's sister.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks man! MT is life! Wishing you all the best! Power, safety, and victory! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason it makes the workout seem easier because weed puts me in the moment. Not really for depression because smoking it used to make me anxious. Now that feeling of anxiety is replaced by feeling of elation and motivation. I hope that makes sense.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't crash. I'm always on the go throughout the day. I think the weed helps. My doctor is against it though I must say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! Never too late! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words! I appreciate it!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words and the nutrition tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you Bro! Keeping the fun alive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you! I hope to be able to say one day that I'm in better shape in my fifties that when I was in my earlier years. Keep up the great work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I would love to fight but I don't think I'm ready yet so I'll just make bags cry for now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 09:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to disappoint. Since I never played sports, I thought and felt (not anymore) that I was way beyond my prime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 09:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 09:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! First day of school today. They should be waking up 3 hours from now. No sleep for the wicked (lies, I'd probably get atleast 2 hours)! And then training at 1PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 08:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Best comment ever. She's pleased. :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input! [I'm working on it](https://www.instagram.com/p/BDHr0IaQu5C).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for taking the time to leave a detailed response! I very much appreciate it! My wife and our trainer always tell me the same thing- to hold my hand up. Thanks for the tips! As for reaching further with the kicks, [here's how I kick the heavy bag](https://www.instagram.com/p/BDHr0IaQu5C).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will keep that in mind. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm feeling blessed! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a CPAP machine that I don't use. It doesn't allow me to sleep on my side because the air would leak. Already tried different masks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words! Very much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the best my friend! It can be an uphill battle at first but stick to your guns and the rewards will be incremental! Most difficult to give up for me was my addiction to donuts. I used to have it everyday with my coffee and cigarettes. Now for breakfast I typically have cheerios or oats. I can feel the difference in my performance if I start with a good breakfast. 

edit: more words for clarity of message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
