<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same issue. Today I did "Brownie Batter". 1 scoop protein powder, 1 TB ground flax, 1 TB raw cacao (great source of Magnesium!), 2 TB half and half, 1 TB melted butter. Mix and eat with a spoon. You can also microwave it for 20 seconds and get a nice Mug Brownie. 240 cals, 21 grams protein, 14 grams fat, 3 net carbs. (I use Reserveage Nutrition grass Fed Whey) TBH you can probably do this without the flax and it will still taste good.   

I also have a container full of cooked chicken thighs in my fridge at all times. Buy in bulk, cook on meal prep Sunday! Snacks and meals for the week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ingredients: 
* 1 TB butter (melted)  
* 2 TB Half and Half  
* 1 TB Super Sprouts and Seeds (or just use ground flax seed)   
* 1 TB unsweetened cocoa powder  
* 1/2 scoop Chocolate Whey Protein (I used Reserveage Nutrition Grass-Fed Whey Protein)   

  Mix ingredients in a mug, and zap for 20 seconds, or just eat raw (brownie butter!) 
  
  Macros (via MFP):  240 cals, 16.5 fat, 13.5 protein, 3 NET carbs.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Dessert] Chocolate Mug Brownie (recipe and macros in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leftover Xmas presents for my coworkers. Spouse was supposed to take them to work long time ago. Thankfully those were the last of em!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I tried it, I drank it on an empty stomach before my morning workout. (Which I remember was a leg day) I remember having crazy, focused energy that morning, of the same caliber as just having drunk NO Explode/Jak3d or other pre-workout, but without the unwanted jitters. I also hit a new PR on deadlifts that morning. I've never been able to replicate this first feeling though, and now I just do strong, plain black coffee to save on calories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ate at a significant deficit the last 7 days and was enjoying the initial water weight landslide on the scale. (Started Keto Dec 15, but had several setbacks. Didn't solidly find my footing until Jan 2.)

  Today, I had terrible insomnia (only 3 hrs.), shark week started, and I just had little to no energy (still trying to find the right mix for the potassium/magnesium/electrolytes thing). On top of that, I was given some bad news, which sent me into a chocolate binge. (Ate 8 of those damn Lindt dark chocolate truffles!).

  Now I'm lying in bed, feeling like absolute shit, knowing that I'll have to take several steps forward just to get back to where I was.  I take full responsibility for where I am, though. NYE 2017 will be the last time I ever resolve to lose weight, and Jan 10, 2017 will be the last time I lose control with food like that! Open to any and all advice on how to undo the damage!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 07:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost track of time during a 16/8 IF yesterday and missed my protein macro by 12 grams. How bad is missing one day? Will it throw off Ketosis? (Was only at 19 net carbs for the day.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
