<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7578</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 09:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Relationship between observed upper mantle structures and recent tectonic activity across the Southeastern United States](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JB012698/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds likely cause for recent southeast U.S. earthquakes: pieces of the mantle under this region have been periodically breaking off and sinking down into the Earth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 09:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 09:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, and to be honest... even though I have given other single malts a higher score... it is one of my favourites as well. It's certainly not what I consider perfect in one sense, but I have packed many a flask with Talisker (more than any other), but it's certainly perfect in another sense. A flask of Talisker on a stroll down the river banks in the autumn, a flask of Talisker to keep me company on the mountain when the air has a bite to it, a flask of Talisker around the fire after the hunt has ended... perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Candidate microbial ichnofossils in continental basaltic tuffs of central Oregon, USA: Expanding the record of endolithic microborings](http://gsabulletin.gsapubs.org/content/early/2016/04/20/B31380.1.abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microbes Make Tubular Microtunnels on Earth and Perhaps on Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A number of pebbles(?) look weakly stretched leading me to believe this is metaconglomerate (see stretch pebble conglomerate [photos](http://skywalker.cochise.edu/wellerr/rocks/mtrx/metaconglomerateL.htm) for example).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little slow on the draw is all. I post the link to the photograph, and then do the write up (can't do it the other way around as far as I'm aware). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Colour*: Golden Honey

*Body*: Full bodied and oily

*Nose*: Citrus, hints of malt, spice (cloves), smoke and peat

*Palate*: Fruity, dried fruit, fruit cake, mixed peel, and prunes. Rolled in clouds of peaty-smoke, with hints of malt and sea salt.      

*Finish*: An explosion of pepper, warming, and long.

*Score*: 88/100

Notes: The picture shows a pairing with [Omnom Papua New Guinea 70%](http://www.omnomchocolate.com/collections/selection-of-omnom/products/papua-new-guinea-70) chocolate, which on its own is a delightful treat, let alone pairing it with Talisker (an excellent pairing I might add). The tasting notes for this Icelandic chocolate are as follows: The sophisticated union of nutty leather and smoky tobacco plays with a whisper of burned oak tamed by a buttery bourbon finish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #6: Talisker 10 year old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volcanoes erupted beneath an ice sheet on Mars billions of years ago, far from any ice sheet on the Red Planet today, new evidence from NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The phylogeny and evolutionary history of tyrannosauroid dinosaurs (open access) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 11:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 05:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of statements within that article that, to properly address your question, would take considerable time and effort to research and cite. I would also state that I am by no means an expert with regard to whisky, and the details within. 

I would, with some degree of speculation and well educated assumptions, however, feel somewhat inclined to agree with the following though also remaining, to a lesser degree, somewhat sceptical:

Oxygen is extremely reactive, and makes up for about one fifth of our atmosphere. Almost any material undergoes a chemical reaction when exposed to oxygen, a common example being metal rusting. Exposing a distilled alcohol to oxygen will cause chemical reactions with the unwanted congeners mentioned above, facilitating their removal from the product. Wood is porous, allowing for only small amounts of air to pass in and out of the barrel, controlling the rate at which the congeners are oxidized. During this process, some ethanol will also oxidize or simply evaporate, and the proof (alcohol-by-volume) will drop slightly. This is called the "angel's share," as early distillers saw the volume drop by itself and so believed that angels watched over their products and took some as payment. The type of climate aside from temperature does play a small role here, though not a very important one. For example, barrels aging near the ocean will absorb small amounts of salt water, but this is very low on the list of reactions affecting the spirit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 11:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's quoted quite often from a number of distilleries, though it's often met with a degree of scepticism. The following is an excerpt from "*Micheal Jackson's Complete Guide to Single Malt Scotch*" 

Seaweed: *The medicinal note in most Isla malts, especially Laphroaig, surely derives from seaweed, a source of iodine. The sea washes against the walls at all distilleries, except Bruichladdich and Kilchoman, and the coast is enwrapped with seaweed. How do the seaweedy, ironlike aromas get into the spirit? It seems likely that that they are carried ashore by the winds and the rain, and permeate the peaty surface of the island. Then, when the rivers and burns flow over the peat to the distilleries, they pick up these flavors and impart them in the steep or the mash tun. If the boggy surface is, indeed, impregnated with the seaweedy rain, then a further opportunity will arise when the peat is cut and burned in the distillery's maltings.*

Breathing Spirit: *The greatest scepticism concerns the belief that the casks in the warehouses "breathe in" the atmosphere. Distillers who use central warehouses, away from the distillery, especially favor this argument*...

As for the actual science, it seems difficult to locate assuming it exits at all. A quick search did provide papers on flavours derived from the [composition of the peat](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19243172), [lignin](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/%28SICI%291097-0010%2819990515%2979:7%3C1015::AID-JSFA321%3E3.0.CO;2-R/abstract), and [charring](http://www.dcs.ed.ac.uk/home/jhb/whisky/papers/charring.htm) etc., but nothing on "breathing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 10:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a reasonable hypothesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White Tree Nymph (Idea leuconoe) - Olympus E-M5, M. Zuiko ED 12-50mm [OC][4608 x 3456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Differentiated impact melt sheets may be a potential source of Hadean detrital zircon](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/early/2016/04/27/G37898.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research suggests that the very oldest minerals on Earth, zircon crystals, are likely to have formed in the craters left by violent asteroid impacts that peppered our nascent planet, rather than via plate tectonics as was previously believed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Curiosity Mars Rover at Naukluft Plateau (360 View) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 09:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on the look out, being relatively new to the world of Scotch, to try a number of distilleries from Islay before venturing further and exploring other regions. I was fairly disappointed with the selections I had found at local pubs until I found a drink menu with a very reasonable selection from region to region. It was a Scottish style pub after all. It was the first one I ordered, Lagavulin 16... I took one sip, and my mind was set. I was to purchase a bottle the next day. It is, without a doubt, one of my top most favourites.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers Have Discovered a Moon Orbiting the Dwarf Planet Makemake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Colour*: Deep copper

*Body*: Full bodied and oily

*Nose*: Butter and sherry, ever so slightly phenolic with noticeable wood-smoke and peat

*Palate*: A coating of toffee sweetness, vanilla - sherried - sea shells tucked in peat, sea spray      

*Finish*: A dry sweetness, long and smoky, fantastically smooth 

*Score*: 90/100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #5: Lagavulin 16 Years Old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50km/s is far too large of an impact velocity for an asteroid:

The minimum impact velocity on Earth is 11 km/s. Typical impact velocities are 17 km/s for asteroids and 51 km/s for comets. The maximum Earth impact velocity for objects orbiting the sun is 72 km/s. - [source](http://impact.ese.ic.ac.uk/ImpactEffects/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Hubble Discovers Moon Orbiting Dwarf Planet Makemake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red-eared slider turtles of Goodacre Lake [OC][4377x2528] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not, and the study TrillianSC2 references is an older study not without its criticisms. Furthermore, several other studies published after his cited study continue to argue in favour of Deccan Trap volcanism, or a combination of the two ^[1](https://news.berkeley.edu/2015/04/30/did-dinosaur-killing-asteroid-trigger-largest-lava-flows-on-earth/) . Perhaps more pertinent information is discussed within the paper itself, but going from the article alone I'm certainly not convinced of their argument. We have good [fossil evidence](http://www.yalescientific.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/volcanism4.jpg) in support of ocean acidification. Questions remain regarding the assumptions this study used regarding ocean conditions at the time, and how they modeled its behavior. My point is that /u/Gypsiee is absolutely correct in stating that the debate is ongoing.

EDIT: The Harvard Museum of Natural History hosted a lecture in March of 2015 called "*The Cretaceous-Tertiary Mass Extinction: What Really Killed the Dinosaurs?*" and if you think the debate is settled I would highly recommend spending the time to watch it, it's available on youtube. 

Excerpt:

Of the three mass extinctions that have occurred since 250 million years ago, they are all very precisely associated with large flood basalt volcanism, large igneous provinces (LIPs). The Deccan Traps for the K-T boundary, the Central Atlantic Magmatic Province (CAMP) at the Triassic-Jurassic boundary, and the Siberian Traps at the Permo-Triassic boundary. So the outlier is the Chicxulub crater of the K-T impact at K-T time. There is no evidence that is widely subscribed to for impact at any of these other boundaries. It gets worse. The Permo-Triassic boundary was recently shown, understood to be a double boundary with a peak here at the end of middle Permian or Guadalupian epoch and then the bigger peak at the end of the Permian. And the Emeishan Traps, eruptions in China, were at 260 million years ago at [this little peak](https://imgur.com/uBJ54BC) and then the Siberian Traps are here... so actually, the last four mass extinction events for which we have the best record are all associated with massive volcanism on the planet...  

The excerpt is not an attempt to convince you of one particular argument, but rather to convey to you that it is certainly not a settled debate, Alvarez himself shares just such an opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fountain in Beacon Hill Park, Victoria, B.C. [OC][4608 x 2471] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 17:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 19:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Long-lived connection between southern Siberia and northern Laurentia in the Proterozoic](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2700.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Large Igneous Provinces to test pre-Pangea or ancient continental reconstructions, researchers disprove previous constructions of Nuna-Columbia and Rodinia, and establishes new arrangements of the continental blocks within them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 19:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 18:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Yes, when ever I do timed exposures a tripod is a must. Sometimes you can get away with using nearby stable surfaces (ie. rocks, trees, and what have you), but that wasn't possible for this particular shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Colour*: Straw

*Body*: Medium body, complex

*Nose*: Citrus, nutty (almond), peaty, medicinal, phenolic

*Palate*: An arrival of peat, smoke and phenolic iodine... marmalade developing into pancakes, some black pepper, a slight maltiness and burning peat.      

*Finish*: Almond, cigar ash, peat, smoke. It is dry and warming.

*Score*: 87/100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #4: Ardbeg 10 year old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First North American monkey fossils are found in Panama Canal excavation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifty years ago, a graduate student named Walter Pitman made a discovery that would change the way we see our planet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 01:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although the current view is that large events [do not](http://www.bssaonline.org/content/102/4/1583.abstract) 'communicate' at global scales there is a small chance that we simply don't have the data to identify whether such a view is entirely true. More recent studies have found [a potential link](https://www.newscientist.com/article/dn23409-can-big-quakes-trigger-others-far-away/), and it remains an area of [active research](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v490/n7419/full/nature11504.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 16:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Dinosaurs in decline tens of millions of years before their final extinction](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/04/13/1521478113) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dinosaurs in decline long before asteroid catastrophe, study reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 16:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volcanic injection of stratospheric sulfate aerosols has been observed to have a *temporary* cooling effect on globally averaged temperatures (see: [Mt. Pinatubo](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Pinatubo#Global_environmental_effects)). Depending on the characteristics of the eruption from Mt. Paektu it is certainly plausible that a large, temporary, cooling effect could occur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Evidence for partial melt in the crust beneath Mt. Paektu (Changbaishan), Democratic Peoples Republic of Korea and China](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/4/e1501513) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking supervolcano makes North Korea and West join forces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the USGS: 

Can you prevent large earthquakes by making lots of small ones...?

Seismologists have observed that for every magnitude 6 earthquake it would take 32 magnitude 5's, 1000 magnitude 4's, 32,000 magnitude 3's (and so on for smaller earthquakes) to equal the energy of one magnitude 6 event. So, even though we always record many more small events than large ones there are never enough to eliminate the need for the occasional large earthquake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The footprints of the dead have revealed new secrets: Professional trackers can read a lot into the trails left by humans and other animals, and it turns out they can also interpret those left by our ancestors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Geomechanical analysis of fluid injection and seismic fault slip for the M4.8 Timpson, Texas, earthquake sequence](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JB012821/abstract?campaign=wlytk-41855.5282060185) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most comprehensive analysis to date of a series of earthquakes that included a 4.8-magnitude event in East Texas in 2012 has found it plausible that the earthquakes were caused by wastewater injection. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How A Geologist Designed The Perfect App For The Window Seat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 20:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 01:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open access: [Characterization of Greenbeard Genes Involved in Long-Distance Kind Discrimination in a Microbial Eukaryote](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002431) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fungi communicate by chemical signals only, but they, like humans, appear to use different dialects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 01:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Most diamonds were created equal](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0012821X16301005) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most diamonds share a common origin story. A similar mechanism for creating older, gem-quality diamonds and younger, fibrous diamonds suggests that Earth has maintained diamond-forming conditions for billions of years implying plate tectonics could have already begun 3.5 billion years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 03:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Years ago is an understatement given that it's not only biologically impossible (about 66 million years impossible), but physically impossible for such a creature to exist within the Loch (about 10,000 years impossible with the end of the Ice Age). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Partial collapse of the marine carbon pump after the Cretaceous-Paleogene boundary](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/44/4/287.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surviving an asteroid strike: A team led by experts at Cardiff University has provided new evidence to explain why deep sea creatures were able to survive the catastrophic asteroid strike that contributed to the extinction of the dinosaurs 65 million years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> International Chronostratigraphic Chart "Version (v2015/01)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 10:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. A common phrase is "the solution to pollution is dilution." Contamination within the immediate outlet, coastal waters, are of concern (fishermen are banned from operating within a 20-kilometre (12.4-mile) radius from the plant), however, the greater Pacific ocean has background radiation levels from naturally occurring radioisotopes orders of magnitude larger than what is being observed from input by Fukushima.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 09:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it beyond belief? The students weren't looking at internal exposure to humans, they were looking at external exposures both within (including the contaminated area) and outside of the Fukushima Prefecture and compared those values to other global values. Internal exposure levels were not a part of their study, so it should come as no surprise that they didn't look at that. 

That's how scientific studies are done, typically focusing and examining, in detail, a single variable or attribute. Now they have more data than they previously had, and internal radiation exposure can remain an area for future research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 07:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairewinds Energy Education... sounds like [a credible source](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Arnold_Gundersen).

Gundersen also contributes to [ENENews](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/ENENews), which is a blatant anti-nuclear propaganda website (related [1](https://www.dailykos.com/story/2015/02/05/1362607/-Misinformation-on-Fukushima-Impacts-Energy-News-Still-Undisputed-Champion) and [2](https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=857562314257491 id=186827501330979)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 03:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot of good science freely available if you are interested: 

[FukushimaInFORM](https://fukushimainform.ca/) (The Integrated Fukushima Ocean Radionuclide Monitoring or InFORM network) provides excellent up-to-date data and [Marine Chemist](https://www.dailykos.com/user/MarineChemist) has some excellent blog posts around the topic (it's best to start from the beginning). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 03:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's incorrect. They did measure levels in the contaminated area, just not *in* the students.

The individual doses (of *external radiation exposure* in high school students) were almost equal *inside* and *outside* of Fukushima Prefecture...

Actually, we didnt measure the doses *in people* living in the contaminated areas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...estimated radiation doses ingested by people living near the coal plants were equal to or higher than doses for people living around the nuclear facilities. At one extreme, the scientists estimated fly ash radiation in individuals' bones at around 18 millirems a year. Doses for the two nuclear plants, by contrast, ranged from between 3 and 6 millirems for the same period. And when all food was grown in the area, radiation doses were 50 to 200 percent higher around the coal plants. **-** [Source](http://www.scientificamerican.com/article/coal-ash-is-more-radioactive-than-nuclear-waste/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. The article is looking at '*what is*' not '*what if*.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fukushima students reach out to tell truth about radiation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 19:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Deliberate body disposal by hominins in the Dinaledi Chamber, Cradle of Humankind, South Africa?](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0047248416000282) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate Erupts over Strange New Human Species: Skeptic challenges notion that small-brained Homo naledi deliberately disposed of its dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 11:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant:
___

- [Staying Safe in Bear Country](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sFaspYZTG-A nohtml5=False) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five new landslide videos - two dashcam films from China, two rockfall films and a video from GNS about earthquake triggered failures - The Landslide Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 03:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Partial collapse of the marine carbon pump after the Cretaceous-Paleogene boundary (pdf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious Pull On Cassini Probe May Help Find Planet Nine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 09:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 07:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40cm (0.4m or 15.748 inches) sounds like a fair amount, but it pales in comparison to the solid rock tides of Jupiter's moon Io. As it orbits Jupiter it flexes resulting in immense tidal heating as the gravitational pull from Jupiter and it's moons change from with its location.

[Here](http://spaceplace.nasa.gov/io-tides/en/gll_moons1.en.gif) the gravity of Jupiter and large moon Ganymede (with help from moons Europa and Callisto) play tug-o'-war with Io playing the part of the rope! Io bulges on two sides. And, [here](http://spaceplace.nasa.gov/io-tides/en/gll_moons2.en.gif), Jupiter and all three of the other large moons pull on the same side of Io.  Io flexes again. This flexing of Io, tidal heating, leads to sold rock tides upwards of ~91m! There's a reason Io is considered the most volcanically active body in our solar system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 07:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A number of people have already stated several ways in which local gravity changes (ie. contrasts in subsurface density) but no one has pointed out the actual corrections that are accounted for during a gravity survey. When all of the necessary corrections are completed the remaining anomaly is known as the Bougeur anomaly (g_B):

`g_B = g^obs - g^base - g_D  g_L  g_FA - g_B + g_TC  g_E`

- g^obs is the gravity observed once solid Earth tidal corrections have been removed.

- g^base is removed permitting all site measurements to be correlated relative to the base station.

- g_D is applied hence removing instrumental drift over time. 

- g_L is applied to account for differences in Earths radius as a function of latitude. 

- g_FA is the free air (elevation) correction and is applied in order to correct for elevation changes relative to the base station.

- g_B is the Bougeur plate correction, and acts opposite to that of the free air correction.

- g_TC is the terrain correction and is applied when significant topographical differences are present.

- g_E is the Etvs correction and is applied for surveys conducted while in motion (on a ship, etc).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Evidence for long-lived subduction of an ancient tectonic plate beneath the southern Indian Ocean](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GL066237/full?campaign=wlytk-41855.5282060185) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive Ancient Tectonic Slab Found Below the Indian Ocean: Scientists discover a surprisingly positioned tectonic plate, buried below the southern Indian Ocean, that spans the entire mantle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to Dig for Fossils: Combining Climate-Envelope, Taphonomy and Discovery Models (open access) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercury anomalies and the timing of biotic recovery following the end-Triassic mass extinction (open access) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 17:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Really Killed the Dinosaurs? A project under way off the coast of Mexico may finally resolve a longstanding controversy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 09:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the use of the star tracker allow you to significantly drop your ISO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 08:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see what's so funny, it's a factual statement that you clearly lack the required information to make an educated assessment. That's not an ad hominem, that is very likely an objective and factually correct statement. However, I'm giving you the benefit of the doubt with that statement, because the other option is that you do have the required information to make an educated assessment but are simply incapable of forming the correct conclusion.

As I mentioned before, it's not just about trend analysis you have to look at the data alongside the trend. [Correlation and causation are easily confused](http://cardinschoolblog.blogspot.ca/2009/10/does-ice-cream-cause-drowning.html) and without looking at the data itself this is one of the many faults (no pun intended) you are making.

The scientists working [within](http://online.wr.usgs.gov/calendar/2015/aug15.html) and [outside](https://news.stanford.edu/news/2015/june/okla-quake-drilling-061815.html) of the USGS have all reached the correct conclusion, and yet you continue to maintain your contrarian view based on little, if any, understanding of geological processes. One last point I'd like to make... if you're proposing an argument to support your position it's good practice to at least know and use the correct terminology. You have consistently used "fracking" in the context of Oklahoma which is, so far as we are currently aware, incorrect. Induced seismicity in Oklahoma is a result of wastewater injection (disposal) wells, and not hydraulic fracturing as has been attributed to induced seismicity elsewhere.  

- [What's Behind the Earthquakes in Oklahoma?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kZUtfEv55Fg) - Stanford University </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 21:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said Oklahoma wasn't seismically active, I said it was "not very seismically active, relatively speaking." By its very nature, intracratonic, it is seismically limited.

Unfortunately I believe you're drawing conclusions based on ignorance, and I'm not willing to dedicate the necessary time it would require to convince you. There are far more data that are analyzed at length that have been used to draw the current scientific position on induced seismicity. Trends in data are one thing, the data itself is quite another. When one clearly lacks the required academic background to asses the data (not just the trend) it's considered a wise and intelligent choice to listen to those of whom do carry the necessary qualifications to make such statements (ie, geologists, geophysicists / seismologists).

"Everyone is entitled to their own opinions, but they are not entitled to their own facts." - D. Moynihan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The relationship in Oklahoma between waste water injection and proximity to fault lines is the major contributor to induced seismicity in the region. In other words, injection of fluids at depth increases subsurface strain regimes along seismically inactive fault planes, subsequently leading to their reactivation. 

Unlike Oklahoma, where the leading cause of induced seismicity is due to waste water injection at depth, hydraulic fracturing has been directly attributed to induced seismicity in [Ohio](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/2rjqad/science_ama_series_im_robert_skoumal_one_of_the/), and [Western Canada](http://www.seismosoc.org/news/ssa-press-releases/fracking-linked-to-most-induced-earthquakes-in-western-canada/) where the apparent dichotomy is a result of the underlying geology of the region. 

I've seen data that shows that Oklahoma has had almost no earthquakes since before 2010...

Oklahoma is not very seismically active, relatively speaking. The [increase in seismicity](http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2015/11/oklahoma-now-no-1-in-earthquakes.html) is linked to the increase in production ([see graph](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/images/OklahomaEQsBarGraph.png)), and can further be seen from the timing of the events which typically occur relatively shortly after injection. 

- [Animation of Oklahoma Seismicity: January 2, 2008 - February 14, 2016](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/OKeqanimation.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 11:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His co-authored paper from 1991: [Drumlins carved by deforming till streams below the Laurentide ice sheet](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/19/8/787.abstract)

And this study: [Erosional origin of drumlins and megaridges](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0037073816000142) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This week's batch of 3D models: Anorthosite with lovely garnet reaction rims, a spherical hematite concretion, and some sweet breccia. Check them out and explore! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 10:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 07:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - [Animation of Oklahoma Seismicity: January 2, 2008 - February 14, 2016](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/OKeqanimation.php)

- [as of Feb 17, 2016](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/images/OklahomaEQsBarGraph.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 07:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're extracting a resource, do you think it might be important to know what effects your activities are having in the subsurface and how they are being generated? While it's important to consider the felt effects on the surface to the general populace, if you're activities are near well populated regions, it's important to a) recognize that what you previously did not take into consideration must now be considered and b) what those effects are, and what the cause is. 

There a lot of variables at play, for example, induced seismicity in Oklahoma is typically attributed to waste water injection, while in Ohio there have been a number that have been attributed to hydraulic fracturing (similar to British Columbia). It's important to understand then why the dichotomy exists so that you can understand the potential risks associated with the activity as well as how to mitigate it or avoid it to begin with.

Recall the historical trend has been along the lines of 1) Hydraulic fracturing can't cause earthquakes 2) Waste water injection is the cause of the increase in earthquakes within some areas, not hydraulic fracturing 3) Hydraulic fracturing, not waste water injection, is found to generate earthquakes but they are thought to be small ( [minor earthquakes](http://www.geo.mtu.edu/UPSeis/magnitude.html)) 4) Hydraulic fracturing is linked to minor earthquakes 5) Hydraulic fracturing is linked to light earthquakes       

With the above noted, I would direct you to the following study regarding two earthquakes of 4.0Mw and 4.3Mw that occurred near Cushing Oklahoma as to better understand why these events, even though they may be barely noticeable to you, are of concern: [Reactivated faulting near Cushing, Oklahoma: Increased potential for a triggered earthquake in an area of United States strategic infrastructure](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GL064669/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 06:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are theoretical limitations with regard to the potential size of induced seismicity depending on its origin (waste water injection, or hydraulic fracturing). It has always been the position that seismicity induced by waste water injection has the potential to be larger than seismicity induced by hydraulic fracturing. An event with a moment magnitude that resides nearest the upper theoretical limits may then be called a "large" event within the proper context. In other words, induced seismicity from hydraulic fracturing that sits above 4.0Mw is a large event when induced by hydraulic fracturing. 

Similarly, it is a generally accepted that mega-thrust earthquakes are the only type of displacement capable of generating a 9.0Mw and that strike-slip motion is simply incapable of generating great earthquakes. So for [a strike-slip rupture to generate a 8.6Mw](http://www.earthmagazine.org/article/sumatran-strike-slip-earthquakes-challenge-seismologists) is an exceptionally "large" seismic event for being generated through strike-slip displacement.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another paper released today that I thought may also be of interest to you:

- Paper: [Hydraulic Fracturing and Seismicity in the Western Canada Sedimentary Basin](http://srl.geoscienceworld.org/content/early/2016/03/28/0220150263.abstract)

- Article on said study: [Fracking Linked to Most Induced Earthquakes in Western Canada](http://www.seismosoc.org/news/ssa-press-releases/fracking-linked-to-most-induced-earthquakes-in-western-canada/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Paper: [Hydraulic Fracturing and Seismicity in the Western Canada Sedimentary Basin](http://srl.geoscienceworld.org/content/early/2016/03/28/0220150263.abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fracking, Not Waste Water Injection, Linked to Most Induced Earthquakes in Western Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 02:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 02:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waste water injection is (currently) a part of the overall process for hydraulic fracturing so it's common for the general public to be less pedantic about the technicalities and simply lump the two together. Waste water injection is not injected into preexisting faults. It is injected into the subsurface at depth, increasing pore pressures, which increases strain on nearby faults which can reactivate them. Hydraulic fracturing, although rare, has been [directly attributed to induced seismicity](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/2rjqad/science_ama_series_im_robert_skoumal_one_of_the/) (Ohio, British Columbia) amongst induced seismicity as a result of waste water injection (Oklahoma). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Induced Earthquakes Raise Chances of Damaging Shaking in 2016. For the first time, new USGS maps identify potential ground-shaking hazards from both human-induced and natural earthquakes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 05:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Europa, and [Enceladus](http://www.space.com/29334-enceladus-ocean-energy-source-life.html) are strong candidates for the exploration of astrobiology. They may support a larger food chain; however, without extensive oxygen or sunlight I would argue that any life discovered wouldn't extend much beyond simple microbial organisms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 02:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The canyons, and other relatively low regions have less gravity because they have less mass present compared to regions of higher elevation. Notice that, without going into detail, that holds for Earth as well with higher anomalies present under mountain ranges and volcanic centres compared to those observed along the oceanic crust ([figure](http://eoimages.gsfc.nasa.gov/images/imagerecords/3000/3666/PIA04652_lrg.jpg)). This is easily seen with much higher resolution of the Himalaya and the Tibetan Plateau ([figure](https://geodesy.curtin.edu.au/local/images/res_him1_large.jpg)).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 02:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Molleweide. A simple google search will bring up endless results. For example, [here](http://cpgeosystems.com/mollglobe.html) are a number of Molleweide projections showing global paleogeography for the past 600 million years.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 01:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A convecting liquid outer-core is essential for Earth's self sustaining geo-dynamo. Earth's outer core is ~2,260km thick, and hot. Mar's outer core is ~200km thick and likely relatively cool in comparison to that of Earth's. It's likely convecting, but as it is likely cooler it's likely convecting at much slower rates - sluggish compared to that of Earth. It's also  10% the width of Earth's outer core so if it did exist it should be much weaker in comparison. Together, sluggish convection over a relatively small region, seems like a reasonable explanation as to the lack of a Martian magnetosphere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 01:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gravity anomaly is known as the Bouguer anomaly (g_B) once all the necessary correction factors have been applied. Gravity increases with height as you have more mass below you (Bouguer correction) but gravity also decreases with height as you move further away from the centre of mass (Free-air correction). 

`g_B = g^obs - g^base - g_D  g_L  g_FA - g_B + g_TC  g_E`

- g^obs is the gravity observed once solid Earth tidal corrections have been removed.

- g^base is removed permitting all site measurements to be correlated relative to the base station.

- g_D is applied hence removing instrumental drift over time. 

- g_L is applied to account for differences in Earths radius as a function of latitude. 

- g_FA is the free air (elevation) correction and is applied in order to correct for elevation changes relative to the base station.

- g_B is the Bougeur plate correction, and acts opposite to that of the free air correction.

- g_TC is the terrain correction and is applied when significant topographical differences are present.

- g_E is the Etvs correction and is applied for surveys conducted under while in motion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth's largest fungal habitat may actually be within the igneous oceanic crust (open access) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 08:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3.5 billion years ago, Earth's oceans were cool, not hot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did some field work relatively nearby and took a similar photo: [Botanie Rock](https://www.flickr.com/photos/luxlaboratories/19505403358/in/photostream/lightbox/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CO2 shakes up theory of how geysers spout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 20:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research (open access): [3.5-Ga hydrothermal fields and diamictites in the Barberton Greenstone BeltPaleoarchean crust in cold environments](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/2/e1500368.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Contrary to the belief that Earths early oceans were hot, new research finds the climate 3.5 billion years ago was a cold environment similar to more recent conditions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 19:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 18:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [The temporal scale of diet and dietary proxies](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ece3.2054/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a study published March 18 in the journal Ecology and Evolution, authors Matt Davis and Silvia Pineda-Munoz argue that scientists need to focus as much on when animals eat as they do what animals eat. Without the proper time context, they say, an animals diet can tell very different stories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 18:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 17:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Taxonomic reassessment of Hydralmosaurus as Styxosaurus: new insights on the elasmosaurid neck evolution throughout the Cretaceous](https://peerj.com/articles/1777/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new look at old bones reveals patterns of neck elongation in elasmosaurids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 17:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 03:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very fine sand is called clay...

Actually, very fine sand is called very find sand, and clay is called clay.

- [Grain size classification](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/e2/Wentworth-Grain-Size-Chart.pdf/page1-1275px-Wentworth-Grain-Size-Chart.pdf.jpg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 18:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Cellular dissolution at hypha- and spore-mineral interfaces revealing unrecognized mechanisms and scales of fungal weathering](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/early/2016/03/07/G37561.1.abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study suggests that scientists have underestimated how much fungal weathering goes on, and that cellular dissolution can ultimately account for 40%50% of the overall bio-weathering, significantly larger than the previous estimate of 1% contribution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 18:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 01:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Impact of meat and Lower Palaeolithic food processing techniques on chewing in humans](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature16990.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A recreation of how early humans managed to eat a diet of meat hundreds of thousands of years before they had fire to cook it with, shows an ingenious use of tools to cut down on chewing time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 00:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/theearthquakeguy you might find this article to be of interest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 00:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Focusing of relative plate motion at a continental transform fault: Cenozoic dextral displacement 700 km on New Zealand's Alpine Fault, reversing 225 km of Late Cretaceous sinistral motion](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GC006225/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealands Alpine Fault has moved more in the last 25 million years than any other known land fault on Earth, according to new research from the Victoria University of Wellington and GNS Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 00:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 19:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [An exceptional fossil skull from South America and the origins of the archosauriform radiation](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep22817) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of scientists have discovered a new fossil reptile that lived 250 million years ago in the state of Rio Grande do Sul, southernmost Brazil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 19:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online Intro Astronomy class: Venus and Mars (part 1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 00:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 06:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, and it's typically called a phreatomagamatic eruption. Phreatomagmatic eruptions are a result of magma coming into contact with water. In the ocean this results in the formation of hyaloclastite infilling pillow basalts. On land, these eruptions often end up forming tuff rings and maars as the rising magma (dyke) comes into contact with the water table ([illustration](http://s3images.coroflot.com/user_files/individual_files/original_242024_5bxc9veozNbBK4d7kcq82wbsx.jpg)).

Some larger known eruptions associated with phreatomagmatic eruptions are Santorini, and Mt. Pinatubo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 23:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Origin of uranium isotope variations in early solar nebula condensates](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/3/e1501400) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered evidence in a meteorite that a rare element, curium, was present during the formation of the solar system, ending a 35-year-old debate and playing a crucial role in reassessing models of stellar evolution and synthesis of elements in stars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 22:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are far too many to list so to be honest, but here's a short list which could keep you busy for a while.

Vancouver Island - Exploring any of the Gulf Island, particularly Hornby Island. It has fantastic beaches to explore with great tafoni weathering, and fossils during low tide at Collishaw Point. 
Horne Lake caves are great good for caving, made of crinoidal limestone. Fossils tend to lay within the Naniamo group predominantly, and a hike up Trent and Puntledge rivers has yielded an Elasmosaur and Mosasaur among the many ammonites. Hikes within Strathcona Provincial Park and the area around Myra Falls. Hikes throughout the West Coast trail and the North Coast trail along Cape Scott.

Haida Gwaii - Agate beach (need I say more?), and Tow Hill (and old volcanic plug surrounded by blow holes).

Lower Mainland: Lots, there is so much. Britannia Mine Museum, the entire Sea-to-Sky dry, hiking in and around Whistler - such as the Black Tusk. Head towards Pemberton, if conditions are right, check out Key hole falls and the hot springs. Head to Upper Joffrey Lakes for more good hikes surrounded by glaciers and enjoy the drive along the Duffy Lake Road. There are hotsprings located at Harrison Lake as well which has a fantastically rich history of gold and curses (see Slumachs Gold, Lost Creek Gold, the Lost Creek Mine, or the Lost Mine of Pitt Lake). Travel the coquihalla for an impressive view of massive plutons, and stroll through Othello Tunnels near Hope (don't forget to drive through "the Canyon" and Hell's Gate).

Check out any number of parks and the hikes within. Wells Gray, Kootenay, Banff, and Yoho National Parks (the world UNESCO Burgess Shale, Mt. Rundle and so much more).

Check out Rock Candy Mine near Grand Forks to dig up your own fluorite. Explore old ghost towns such as the Phoenix Mine and Phoenix city, and Barkerville. Tour the historic gold mine at Rossland - Le Roi Gold Mine. Head to the Purcell Mountains to hike the Mt. Nimbus Via Ferrata.

Further north you can visit Jade city, and head to Stewart / Hyder to check out glaciers, and the history of the area known as the Golden Triangle, and more specifically a gorgeous hike through the historic Mount Edziza Provincial Park. Check out Nisga'a Memorial Lava Bed Provincial Park host to the Tseax Cone. 

I'm certain I have left out a plethora but if you're interested in the geology of the areas and not just the beauty it's best to find a companion book that can help point you to significant geological features in the area. For example, "Roadside Geology of Southern British Columbia" and "Geology of Southern Vancouver Island."

For Alberta, the obvious one stands out - the Drumheller area hoodoos and hikes, Dinosaur Provincial Park and the Royal Tyrrell Museum. The McConnell Thrust at Mt. Yamnuska near Exshaw. Of course, as I've stated, there are a lot to explore but hopefully that can help guide in a good direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where abouts are you located, or are willing to travel to? Are there features that you're particularly interested in more so than others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 11:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Events | Earth | Mars
---|---|----
Formation | 4.543Ga| 4.503Ga
H2O by | 4.4Ga |  3.8Ga
LHB | 4.1Ga | 4.1Ga
Fossil life | 3.5Ga | N/A

Assuming the Cool early Earth - it took ~143Ma for the presence of water on Earth to occur. I don't have a figure for Mars, but let's assume it to be equal for the sake of simplicity. It follows then that we have water on Mars by 4.36Ga (consistent with   3.8Ga). The time span between the two periods of water present on the surfaces of the two planets is a mere 40Ma. According to the fossil record, life on Earth didn't emerge until ~3.5Ga or 1Ga after its formation. Taking the fossil record into account and our educated estimate relative to significant events in planetary histories it seems far more reasonable to invoke Occam's razor and forgo the added complexities of interplanetary panspermia in favor of a far more simpler origin... that carbon based life as we know it, originated on Earth.

Interstellar panspermia is another story all together though I think it's likely pointless to even consider (how can you test it?). All that being said, I'm not outright denying the possibility, I simply think it's far more likely that carbon based life as we know it originated on Earth (and it's fun to at least try to put some numbers in where I can).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The time scale in regard to the evolution of life is not supportive of panspermia being more or less likely if each planet contains the same initial potential for life and each planet was presumably just as uninhabitable as the next due to temperatures being too high. 

Furthermore, recall that there is evidence that goes against a hot inhospitable early Earth as well:

Extensive surface water of indeterminate temperature and long-lived continental crust... present by 4.4 billion years ago. Surficial weathering by liquid water between 0 and 100C occurred by 4.2 billion years ago... - [Initiation of clement surface conditions on the earliest Earth](http://www.pnas.org/content/98/7/3666.full) (pdf) 

Otherwise known as the [Cool early Earth](http://geoscience.wisc.edu/geoscience/people/faculty/john-valley/a-cool-early-earth/) which existed shortly after the formation of the moon ~4.45Ga and prior to the Late Heavy Bombardment ~4.1 - 3.8Ga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 02:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [The Cretaceous-Paleogene boundary deposit in the Gulf of Mexico: Large-scale oceanic basin response to the Chicxulub impact](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JB012615/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 20 years the release of commercial drilling data, from within the Gulf of Mexico, has lead scientists to constrain the thickness, volume, and nature of the Chicxulub impact crater, an impact event which contributed to the demise of the dinosaurs 65 million years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 02:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friday fold: Siccar Point video from BGS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 01:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A record-breaking number of injuries in a theropod dinosaur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 11:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 01:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would tend to lean in favour of eroded basalt flows as well as they bear some resemblance to the [coulee's](http://webpages.charter.net/jszecsody2b/geocache/Fr.coulee.air.jpg) and terrain of the Sun Lakes-Dry Falls State Park in Washington.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 20:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Formation of lower continental crust by relamination of buoyant arc lavas and plutons](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2662.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study raises questions about one popular theory of how the Earth's continental crust forms, while providing new support for another - suggesting that it is not delamination that determines the composition of continental crust, but relamination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 20:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 03:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically it's not a single rock. It could be called a single *type* of rock, but it's actually carved out of the rock that makes up the [Deccan Traps](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ellora_Caves#Geology_of_Ellora) (basalt) which are composed of numerous lava flows, each flow or [layer](http://tapioca.xyz/ellora-rockformation) with it's own unique [lithological](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lithology) properties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portion of ancient Australian chert microstructures definitively pseudo-fossils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portion of ancient Australian chert microstructures definitively pseudo-fossils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 12:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Slimdiddler summarized it nicely, but I'll try to expand on the summary in a bit more detail. There are three naturally occurring isotopes of carbon C12, C13, and C14. C12 and C13 are stable isotopes while C14 is unstable and will decay relatively quick. C14 is produced by cosmic rays and makes up only a tiny fraction of the total carbon (0.1%). C13 constitutes ~1.1% and C12 the remaining 98.9%. For that reason we can look at the ratio of C13 to C12, noted as [13C](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%CE%9413C). The more positive the value (typically understood as the "excursion") the more C13 is present. The smaller the value the less C13 there is. In general then a (+) means it's heavy and will have more C13, and a (-) value means it has considerably less C13, or it is "lighter". This process can be done for a multitude of other stable isotopes including oxygen, which again has three stable isotopes, O16, O17, and O18. The ratio of O18 to O16 is known as "delta 18 O" or [18O](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%CE%9418O). Different processes (fractionation) will give rise to different ratios. Plants find it energetically favourable to use the lighter isotopes (12C) when they convert sunlight and carbon dioxide into food so the result should be a (-) excursion in 13C and indeed this is what see with plants: C4 plants have a 13C of 16 to 10, and C3 plants have a 13C of 33 to 24. This is known as an isotopic signature, or in essence, a type of finger print. Combining multiple isotopic signatures can help unravel numerous mysteries and is also a branch of forensics. This is also how we can trace where the carbon in our atmosphere is coming from and state with confidence that the (-) excursion in 13C can be attributed to the burning of fossil fuels (known as [the Suess Effect](https://imgur.com/A8hvCcl)). So when people state that the carbon is organic, they are referring to the 13C value, as it is typically a tell tale sign as to which process may have given rise to said value, and is a very powerful tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 05:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a common misunderstanding. Geochemical processes don't solely rely on elemental mass, but are dictated by such things as ionic radius and valence which give rise to the compatibility of an element, or stated else wise the [incompatibility of an element](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Incompatible_element). This is why, for example, the crust is enriched in potassium, uranium, and thorium where as the mantle is relatively depleted in these LILE and HFSE elements.

It is for these reasons that some Earth scientists prefer to use the [Railsback Periodic Table](http://www.gly.uga.edu/railsback/PT/815PeriodicTable48d013600.jpg) over the more traditional table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 00:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [On the nature and significance of rarity in mineralogy](http://www.minsocam.org/MSA/Ammin/AM_Preprints/5601HazenPreprint.pdf) (pdf)

Another article: [Earths rarest minerals could hint at life on other planets](https://www.newscientist.com/article/2077359-earths-rarest-minerals-could-hint-at-life-on-other-planets/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worlds 2500 rarest minerals have now been categorised for the first time, revealing intriguing implications. Most have been formed in processes directly or indirectly related to living organisms, and so they may serve as a signature of life on other planets, the authors suggest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 00:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Structural complexity of simple Fe2O3 at high pressures and temperatures](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160211/ncomms10661/full/ncomms10661.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered new iron oxides, pointing to a large oxygen source within Earth's lower mantle and that may play a significant role in oxygen cycling between earth reservoirs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 20:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [The Role of a Mantle Plume on the Formation of Yellowstone Volcanism](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GL067131/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study using an advanced computer model casts doubt on previously held theories about the Yellowstone supervolcano's origins, adding to the mystery of Yellowstone's formation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 20:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crepuscular rays hang over Ammonite Falls, Vancouver Island, British Columbia [4608x3456][OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 20:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ammonite Falls, Vancouver Island, British Columbia 25s [4608x3456][OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth-like Planets Have Earth-like Interiors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Arabia was green: Lush grasslands helped early man make leap out of Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 00:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also approximately coincident with [Sturtian and Marinoan](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Template:Cryogenian_graphical_timeline) glaciations (snow ball Earth events) which I feel would have a greater role in the evolution of life than the onset of the formation of the inner core; however, I'm unaware of any conclusive studies that describe such possible relationships in regard to core formation and life, and may represent a region of interest for you to explore in detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 09:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly has a [ways](http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/life-unbounded/files/2014/11/MarsCuriosityTrek_20140911_A.jpg) to go yet **(**just within [the Paintbrush unit](https://d2cj35nmzi9erd.cloudfront.net/msl/imgs/2016/02/MSL_TraverseMap_Sol1243-full.jpg) **(**[pdf](https://d2cj35nmzi9erd.cloudfront.net/files/msl/2014-MSL-extended-mission-plan.pdf)**)** [now renamed the Murray Formation]**)**, and plenty left to discover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consistency of Earths magnetic field history surprises scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 23:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 20:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Dehydration of lawsonite could directly trigger earthquakes in subducting oceanic crust](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v530/n7588/full/nature16501.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research finds an explanation for intermediate depth earthquakes in subduction zones, regions where pressures are so high that the normal process of frictional sliding associated with earthquakes is inhibited. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 20:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 07:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The narrower the gap between when we know life existed and when we know it couldn't yet arise, the less likely it is that it arose during that span of time in that environment.

My point is that such a gap, though important for the time scale in regard to the evolution of life, is not supportive of panspermia being more or less likely if each planet contains the same initial potential for life and each planet was presumably just as uninhabitable as the next due to temperatures being too high. 

Recall that there is evidence that goes against a hot inhospitable early Earth as well:

Extensive surface water of indeterminate temperature and long-lived continental crust... present by 4.4 billion years ago. Surficial weathering by liquid water between 0 and 100C occurred by 4.2 billion years ago... - [Initiation of clement surface conditions on the earliest Earth](http://www.pnas.org/content/98/7/3666.full) (pdf) 

Otherwise known as the [Cool early Earth](http://geoscience.wisc.edu/geoscience/people/faculty/john-valley/a-cool-early-earth/) which existed shortly after the formation of the moon ~4.45Ga and prior to the Late Heavy Bombardment ~4.1 - 3.8Ga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 06:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water bears (Tardigrades) are complex life forms and are not at all representative of early life on Earth around 4.1Ga or even much earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 06:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...it becomes that much more likely that it actually didn't originate on Earth but arrived from elsewhere.

*If* each planet contains the same likelihood that life will emerge on its own, how does this increase the odds of panspermia? Also recall that the [Late Heavy Bombarment](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Late_Heavy_Bombardment) (4.1Ga - 3.8Ga) theoretically should have added substantial heat to the inner planets in roughly proportional amounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, I never received a reply to [my questions](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/3fx008/were_engineers_scientists_and_the_curiosity_rover/cttdzd2) regarding the hypothesized microbial mats... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two types of Jade: Nephrite, and Jadeite. This certainly doesn't look like Nephrite and a piece of Jadeite that large would be significantly expensive (ie. there's no way that's Jadeite). Common faux Jades are typically made of soapstone, serpentine (such as bowenite), chrysoprase, quartz (aventurine) etc.

Typically values are assigned by similar methods as diamonds (consistency, cut, clarity, colour) except that cut isn't really that relevant for Jade. Consistent (texture) - you want the same colour throughout, no changes in colour or imperfections, fractures, inclusions, etc. Clarity - the more translucent the better. Colour - this depends but more often then not the closer one is to an "imperial green" the higher the value assigned. Size is another factor but the primary ones that dictate the price relative to the size are already listed above.

Of course it can become more complicated as well with Type A (all natural, untreated), B (chemically bleached and or injected with polymer to remove impurities and enhance translucency), and C (the same as B but with dye to enhance colour).

Top quality Jadeite can fetch a fair penny. This pair of [Jadeite bangles](https://a248.e.akamai.net/f/1202/1579/4m/i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2013/06/18/article-0-1A611708000005DC-42_1024x615_large.jpg) sold for 3,732,365. 

A quick and easy way to eliminate some possibilities would be to do a scratch test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Spirit Rover: Silica Formation on Mars Spotted by Vehicle Could Hint at Alien Life, Astronomers Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Company of Volcanoes: How fast is volcano-fast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 06:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't. As per the USGS Earthquake Myths FAQ

**Can you prevent large earthquakes by making lots of small ones...?**

*Seismologists have observed that for every magnitude 6 earthquake it would take 32 magnitude 5's, 1000 magnitude 4's, 32,000 magnitude 3's (and so on for smaller earthquakes) to equal the energy of one magnitude 6 event. So, even though we always record many more small events than large ones there are never enough to eliminate the need for the occasional large earthquake.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to go out on a limb here and say it *might* have something to do with [corporate interests and lobbying](https://stateimpact.npr.org/oklahoma/2015/06/01/gov-fallin-signs-bill-to-prevent-towns-cities-and-counties-from-banning-fracking/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks. I have plenty of reviews to go up, however, I prefer to have my own unique photograph to pair with it. It can be a bit of a pain at times because I force myself to wait for a specific shot or to think of something creative (that can take a while) and then I hope the shot turns out. For example, I have an Ardbeg 10 review to share and attempted a few creative photos with it, from different angles, etc. I thought they turned out well until I left the location, returned home only to find a reflection on the bottle and a smudge mark that ruined everything for me. Now I have to find not only the time, but the right weather   lighting again to attempt the shot before I share the review... it's a lot of fun though so I'm glad to hear that you're enjoying the photos as well as the review(s). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What most of you aren't seeing in the news is that we went from having zero earthquakes, to having a few 4.0s a week here now.

Some good [visual data](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/images/OklahomaEQsBarGraph.png) provided by the USGS helps depict the increase in induced seismicity:

- [Animation of Oklahoma Seismicity: January 2, 2008 - November 24, 2015](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/OKeqanimation.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're assuming that they are limited to Mw4.0... [they're not](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/early/2013/03/26/G34045.1.abstract), and they have the potential to do serious damage:

"*the Wilzetta-Whitetail fault zone south of Cushing, Oklahoma, could produce a large, damaging earthquake comparable to the 2011 Prague event. Resultant very strong shaking levels (MMI VII) in the epicentral region present the possibility of this potential earthquake causing moderate to heavy damage to national strategic infrastructure and local communities.*" [Reactivated faulting near Cushing, Oklahoma: Increased potential for a triggered earthquake in an area of United States strategic infrastructure](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GL064669/pdf) (pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. As per the USGS Earthquake Myths FAQ

**Can you prevent large earthquakes by making lots of small ones...?**

*Seismologists have observed that for every magnitude 6 earthquake it would take 32 magnitude 5's, 1000 magnitude 4's, 32,000 magnitude 3's (and so on for smaller earthquakes) to equal the energy of one magnitude 6 event. So, even though we always record many more small events than large ones there are never enough to eliminate the need for the occasional large earthquake.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 09:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open access paper for this particular study: [Kisameet Clay Exhibits Potent Antibacterial Activity against the ESKAPE Pathogens](http://mbio.asm.org/lens/mbio/7/1/e01842-15#figures)

And an open access paper for another medical clay, Oregon blue clay, can be read here: [Unearthing the Antibacterial Mechanism of Medicinal Clay: A Geochemical Approach to Combating Antibiotic Resistance](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep19043)

EDIT: One more open access paper: [What Makes a Natural Clay Antibacterial?](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3126108/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 03:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Colour*: Fools gold

*Body*: Full bodied, oily

*Nose*: A smoldering peat bog with vanilla, and toffee. Pipe tobacco and sea spray.

*Palate*: A divine sweetness rushes to the front of the lips with fruit, citrus, vanilla and spice only to be subdued by peaty smoke, and then more peat. Upon a long exhale the ghost of a smoldering peat bog emerges in full.      

*Finish*: Warming, long and lingering. A hint of sea spray before the smoke from a smoldering peat bog rises and coats the walls of your mouth.

*Score*: 86/100

*Note*: At 208ppm phenols this peat monster will have peat pushing out from your pores; it's not for the faint-hearted. At five years of age it's truly impressive that it is so well mannered, and smooth for 59.5% abv. Some would say the cost doesn't pair well with the age, but that misses the point... it's a five year old scotch that easily behaves more than twice its age, an impressive feat that very well may justify the cost to a large degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #3: Bruichladdich Octomore 07.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 02:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The greatest ever debris flow video? Aconcagua in Argentina - The Landslide Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 11:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the term you are looking for is a Mammoth-steppe: 

During the Last Glacial Maximum (LGM), mammoth steppe (MS)
was Earths most extensive biome... At the last deglaciation Earths largest biome, mammoth-steppe, vanished. - [Mammoth steppe: a high-productivity phenomenon](http://www.lter.uaf.edu/pdf/1754_Zimov_Zimov_2012.pdf) (pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 20:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Atlantic Ocean is 250 million years old which means no craters from before that time are visible.

The Atlantic ocean began to open up with the break-up of [Pangea](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pangaea) which began ~175-180Ma (million years ago). Oceanic crust typically (on average) is no older than 120-140Ma due, in large part, to buoyancy. It cools as it ages, becoming negatively buoyant whereby it begins to sink into the mantle. A map of oceanic crustal ages shows that the oldest regions are no older than 180Ma which certainly includes pats of the Atlantic. ([Oceanic crustal age map](http://www.ucmp.berkeley.edu/tectonics/crustages.jpg)). Furthermore, as many others have also pointed out there are plenty of craters older than 250Ma located within continental crust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunting blueschist (with bonus newt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 00:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note that I disagree with Glen Brown's interpretation (as do countless other geologists), but the position that the seismicity in Oklahoma is induced by natural means has been argued in favour of in the past...

http://www.koco.com/news/geologist-worldwide-seismic-uptick-responsible-for-oklahoma-earthquake-swarm/27118772 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 23:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be more specific the [induced seismicity](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/images/OklahomaEQsBarGraph.png) in Oklahoma is attributed to waste water disposal, and not to the particular phase that is hydraulic fracturing - they are separate phases. Induced seismicity directly attributed to hydraulic fracturing, while not as common as their waste water disposal brethren, do occur however (as has been noted in Ohio, and British Columbia for example).

- [Animation of Oklahoma Seismicity: January 2, 2008 - November 24, 2015](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/OKeqanimation.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 23:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not really. As per the USGS Earthquake Myths FAQ

**Can you prevent large earthquakes by making lots of small ones...?**

*Seismologists have observed that for every magnitude 6 earthquake it would take 32 magnitude 5's, 1000 magnitude 4's, 32,000 magnitude 3's (and so on for smaller earthquakes) to equal the energy of one magnitude 6 event. So, even though we always record many more small events than large ones there are never enough to eliminate the need for the occasional large earthquake.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geological explanation for rings of stunted tree growth in northern Ontario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 21:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 07:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mw4.8](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/edmonton/fox-creek-fracking-operation-closed-indefinitely-after-earthquake-1.3400605) *might* take that title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Qualicum, Vancouver Island, B.C. [3920x2928] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home for the night on Forbidden Plateau, BC - 20s [4608 x 3211] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 21:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cataclastite](https://structuredatabase.files.wordpress.com/2014/08/screen-shot-2014-08-18-at-3-29-43-pm.png)

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cataclastic_rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 20:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colour: [Amber](https://www.flickr.com/photos/luxlaboratories/23345233183/in/datetaken-public/lightbox/)

Body: Full bodied, oily

Nose: More refined than the quarter cask, a good balance between peaty smoke, spice, and buttery caramel. Notes of honey and sherry sweetness. Soft and subtle new-mown hay after a gentle rain.

Palate: Peaty smoke and spice, big and bold, peppered steak perfectly served.    

Finish: A lingering finish, it coats the mouth, long and bold. Peat smoke, and spice fade into the night, while a note of toffee is awakened. long length.

Score: 92/100

Note: A more matured dram, refined, it's not as smoky or peaty as others like Laphroaig Quarter Cask. Complex, a fine balance is merely met. An excellent nightcap. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #2: Laphroaig 18 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 19:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 04:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...too much good whiskey is barely enough." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 00:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colour: Golden Yellow

Body: Full bodied 
 
Nose: Rich peat and campfire smoke, with melted butter, caramel and toffee. Hints of a distinct fruity, banana sweetness.

Palate: A sweet and spicy arrival hastily developing into a peaty phenolic steam engine belching smoke. Buttery notes hide well in the background but don't go unnoticed. 

Finish: A lingering finish, fading peat and spice, a dry smoke rises in one final show. Medium length.

Score: 89/100

Note: I packed a flask with me on a snowshoeing, winter camping excursion only to find that it paired exceptionally well with a trail snack of original beef jerky - hence the photograph which was taken upon my return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #1: Laphroaig Quarter Cask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 00:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 19:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having an agenda would imply that I have a bias... I don't. I'm here to acknowledge the science and make sure there is no bias which is why I'm calling you out on your bullshit, repeatedly. 

Apparently the argument still hasn't sunk in. Simply because there have been numerous wells without incident doesn't mean that there cannot be wells without incident. Furthermore your reliance on such a position, as I clearly pointed out previously, is erroneous as the set of conditions has changed over time.

Great damage *can* occur... do you I really need to quote the study for a third time? It's like talking to a brick wall. Let's be clear here... the only thing dogmatic is your refusal to accept the science, your outright denial of the facts. I'm glad you're done with this, but to be fair, with nothing but a personal bias and misleading statements you shouldn't have even started in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These tremors and small earthquakes in general do not relieve the stress of larger earthquakes. Essentially the number of earthquakes required to relieve any stress related to larger earthquakes is simply too large, because the difference in energy is simply too large between the two. 

[USGS](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/learn/topics/megaqk_facts_fantasy.php): 
"*Seismologists have observed that for every magnitude 6 earthquake there are about 10 of magnitude 5, 100 of magnitude 4, 1,000 of magnitude 3, and so forth as the events get smaller and smaller. This sounds like a lot of small earthquakes, but there are never enough small ones to eliminate the occasional large event. It would take 32 magnitude 5's, 1000 magnitude 4's, OR 32,000 magnitude 3's to equal the energy of one magnitude 6 event. So, even though we always record many more small events than large ones, there are far too few to eliminate the need for the occasional large earthquake.*"

Within the Cascadia Subduction Zone there are three main zones. The locked zone, the transition zone, and the slip zone (see [figure](http://images.slideplayer.com/17/5276898/slides/slide_5.jpg)). These earthquakes and tremors are related to episodic tremor and slip events (depicted [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R_Im-KMNJxI)   [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mMwfHOsAiEc)). The "Big One" is expected to rupture within the locked zone, as such, not only do smaller earthquakes not release enough strain to mitigate larger earthquakes, but these tremors have no bearing on building stress within the locked zone as these are typically occurring within the transition zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 40,000-Mile Volcano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 21:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An animation made by Aaron Wech from the Alaska Volcano Observatory shows 171,197 tremors in the Cascadia Subduction Zone from 2012 to 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An animation made by Aaron Wech from the Alaska Volcano Observatory shows 171,197 tremors in the Cascadia Subduction Zone from 2012 to 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps, I should've clarified that I was referring to quakes perceptible to anything other than sophisticated measuring devices.

You most certainly were not, and appear to be struggling to "save face." Furthermore, even if you were such a statement would still be false. Mw4.6 earthquakes are quite noticeable without the use of highly sensitive instrumentation. 

From the paper you linked: Based on results from this study and the similarity of the conjugate strike-slip fault systems in Cushing and Prague, we suggest that a moderate-magnitude (Mw5.6) earthquake, similar to the 2011 Prague earthquake (Mw5.6), could occur at the conjugate fault intersection directly beneath the Cushing oil storage facility.

I fail to see the point of this as it is in full agreement with what I've stated thus far.

Do you have evidence of a fracked well causing damage? 

Again you appear to be missing the argument being made. It is not what has been documented, but rather the potential or statistical likely hood for lack of better words. Under present conditions there factually exists a certain probability, no matter how unlikely to cause significant damage (I repeat myself):

"*Resultant very strong shaking levels (MMI VII) in the epicentral region present the possibility of this potential earthquake causing moderate to heavy damage to national strategic infrastructure and local communities.*"

Failing to recognize this is nothing short of willful ignorance, unreasonable and irresponsible. It's not "but whatever..." it's lunacy to ignore the facts when presented with them, let alone attempt to mislead others purely based on a strong personal bias that clearly overshadows ones reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 11:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standing by your original statement is nothing short of willful ignorance. For one you claimed that

"...fracking doesn't cause earthquakes; waste water disposal does."

This is clearly incorrect, and was shown to be incorrect with multiple sources that do not support your original claim. Subsequently you have attempted to build a straw-man argument suggestive that you never made such a claim, and further implying that the study implied that hydraulic fracturing *will* generate a damaging earthquake. This is not at all what the article claims, and nor what the study I linked claims. The article states, as you yourself quoted:

"...Even a magnitude four in the right place could cause great damage."

*Could*, not *will*. Such a statement entails a probability, for which the study I linked also supports this possibility. If you wish to argue otherwise I would recommend publishing your findings. 

Furthermore statements such as

"We have been using hydro-fracking in the oil patch for over 60 years on millions of wells and while very small and imperceptible, to humans, movement can occur from fracking, there has never been a report of a fracked well causing damage... out of millions!"

must be able account for [the increase in induced seismicity](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/states/oklahoma/images/OklahomaEQsBarGraph.png) which it clearly cannot. It fails to take into account the increased density of well sites, and the increased pore pressures with improvements in technology amongst many others. Though the increase is largely due to waste water disposal the point should not be lost. Arguing that it's been done for "x" amount of years with little disturbance does not apply because the conditions are not the same, they've changed over the course of those years. It's an argument akin to the clich "when I was a kid..." Well grandpa I've got some news for you, things have changed since you were a kid.

Feel free to stand by your original post, but it will only highlight your personal bias on the topic as the facts state otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 09:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not straight-up bullshit, it's a reality and dependent on the geology of the area, and the infrastructure. Though very unlikely to cause severe damage, it is *not* bullshit. You can read an article or the research paper (or both):

 - [New Concern Over Quakes in Oklahoma Near a Hub of U.S. Oil](http://www.nytimes.com/2015/10/15/us/new-concern-over-quakes-in-oklahoma-near-a-hub-of-us-oil.html?_r=0)

 - "*the Wilzetta-Whitetail fault zone south of Cushing, Oklahoma, could produce a large, damaging earthquake comparable to the 2011 Prague event. Resultant very strong shaking levels (MMI VII) in the epicentral region present the possibility of this potential earthquake causing moderate to heavy damage to national strategic infrastructure and local communities.*" [Reactivated faulting near Cushing, Oklahoma: Increased potential for a triggered earthquake in an area of United States strategic infrastructure](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GL064669/pdf) (pdf)

As a reminder to geologists and non-geologists alike: fracking *can* cause earthquakes, though the majority of induced seismicity are related to waste water disposal.

For a good review I would recommend the following:

- [Yes, Humans Really Are Causing Earthquakes](http://online.wr.usgs.gov/calendar/2015/aug15.html) presented by Justin Rubinstein, USGS Research Geophysicist

- Hydraulic fracturing linked to induced seismicity: *Science AMA Series: I'm Robert Skoumal, one of the co-authors on a paper that linked small magnitude earthquakes to hydraulic fracturing in Poland Township, Ohio, in March 2014. AMA*: https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/2rjqad/science_ama_series_im_robert_skoumal_one_of_the/

While the data currently leans in favour of waste water disposal being capable of producing larger magnitude events than events generated by hydraulic fracturing, seismicity in Northern BC has reached Mw4.6 due to hydraulic fracturing ([source](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/british-columbia/summer-earthquake-confirmed-as-largest-caused-by-fracking-in-bc/article27798765/)), and not waste water disposal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you by chance know the geology of region? I was curious to know what kind of deposit type this may be, and while it is currently located in a marine environment suggesting SEDEX or a VMS type setting, the proximity so far on shelf ([Jiao-Liao-Ji Belt](http://image.sciencenet.cn/album/201110/11/170118w532sjmxsrqmzwjx.jpg)) and at a depth of 2km might suggest this deposits is within an older orogenic belt and might be related to that... or it could be related to much younger [tertiary volcanism](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shandong#Geology). I suppose the age of the deposit itself would shed light on this...

I have absolutely no knowledge of the geological history of this region, and I haven't been able to locate a company site discussing the project details so I'm purely speculating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home for the night on Forbidden Plateau, BC - 20s [4608 x 3211] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 02:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Earthquakes  Mw4.0 from 2000 - 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 19:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps even more importantly than the numbers themselves, is the fact that it represents a clearly defined temporal boundary on a global scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
