<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, before you complain, no, it is not too early to talk about the 2020 election. It is not. The RealClearPolitics polling average for the Republican primaries in 2016 began in July 2013, with eventual winner Chris Christie holding a narrow lead over 2016 runners-up Marco Rubio and Rand Paul. No, Donald Trump wasnt included in those polls, why do you ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven percent of Trump voters say theyd vote for someone else in 2020 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rep. Maxine Waters (D-Calif.) says she doesn't trust President Trump to negotiate with the world on behalf of the U.S.

Dont forget, you cant trust this president. When he comes out with one thing, hell change the next day, Waters told Yahoo News on Thursday.

Waters noted that Trump railed against the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) throughout his campaign, only to announce he will not pull the U.S. out of the trade deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maxine Waters: You cant trust this president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A ban on exporting coal through Canadas west coast ports would put a crimp in Trumps promises to revive US coal mining employment (promises that are likely unrealistic anyway), further endear Trudeaus government to Trumps domestic political opponents, and likely do the environment some good. Its also simply a reminder that Trump isnt the only person in global politics who can play the game of threat and bluff, and that most of his opponents in said game probably have a much stronger grasp of the underlying issues.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Columbia has a plan to counter Trumps tariffs with a blow to American coal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British police said armed officers arrested a man carrying knives near Prime Minister Theresa May's office in Westminster on suspicion of preparing an act of terrorism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An earlier statement from the Russian Defense Ministry said the Liman had been breached below the waterline on the starboard side and that its crew were fighting to keep it afloat, state-run news outlet Sputnik reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian ship sinks in Black Sea after collision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chairman: Trump and House GOP have '80 percent common ground' on taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The order would essentially seek to reverse former President Barack Obamas actions to restrict offshore drilling.

Obama took drilling in the Arctic, Atlantic and Pacific oceans off the table until 2022, and blocked drilling indefinitely in select Arctic and Atlantic areas. He also implemented aggressive safety regulations on the industry.
The order would come on Trumps 99th Day in office amid a big push to close out the first 100 days of his presidency.

The Friday order would be aimed primarily at expanding drilling by directing the Interior Department to review the current schedule for offshore drilling allowances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wants to expand offshore drilling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Defence Ministry apologized for allowing a badly photoshopped picture of navy ships and fighter jets to appear on its social media accounts over the weekend, after hundreds of people poured scorn on the image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The explosion "shook the Damascus International Airport area at dawn today. A thud could be heard in Damascus city and surrounding areas," a statement from the monitoring group's founder, Rami Abdulrahman, reads.
"A fire broke out in the area but the cause of the explosion is still unknown," Abdulrahman said.
Two Damascus residents who spoke to CNN reported hearing a massive explosion near the airport.
Civil war broke out in Syria in 2011 after an uprising against President Bashar al-Assad but escalated as militant groups and regional players such as Iran,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A loud explosion hit close to the Damascus International Airport in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressional GOP leaders and the chairmen of the tax-writing committees said in a joint statement Wednesday that President Trump's tax-reform principles "will serve as critical guideposts for Congress and the administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The report says that a Russian intelligence unit targeted the Macron campaign in March and April using schemes like sending emails designed to bait mid-level campaign managers into handing over their passwords. Trend Micro believes that its the very same Russian group, known by a number of names including Pawn Storm and Fancy Bear, that stole emails from the Democratic National Committee in the run-up to the 2016 US presidential election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cybersecurity group thinks Russia is trying to hack the French election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House unveils dramatic plan to overhaul tax code in major test for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the first messages appeared that warned Parisians that a serious event was ongoing on the Champs-lyses and that a police officer had lost his life, a little voice told me it was you ... and brought me back to that generous and healing phrase: You will not have my hate. I dont feel hatred, Xavier, because it is not like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You will not have my hate: watch the eulogy to the Paris police officer killed last week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CSRs make a genuine difference in the lives of real people. When you suffer from heart disease or cancer, you depend on regular access to your doctor for prevention and to keep your treatment on track. For someone who makes less than $18,000 a year, or a family of four living on less than $39,000 a year, even $10 or $20 is a significant cost. This program lowers out-of-pocket costs like deductibles and co-pays, making coverage more affordable. 
For example, on a typical CSR plan, a person making $18,000 a year could have their deductible lowered from $3,500 to $250 and their urgent care co-pay lowered from $75 to $25.  Without this program, millions of Americans simply could not afford their healthcare.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress must remember healthcare program that millions of Americans depend on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "South Korea and the United States have been working to secure an early operational capability of the THAAD system in response to North Korea's advancing nuclear and missile threat," the ministry said in a statement.

The battery was expected to be operational by the end of the year, it said.

The United States and South Korea agreed last year to deploy the THAAD to counter the threat of missile launches by North Korea. They say it is solely aimed at defending against North Korea.

But China says the system's advanced radar can penetrate deep into its territory and undermine its security, while it will do little to deter the North, and is adamant in its opposition.

"China strongly urges the United States and South Korea to stop actions that worsen regional tensions and harm China's strategic security interests and cancel the deployment of the THAAD system and withdraw the equipment," Chinese foreign ministry spokesman Geng Shuang told a briefing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. military started moving parts of an anti-missile defense system to a deployment site in South Korea triggering protests from villagers and criticism from China, amid tension over North Korea's weapons development </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump will sign a new executive order, this time on education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Trump will sign an executive order that directs Education Secretary Betsy DeVos to review "where the Federal Government has unlawfully overstepped state and local control" in education.

The order  titled "Executive Order Enforcing Statutory Prohibitions on Federal Control of Education"  is in line with both Trump's campaign promises on education and what DeVos advocated for before entering the federal government.

Here is a statement from a WH official:

"This Executive Order is intended to return authority to where Congress intended -- state and local entities. Current law recognizes that, although the Federal Government has a Department of Education, state and local entities retain control over their schools. This Executive Order directs the Secretary of Education to conduct a study and determine where the Federal Government has unlawfully overstepped state and local control." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump could make himself richer through tax reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House staffers to get training on social media, email security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China launched its first domestically built aircraft carrier on amid rising tension over North Korea and worries about Beijing's assertiveness in the South China Sea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Trump's daughter Ivanka, an unpaid White House adviser, gave an exclusive email interview to Breitbart News after speaking at a panel discussion about empowering women in Germany.

Trump, who has positioned herself as an advocate for women's issues in the White House, called her father's calls for paid maternity leave and better access to childcare "central" to that work.

These policies are central to the economic empowerment of women and they will ensure economic growth and job creation across the country, Trump said.

In her email to Breitbart, Trump says that supporting policies that keep women from leaving the workforce "is vital as well as breaking down the barriers for female small business owners so they can become job creators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump gives exclusive interview to Breitbart News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross defended the administration's decision to slap tariffs on Canadian lumber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico's foreign minister blasted President Trump's proposed wall on the southern U.S. border as a "hostile" act, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New polling from the Washington Post and ABC News suggests that no matter what they come up with, they've already likely lost the messaging fight over health care.
Just more than one in three respondents (37%) said they prefer that Republicans repeal and replace the ACA. By contrast, 61% would rather see Congress keep the law and work to improve it.
Democrats, as you might expect, are nearly unanimous (88%) in favor of keeping and improving Obamacare. Far more surprising to me is that one in five self-identified Republicans (21%) prefer keeping and improving the law as opposed to repealing and replacing it. Independents clearly favor the keep/improve option; two thirds say they prefer that to repealing and replacing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are losing the health care fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Donald Trump's former national security adviser did not properly disclose payments from Russia and does not appear to have complied with the law, House Oversight Chairman Jason Chaffetz and ranking Democrat Elijah Cummings said Tuesday after reviewing Michael Flynn's application for a security clearance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House oversight panel: No sign Flynn complied with the law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rep. Elijah Cummings and Rep. Jason Chaffetz comment on the White House denying the committee's request for documents related to Michael Flynn and the Russia/Trump probe. (See below for more on that.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration has denied a request from the House Oversight Committee for more information on payments that former national security adviser Michael Flynn received from foreign governments, including from the Kremlin-backed television station RT and other Russian firms.

Legislative affairs director Marc Short argued that the committee was requesting both documents that are not in possession of the White House because they involved Flynn's activity prior to President Trumps January 20 inauguration and others that involved sensitive information.

"It is unclear how such documents would be relevant to the stated purpose of the committee's review, which according to your letter is to examine Lt. Gen. Flynn's disclosure of payments related to activities that occurred in 2015 and 2016, prior to his service in the White House," Short wrote in a letter dated April 19, sent to committee leaders.

In March, the committee sent a letter to the White House and the Defense Department demanding a range of records related to the payments Flynn, who also worked on Trumps campaign and presidential transition, received.
On Tuesday morning, the committee reviewed a batch of documents responsive to the request from the Pentagon, behind closed doors.

Flynn did not list the payments from Russian companies in his original financial disclosure forms submitted in February. He filed an amended disclosure last month reporting payments for speeches from three Russian-linked companies, including RT, but the move has remained under scrutiny amidst the FBIs ongoing investigation into possible coordination between the Trump campaign and Russia during the election.

Flynn was forced to resign in February after it came to light that he had misled Vice President Pence and the public about the content of a phone call with Russian Ambassador Sergei Kislyac.

The former intelligence official has offered to testify before the Senate and House Intelligence committees  which are both investigating Russian interference in the election  in exchange for immunity, but neither committee has accepted the offer.

Oversight Committee Chairman Jason Chaffetz (R-Utah) had recently suggested that Flynn could potentially be on the hook for tens of thousands of dollars in remittance to the U.S. government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rep. Adam Schiff, the ranking member of the House Intelligence Committee, and Sen. Tim Kaine, a member of the Senate Armed Services and Senate Foreign Relations committees, sent a letter to Trump asking for the legal basis for the Syria strike earlier this month.

They wrote: "By articulating a legal basis for military action, as well as laying out a strategic vision for such action, a president provides a justification for the use of the momentous power to commit American lives to a cause, but also an understanding of the limits of those powers."

Trump ordered the strike without Congressional permission on April 6 in direct response to the chemical attack in Syria by Assad's regime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic leaders send letter to Trump requesting legal basis for Syria strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The basis of those charges is not that the FEC found the descriptions of those expenditure inaccurate it did not, Schocks lawyers say. Rather, the governments theory is that those descriptions did not meet reporting standards that were crafted by prosecutors for purposes of this prosecution and never publicly disclosed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Rep. Aaron Schock (R-Ill.), who has been indicted on two-dozen fraud-related charges, wants a federal court to dismiss five counts on the falsifying of campaign finance records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She will be there at the invitation of German Chancellor Angela Merkel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. general says 'not refuting' reports Russia supplying Taliban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dirty side of "El Clasico" Fouls, Fights, Red Cards and Dives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump calls NASA astronaut to congratulate her on space duration record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue came up after Democratic National Committee Chairman Tom Perez and Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) received backlash this week when they planned a rally with Heath Mello, a Democratic mayoral candidate in Omaha, Neb., who supported abortion-related ultrasound legislation eight years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) said Sunday that a person can be part of Democratic party while being against abortion rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The White House is preparing for the worst and hoping for the best as it plans for the possibility of a government shutdown next week. But the insistence on including many of President Donald Trump's priorities in the government spending bill has added some roadblocks to a bipartisan effort to pass it.

Both the president and his chief spokesperson expressed confidence Friday that the government would not shut down when current funding expires at midnight on April 28. "I think we're in good shape" President Trump told reporters in the Oval Office Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Optimism on Shutdown Complicated by Trump Demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren builds her brand with 2020 down the road </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
