<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7467</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I understood that this sub is against censorship, right ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cultures are differents. You don't like it ? Don't go there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is, you go somewhere, you adapt yourself. The country won't change for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do women even play chess ?

Shouldn't they be cooking and cleaning ?!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, and that's the problem. It works in one way only. How can we integrate immigrants that don't drink nor smoke nor eat pork when we do all the opposite ?

I'm French by the way, kids should be forced to drink wine, smoke cigs and eat dry sausages to become a true patriot. Otherwise they would loose their French nationality. Make France great again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she is doing the exact same thing that Muslims do in our country, she refuses to adapt herself to the culture of the country she is going. Imposing her culture to others.

And you guys are supporting her ? Mmhkay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True enough !  As a French guy living in Australia, I can confirm that most women love the accent. Better be a French abroad than a French in France. And yes we basically hate everyone, but mostly the Brits for their sneaky attitude during the great wars and their plastic like cheeses.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nala smiles for Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed but if he wouldn't have pushed for this threesome to happen I would have never sleep with her at all. No alchemy would have started.

 All I say is that it might reveal some unwanted feelings between friends. 

In this case she wanted me and I was not strong enough to stop her from getting what she wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it with my best friend and his girlfriend. Was great but it ended up having sex with her afterwards without him as she loved me. He got obviously very mad and destroyed my cannabis plantation. Cops got involved and I got 3 months of jail with probation period of 5 years.

If you do it with people you know, make sure they don't know if you do illegal stuff or they might use it against you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody in france says sacre bleu apart from english speaking people.  I don't even know why or where that thing comes from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The  matchmaking is already shit so if the server needs to find all same faction players it would be even more annoying and slow. But I like the idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they get close nobushi can go into hidden stance and kick them quick. Then GB GB and light one for bleeding.  

But yeah I feel you yesterday I got destroyed by a warden prestige 3 about 4times. His way was to constantly push and get close while bashing and light fast attacks. He would block and parry everything. Hidden stance would result in a fast attack.

Its hard to handle hidden stance and it drains lots of stamina. Oh and when the beserker do one heavy attack successfully and takes away half of your HP, I really wonder why people are saying nobushi is OP.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is why I love Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duel !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yeah I feel you, I'm from the country side too originally. I was playing WoW with a 56k modem back then.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries mate , good luck ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha yeah but man it's boring af to cut them, dip them and coat them one by one! Trust a guy that had to make about 200 per week for 2years!

Someone should invent a lamington cutting,dipping and coating machine ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking morons they deserve to be in a wheelchair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes so much sense to a pastry chef. Thank you ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how come some players are totally fine and others have issues ? It must be your connection right ? I just did a speedtest.net : Down:100M/s  Up:10M/s  Ping:8ms  

What to you get ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just look the steam reviews.. filled with angry players that can't play or have too many issues.

For me everything works like a charm I never had a disconnection in 17hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only we could discover another race somewhere in space or at the bottom of the ocean, humanity could unite against them and blame them for everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  once your team starts losing and respawing staggered, it is very hard to come back

SO true. I had it yesterday again, it was so annoying to respawn and get ganked per 3-4 guys in a few seconds, rinse and repeat 5times I was surprised to see none of my team mate ragequit.

They should make people respawn is an unattainable position so the loosing team would have a chance to regroup there instead of dying one after each others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sponge: 500g butter /660g sugar / 740g flour / 8 eggs / 120g milk

Icing: 200g butter/ 2kilo icing sugar / 80g rum / 500g raspberry puree / 80g water

Filling: 1 kilo raspberry puree/ 100g sugar / 20g pectin

Its a big recipe for restaurant quantity so I advise you to divide it by at least 4 if you dont wanna make 100 of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright,

Sponge: 500g butter /660g sugar / 740g flour / 8 eggs
/ 120g milk

Icing: 200g butter/ 2kilo icing sugar / 80g rum / 500g raspberry puree / 80g water

FIlling: 1 kilo raspberry puree/ 100g sugar / 20g pectin

Its a big recipe for restaurant quantity so I advise you to divide it by at least 4 if you dont wanna make 100 of them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yeah ok nothing to do with driving xD 

I know what you mean then, in France they do it (or at least used to) with crepes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
