<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8985</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think that car's brake pads are made of rubber? There can rubber in it, but it's mostly a binding agent for the abrasives, aramid fibers like Kevlar, glass, etc. It's really nothing at all like soft rubber on the end of your pencil; even relatively "soft" racing brakes are still nothing like a "rubber eraser" in any meaningful way.

The original "modern" brake-pad was actually made from asbestos, until it was realized that it might not be wise... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, if they wake up one day and stop giving a crap about tourism... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an old "cover" gif from Quantum Magazine... I couldn't find more of a source than that, or I'd include the artist name/link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Barbie melts on grill* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Hole Sim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce: https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/scientists-find-giant-wave-rolling-through-the-perseus-galaxy-cluster

Combining data from NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory with radio observations and computer simulations, an international team of scientists has discovered a vast wave of hot gas in the nearby Perseus galaxy cluster. Spanning some 200,000 light-years, the wave is about twice the size of our own Milky Way galaxy.

The researchers say the wave formed billions of years ago, after a small galaxy cluster grazed Perseus and caused its vast supply of gas to slosh around an enormous volume of space.

"Perseus is one of the most massive nearby clusters and the brightest one in X-rays, so Chandra data provide us with unparalleled detail," said lead scientist Stephen Walker at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland. "The wave we've identified is associated with the flyby of a smaller cluster, which shows that the merger activity that produced these giant structures is still ongoing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what way do you feel that it was a civilizing force? I'd love some concrete examples; keep in mind that it was born in the greatest civilization that would exist until the industrial revolution nearly two thousand years later... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You rejected the idea that it was a defensive war, while I provided evidence that it was. 

No, you just provided evidence that you don't understand what "Defensive" means in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. says American service member killed in Somalia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what I said? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crusades were a defensive war in response to Islamic aggression.

Not even close, although granted that was the stated reason. Essentially knights needed a way to fight and loot and all of that good stuff without fighting and looting other Christians; the pope had a bright idea and bam... 1st Crusade. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Romans hadn't half-assed it, the world would be a more diverse and interesting place today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be, but calling a title clickbait because you just can't imagine that the people involved are anything other than mentally ill is... shitposting at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What more is there? Noise complaints?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible even a little longer... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I mean... that's more accurate than not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably eating that foreign muck, you know... *French* mustard and such! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a baby face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm loving the range of responses... I got yours and this one in my inbox at the same time. 

/u/ragingrufusig 
I wouldn't do anything because I'm a nice dood

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Television psychics, and televangelists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bulbman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It was *their* fault!" -Our collective dumbass tombstone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure, I really enjoyed your post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Difficult to grasp... something in the realm of quantum field theory. Difficult to experiment on (descending from most inconceivably difficult), GUT theories, Dark Matter and Dark Energy, Neutrino astronomy, Gravitational astronomy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can definitely make that argument, but it would probably take a fairly long and involved study to make it more than argument. That said, I think it would be hard to argue against a correlation of high meme:non-meme expression, and anti-intellectualism. 

We have to remember though, that the internet has more people from a broader slice of life talking to each other than ever before. It can be tempting to assign the results of a greater experience with our fellow human to some new factor. That doesn't mean that people aren't getting dumber, or crazier, etc... but you have to be careful about that kind of thinking too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're confusing the notion of a quantum vacuum, in which pair production/annihilation spontaneously occurs, the notion of zero-point energy, and the kind of energy you need to do Work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you define "difficult" in this context? Involving the most intellectual taxing calculations, or something like hunting for Dark Matter or a particular kind of neutrino, i.e. technically very difficult and you may never find it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're *massive* animals, and they've evolve to support that mass with buoyancy. Out of the water they struggle to breathe, struggle to support their mass, they dry out and die of exposure or exhaustion. 

In essence... you could only spend so long treading water before you just... slipped under the waves. Well... a whale or a dolphin can only spend so long *out* of the water, straining, before they can't survive any longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say his first statement is hyperbolic (and probably intended that way), and the second... he kind of nailed it. In any given thread on the front of /all a reasonable person could predict at least a dozen of the top comments. 

I think the problem is that it's not memes that are somehow sapping people's wits, it's just that memes have become the language of the witless. The thing is... memes are the language of everyone else too, and no one likes to be lumped in the with the LCD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triage is a thing, and that must be one giant list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you say. 

Edit: ...And by the way, how damaged do you need to be to object on the grounds that he's president, not that it's murder?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the same reason that it's easy to lay down rather than jog; one is a relatively passive, low-effort activity, and the other is learning something new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a century+ of steady research, and luck; nobody is close enough to using fusion to make viable power plants to even really talk about it in concrete terms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Through a powerful satellite telescope... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to score the weakest point ever, or are did really respond to a well considered post with that... shit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because a vast majority of the world only regrets that he missed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Elon will be laughing at you from Mars, with neural lace and a vac-train!" 

-Fanboys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The news and political subs of Reddit attract them like flies. Moderators on Reddit, even the truly well-meaning ones, still lack the tools to actually ban people who don't want to stay banned. The result is the endless flood of "new" accounts with the same old shit to say. If they get someone else banned, so much the better for them, and if they get banned... so what? Roll a new account, and call it a day. 

The problem is that from the moderator's perspective, the sum total of their power really comes down to pressing one of a few buttons, all of which rely on someone basically agreeing to the process. So... we wade through shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Hetzjagd auf Nazis* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Descent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've forgotten what being open gets them in the long run...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains why everyone bullies everyone else... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently made a post claiming to have a theory, but am unable to derive the necessary equations to test it

Then you don't have a theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much... we're just apes with a particularly well-developed internal monologue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew! But yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another deflection and no answer. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your life is clearly full of importance" is still odd enough. 

Plus you didn't answer my question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my pick too... be amazing at cleaning anything, then get a job as the world's greatest restorer and cleaner of fine and rare art. 

Plus, you know... never make another bed until the day I die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your life is clearly full of importance to be willingly embedding propaganda.

English not your first language? What is?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they tried to explain that to Russia for a while, but Putin was notably unimpressed with that argument. So... now they're Russian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, if you're god, you can be subtle in a profound way. I think the best discussion of this in some form I've heard is from Jim Butcher's *Dresden Files* in regards to his concept of fallen angels. In essence, even without *any* power their age, knowledge, and incredible perspective of a *vast* time and multitude of lives makes them insanely formidable. Needless to say something with *all* of the knowledge of *everything* is another step up.

That being the case, a huge number of things could avert catastrophe, even before catastrophe was evident. After all, sea level rise is a symptom of a larger problem, and by averting the cause (emissions, energy demand, energy production, human population size, etc) you could simply annul the problem.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=edCqF_NtpOQ

Anyway, that's how I'd imagine a god operating... otherwise what kind of god is it really? You can't exactly have a crisis if you're omniscient... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that it could be anyone in the world; the person you kill could be a hostage-taker, kidnapper, or despot...  not just someone you hold a grudge against.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going down the sewer of the "Censorship means every craven decision a broadcaster makes!"... non-argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes

Edit: But consider that you would then only excel *in school*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They *could*, but it would be unrelated to arthritis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Coverage*... not Reddit posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Have you been reading *Calvin   Hobbes*?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he certainly had more compelling dialogue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessss!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not bad taste... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, you'd be on fire long before you had to worry about scooping magma. 

Edit... The Misadventures of Barnaby and Throckmorton: Journey To Way Too Close To The Mantle

Barnaby: "I say chap, have you burst into flames or is it just me?"

Throckmorton: "Come on man, stiff upper lip!"

Barnaby: "About that Throcky, it's melted off..."

Throckmorton: http://i.imgur.com/nJZ0pkT.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... it's God... hold up a hand for a while and reflect some sunlight? You've sort of thrown all of science out of the window by definition when omnipotence comes into the picture; by definition this includes the ability to changes pesky things like the laws of physics. 

Along that line, a god could probably slightly tweak the mass of the Earth or its orbital inclination or lock the water in away ice by fiat....


...it's god! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the coverage... everyone is talking about Brexit and Trump and Syria and Russia, and Europe, and Migrancy, etc. I would suspect that a lot will be *said* and little will be done. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the case of teeth that's a bit different; there's a live nerve inside of a healthy tooth, and it's *sensitive* as you learned; even through a layer of dentin. People with horribly rotted teeth have certainly experienced incredible pain for a while... then the nerve died, and that was that. No nerve, no pain, but mind you that's not necessarily a good thing. Rotting teeth and unhealthy gums are *dangerous* in a chronic sense, but also in terms of a risk for dangerous infections of the mouth and jaw.

Pain is at the end of the day, a warning, but it can go wrong. As to evolutionary purpose... crippling chronic pain is not evolved, it's a breakdown of the human being. Most of the time though, it's not going to happen during your most fertile breeding years, right?

"Evolution" such as it is, gives no shits about you if you can pass along your genes; if what's killing you wouldn't show up until much later... womp womp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the hope; there have been experimental events which indicate that it's possible, but the truth is that it's *incredibly* difficult even on a tiny scale. On the scale of a power plant... it may or may not be feasible. A lot of people on Reddit seem to think that fusion research now is about "building a power plant" or finding a good power plant design. Really, it's nowhere near that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neonic Pesticides Threaten Wild Bees' Spring Breeding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an important distinction... you're getting more energy than you put into it, but *not* more energy than was put into it. As /u/shadydentist said you can burn hydrocarbons and release energy, *but* it took energy to assemble those hydrocarbons in the first place... it's just that none of us expended that energy. In the case of fission, you're splitting atoms that already exist; you didn't expend the energy to create them in the first place. 

In the case of fusion, it's a bit different on the surface, because you're creating a new element and harvesting some of the excess energy of that reaction. The total binding energy of the new Helium nucleus is a bit lower than the total binding energy of the nucleons which formed it, and that excess can't vanish, so it's released. Fusion is all about harvesting that excess; you want to spend less energy fusing H, or He, or whatever, than you can theoretically get out of the reaction. 

That... is the hard part. Without a star's mass of material to work with, it's tough to fuse atoms; they have a strong mutual repulsion you have to overcome (Coulomb Barrier). In a reactor you can't have a giant mass, so you need high pressures and temperatures... that's hard, and it takes a lot of energy. 

That said, there are some energetically favorable pathways to nuclear fusion, by using "fuel" that already exists (now we're getting back to the start of this post) such as 2 and 3 isotopes of Hydrogen (Deuterium, Tritium). Deuterium is plentiful, but Tritium is definitely *not*.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an expert, but I have eyes... answer: cheating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check that out, thanks for the tip. I'm always down for any good open source project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, in fact the opposite is more likely to happen, and the stress of constant pain is likely to be harmful. In addition pain relief can allow you to have more activity in your day, which is better for things like arthritis, for one example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the pendant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's closer than I've gotten before, thanks for the feedback. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela death toll rises as foes protest Maduro's power shakeup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... compromise is a necessary part of life. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aodhn  Rordin

Ok... now my instinct tells me that's pronounced "Ay-dahn Oh Rear-Dane" but I'm *never* right with Celtic languages. How is that name really pronounced, if you don't mind?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "non-geeks" will take the path of least resistance, don't follow them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poe's Law is a bitch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adorable cat, great sign, really lovely kitchen and nice hardwood floors. Maybe the judgment is ultimately favorable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god... those giant paws are almost as big as the head!!!! And that *face*...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signal... open source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes... the Charlie Sheen version of "Winning" strikes again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *His only limitation is the length of the building... he is... SPROING Springy Bob!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why move from one closed-source product to another? Try Signal, it's open-source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it'll be more or less than the women who falsely accused that guy of rape (from the FP yesterday)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could be right, this is one of those, "We're going to have to wait and see," situations... for better or worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Shrug*

!RemindMe 10years [are we still here?] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump? Who knows. SK? Hmmmm... maybe. Japan? Under Abe?

Noooo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been saying that for decades; they've survived famine and being pariahs on the world stage. Meanwhile they show no particular sign of implosion, while the UK and US are throwing their respective political tantrums, and Russia and China wet themselves laughing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that there are some very rich people who believe in this, or hope to make it come to pass, but it's exceedingly unlikely. I mean, sure... they can "fly to space" and then die in space; there's no technology on the horizon which could support a completely self-sustaining colony away from Earth. 

The sad truth is that the very rich are not necessarily the very smart or the very technically minded; they may well be the types who think that money and a metric ton of nerds can solve any problem. They are wrong, and while they might fare better at first, they're not going to survive in the long run.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time that was tried a war was fought over it; you might be surprised about the unsettled issues of geopolitics inherent in the Korean peninsula.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CIA doesn't operate on Americans in the US

http://i.imgur.com/6QXtPyI.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not capitalism or communism or any -ism really... it's people; we're the problem; we are why we can't have nice things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got you!

https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/scientists-find-giant-wave-rolling-through-the-perseus-galaxy-cluster

Combining data from NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory with radio observations and computer simulations, an international team of scientists has discovered a vast wave of hot gas in the nearby Perseus galaxy cluster. Spanning some 200,000 light-years, the wave is about twice the size of our own Milky Way galaxy.

The researchers say the wave formed billions of years ago, after a small galaxy cluster grazed Perseus and caused its vast supply of gas to slosh around an enormous volume of space.

"Perseus is one of the most massive nearby clusters and the brightest one in X-rays, so Chandra data provide us with unparalleled detail," said lead scientist Stephen Walker at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland. "The wave we've identified is associated with the flyby of a smaller cluster, which shows that the merger activity that produced these giant structures is still ongoing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not, but they probably can until the US finishes imploding, Europe fragments, and nobody can stop them from just massacring or interning DPRK'ers who annoy them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...But no one in Ireland can remember.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/QYHSG2w.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you familiar with the NSA, CIA, FBI, and police?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and 10 O'Clock Live is another... still, if that's all it takes to foil automated systems again and again, it's not going to stop people from posting some sick shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking helps your asthma?! Wow, I wouldn't have guessed that, but if it works, good for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR The answer isn't "Crates of virgins" unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/EouEzI5bBR8uk/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/83aoGyM.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://img.memesuper.com/c108a3cf9db176ebf665b48a3d9e6603_mayweather-sr-rips-pacquiao-meme-didnt-read_510-421.jpeg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that were really true I wouldn't be watching Never Mind The Buzzcocks on Youtube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/0RN7XZR.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow I doubt that it could support millions of Nigerians, even if they could get there, adapt to the climate, and the Russia didn't object. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you were serious, it's not a "solid" patch as such. Any other ideas that don't involve treading water?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What should they have done?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that they won't; they don't support the DPRK out of love, but a desire not to have to deal with the collapse of the DPRK and all that would entail. It's nothing that some verbal sparring on the public stage changes.

China is going to keep this up until/unless they feel they can close down that border, or deal with that influx and the the US on their border.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who's ever eaten kimchi knows this is no hollow threat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 250 Mly away... this is incredible stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Simulation of Distant 'Tsunami' of Gas in The Perseus Cluster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Machines which could do all of the things humans do in mines would be *extremely* expensive, and very difficult to produce/maintain. As a result, even if they were possible, they would be very expensive. Coal is only useful because it's *so* incredibly cheap, and the cheapness comes from using humans as disposable cogs and ignoring environmental externalities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the only "cure" for all cancer would have to be purely hypothetical, very versatile and *very* smart nanotech. Until/unless that starts to emerge, "cure for cancer" is likely to only ever mean, "Cure for a specific type of cancer" at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/3o6UBpHgaXFDNAuttm/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear, they're a week away from just saying that in their next issue, they'll offer, "A final solution to the Muslim problem..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
