<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8219</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this...but it sort of defeats the purpose of doing it as a team if they just do nothing. And i dont think they should then get the same amount of money.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My beef with contact missions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just completed a mission. I cant remember the name its the one where you have to steak a merryweather buzzard and go round killing their troops at various outposts...its a pretty hard mission.

Anyway. There was me and some random player who at the first stage uses up all the team lives leaving me to do 90% of the mission alone. Which I did. 

I dont think its right that he then gets the same amount of money as I do. I've also done missions where lazy bastards just sit in your car doing nothing and still get the same cut. 

It annoys me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, wasted a fair few million on mc shit i never use. 

It had made me more business smart though. I'll always consider if somethings worth a big outlay before buying. The CEO business is great though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stock up vehicle warehouse. Get a feel of the sessions you are in. When you find a chill session with like only a few players, sell your vehicles and make millions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God. I feel so triggered right now 


My character is non binary cis fluid gender.

And to suggest they are a he/she is any one gender is oppressive.

I am a snowflake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id just like a thermal scope 

A flame thrower

A chainsaw 

Dual smg

Mortars

Wire guided missiles

Medieval ball and chain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to add. I have kids. I work with kids. I know how kids are influenced by video games etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but just no.

I work in a school and get kids talking about it all the time.

1. Drug and alcohol abuse
2. Prostitution and sex scenes
3. Violence and crime constantly with no consequences 
4. The trolling and abuse from other online players
5. Constant bad language

Its a great game. I love it! But it's not for little kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Import and export definitely. No driving shitty slow vehicles where you could lose the lot. You get to drive brilliant cars that would cost millions. It gives you an idea of what to spend your money on.

You may lose the odd thousand here or there, but last week I had spent all my money, this week just doing import export and contact missions, I am almost up to two million. And can never play more than two hours a day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youth mental health workers here.

I like the series. I am on episode 6. Its intriguing and interesting. However I do feel it gives a glamourised view of teen suicide.

The thought that you can teach all the bullies and nasty people a lesson by killing yourself...it may look attractive to a young person. Just like when they televise school shootings and more happen..

Ultimately if a kids thinking seriously about suicide they will do it regardless. 

As an adult and a parent, and indeed a youth mental health worker....its terrifies me the culture that glamourises and minimises suicide. Look at the stupid fucked up and sick thing that is the blue whale challenge. I think more needs to be done to prevent suicide in young people. I'm not saying 13 reasons will drive kids to kill themselves. I just think it missed am opportunity to show kids a better way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will let us buy the rail gun. Which really isn't all that fun to use... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 10:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am better than her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im British and seriously as a country. Its just a bunch of cunts on an island. Once we were cultured and awesome.

Now it's morons governed by morons. Doing moronic things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I am just going to come out and say what everyone really thinks....

The burkas, niqabs and any other face covering should be compulsory for women that look like angela Merkel. In all countries. At all times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People play tiny racers ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Manchez is the best in my opinion. I have million dollar sports cars, fully customised vehicles of all types, yet I still use my dirt bike the most. 

They are great fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Remove] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hydras suck.....for those that don't own one 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you London cunts. 

Northerners all the way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best and most interesting way to make loads of money is by pursuing various means. If i can fuck up a rivals delivery whilst making my own....i will. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely not how it's meant to be played...hence the notifications saying "destroy rivals cargo/vehicle"

GTA is not about being nice and helping each other. Its about being a criminal bad bastard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 11:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The contact missions are the easiest way to make cash.  I got 600k last night in an hour and a half... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
