<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6412</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will do so, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PayPay is telling me I have to give a refund to a buyer that bought a PC from me two and a half months ago because now it's not "working right," even though in a message she told me it had been turned on for the first time last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/amp/kotaku.com/the-sad-story-behind-a-dead-pc-game-that-cant-come-back-1688358811/amp

I found this article when I went looking for why it's not even on Steam. It's interesting (and sad). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just talking about that the other day with my boyfriend... it wasn't just the gameplay, it was the soundtrack too. I'd love to see a proper Part 3 (though that will never happen). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny, I never once touched Blitz. I had Hitz '02, '03 (pictured and definitely my favorite) and Pro, which sort of torpedoed the fun I thought. It's a game where you light yourself on fire and can play as an alien... it did not need to be more "realistic." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If ever there was a video game franchise that deserves a comeback, it's NHL Hitz. Case in point, my team's star player... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone in Centralia knows about the Crick It... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zv4li/everyone_in_valley_forge_knows_about_the_crick_it/?st=J14AEJJM sh=12aa474d)

[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60zd51/everyone_in_pennsylvania_knows_about_centralia/?st=J0VS69TW sh=0c64a328)

[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/62b67z/you_dont_know_the_first_thing_about_the_crick_it/?st=J0VS7TPF sh=3fa925d0)

[Part 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/63iikr/everyone_in_valley_forge_knows_about_the_crick_it/?st=J14AMBEP sh=00a93e93)

[Part 6](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66dguu/its_what_were_all_about_here_in_centralia/?st=J1PIYEW9 sh=a04bf5c8)

[Part 7](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/68oyzl/centralia_pennsylvania/?st=J26NIWT0 sh=929a897d)

"I don't know what they call It now," he had said, "but back then, in Centralia, everyone called It the Crick It."

The Crick It. The term reverberated in my skull for the umpteenth time that day. Especially now that I had arrived in Centralia.

The sun just began to shine over the dew covered grass sticking up sparsely through the uneven cracks that spread like veins across the former town's Main Street.

Last night, I found myself tossing and turning in my dorm room, periodically getting up and just wandering around the empty building. It was an old hotel, one of the oldest buildings in modern downtown Pittsburgh. It had been converted into dorms only a few years ago, yet the place still looked like it belonged in the 30's.

At night, they said a ghost shuffled along the halls. I even heard a recording of it walking around a friend's single dorm. Spooky stuff, sure, but what concerned me most was the feeling of the place. Too quiet even in the daytime, at night an eerie yellow mood draped the endless, beige hallways. It sounded like the bottom deck of an old ship, the never ending settling sounds of the ancient building coming off like lame waves striking the hull of a powerful wooden boat.

It was hypnotic almost. That's the only way I can explain the brown out I experienced as I realized I was no longer in the building. I wasn't even on the street. Instead I was in my car, the old Crown Vic the orphanage had managed to get me on my 16th birthday. In my car and already over half way to the Pittsburgh city limits.

I almost gasped as I found myself turning on to the highway. The sudden shock of what I was doing hit me like a punch in the face. I rolled down the manual window, letting a little fresh air in. The last thing I saw as I left the city behind me was what looked like two bums fighting or fucking under the overpass bridge. One of them wasn't moving.

I blinked hard and they were both gone. A trick of the light. Or maybe it was my mind's way of telling me I really should be in bed. Not in my dorm. Not at the orphanage. But at home. Where I belonged.

My mind lingered on my family, taken from me far too early. Taken by a monster, or so I was told. As unbelievable as it seemed, the part of my brain that dragged me to my car in the middle of the night certainly thought there was some truth to it.

"Everyone in Pennsylvania knows about Centralia," I muttered in a daze. A daze I snapped out of as I realized the sun was almost up and I had just pulled up to the abandoned town's city limits. A barely standing Welcome signed loomed in front of me:

"Welcome to Centralia! The gem of Central Pennsyl-WARNING! RESTRICTED ENTRY! ALL TRESPASSERS WILL BE ARRESTED! DANGER! HAZARDOUS!"

The orange flyer covering most of the sign looked fresh.

"Impossible," I said to myself as I glared at the warning before me. 

240 miles. Like that. I didn't even stop to get gas. Yet a glance at my nearly full tank told me differently. I shut off the car and the fuel meter immediately dropped, a blunt refusal to acknowledge the impossibility of the situation.

I hastily exited the car and looked past the sign. A large fence now wrapped itself around what seemed like the entire parameter of the small town. Like the orange warning, the fence too looked less than a few weeks old, it's metal woven trappings shining brilliantly in the dawn's morning light.

"Hey."

I froze. Somebody mumbled just behind me, a muted voice that sounded almost defeated.

"Hey," he said again. "Turn around."

I did as I was told, coming face to face with what looked like a park ranger. Dark circles under his eyes gave him a gaunt look, almost haunted.

"Sorry," I started. "I didn't mean to be any trouble. I was just... it's been awhile since I've been here."

"Not supposed to be here. Follow me."

The man nodded and approached me. Before I could even react, he walked right past where I stood, waving awkwardly for me to follow as he approached the large fence.

Not really knowing what else to do, I followed. We reached the parameter of the fence in no time and the man lead me to a padlocked medal door. Expecting this man to be some sort of official, I waited for him to produce a key-

With a loud crash, the guy kicked the door as hard as he could. It swung open, slamming with a crash against the other side of the fence.

"Oh, um..." I stammered.

"Follow," he said again. Though his voice...

"Am I in some kind of trouble or-"

"Hey!" a familiar voice shouted from behind me. I turned around. "Hey kid!"

There, by my car, was another man. A man dressed like a park ranger. A man who looked identical to the one I had just followed to the gate. He was running as fast as he could. In his hand, he was pointing a pistol.

"Oh, shit..." I heard my own voice trail off as the man behind me began to produce a strange gurgling noise. Before I had a chance to even turn around, I felt something grasp my ankle and pull.

I fell to the ground, hitting my head as my body spun around just in time to see the Thing that lead me into Centralia. Through my blurred vision, I could see that It kept the form of the park ranger. It was now within the fence, a solid fifteen feet from me. Its grotesque, elongated appendage, imitating the arm of a man, was still wrapped around my ankle. Such a creature, out and about in the morning sun...

It began to drag me. Dilapidated buildings began to appear in my peripheral. Downtown Centralia, a skeleton of what it once was. As I moved, I swore I could see shapes in some of the windows, watching as I helplessly struggled against the Thing's grip.

Behind me, I could hear the man, the real man, shouting after me. The fucking Thing was whistling. Sounded like Kings of Leon. 

It only stopped when I heard the gunshots begin to echo throughout the town. Two of the bullets struck the creature... struck the monster in the shoulder. My vision began to clear and my mind began to give the rest of my body the kick in the ass it needed.

"Stay down!"

I barely had time to react to the shouting man before I saw that he had ran right up to the side of the Thing. It began to grow, stretching upwards, morphing the face of the man It was trying to imitate and intimidate.

The ranger didn't even hesitate. A shotgun now in his hands, he placed the barrel directly into the mouth of his doppelgnger and pulled the trigger. The monster snarled and screeched, unleashing a torrent of what almost sounded like English curse words.

It hit the ground with a thud, a lifeless husk for barely a second as new appendages appeared around the side of the creature, dragging Itself off into the town with breakneck speed.

It twisted Itself around a corner and back over the fence, disappearing into the nearby woods.

I exhaled. I hadn't even realized I was holding my breath throughout the entire ordeal.

"Here," the ranger said, holding out his hand for me to take. Sensing my hesitation, the man kneeled down, helping me to my feet whether I liked it or not.

And then I began to cry. Turning to the man, this stranger, I began to weep openly. He eventually embraced my shoulders. I think he may have been holding back tears himself.

And that's when we heard a new voice.

"Such love," a sickly sweet voice rung out. "It's what we're all about here."

The ranger dropped the embrace, taking aim with his shotgun without missing a beat.

It was an older man, he had just walked out of a nearby church. He was wearing an impeccably tailored suit, his hands outstretched before him. Behind him, exiting the other buildings one by one, were others, all dressed in similar attire.

"Such love," he said again. "It's what we're all about here in Centralia."

I found myself stepping closer to the ranger as I took a glance behind me, back towards the entrance.

Back towards the vacant spot in the road where my car once was.

"Shit," I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like saying I can't fully enjoy Back to the Future because I wasn't alive during the 50's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "EveryONE in VALLEY forge KNOWS aBOUT the CRICK it..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zv4li/everyone_in_valley_forge_knows_about_the_crick_it/?st=J14AEJJM sh=12aa474d)

[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60zd51/everyone_in_pennsylvania_knows_about_centralia/?st=J0VS69TW sh=0c64a328)

[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/62b67z/you_dont_know_the_first_thing_about_the_crick_it/?st=J0VS7TPF sh=3fa925d0)

[Part 5](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/63xvuo/everyone_in_centralia_knows_about_the_crick_it/?st=J1792IJP sh=439688d8)

[Part 6](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66dguu/its_what_were_all_about_here_in_centralia/?st=J1PIYEW9 sh=a04bf5c8)

[Part 7](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/68oyzl/centralia_pennsylvania/?st=J26NIWT0 sh=929a897d)

I froze for a moment, unsure if this was some kind of prank. If it was, it was in pretty poor taste just two days after Reynold's breakdown. I rose from my chair and walked towards the walkie, empty static now filling the room as I began to speak.

"This is Sam, who is this? Over."

No response. And suddenly I realized just how quiet the cabin was without anybody else by my side. Even the usual forest noises had ceased. A lot of people seem surprised by just how loud the woods can be at ni-

Something darted by the window, low to the sill, but fast. I moved over as swiftly and quietly as I could, grasping my heavy flashlight by the handle as I did. It may not be a gun exactly, but the thing could pack one helluva wallop.

I hunched forward, peeking through the quiet darkness, holding my breath. 

Nothing. 

Just the usual pitch black canvas filled with trees. And my overactive imagination filling in the blanks with old monster movie memories.

I smiled, though it was short lived. I really wasn't in the mood for this shit tonight. I raised the walkie, ready to lay down a little hell, my finger poised to press the button so hard it might even snap off. 

"Everyone IN Valley ForgE KNOws about the CRIck IT," the voice repeated. It was louder this time and slightly less distorted. I almost fell backwards, fumbling the radio as I did, getting a firm grasp only as I lost my balance and fell back into the chair.

I could only stare at the walkie. I found myself suddenly too wary to respond, all the spit and vinegar I was saving up disappearing in a single instant.

I was afraid. There was something about that voice. It was like hearing something that was read in reverse but then played in the correct order and on a loop. Mechanical, distorted and all wrong.

I pressed the receiver. Only static again. I hesitated, licking my lips nervously.

"Hey, whoever this is-"

Something walked across the roof. Skittered was more accurate, from one end of the cabin to the other.

I froze for what felt like an eternity, my eyes glued to the ceiling, my free hand wrapping once more around my flashlight.

And that's when the radio crackled to life once more. Only this time, I didn't feel fear. There wasn't a term for it, honestly. But it wasn't good. 

Of all the horrors I would experience in the coming minutes, it's only a single uttered, nearly whispered word that still undoubtedly and unequivocally shakes me to my core as I reflect back on all of it:

"Daddy?" the distorted voice on the other side of the radio sheepishly asked.

Slowly, I found my line of sight transferring back to the walkie in my shaking grasp. My flashlight fell to the floor, breaking in two parts and rolling in opposite directions.

"Whaa-?" I sort of asked, my lips and tongue too paralyzed to create proper words.

"DaddY? WheRE are YOU?"

The red hot tears were falling from my face before I even had a chance to realize I had started crying. I rose from the chair, clutching the walkie for dear life.

"DAddy!"

"Au... Austin? I'm... I'm right here buddy, I'm right he-" I began to break down, my body heaving as I embraced the walkie, unable to even comprehend my surroundings.

Until I heard the laughing. That same distorted voice, now a low cackle on the other side of the radio. I wiped at my eyes, my emotions sobering up.

"What is this!" I demanded, my voice just a nothing in the silence.

The laughing ceased as my eyes were once again drawn to the window. There was some kind of commotion by the tree line. Six bulky figures, moving through the darkness.

And that's when the door flung open. A woman walked in, wearing high heels and a business suit. Here, in a cabin in the middle of the woods. But that wasn't the only thing alien about her. Something was off, the tightness of her skin, the way she walked in a stiff waltz across the floorboards. Gracefully peculiar. And her age... could have been anywhere between 40 and 200.

"Who the hell are you?" I demanded, my glare racing back and forth between the walkie and this new intruder.

"Relax, Samuel, try to relax," she said, desperately trying to mask the natural malice in her voice. "I'm a doctor. And I know what you're going through right now and I just wish to help."

The entire world suddenly lit up from the outside as, through the window, I saw a stream of flames spewed forth upon a nearby tree.

Flamethrowers. Those bulky figures were men with fucking flamethrowers. They had dogs too, giving the impression of some sort of suped-up hunting party. The sight sent me leaping back once again, an eerie orange hue now draped across the innards of the cabin.

Before I could ask another question, the "doctor" was by my side. She tried to whisper soothing words again, but I felt the tip of the needle before she even opened her mouth.
 
I shoved the woman as hard as I could. She fell back, though caught her balance. I could actually see her legs flex with a queer resistance as she regained her composure.

The orange hue grew with intensity as from outside three more flamethrowers joined their brother in seemingly burning the forest to the ground.

And then I saw the ground move, just below the men's feet. Some of the dogs began barking. And one of the men began to shout. And then firearms replaced the flamethrowers, gunshots reverberating throughout the nearby woods.

I turned back to the woman. In the brief seconds since I had shoved her I almost forgot she was even there. There was a gun in her hand now, though after everything that had happened, I barely comprehended it as a threat.

"The fuck is that Thing? How did It sound like... what is It?" I shouted, holding the walkie in the air like a weapon. I began to babble, almost incoherently.

But I was cut off as a severed... something struck the window. The glass didn't give, but the sensation was that of the entire cabin shaking at once. As the bloody appendage slid towards the grass below, I could have sworn it was twitching.

"Listen goddamnit!" the doctor shouted, waving the gun around dramatically with each syllable. "We could've done this the easy way, but I see that's not going to happen! Now I can explain every-"

I threw the damn walkie as hard as I could, hit her right in the face too. Before she fell to the ground, I noticed her blood. It was dark... still red, but black too. A sweet odor not unlike freshly mowed grass filled the cabin.

And then the cabin really did begin to shake. Violently. I began to stagger, grabbing the nearby wall to steady myself. I noticed the shouting and barking and gunshots had ceased.

The floor gave in... well gave out was more like it. Something green and brown and red and fleshy burst through the newly formed hole. It was vaguely humanoid and had what might be described as appendages, ghoulish lumps hanging off Its side. There was an open crevice towards the top of It you might even call a mouth. It certainly had teeth. And a revolting black discharge, like puss, dripped from Its every pore. 

I couldn't speak as I took the surreal scene in. But in that instant, I knew I was in the presence of something weird and something pissed off. Something old.

Something evil.

Somehow, I dared not look away. The Thing was before me for less than a minute, smoke now billowing through the surrounding crevice in the floor. And yet, in that small moment, a clear picture took form upon the bulk of the Thing. 

Austin's face. And then his shoulders and then his arms. Clear as a bell, mere inches from my body. My son was climbing out of this fucking Thing before me, reaching out and dripping with blood and dirt.

Before I could take his hand for the first time in 5 years, an electronic, ear splitting sound emitted from the woman on the ground. Austin vanished instantly and the Thing recoiled. It almost seemed disgusted.

A haze I hadn't even realized I was in dissipated as the piercing sound continued to fill the cabin... it was a full five seconds before I realized the Thing before me was making Its own noise, shrieking like a crying child... my crying child.

I ran for the door. Before my hand was on the knob, my brain kicked into overdrive and made a split second decision that may have saved my life.

I stooped down next to the woman. Her eyes were glazed as she seemed to be drifting in and out of consciousness. Her hand reached for mine pathetically. I ignored it as I grabbed the gun off the floor and snagged the phone and car keys sticking out of her jacket pocket.

"DaaaaDDY?" I heard behind me through the shrieking.

I didn't even try to look back as I made my exit.

I barely recall running through the woods. My truck was parked directly on the other side of the cabin and yet I didn't even think about going for it. That meant another potential glimpse of that damned Thing.

Instead, I made a direct line towards the woods. The branches crashed against my heaving chest and shoulders, my park hat long left behind. 

After what felt like hours (in actuality, maybe 5 minutes), my tired legs carried me into the visitor's parking lot, the newfound quiet darkness shocking me out of my funk. 

A pair of black vans and a single sedan sat isolated in the center of the paved lot. Without even thinking about it, I removed the woman's keys from my jacket pocket and pressed the lock button. The sedan's lights flashed followed by a honk that pierced the eerily quiet scene. I actually shushed the damn thing as I climbed into the driver's seat. Collapsed into it actually.

I took a moment to breathe. Before me, through the shrouded woods, I could just make out the cabin, a flaming orange, ever moving dot within the landscape.

I rubbed my eyes, forcing my mind to recollect everything it had witnessed in the last... what? Only twenty minutes? I knew even the attempt at comprehension could drive me mad.

And that's when I noticed the stack of folders piled haphazardly on the passenger's seat. Atop the very first one, my name was printed neatly.

I should have thrown that stack out the window. Maybe hightailed it for my parent's house, or even my ex's... somewhere completely unpredictable. But no. No, instead my curiosity had me picking up the top folder and opening it.

Everything. Everything imaginable about me from the hospital I was born in to my marriage right out of high school. Everything about me, my parents, my ex... the accident... Austin...

And then I began looking through every folder. Next up was Reynolds followed by the family from two days ago. Their daughter. 

Their dead son.

After that, the info dump. Nothing directly about what this Thing was, but certainly plenty about It. Glancing back and forth towards the cabin from time to time, I tried my best to speed through the notes.

Before I knew it, a vague though no less horrifying picture was painted before me. The missing persons throughout the years all through the area... the authorities and the media (local and national) told to ignore it. The clean up that would occur after an attack, both physically and financially, was almost too much to handle. And yet they still managed to keep It a secret.

Because they were cultivating It. Had been for years. Whatever It was, It was incredibly dangerous. Seemingly at will, It was capable of... transforming. Shift shape into whatever the hell It deemed necessary to accomplish Its goals. And what were Its goals? Even the damn Thing's handlers didn't seem to have a clue.

The implications of such a creature existing were dizzying to think about.

I came to the final page. It was a map, a very old map. At the top was a note, written sloppily and jammed into the corner:

"Dr. R-

Say Hi to Bradfield. Tell him baby's doing just fine but misses his scent. Tell him baby loves him. Show him baby's progress.

-Smith"

The map was a town, looked almost barren. However there were lines scribbled across it, clearly from a marker, written in the same style as the note.

"Two miles today."

"Dog and cat here. Baby played with dog's tail before dinner. Cat didn't stand a chance."

"Hitchhiker on 61. Old man, easy prey. Baby started feet first, the vagrant didn't stop squirming until baby was up to his neck."

"Tourists on 61. Mother, father, toddler. Dad tried to fight, had to use gun. Mom was first, holding crying toddler while baby ate."

And there were plenty more just like it. Dozens of little notes dotted the map with crude X's. Though I wasn't entirely sure what I was reading, I had a good idea and the sensation literally sickened me. I opened the driver's door, vomiting on to the cool pavement below. Steam began to rise almost immediately.

My nausea was replaced with anger as I wiped away the remaining spittle around my mouth. Years. Actual years this Thing has been roaming around, doing (and eating) as It pleased. My blood boiled as I glanced into the rear view. A shotgun hung idly against the left backseat. I swung around to find a box of shells directly underneath.

I looked forward again, starting the car. Almost a full tank. I took one last glance at the burning cabin. For a moment, it looked like something was stirring, but I couldn't be sure. And I didn't want to wait and find out.

I removed the woman's gun and cell from my pockets, tossing them onto the pile of folders as I pulled out of the parking lot, trying my damndest not to waste any more time. As I took off towards the park's exit, the morning's light just began to peek over the tree line. I stole another glance at the tattered map, taking in the title scrolled across the top. Strange name for a town, even a little ominous. But it was only a two hour drive.

I needed answers. Or maybe it was revenge. Petty revenge just for having to face that goddamn Thing. Either way, I had the distinct feeling I would find both in Centralia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not so much a resident, but more of an... official (more to come in the future). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
