<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9949</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheap, quick, and painless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **IT'S JUST A PRANK, BRO!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Doesn't Read, So Protesters Are Flooding His Office With Books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Chief Spreading Bull

Racism is fun, huh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christian values right there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No we wouldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from the fact that it is an execution method, the guillotine is a surprisingly humane form of execution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton is not quoted anywhere in this "article".  Downvote and move on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this poll an outlier or is their other polling data to suggest that this poll is accurate?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  Liberals need to fully embrace their role as the opposition make their voices heard every chance they get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that is your understanding of "fascism", perhaps you need to spend some time at a university.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He then calls the "so-called" state trooper "weak" and "terrible".  Sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repeal and Replace....right guys?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Wants to Tear Down the Wallthe Wall Between Church and State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *whining* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When will these bleeding heart liberals wake up...it amazes me that there are that many naive, gullible, and reckless liberal democrats," one Mad World News reader commented on the site's Facebook page. "I thank God everyday Trump is the President!"

A direct quote from the article which cites facebook users for sources.  What a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnny Lawrence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had a hurt foot, ok?  While the loser John McCain battled the NVA and was captured, Donald Trump bravely waged his own personal war against bone spurs.  A war, by the way, which he won! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she even know where Canada is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *SNIFF* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refuse to tolerate edits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is acceptable to not tolerate intolerance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but it worked for Gandhi, King

I suck at history, could you tell me what ever became of Gandhi and King?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then please, enlighten me.  What has she done that has prepared her to run the nation's education system at the federal level.  Please, be specific.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You have no idea what Betsy has done for arts and education programs.

What Betsey has done for arts and education has NOTHING to do with her qualifications to be Education Secretary!  If I give a shit-ton of money to the Red Cross does that make me qualified to be the Surgeon General?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumpism Will Not Be Defeated by a Polite, Cuddly, Ineffective Left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but take a look at her works before parrotting somebody elses view about her inexperience.

She has a bachelor's degree, is it an education degree?  Did she attend public schools?  Did her children attend public schools?  Has she ever been a teacher?   Has she ever been an administrator?  

Answer those questions for me and then fuck off for assuming I am parroting the views of someone else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the poll an outlier or are there other polls that show similar results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opposition to Gorsuch isn't about his qualifications, it has everything to do with the fact that before Gorsuch gets a hearing Garland should get a hearing.  

That is Garland's seat, not Gorsuch's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She bought a cabinet position.  It's obvious to everyone.  The problem is, Trump supporters don't care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought V for Vendetta was better than the graphic novel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't aware that "Christian civilization" needed defending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M-A-R-S.  Mars bitches!  Red Rocks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Walter had some endearing characteristics, however misguided they may be.  He obviously cared deeply for Jessie and his son.  Yes, he was a drug lord but remember that his original reasoning for making meth was to provide for his family after his death.  Don't get me wrong, Walter was evil, but there were aspects of his character that resonated with people.  

Skyler was just a bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the surface, it would appear so but keep a few things in mind:

Both of the last two Republican presidents were elected with fewer votes than their opponent. 

Many of the state-houses that are currently controlled by Republicans are maintained through extremely gerry-mandered districts.  The courts have begun to take notice of this and at some point I feel certain the judiciary will correct this practice.

While in public there appears to be a chummy relationship between the Executive and Legislative Branch, a lot of reporting suggests that GOP legislators are not happy with Trump.

White House leaks suggest that even within the WH there are a number of officials who are very concerned with Trump's behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because not only was she annoying, she was also a willing participant (depending on the episode and season) in Walter's meth empire.  She could have walked away at anytime and she didn't.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The staff meetings in the "Diversity Day" episode of The Office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McCain made a star out of Sarah Palin.  I'm not going to come to his defense.  He is a loser, I'm glad his party is burning down around him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyler was the worst.  At least Marie maintained her moral compass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then people started to notice something else: The tweet was sent at 10:51 a.m. Eastern, about 20 minutes after Trump was supposed to have been participating in his daily intelligence briefing, according to his published schedule.

Not only that, but the tweet was sent from an Android phone. Trump has an Android phone  apparently the same one hes used for years. Wired called that device very, very risky given that hes using an old phone thats significantly vulnerable to hacking. This prompted another concern: Did Trump have that phone in the briefing with him? Was he carrying an insecure device with a microphone into one of the most secure places in the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What President Trump is supposed to be doing while hes tweeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon rising in front of the Milky Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon rising in front of the Milky Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, no shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know not with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with sticks and stones.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, the chances of Dems retaking the House or Senate in 2018 are slim. A lot of the seats up for grabs are in very, very, very red districts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elections of consequences.  You dun goofed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should be aware of this: 

Luther Strange was, until this appointment, Attorney General of Alabama.  As Attorney General he was responsible for overseeing and carrying out an investigation into the misuse of funds in relation to a sex scandal involving the governor of Alabama, Robert Bentley.  Some are claiming that this appointment is being given to Luther Strange in exchange for his office bringing about an end to the investigation.

Corruption in Alabama politics is nothing new, it seems that this could be taking the corruption to a whole new level.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Republicans Are Off to a Pitiful Start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corruption feared as Alabama governor picks Jeff Sessions replacement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.yahoo.com/news/m/2167be2f-ec58-31e6-b417-c5761d94d4cd/ss_corruption-feared-as-alabama.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corruption Feared as Alabama Governor Considers Jeff Sessions Replacement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Katshki Pillar Monastery, Chiatura, Georgia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Katshki Pillar Monastery, Chiatura, Georgia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Katshki Pillar Monastery, Chiatura, Georgia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Quebec mosque attack immediately comes to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean blood diamonds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's New Pastime Is Rubbernecking at Kellyanne Conway Interviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have forgotten about Benghazi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only link I can access from this computer is the Breitbart link.  I can't speak to the other link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump again calls out Chicago on violence and repeats debunked murder rate claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a picture of one guy who was punched.  The police report that "two or three" injuries occurred.  A guy was punched at a Trump rally too.  You call one terrorism and not the other and then you call me a "dense fuck" for calling out your hypocrisy.  Classic.

Tell us more about how someone getting punched at a Berkeley protest in "terrorism" but someone getting punched at a Donald Trump rally is "an assault".  Come on, tell us, you dense fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia Today had the number at 80%.  Which should I trust?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breitbart is fake news.  How about a local report that gives better statistics: 

http://www.berkeleyside.com/2017/02/02/berkeley-police-injuries-extensive-property-damage-no-arrests-no-force-used/

According to local reporting, "two or three" people were injured.  So, I ask again, if that is "terrorism" is the assault of a protester at the Trump rally also terrorism.  

I'll await your response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People at Berkeley were "beaten into a coma"?  Not every act of violence is terrorism.  Police report that "two or three" people sufferred injuries during the Berkeley protest.  Remember when the guy at the Trump rally sucker-punched someone who was speaking out against Trump?  Was that terrorism too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down, President Cartman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of A1 sauce are you eating that has "heat"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you said it was brown, not orange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyin' Ted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Trump not recognize/understand the fact that the Judicial Branch is a co-equal branch of government?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool un-biased website, bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how is it not assault when "two or three" people at Berkeley get punched/injured? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  are Muslim Extremists misunderstood and we need to stop bombing them

I never said that.  Radical Muslim extremists are a threat, no doubt about it.  But to sit there and completely disregard the threat coming from right-wing extremists groups/individuals is foolish and shows just how partisan you are regarding this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The protester at the Trump rally who was punched while being escorted out...would you call that terrorism?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two are three people who are injured during the course of a protest is not terrorism, its simply a crime unless it can be proven that those responsible had a political agenda and were not simply taking advantage of the chaos.  

Someone running into a mall and blowing themselves up (even if nobody gets hurt) is terrorism.  

I think the difference is clear to anyone with critical thinking skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, they are both a threat.

It took you long enough to get there, but I'm glad you finally admitted it...the POTUS should as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So you think he's sane?

No, I think he is crazy just like I think that most terrorists are crazy.  

Can you do me a favor and let me know what items are the 'radical ideological politics' agenda? It seems like a catch phrase but I'd like to know what exactly this ideology teaches people.

www.stormfront.org

Start there. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was indoctrinated by right-wing racial propaganda he found online.  You don't need to be affiliated with a church/mosque to be a terrorist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two to three injuries

Yeah, I'm having a hard time calling this terrorism. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.stormfront.org

While these people aren't being "indoctrinated" through churches, they are being "indoctrinated" through right-wing organizations who are tied to racial ideological politics.  It is a little unsettling that you would go through the mental loopholes to try and argue otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't rub me the wrong way, I'm not the one who is willing to call Muslims who committed violent acts "terrorists" but when a white person does it they are "mentally ill".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Doesn't mean someone has to die for it to be violent.

I agree, but I think that in order for it to be "violent" someone at least has to be hurt or attacked.  Was there an attack at Berkeley? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dylan Roof is a mentally ill person.

Ahhhh, the old "white people are mentally ill" argument.  Nice. 

edit:  Also, to completely disregard the movement that produced the literature that Dylann Roof was reading is foolish.  While there may not be "schools" that exist that teach the hatred that Dylann Roof believed in, there is a curriculum out there that is available to anyone who wants to seek it out.  He was a terrorist and he was mentally ill.  Those things are not mutually exclusive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 168 people were killed in the Oklahoma City bombing that was carried out by a right-wing terrorist.  

Damn those pesky facts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the unlawful use of violence

Again, who was harmed in the Berkeley protests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Editorial: Why won't Trump say 'radical right-wing terrorism?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those were anarchists, not "left terrorists".

Also, how many people were killed at Berkeley?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I didn't realize Obama was still the president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EDITORIAL: Why won't Trump say 'radical right-wing terrorism?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Montana Supercell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polished Malachite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polished Malachite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She should be forced to substitute teach at a failing inner-city school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We dun goofed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Montgomery teacher charged with having sex with a student </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wsfa.com/story/34446093/montgomery-teacher-charged-with-having-sex-with-student </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who doesn't pronounce it "meem" can cash me ousside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using tax dollars to fund private schools a terrible idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Thaiss a catcher? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eduardo Rodriguez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, well that makes a lot of sense if you don't think about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Southern Defense Force

Defending against what, exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Programs fighting right-wing extremism at risk of losing Obama grants under Trump administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hail DeVos, fuck Satan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Paris and San Bernadino attacks are on the list.  I seem to remember both of them getting a little coverage in the lame stream media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a force

Bubba and his truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's top leader mocks 'newcomer' Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media didn't even report on the Bowling Green Massacre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But in an interview with the Times today, Trump  who the paper pointed out does not read books"

Of course he doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's foolish to assume that the current administration and Congress, even if the Dems had not nuked the filibuster for lower court nominees, wouldn't use the nuclear option to get their SCOTUS nominee confirmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the average level of education in those states? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back To The Future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late round flyer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No bananas.  No bananas.  You're the bananas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any poll that shows a dislike for Trump or his policies = "fake news"

Any poll that shows support for Trump or his polices = valid poll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump, The Far Right, And The March Against Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't cut yourself on all that edge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matthew McConaughey is a fine actor.  I could not disagree more with his statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F A S C I S M  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is only concerned about his supporters.  His supporters do not go, nor have they ever gone, to college.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have been trying to repeal and replace Obamacare for YEARS, why not just use one of the existing replacement plans they have?  Oh yeah, they don't have a replacement plan because the numerous votes to repeal and replace were just for show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gerrymandering should not be legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush Jr. is George W. Bush, who won in 2000 despite losing the popular vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misspoke, Lie, six of one, half dozen of the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly both?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of those two has publicly and passionately advocated for a hostile relationship with the Muslim community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking ninjas.  Every fucking time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What city do you live in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps if you and your boss didn't lie every fucking time you opened your mouth you wouldn't feel this way about the media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's just fantasy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It came from the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jet fuel and steel beams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al-Qaeda ignited 'the flame of jihad" with the 9/11 attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just fucking with you mate.  Ben Carson, current HUD Secretary, claimed that the pyramids were built to store grain.  Almost everyone disagrees with his analysis, so it has become a bit of a running joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   in defense of his right to speak at a privately funded campus event

Do the protesters not have a right also to protest?  If their protest is so popular that Snowflake Milo is scared to show his face, well then I'd say that is a successful protest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Ben Carson.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I know you're lying because you're still spewing your bullshit and the "violent" liberals haven't stopped you yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  Needed the pyramids to store grain.  Grain storage.  Grain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wonder, were these simply the first skyscrapers? 

Nope, they were used to store grain.  Everybody knows that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Aberherm Linkern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarcastic columnist.  It's obvious, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bowling Green Massacre is so fetch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://static.panoramio.com/photos/large/52916254.jpg) is a photo from the same location, clearly showing that the photo is plausibly real. To convince yourself, compare the wall on the right. It's the same wall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The president gave Australian Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull (who is a total failure!) a good chewing out this week, telling him a refugee agreement between the two countries was the worst deal ever, calling their conversation the worst call and hanging up 25 minutes into what was supposed to be an hour-long talk. It was clear from accounts of the talk that Trump thinks Turnbull is almost as much of a basket case as the Mexican guy Trump yelled at the week before.

"Mexican guy Trump yelled at the week before." 

Top kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, not a massacre at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, not a massacre at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cairo encroaching on the pyramids of Giza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cairo encroaching on the pyramids of Giza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a student at BGSU when the Bowling Green Massacre didn't happen. I'll never be able to not forget what I didn't see that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't make me feel safer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities: Man Facing Child Porn Charges Found Dead - Alabama News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who had beer and condoms in his car found leaving local high school with four girls. He was subsequently charged with child porn. Now, he has been found dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.alabamanews.net/2017/02/02/authorities-man-facing-child-porn-charges-found-dead/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a student at BGSU when the Bowling Green Massacre didn't happen. I'll never be able to not forget what I didn't see that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a student at BGSU when the Bowling Green Massacre didn't happen. I'll never be able to not forget what I didn't see that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a student at BGSU when the Bowling Green Massacre didn't happen. I'll never be able to not forget what I didn't see that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drums of war... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you also passionately vocal in your opposition to violence perpetrated by conservatives against liberals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will the mentally ill protect themselves if they aren't allowed to buy guns?!  If we don't allow the mentally ill to buy guns only mentally ill criminals will have guns!!  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Reddit, I hope you have enjoyed your first 27 minutes!  /r/politics is a great place with great people, hopefully you can use this sub to educate yourself as it appears you don't know what the fuck you are talking about.

Let me explain something, in the United States of America we have a founding document called the Constitution.  The foundation of our government and it's laws lay in this document.  Sharia law, for the most part, is unconstitutional.  Please educate yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a bunch of *conservative* lone wolves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Progressives Are Appalled

What a shit headline.  Progressives aren't appalled at this particular decision, progressives are appalled that Barack Obama's supreme court nominee wasn't given a full hearing per the Constitution of the United States.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This administration is committed to stopping all terrorist attacks, even those that haven't even been planned.  President Trump has done more to stop terrorism than any president in history, period.  Mrs. Conway isn't lying, she is just providing the American people with the whole truth."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they fight their supporters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservatives burned Obama in effigy, had armed standoffs with federal agents, shot up a Planned Parenthood location killing three, murdered African Americans while they worshipped in a church, murdered Sikhs because apparently they can't tell the difference between Sikhs and Muslims, ect.  

But please, tell us how Conservatives "protested peacefully".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right, because conservatives never protested during the Obama administration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is happening right now, no need to "expect" it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't appropriate, but it is funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirt bike accident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://spotcrime.com/al/montgomery

Looks like a lot of crime is happening in west Montgomery, and not just along the two streets that you mentioned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain how Trump is responsible for job growth that occurred when Obama was president?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://climate.nasa.gov/scientific-consensus/

I'll just leave this hear as a response to the bullshit you posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White guys aren't "terrorists", silly liberal, they are "mentally ill".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why conservatives are more likely than liberals to believe false information about threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skull found a girl wearing a ceramic flower wreath, from 300-400 BC Greece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skull found a girl wearing a ceramic flower wreath, from 300-400 BC Greece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pyramids as seen from a Cairo street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pyramids as seen from a Cairo street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pyramids as seen from a Cairo street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter ruthlessly mocks Kellyanne Conway's 'Bowling Green Massacre' that never was </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kellyanne Conway whines and complains that Democrats are acting like babies.

Oh, the irony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Reddit!  I see that it is your very first day.  If you have any questions please ask, /r/politics is a very helpful community!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Declares a Vision of Religious Nationalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Trump Trying to Tweet Us Into a War with Iran? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about political activity by mosques? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
