<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4592</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Power Plants Survived WWII Bombs But Maybe Not Merkel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but Dragon is not human rated yet. But theoretically, in an emergency,  the crew could pile in Dragon instead of samples. 

It would be a bumpy ride without proper seats, some would probably get hurt, but they would survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loathe Trump, he is hurting USA and the world, he is an asshole and the last person that should go into politics.
Although lot of it might be the Alzheimer (look it up it's in his family).

But in this case he is right. Just like the proverbial clock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much clay... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jara Cimrman:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YXuWSH-U_-o

Some of it is lost in the translation, the premise is that there was Czech (Austro-Hungarian) genius forgotten by history and these guys are rediscovering his theatrical work. 

They even made a mockumentary about him in the  80s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czech foreign minister: free movement could break up the EU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I saw them take Anatolia. Way back in 2.0 or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drr Drr Drr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the fund where bulk of money comes from oil sales? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great move by EPA and not just on humanitarian level.

Politically speaking this is the best thing they could have done right now. Their budget is in danger of getting slashed and they have idiot in charge. But intervening in such a high profile case of misconduct reminds politicians of how they are useful.

Not to mention that fact that being associated with stories like these is a really good publicity, something all politicians crave.

Let's hope it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call your congressmen, vote in EVERY ELECTIONS, build support in your state, the budget didn't pass yet and lot of it is incredibly unpopular in Congress. Same goes for Trumpcare.

You live in a democracy, act like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's just like flint then. Corrupt politicians ignoring the needs of people while enriching themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pero seor, me llamo Slowpoke Rodriguez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My. Face. Is. Tired.^Please^kill^me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can I always do this kind of thing for my fortresses. 

Network of canals connected to stream or river, some underground cisterns and boom, you got defense, power and irrigation solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer games firm Bioware accused of deliberately making female characters 'ugly' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of ignorance about Hungarian history in this thread is staggering. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's about what kind of people respond on different stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a sovereign country in EU the Scottish government would have much more power than as devolved government in, what is essentially, unitary state.

Not to mention the fact that Scotland would be recipient of EU subsidies, I can speak from experience that these are frequently abused by local politicians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nationalism for you, only thing that matters is that they are "free to choose their own path" and "not forced to follow Brussels/Westminster".

The logic does not matter to these people, only feelings and, in case of their leaders, lust for power. Because guess who would have guaranteed government in Scotland for next decade or so if they seceded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Master had the right idea about politics.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
I'm gonna look for some FEV and demo fallout shelters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what happens when the Helium inevitably seeps out?
Will it still work, will the speed drop, temperature rise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was on salts it would be much more inventive.

What we ended up with looks more like shitton of weed.

"Wow, we have soooooooooo many colors, I never, never thought about how many colors we have in those.. mm.. games. Yeah. Joker and EDI they're like a.. ah.. synthesis you know. Like between synthetics and organics. Yo, that gives me a kick ass idea. But first some snacks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least the game is made that way on purpose and not just because of incompetence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fuck? Well some stuff seems to make sense now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a stuff of nightmares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS IS A LINE IN AN ACTUAL GAME.

If you thought 2016 was bad 2017 just started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she help him? Cause that might explain some stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he does not identify as Krogan? Did you think about that?

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is also their last full release.

Seriously how hard you must try to mess up facial and walking animations 10 YEARS after first Mass Effect did it right?

Don't tell me they didn't notice that shit in the testing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could they fuck it up so bad? How, I mean original Mass Effect looked better than this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but it does not take much to turn one into the other.

Remember, most Germans didn't want to kill all Jews, they just had leaders that did, and they didn't know/care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In fealty to the God-Emperor (our undying Lord) and by the grace of the Golden Throne, I declare Exterminatus upon the Imperial world of Typhon Primaris.
I hereby sign the death warrant of an entire world and consign a million souls to oblivion.
May Imperial Justice account in all balance.
The Emperor Protects." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prepare for unforeseen consequences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France: Arrest after shooting at Grasse school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad fact is that entire Europe was incredibly antisemitic back then.

And it still kind of is today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for Poland, but in Czechoslovakia almost entire German population was deported.

Thousands were tortured, raped and killed. 
To put it in perspective. My grandfather spent much of the war in Gestapo prison, almost died, voted for communist party and had several Jewish friends. And even HE was distressed at what was happening to Germans after the war.

Every Czech child learns about it today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Proposes Historic Cuts Across Government to Fund Defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military wins in first Trump budget; environment, aid lose big </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be quite a train wreck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also known as EA Effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said much, not all of it. Mostly the anti-immigration sentiment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That controversy actually killed his campaign. 
The current prime minister essentially adopted much of his rhetoric and acted tough, couple that with good old rally to the flag effect and fact that all parties said that they will not form government with him, and Wilders' chances dropped pretty quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that the biggest problem with feudalism, by far, is that it never was some kind of unified system.

For example, in early to high medieval Bohemia it was essentially ad hoc setup where original tribal chiefs adopted titles used among their neighbors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal judge blocks new Trump travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumps only good pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope there even is an infrastructure bill. America really needs something good right now.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made myself a submod giving a nerf to Haidas. Otherwise it's goodbye northwest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, when I compared them to Magneto it... was not well received. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Reveals Donald Trump's 2005 Tax Info Ahead of Rachel Maddow Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them do, it is actually one of the reasons so many people leave. 

The burden all Catholics bear is that Church as an institution did so much wrong in the history and still does now, for many it's too much and leave. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, Lutherans are in partial communion with the church after all.

The shit really went down when it became a political matter, but I guess you can say that about pretty much all theological disputes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my experience on the internet is anything to go by then almost every dedicated community on popular platforms attracts weird people.

Political, religious, social, gaming, oh that one time I found radical ASPIE SUPREMACIST in a forum for people with aspergers.

I'm not kidding, those guys seriously believed that they were superior and that they should make their own society.

So, yeah your experience is pretty much the norm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is there any chance of them hitting say... small house somewhere between Virginia and Maryland?

Or maybe some drug smuggling operation disguised as a resort in Florida? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt he remembers that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say this, but travel ban on Iran might be a proper gesture.

We all know it's not going to change their policies or make america more secure, but I have a feeling that country doing this kind of shit, SHOULD be isolated.

Now I'm not saying I like TD, in fact I think he is crazy and if half of his policies get implemented the america will suffer for decades. 

But this kind of shit makes his travel ban seem like a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did what you wanted. They overturned it by a pretty nice majority. 15-11
SO STOP SHITTING ON THEM PLEASE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did what you wanted. They overturned it by a pretty nice majority. 15-11

SO STOP SHITTING ON THEM PLEASE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work Arkansas senators.

Remember people, if you like what your representatives do, support them in next election or contribute to their campaign funds.

Otherwise whats the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I don't think this is some kind of massive fraud.

Not even Republicans have that much power in swing states and don't forget who was president at the time, I didn't see eye to eye with Obama on many security issues but I doubt, really doubt that he would let the biggest electoral fraud in history of United states happen on his watch.

So while it is depressing I think that the truth is much more terrifying. People didn't give a shit.

And by the way, almost every democracy has that problem today.
America just gets hit the hardest because of First-past-the-post system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBO report: 24 million fewer insured by 2026 under GOP health care bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK YOU INDEPENDENT! A GUY GETS RAPED AND YOU USE HIM AS A CHEAP FAKE NEWS CLICKBAIT?

I am pretty tolerant guy and I don't like Trump either but this is morally wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do it all the time in Czech Republic, it's effective if uncommon procedure.

We used to offer normal castration too but, I think we have discontinued that in the nineties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans are politicians, that means they say whatever they believe will keep them in office.

Their base demands from them to act "tough" on "leeches" and part of that is pretending that Social and Medicare are abused by millions of welfare queens.

They know it's bullshit, well most of them do, you don't finish Ivy league school unless you are very intelligent. 
But their voters don't know that and demand that something should be done about it.

And so Republicans throw shit at those programs while pocketing bribes and passing laws enriching them and their friends.
And both sides are happy.

You are not happy and most Americans are not happy, but they have consented to that by not showing at the elections.

It is really astonishing, for centuries people fought and died for their right to elect their own leaders, and now that they can they don't want to do it.

Of course you can say that it's because of gerrymandering, but that is more of a symptom than the cause.
The Republicans could never pass the needed legislation if they didn't have votes for it. 

What is even more amazing are the election demographics, you would think that poor people, minorities and young people will show  up the most. After all they are the most vulnerable and dependent on their country.

Wrong, young, poor and minorities vote least of all. 

You would expect people to be energized by last years elections, but instead the USA had lowest turnout in 20 years.
At this point the blame rests not just on the politicians but also on the electorate.

TLDR: Democracy doesn't and cannot work when people don't participate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how contracts work people. 

If you had kind of negotiating position she had you too would get nice packages, not millions but nice.

Unfortunately, the unions in USA tend to either turn into corrupt semi-mobs, or they don't exist in the first place.

You could vote in politicians that would change the workforce laws but then you would have show up during elections.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These subsidies:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Budget_of_the_European_Union#EU-28_contributions_.282014.29

Although they might not be called that way they effectively are.
The biggest among them is CAP but there are others mostly those involved with infrastructure grants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swedish military is laughably incapable as proven by its own reports. 

https://www.svd.se/forsvar-med-tidsgrans

Also conscription ended in 2010 and was reinstated this year exactly because how pathetic the Swedish army became without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I meant, regions as Government Office Regions, those include for example entire Midlands, North West, South east etc.

As detailed here https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Regions_of_England

The question you should ask yourself is who funds these divisions and how many would a Scotland be able to afford.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of 40k Arco-flagellants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure:

https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2017-02-23/u-k-faces-60-billion-euro-brexit-bill-austrian-chancellor-says

https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-03-04/u-k-has-no-obligation-to-pay-eu-in-no-deal-brexit-lords-say

https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2017-03-09/german-brexit-memo-stresses-eu-unity-will-be-paramount-in-talks

From last week or so.

But you must understand that Finland, Czech Republic for that matter, have almost zero say in these things.

It will come down to net contributors to EU budget, which are just Germany, France, Spain and Italy, they have leverage to pass pretty much any law they want in EU parliament and to make our governments sign almost any treaty.

Those subsidies are just too much of a treat to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't she a lesbian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they would be country of five million people, there are regions in England that have more than that, with left-leaning government made up of basically just one party, so I suspect they will treat their military like Belgium or Sweden.

Neglect it and hope that they will never need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well situation changed and emotions run high, which is good for the nationalists because that's pretty much all they have, emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rhetoric from EU is very negative in that regard.

Basically they want to punish the UK for the Brexit and make it sort of example to the others.

The more UK suffers the less likely it is that others will try to break off in the future. even better if it breaks apart.

Sad, but that's the way EU politicians play the game.
Not that I don't understand it, from a political point of view, it's not nice but it definitely is a effective approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you got really angry and insulting there, not just towards UK but Poland too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey my great grandfather was stationed there in WWI! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't get this. 

I mean why don't you just vote for politicians running pro-infrastructure platform? What's hard about that?

If America was unitary state I would understand this kind of problem, but you are federation for crying out loud, your states have enormous power, especially when it comes to your infrastructure, not to mention your cities.

LA, NY, and other cities are filled with educated Democratic voters so why the hell can't they press their representatives to do something about it. 
Cities even collect their own property taxes, that's like the easiest type of tax to collect, almost unavoidable.

Can someone explain to me what a hell is going on over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When everything is offensive, nothing is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politicians are mentioned often, but how often we actually talk about their policies, what party we vote for etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I do not think so. Only thing that would accomplish is driving them into arms of the Russia.

And lets be honest that's like the last thing we should want at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we got political rallies with flags and signs now? 

I though people made fun of Americans for doing these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me Czechs don't give a shit about religion.
Sure there are plenty of jokes about promiscuous priests and greedy Jews, but most of the time the topic of religion is just like topic of politics, rarely mentioned.

Unless you act like an asshole, we don't like fundamentalists around here, no matter the creed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty much the way it always was. 
Most of the time people never really cared about faith, hence many ignored Papal edicts and calls for crusades and what not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Imperial Authority is high again, Kaiserin will soon convene the estates and enact Gemeiner Pfennig!

But those imperial lands in Britain are probably going to fall into hands of non-member very soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then there is your answer, help him build it and learn from it.
And later you might get him to make you some parts for you machine on it.

DIY community pretty much runs on these kind of deals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my experience it mostly depends on how much time do you have, if you are willing to make compromises on quality and of course your skill.

You can scavenge lots of stuff like stepper motors from old printers, sometimes you can even use their axis but they rarely have the required qualities.

What you can't do without is microcontroller, Arduino is the obvious option, it has lot of open sourced projects you can use for code and circuitry. Not to mention shields tailor made for similar purposes.

You can have someone with 3D printer make you the gears and smaller parts, so you can save a lot on that.

The larger parts of the assembly you can make yourself, if you have schematics and small workshop its not that hard.

Of course all of this, while cheap, will cost you a lot of time, especially if you never did it before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well comenter asked who is worse than Netanyahu. I gave him a list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This DLC is just retarded, sorry I had to say this.
Along with the upcoming changes in EU4 it seems to me that Paradox is losing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of my head:

Kim Jong Un

Rodrigo Duterte

Maduro

Bashar Assad

Ayatollah Khomeiny

King Salman of Saudi Arabia

Robert Mugabe

Vladimir Putin

Xi Jingpin



There might be more but I would have to look them up, or widen the criteria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More or less, but most of the time it's done tastefully. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job Australia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this distinct feeling that Trump might no longer be in charge.

Or that he might no longer be sane.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I know lot of Republicans/Trumpists actually are upset and ashamed. The problem is that these are not nearly as visible as those that still support him.

His approval rates keep falling, liberals didn't like him from start so only logical explanation is that his own base is deserting him.
As for GOP itself, they are scared as fuck.

Don't get me wrong, GOP fuck people over all the time but they at least try to look good doing it. Trump makes that strategy impossible, he is so visibly criminal that it makes entire GOP look like crooks, even in the eyes of their voters.
To make things worse if he is not subdued by 2018 elections people could go and actually vote for Democrats.

In lots of districts Republicans only win because majority of the population DOESN'T SHOW UP, if these people get pissed/scared you can bet your ass it won't help some House members get reelected.

Technically speaking Trump is much worse for conservatives/GOP than for liberals/Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outsourced graphics department. 
/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was widely considered to be NAFTA on steroids.

Basically the prices would drop but lots of stuff could get more easily outsourced.
Plus there were some legal issues that I won't pretend to understand and that I personally believe were blown out of proportion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy was mentally ill, there are plenty of examples of actual radicals among migrants, we don't have to fabricate new ones.

And in fact we should not, it's not only dishonest and dangerous, it devalues our position. 

The same goes in general. There are probably plenty examples supporting your position, do not undermine yourself and your opinions by fabricating stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Multispeed Europe Will Be Hard to Pull Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give some to Trump, QUICK!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it is technically a social program of sorts. It's meant to get as many young men of the streets and give them some skills, experience and sense of order, plus it drags down jobless numbers.

It's not the most effective way of doing it but it sort of works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good step, it doesn't make him conflict of interest free but it is a step in right direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure american government pulled some dick moves in past, but so did everyone else. 
Sure you got total asshole for president now, but other countries had them too and much worse, including the wealthiest European countries. Plus he will be gone in a few years.

My point is, USA is our friend and we don't abandon friends just because they made some bad choices, sure we call them out, but acting like they are worst piece of shit the world has to offer and pretending that Trump is some kind of hellspawn of Hitler and Stalin is just stupid.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will edit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's why pretty much everyone went, and stayed, in the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defense? Opposition to Russia? Hmm, I think that's it.

Not that we are much better.

Edit: And money, but that's true for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a nationalist, that by itself makes him inclined to be irrational.
You can't win argument with these people, they just repeat themselves like broken record and have no self reflection at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negligible compared to many regions in UK and many EU countries, being resource rich is nice but wait until you have to explain to locals why their land must turn into mine.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it isn't nationalism than call for referendum in entire north, and don't call new country Scotland but Union of North Britain, and maybe everyone should get to vote in entire UK, or even better, let counties have their own referendums if they want to leave or stay, after all this is not about nationality at all.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but they were not the main points, just like with brexit it came down to emotional arguments.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it? Maybe negligible population, superior ports just stone throw away, economic inertia from previous centuries when Scotland was really poor and undeveloped because of climate, global economic downturn in rural areas or maybe local government with wide rights and capabilities that somehow still manages to blame rest of the country.

Maybe those are the reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the oil is not the cash cow it used to be thats for sure. 

But as I said before, this is and was about feelings not the facts.

Because if it was they would talk about trade balance, industry supply chains and currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think nationalism has anything to do with reason.

I think that, just like all political issues, it is more dependent on feelings.

Right now lot of Scottish are pissed at "Westminster" and feel like they were lied to. So they want to retaliate. 

Just like Englishmen were pissed at "Brussels bureaucrats"  and felt like they were lied to. So they retaliated.

Even the arguments are the same, they just replaced few terms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is stupid but yeah, that's nationalism for you.

Essentially as big a fuck up a brexit was the independence would be much worse, especially with current oil prices and the fact that Scotlands economy is incredibly tied to UKs. 

One way or the other, we are going to get downvoted for this.
Hating UK is so cool these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is simplistic I know that. I don't have time or energy to discuss this at length so I resort to short summaries. 

My point is, that today it's sometimes presented like clear cut kind of conflict, fascist vs. democrats, when in fact it was much more complicated and looked more like Syria today then American revolution in 1700s.

Anyway, time and time again, when these types of conflicts erupt, the most ruthless and radical factions tend to win.
For example: Russian revolution, Syrian civil war, French revolution, Chinese civil war, if we are really liberal with definitions than Germany in 20s/30s, Iranian revolution, Cambodia, the list goes on and on.

Sure in the end the things stabilized but only after often decades of terrible oppression and immeasurable slaughter. 
So, my personal opinion as a person with next to none academic history education, is that in the end victory of moderate republicans was very, very unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about ol' Martel or Pepin the hunchback? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you wonder why there is a growing resentment in the east? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a subsidy elimination, fucking clickbait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, the civil war was essentially fight between two evils, we will never know what eventual outcome of republican victory would look like. 
But judging by their actions and tendencies it wouldn't be much better, and it could be possibly much worse.

Imagine Iberian Yugoslavia... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, I can still see the iron curtain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spain was kind of a black swan, and that's mostly thanks to fact that Franco, while a ruthless dictator, didn't go mad with power and remained, more or less, reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Nine Charts Show How France Is Pessimistic and Optimistic at the Same Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job LA, and I hope others will follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
