<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met it not long ago, and felt like "damn well, mate, I agree with you". Most problems they show up there I've seen happening on a personal level with male acquaitances, and heh, I like to be against problems on both sides anyway, so it was easy to feel at ease there to me.

Either way, I wouldn't compare them to MGTOWs; they're closer to "feminist men" (a good bunch sees women's problems, too, and wants to change that as well) than to MRA. In a way, they're against anyone who tries to carry on toxicity, be it men or women. 

And well, I'm subscribed to their sub :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the r/MensLib sub, seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you guys got r/incel banned

I didn't know I had telepathic capabilities that took care of stuff I 100% didn't give a shit about and sent it to mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bepis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> women dating men from other races

These guys would be screeching at the background of my mother's family :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *It's the freakiest shooooooow* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL no. It's that one with a slightly longer than usual chin and odd angles on the sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a way, you did seem to lead her on a bit by what I read here (or you two have a kind of "colourful friendship" and I didn't get at first; maybe that could have made her try to go on if that's the case?) by letting certain stuff happen. No, 'm not talking about the kiss, but more of something else you mentioned here :^D 

But anyway, if you don't really feel like you *love* her, I think you'd better be honest with her and not "lead her on" on her attraction. It seems like you felt like it'd be a dick move and all, but really, letting her believe something that *probably* won't happen (now, at least), considering the overall of what you said, is worse. Tell her the truth.

EDIT: oh, and if needed, do take some time to yourself to think more deeply about the situation. That'd probably also give her some time, too. Feels like you're both not feeling *that* well over the situation for different reasons, so, do take some time before saying anything to not end up on an unnecessary argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at their "prime ages/riding the CC phase".

Still virgin. Hell, even my zodiac calls me that.

EDIT: oh, and my two bosses chit chat "like girls" a lot. They know the life of at least half the population of this town, ffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jewish looking nose

Hey there, fellow Jew-nosed. Add a slightly slav jaw and you have the incredibly awkward-looking me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I do feel bad that they're isolated. It doesn't last very long, though, because it gets clear that they isolated themselves of everyone else on purpose and, instead of admitting their actions, just go full "REEEEEEEEeEEeeeeeEEEEeeeEeeE" over those who approach trying to help.

So, yeah, I honestly *want* them to notice that it's not other people's fault and get back to a normal life, but at the same time I keep my distance :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE OP IS A RED SPOI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you want a parade?

ACTUALLY, I WANT TWO. 

WITH DRAG QUEENS.

AND IF YOU WANT TO CALL THE GACHIMEME GUYS, I'M ALSO UP FER IT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading it as Robbie Rotten makes it 3 times cooler, actually :^D

On the other hand, poor Robbie Rotten; such an alpha lazy man being compared to this beta chunk of carbon-based life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods.

*Do it*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brazilians

PFFT, if they think people over here accept these "BP Norms" they're waaaaaay out of their minds. "#Bolsonaro2018" tag popularity in a non-sarcastic way expresses my point really well here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I've seen a male dealing with that on a personal level, and it was my brother. Honestly, some can be twice as evil as rough dudes with words, and it's saddening :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit oh shit oh shit-

Man

This post

It's on my saved post list, thank you a lot for the kek :^DDDDDDD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, sorry.

Tl; dr: the news probably won't show anything about this guy *here* because they don't care about this here. The maximum they do about USA's news is Trump.

And yeah, news media avoid using words like "mysoginy" in fear of being bashed to nonexistence "accused" of feminism. It's awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like 3/7 of the male fellas I see coming at the place I work at to ask about wtf happened to his computer and if it's a virus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sidenote: I didn't think this post would get so many updoots, holy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny and tragic at the same time :'^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> leaner chad with glasses

How about no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heeeeeey, don't you dare compare Terpers to Tolstoy, he was a crazed Russian man but not this level of crazy :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be if everyone here wasn't already aware of the situation, son. We ain't a tabloid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even ShitRedditSays Is Tired of TRP. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I'm an aberration on the eyes of God.

r/SCP, you can take me nao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

That would be... *your mother.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOI 'ROUND HIER' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You summed up a good part of my complaint here. Seems like they lack a sense of humour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
