<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4485</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw an autoplaying movie trailer at the top, followed by this headline:

Queensland Premier Annastacia Palaszczuk urges Federal Govt tax rebate boost for Gold Coast films

i then left the site, to downvote op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only good thing we've ever gotten from this is when the bull wins

and of course - the names Lamborghini uses for their cars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bears eat a lot of blueberries before they hibernate. this stores fat. (from one of david attenboroughs films)

Fat is then used as fuel while its not eating anything.

That you lose muscle while fasting is a myth you gotta forget all about. it's simply not true.

The same principle is true in humans. 

There is a process called gluconeogenesis but it only lasts for a couple of days, and we're only talking a few grams. after that, the body starts breaking down fat for energy, and fuels your brain with ketones instead (which are made from fat)

Jason fung explains it here, pretty well - in under 2 minutes:

https://youtu.be/nwE4D8Xe8JA?t=2m17s

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a christmas holiday.. not "daily life" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, in Dark Souls, which has singleplayer MIXED with multiplayer, you cant really communicate with those ... motherfuckers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the day off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try this

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p8qeLXjiVms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rotate the damn fan on your cpu cooler... amd logo is on the right side :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could be unannounced products, partnerships or .. i dont know. maybe they buy samsung? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time for another Paul Blart movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changed mage armor icon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smell a doom mod for skyrim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While i love both rockets and lego

This would be extremely boring to build </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sleeping is extremely healthy.

Good initiative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. i've gone from sugary cola to no sugary energy drinks

there are no soda with the same taste..

and its more expensive per liter, so i assume the earnings are much higher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fasting.

/r/fasting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.. It's NOT as simple as that.

Your body will lower it's energy requirements, if you eat fewer calories over a period of time.

so you'll eventually stop losing weight

some explanation and source links here

http://healthyenough.net/calorie-counting/ there are more... more but i cba


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> combined with the /r/keto foods you should be golden. it can be hard though, avoiding certain types of food.

I've lost 30 pounds in 3 months, from eating keto food. no fasting. i imagine combining it would go even faster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/fasting - plenty of helpful info and sources here.

most people dont recommend fasting for more than a month at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll add, jason fung also have a youtube channel with a few of his presentations on there (usually 20-60 minutes long) he doesnt upload frequently at all, but worth a look.

I've heard a few of the videos as mp3, while driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're fixing electrolyte shortage, by getting some salt. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just google black poop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iirc Thunderf00t on youtube made a video about this not too long ago. also debunking some plastic panel-type road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that bitumen can be reused after you "de-pave" a road... and make fresh asphalt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plastic?

how well does it actually work?

Coz the roads are have today are pretty sturdy.

Also, plastic is kinda shit in comparison?

regular plastic breaks very easily when scratched.. how is it gonna handle a 20 ton truck at 55 mph?

and its not like roads are bad in terms of environmental damage.. its just some rocks are that tar like substance you mix.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww hvor er det synd for dig...

du kunne jo s enten finde et andet sted at arbejde, eller... tage dit trklde af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i never do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this makes me hate every single give-away on the internet...

99% of everything is either shit or US only </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've run Super Mario 3D world in 4K (On my 1440p monitor) runs smooth as butter, but looks better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can just imagine them standing in a room saying something like:

"Ok... let's bomb this group of random civilian potential tax payers, that'll show them living here!"

:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, apple dodges more taxes than Neo dodges bullets..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! then we can argue which politics are the worst, on the rock as well!

i can't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those look like lego-men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i dont think thats gonna work for most companies, with shareholders and such wanting a cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Det har vel mere at sige hvad de fodrer koen med ?

der var da en overskrift en dag her p reddit et sted omkring en type tang, som man kunne fodre ker med, der reducerer deres co2 udledning med 75%~  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i can reach that too..

but i want 60 fps AND high settings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart move by the king!

less work for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant see the whole area, from 1 point, but you can see other areas from other areas. well maybe, from the top of the healing church (the very very top)

I remember seeing byrgenwerth from the forest and of course the castle from the church </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed

but leaving every formerly "rich" country without any jobs... would mean they cant sell their products to anyone anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the scandiavian countries are always the lowest of the bunch

fact is, they are so much alike that it barely makes any difference

many danish people live in sweden and many swedish live in denmark, for example. doesn't really make much of a difference. The main one being... taxes on cars, as far as im aware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what the yellow color in their flag represents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The inside of the lid of the box! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make fun of the austrians, the swiss and so on?

scandiavians secretly love each other and we show it by telling them how terrible they are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my webcam plugged into a powered usb hub (apart from the webcam i only use it as a phone charger and for random USB sticks)

i can simply turn it off when i dont use it... no fiddling with a cover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it makes ok graphics benchmarks iirc? 

but other than that... its a ubisoft game, so obviously you avoid it like the plague... or an EA game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smell a freemium service popping up at some point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and i get about 40-60 fps in 3440x1440p

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or just completely reboot it

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he certainly looks about 3, a lot more than 8.

using a straw is a brilliant idea. 

My 3 year old cant blow on his warm food either.. he just ... sorta drools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Becel?!

booooo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/engineeringporn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to teach a friend from the netherlands how to just pronounce random words we saw (street names and what not) and he failed at everything that included that soft D.

Our "Rd grd med flde" is basically just ... soft D's all over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check top comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What i've done is... i try to fix it together with my kid. if we can, we do it. if not, ill tell him i cant, and that he'll have to either throw it away or fix it himself. he usually gives up on it after a few minutes and accepts it. then he plays with something else

its cheaper and he learns that not everything can be fixed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> send en regning

betaler de ikke, s smid ledelsen i fngsel og overtag firmaet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just what i read, on reddit, around the time the "new" cosmos was released, with Neil Degrasse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, some of the info in this show is now out-dated and thus incorrect.

still entertaining and interesting. and of course, most of the info is still true :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's over 90 years old...

i dont think he's doing too much in his daily life. he said in an interview, that all he does is do interviews. i assume he spends the rest of his time just chilling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
