<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like dividing the battle into 24 beats was too much. At least from the thumbnails it looks like the first two beats are the same thing, as well as numbers 10 and 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of don't agree. We don't even find out the real reason why he wants to keep the land so badly until halfway through the movie, Jeff Bridges' "investigation" was pleasantly understated (basically him deducing where the robbers will strike next and just sitting around waiting for them) and I definitely didn't expect [Chris Pine to actually get away with it. The final scene between Pine and Bridges had a nice questing beast ring to it.](#spoiler)

EDIT: Also the waitress covering for them was a nice touch and all the trigger happy townspeople chasing after them towards the end was oddly hilarious for me as a European with a clear "Don't mess with Texas" picture in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, a city gets destroyed by CG. Haven't seen that before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Braveheart actually won best picture?

Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For example, Deckard all of a sudden has an obsession with these photos that he found at a house that I didn't even realise he went to, and then we get this long scene of him looking at one of the photos and eventually finding an image of a replicant within it, but how did he know to go see her or that she was a replicant?

No offense but it seems like you really weren't paying attention. First of all, he knew how all the escaped replicants looked from the files he was shown by the police boss. The apartment he went to belonged to the replicant Leon Kowalski - he was the one from the opening scene of the movie that shot the other blade runner during the test. Deckard went there to investigate. In the apartment he found the pictures, so he took them as evidence, along with the snake scale in the bathtub. He looked through the photos and noticed a reflection in the mirror, which he enhanced in his computer to reveal one of the replicants with a snake. He realized he could track her down using the snake scale he found, because the snake was genetically created. So he takes the scale to the marketplace where a snake seller tells him the snake belongs to the replicant Zhora. he goes to the night club, has a chat with Zhora, chases her through the street and kills her. Meanwhile, Roy takes JF Sebastian to meet and kill Eldon Tyrrel. Since they used JF Sebastian's identity to get inside the building, Deckard knew to go to JF's house to look for the replicants, where he shoots Pris and fights Roy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was because the logo on the cabin has switched colors compared to the logo on the...uh...I don't know what you call the back part of the truck in English, but that thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but isn't that pretty risky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I made a gif of four shots that lined up](http://imgur.com/a/mSpUD) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was predictable about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was miles ahead of the previous two Wolverine movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I made this into a gif](http://imgur.com/a/PGfnJ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   lazy and trite writing all around

so what else is new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hell or High Water

4 Oscar noms including best picture... how is that "quietly" great? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you define "quietly great"? Captain Fantastic had an Oscar nomination and Silence had good reviews and the added publicity of being directed by Scorsese. I wouldn't call either of those as quiet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for taking the time to respond. 

Obviously I would've preferred STID as an original story, too. I had big expectations of the movie and I remember after seeing I just couldn't believe this is what they came up with after four years between ST and STID.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a few improvements to the three Chris Pine Star Trek movies and I explored some possibilities of what's next for the current Star Trek film franchise (long post, hopefully a good read) - xpost from /r/startrek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize this first part will be nothing more than crying over spilt milk, but let me start with examining the first three movies. I have a few ideas on how to improve them and make them more interesting. Of course, these are all just my opinions, but hopefully you will find them valid.

**Star Trek**

This movie did a lot of things right, but there's still room for improvement. They connected the new movies to the old ones by including Spock Prime and at the same time they set them completely apart by making this an alternate timeline. I think they did this for two reasons. One, they wanted to have Leonard Nimoy in the movie to grant it more legitimacy and please old fans. And two, they wanted to have the ability to tell new stories and change things without negating or retconning what came before. Both were wise decisions, but why not take the concept a bit further and utilize Spock Prime in a more interesting way? In my scenario Spock Prime is more of a character than a presence and we see more things from his perspective. He fails to save Romulus from the supernova but he realizes that the resulting black hole could take him back in time and he would have another shot at saving the planet. Unfortunately, Nero witnesses the destruction of Romulus and oblivious to Spock Prime's plan, he follows him into the black hole seeking revenge and this action causes both Nero and Spock Prime to be thrown out of the black hole at the wrong point in space and time. This creates the new timeline because the Nerada interferes with USS Kelvin. So Spock Prime's action inadvertently creates an alternate reality and kills Kirk's father. Much of the film then plays out similarly or equally to the existing film, showing us the Kirk origin story and putting the crew together, etc. But Spock Prime watches from a distance, fascinated. Then a great source of conflict would be the destruction of Vulcan, which I would change from the way it was done in the movie. The destruction of Vulcan would actually be the finale of the movie instead of happening in the middle and Spock Prime would have to sacrifice the planet in order to defeat Nero, causing great inner conflict both for himself and for the young Spock. Let's say Nero goes to Vulcan to steal a prototype of what would eventually become Spock Prime's black hole machine and he wants to use it to destroy not only Vulcan, but the whole galaxy. He starts creating a massive black hole but before he succeeds, the Enterprise and Spock prime create a smaller black hole that sucks in the Nerada but also destroys Vulcan in the process and kills Spock Prime.

**Star Trek Into Darkness**

Let's say you absolutely have to go darker and you absolutely have to use Khan. Sure. But why not go all the way and be really dark? Why not use Khan in a way we haven't seen yet? General (?) Marcus wanted to prepare the Federation for future wars, so why not show one? In my scenario for this movie, the Federation is at war with the Klingons and it's losing. Like really getting their asses kicked. Pike is not riding a desk but leading the charge into hopeless battle, with Kirk and the Enterprise by his side. Pike's ship is destroyed in front of Kirk's eyes and he feels tremendous sorrow at losing his surrogate father figure, and he feels guilt over not being able to help him, which turns into blind rage. He is determined to have his vengeance and defeat the Klingons. This is Wrath of Kirk more than Wrath of Khan, already turning this remake on its head and doing something different. Kirk studies the Starfleet archives to learn new tactics from older, more savage times and during his studies of the Eugenics wars he learns of the program that created Khan. Appealing to Starfleet and recruiting Marcus to his side he instigates Khan's resurrection, which helps turn the tide and gives Starfleet the upper hand in the war. But for the mad Khan winning battles isn't enough and he starts to kick the Klingons' ass so much that he starts committing atrocities. He goes full Kurtz and Kirk realizes that his revenge is causing the same kind of pain and suffering that he went through and he is no better than the Klingons. Moral dilemmas and introspection galore. In the end Kirk has to go up the proverbial river to stop Khan, sacrificing himself in the process, because the survival of many outweighs the need for revenge of the one. Aaand then they can bring him back with Khan's blood or whatever.

**Star Trek Beyond**

This movie got a lot of things right, owing to Simon Pegg's script. The first twenty or so minutes of the movie are brilliant, setting up inner conflicts, emotional stakes and exploring the toll of isolation in space. However, much of that is later lost and completely obscured by studio-mandated action. In my scenario, Enterprise's destruction still happens, but it's much more emotionally impactful because it hasn't already happened twice in the two previous movies, so instead of going "not this again" the audience goes "oh my god the Enterprise is down" which is obviously much better. And if you absolutely need to have an evil villain in a Star Trek movie, make him more compelling. Dispense with action in favor of characters. Trek is absolutely the kind of franchise where the villain should talk to the hero and explain his entire motivation and plan. You know, what the Bond movies have been doing for decades. At the beginning of the movie Kirk is weary of space exploration, so have him confront the results of exploration gone wrong. What happened to Krall could easily have happened to Kirk, too. Don't give Kirk a motorcycle, give him inner conflict and demons to confront. And have Spock help him find the right path, solidifying their friendship and showing Spock that Kirk really needs him more than the Vulcans, so he can't leave Starfleet and Kirk's side.


So what is next in store for the crew of Starship Enterprise? I have a couple of ideas for future movies that would solve some of the problems of the existing three installments.


**Alternates**

The franchise already exists in an alternate timeline, so let's play with that a bit. Mirror universes, alternate realities and various timelines are staples of Trek. These sort of things work best when you already have your characters established, making it more interesting and entertaining to meet their counterparts and see them behave differently. It's also a good way to learn something new about the existing characters when they meet their counterparts. After three movies the new Trek crew are established well enough to warrant taking this route. Have a bit of fun with it but also explore the characters in depth at the same time. For example, one scenario could explore a world where Kirk never joined Starfleet. After he ran away from home he led a pointless existence, eventually going to space on a freighter and working a blue collar job. Not bound by duty to Starfleet or any five year missions, he also had the opportunity to create a family. Now what if that Kirk switched places with the Starfleet captain we know and love? Freighter Kirk would miss his family, but he would discover what it means to be captain and having the crew as family, learning something about duty and friendship along the way and confronting his past. Meanwhile, Starfleet Kirk would discover what it is like to have an actual family and what life without the Enterprise could be like, questioning his career. Throw in some conflict (for example, the Kirk switcheroo may have been deliberately caused by an antagonist) and you have yourself a movie.


**Make the Enterprise great again**

The Enterprise is supposed to be a flagship. Top of the line. A formidable opponent and an imposing presence if need be, but also a vessel of pure research and exploration. So far in the three new movies we've seen almost none of that. The ship repeatedly gets its ass kicked and performs no science whatsoever. But in the original series the ship is like a submarine in space (this idea largely reflected in the stealthy and subtle combat scenes as well as the use of torpedoes) and this is something I miss in the new franchise. It's also on a mission to explore strange new worlds and seek out new life and new civilizations, but science was notably absent in the new movies. What has Spock done in his capacity as Chief Science Officer? Have they ever really fired a probe or scanned a class M planet? Has the ship ever had the upper hand in a standoff or posed a threat to anyone? Since they once again destroyed it in Beyond, now is the perfect opportunity to design a new Enterprise and have it do new things (and by new I mean have it do the really old things it was always meant to do). 


**Star Trek doesn't need a villain**

The universe is vast and poses threats beyond some generic bad guys out for revenge or world domination. While the franchise has a nice roster of villains and antagonistic alien races, it's not all about those types of conflict. The ship is on its way to literally a place where no one else has gone before ...so why should it encounter familiar things? Give me a crystalline entity, a planet eating ship, an exiled Greek god or a long extinct civilization that's still holding secrets. Give me a large animal living in space like a deep sea creature, or a space-time anomaly, or a mysterious cosmic event. Give me anything besides a traditional villain. The Enterprise can fight all sorts of foes and stand up to all sorts of dangers. And why should it always encounter an opposing force or a threat to begin with? What if you had a movie like Contact set in the Star Trek universe? The Enterprise is somewhere far away, charting new territory, when it receives a signal. The crew have to work together to decipher it, the captain is faced with a difficult decision whether to pursue the signal into the dangerous far reaches of space or not, and overcoming some problems and dilemmas along the way they finaly get to a new destination where they learn something new. And what about a scenario like Arrival? Why do we need a standalone movie from a director largely known for thrillers to show us a perfect first contact story while a franchise that should be all about stuff like that is pretending to be an action movie? What happened to mystery, intrigue and discovery?


**Star Trek doesn't need Kirk and Spock**

I realize there's a new show coming up, but I'm going to make this point anyway. Star Trek doesn't need familiar things to succeed. It's vast and filled with great characters just waiting to be discovered. TOS, TNG, DS9, Voyager and Enterprise created a shared universe decades before anyone even dreamed of the Marvel Cinematic Universe, and yet we're pretending as if the MCU is some unbelievable new thing. Trek already had what the MCU spent many films establishing. But instead of utilizing that fact, the producers decided to just bring back a new flashier version of nostalgic characters. I understand why they did it, there is no need to explain box office appeal or the logic behind reboots. But after three movies that were wholly average and underwhelming at the box office, maybe it's time to experiment and create something new. I don't expect them to make a long overdue DS9 movie or to bring back the TNG crew. I don't *want* them to. But they could start fresh. Maybe make a Generations style crossover movie with an appearance from the Kirk crew, but make something new. Show us a different part of Starfleet. Or take the Rogue One route and depict a well-known event from Trek lore that we never really got to see.


**Star Trek doesn't need a big budget**

If you're going to make a big budget movie, you need it to make all that money back, and then some. To make sure that happens, you need to make that movie appealing to a broad audience. That's how you get Star Trek Beyond the action movie instead of Star Trek Beyond the character driven space drama. What you end up with is an action movie that's too generic to please the general public hooked on Marvel and Star Wars, and also a movie that's not going to appeal to your core fan base. In other words, you have a mess that cost too much and made too little. But Star Trek was never about big budgets, it was about big stories. Week after week the creators managed to churn out great episodes on TV budgets with insufficient special effects. That creates restraint and science fiction has always benefited from restraint. Filmmakers like George Lucas and James Cameron have talked about having big ideas that weren't possible to film because the technology hadn't caught up with their visions. But when you look at their output created under restraint (Star Wars, The Terminator) and compare it with their technologically advanced output (Attack of the Clones, Avatar) it's clear that restraint breeds better results. Jaws was so effective because it revealed the shark gradually. It didn't blow its load with a money shot right at the beginning but kept the shark shrouded in mystery and menace. It was incredibly effective and it was due to restraint. The rubber shark puppet was unrealistic and often malfunctioning, so it had to be used with restraint. And the result is movie history. When you watch TOS episodes, most of the show has sets that are nothing but a blank wall bathed in colorful lights. Does that take away anything from the story, though? I am all for beautiful visuals and great effects, but the need for them does not outweigh the need for a good script. I would much rather sacrifice the former in favor of the latter. As it stands, the three new Trek movies are very much like the hated prequel trilogy of Star Wars. Lots of style, not enough substance. Give me a low budget Trek movie that doesn't have to make huge money to break even. Give me a story that doesn't have to be appealing to a general audience. Arrival's budget was $47 million yet it managed to have cool spaceships, cool aliens, great actors, and a great story. Star Trek Beyond had a budget of $185 million, which is ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me just point out that I never said I want a DS9 or TNG movie, or to reboot those two properties. In fact I specifically said I don't want that.

Relevant:
 I don't expect them to make a long overdue DS9 movie or to bring back the TNG crew. I don't want them to.

Also, as far as that success of the new films go, not one of them made any big money and Into Darkness is considered by fans to be the worst Trek movie ever, so I wouldn't really call that successful. As far as the marketability of a new crew goes, that is why I also proposed lower budgets for these movies. Lower budget means it has to make less money back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because your body knows it's going to happen soon since you're already there so it doesn't have to make such an effort to hold it in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civil War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear about your friend. But to clarify, was he part of your trip or did he pass away back home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a few improvements to the three Chris Pine Star Trek movies and I explored some possibilities of what's next for the current Star Trek film franchise (long post, hopefully a good read) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize this first part will be nothing more than crying over spilt milk, but let me start with examining the first three movies. I have a few ideas on how to improve them and make them more interesting. Of course, these are all just my opinions, but hopefully you will find them valid.

**Star Trek**

This movie did a lot of things right, but there's still room for improvement. They connected the new movies to the old ones by including Spock Prime and at the same time they set them completely apart by making this an alternate timeline. I think they did this for two reasons. One, they wanted to have Leonard Nimoy in the movie to grant it more legitimacy and please old fans. And two, they wanted to have the ability to tell new stories and change things without negating or retconning what came before. Both were wise decisions, but why not take the concept a bit further and utilize Spock Prime in a more interesting way? In my scenario Spock Prime is more of a character than a presence and we see more things from his perspective. He fails to save Romulus from the supernova but he realizes that the resulting black hole could take him back in time and he would have another shot at saving the planet. Unfortunately, Nero witnesses the destruction of Romulus and oblivious to Spock Prime's plan, he follows him into the black hole seeking revenge and this action causes both Nero and Spock Prime to be thrown out of the black hole at the wrong point in space and time. This creates the new timeline because the Nerada interferes with USS Kelvin. So Spock Prime's action inadvertently creates an alternate reality and kills Kirk's father. Much of the film then plays out similarly or equally to the existing film, showing us the Kirk origin story and putting the crew together, etc. But Spock Prime watches from a distance, fascinated. Then a great source of conflict would be the destruction of Vulcan, which I would change from the way it was done in the movie. The destruction of Vulcan would actually be the finale of the movie instead of happening in the middle and Spock Prime would have to sacrifice the planet in order to defeat Nero, causing great inner conflict both for himself and for the young Spock. Let's say Nero goes to Vulcan to steal a prototype of what would eventually become Spock Prime's black hole machine and he wants to use it to destroy not only Vulcan, but the whole galaxy. He starts creating a massive black hole but before he succeeds, the Enterprise and Spock prime create a smaller black hole that sucks in the Nerada but also destroys Vulcan in the process and kills Spock Prime.

**Star Trek Into Darkness**

Let's say you absolutely have to go darker and you absolutely have to use Khan. Sure. But why not go all the way and be really dark? Why not use Khan in a way we haven't seen yet? General (?) Marcus wanted to prepare the Federation for future wars, so why not show one? In my scenario for this movie, the Federation is at war with the Klingons and it's losing. Like really getting their asses kicked. Pike is not riding a desk but leading the charge into hopeless battle, with Kirk and the Enterprise by his side. Pike's ship is destroyed in front of Kirk's eyes and he feels tremendous sorrow at losing his surrogate father figure, and he feels guilt over not being able to help him, which turns into blind rage. He is determined to have his vengeance and defeat the Klingons. This is Wrath of Kirk more than Wrath of Khan, already turning this remake on its head and doing something different. Kirk studies the Starfleet archives to learn new tactics from older, more savage times and during his studies of the Eugenics wars he learns of the program that created Khan. Appealing to Starfleet and recruiting Marcus to his side he instigates Khan's resurrection, which helps turn the tide and gives Starfleet the upper hand in the war. But for the mad Khan winning battles isn't enough and he starts to kick the Klingons' ass so much that he starts committing atrocities. He goes full Kurtz and Kirk realizes that his revenge is causing the same kind of pain and suffering that he went through and he is no better than the Klingons. Moral dilemmas and introspection galore. In the end Kirk has to go up the proverbial river to stop Khan, sacrificing himself in the process, because the survival of many outweighs the need for revenge of the one. Aaand then they can bring him back with Khan's blood or whatever.

**Star Trek Beyond**

This movie got a lot of things right, owing to Simon Pegg's script. The first twenty or so minutes of the movie are brilliant, setting up inner conflicts, emotional stakes and exploring the toll of isolation in space. However, much of that is later lost and completely obscured by studio-mandated action. In my scenario, Enterprise's destruction still happens, but it's much more emotionally impactful because it hasn't already happened twice in the two previous movies, so instead of going "not this again" the audience goes "oh my god the Enterprise is down" which is obviously much better. And if you absolutely need to have an evil villain in a Star Trek movie, make him more compelling. Dispense with action in favor of characters. Trek is absolutely the kind of franchise where the villain should talk to the hero and explain his entire motivation and plan. You know, what the Bond movies have been doing for decades. At the beginning of the movie Kirk is weary of space exploration, so have him confront the results of exploration gone wrong. What happened to Krall could easily have happened to Kirk, too. Don't give Kirk a motorcycle, give him inner conflict and demons to confront. And have Spock help him find the right path, solidifying their friendship and showing Spock that Kirk really needs him more than the Vulcans, so he can't leave Starfleet and Kirk's side.

So what is next in store for the crew of Starship Enterprise? I have a couple of ideas for future movies that would solve some of the problems of the existing three installments.

**Alternates**

The franchise already exists in an alternate timeline, so let's play with that a bit. Mirror universes, alternate realities and various timelines are staples of Trek. These sort of things work best when you already have your characters established, making it more interesting and entertaining to meet their counterparts and see them behave differently. It's also a good way to learn something new about the existing characters when they meet their counterparts. After three movies the new Trek crew are established well enough to warrant taking this route. Have a bit of fun with it but also explore the characters in depth at the same time. For example, one scenario could explore a world where Kirk never joined Starfleet. After he ran away from home he led a pointless existence, eventually going to space on a freighter and working a blue collar job. Not bound by duty to Starfleet or any five year missions, he also had the opportunity to create a family. Now what if that Kirk switched places with the Starfleet captain we know and love? Freighter Kirk would miss his family, but he would discover what it means to be captain and having the crew as family, learning something about duty and friendship along the way and confronting his past. Meanwhile, Starfleet Kirk would discover what it is like to have an actual family and what life without the Enterprise could be like, questioning his career. Throw in some conflict (for example, the Kirk switcheroo may have been deliberately caused by an antagonist) and you have yourself a movie.

**Make the Enterprise great again**

The Enterprise is supposed to be a flagship. Top of the line. A formidable opponent and an imposing presence if need be, but also a vessel of pure research and exploration. So far in the three new movies we've seen almost none of that. The ship repeatedly gets its ass kicked and performs no science whatsoever. But in the original series the ship is like a submarine in space (this idea largely reflected in the stealthy and subtle combat scenes as well as the use of torpedoes) and this is something I miss in the new franchise. It's also on a mission to explore strange new worlds and seek out new life and new civilizations, but science was notably absent in the new movies. What has Spock done in his capacity as Chief Science Officer? Have they ever really fired a probe or scanned a class M planet? Has the ship ever had the upper hand in a standoff or posed a threat to anyone? Since they once again destroyed it in Beyond, now is the perfect opportunity to design a new Enterprise and have it do new things (and by new I mean have it do the really old things it was always meant to do). 

**Star Trek doesn't need a villain**

The universe is vast and poses threats beyond some generic bad guys out for revenge or world domination. While the franchise has a nice roster of villains and antagonistic alien races, it's not all about those types of conflict. The ship is on its way to literally a place where no one else has gone before ...so why should it encounter familiar things? Give me a crystalline entity, a planet eating ship, an exiled Greek god or a long extinct civilization that's still holding secrets. Give me a large animal living in space like a deep sea creature, or a space-time anomaly, or a mysterious cosmic event. Give me anything besides a traditional villain. The Enterprise can fight all sorts of foes and stand up to all sorts of dangers. And why should it always encounter an opposing force or a threat to begin with? What if you had a movie like Contact set in the Star Trek universe? The Enterprise is somewhere far away, charting new territory, when it receives a signal. The crew have to work together to decipher it, the captain is faced with a difficult decision whether to pursue the signal into the dangerous far reaches of space or not, and overcoming some problems and dilemmas along the way they finaly get to a new destination where they learn something new. And what about a scenario like Arrival? Why do we need a standalone movie from a director largely known for thrillers to show us a perfect first contact story while a franchise that should be all about stuff like that is pretending to be an action movie? What happened to mystery, intrigue and discovery?

**Star Trek doesn't need Kirk and Spock**

I realize there's a new show coming up, but I'm going to make this point anyway. Star Trek doesn't need familiar things to succeed. It's vast and filled with great characters just waiting to be discovered. TOS, TNG, DS9, Voyager and Enterprise created a shared universe decades before anyone even dreamed of the Marvel Cinematic Universe, and yet we're pretending as if the MCU is some unbelievable new thing. Trek already has what the MCU spent many films establishing. But instead of utilizing that fact, the producers decided to just bring back a new flashier version of nostalgic characters. I understand why they did, there is no need to explain box office appeal or the logic behind reboots. But after three movies that were wholly average and underwhelming at the box office, maybe it's time to experiment and create something new. I don't expect them to make a long overdue DS9 movie or to bring back the TNG crew. I don't *want* them to. But they could start fresh. Maybe make a Generations style crossover movie with an appearance from the Kirk crew, but make something new. Show us a different part of Starfleet. Or take the Rogue One route and depict a well-known event from Trek lore that we never really got to see.

**Star Trek doesn't need a big budget**

If you're going to make a big budget movie, you need it to make all that money back, and then some. To make sure that happens, you need to make that movie appealing to a broad audience. That's how you get Star Trek Beyond the action movie instead of Star Trek Beyond the character driven space drama. What you end up with is an action movie that's too generic to please the general public hooked on Marvel and Star Wars, and also a movie that's not going to appeal to your core fan base. In other words, you have a mess that cost too much and made too little. But Star Trek was never about big budgets, it was about big stories. Week after week the creators managed to churn out great episodes on TV budgets with insufficient special effects. That creates restraint and science fiction has always benefited from restraint. Filmmakers like George Lucas and James Cameron have talked about having big ideas that weren't possible to film because the technology hadn't caught up with their visions. But when you look at their output created under restraint (Star Wars, The Terminator) and compare it with their technologically advanced output (Attack of the Clones, Avatar) it's clear that restraint breeds better results. Jaws was so effective because it revealed the shark gradually. It didn't blow its load with a money shot right at the beginning but kept the shark shrouded in mystery and menace. It was incredibly effective and it was due to restraint. The rubber shark puppet was unrealistic and often malfunctioning, so it had to be used with restraint. And the result is movie history. When you watch TOS episodes, most of the show has sets that are nothing but a blank wall bathed in colorful lights. Does that take away anything from the story, though? I am all for beautiful visuals and great effects, but the need for them does not outweigh the need for a good script. I would much rather sacrifice the former in favor of the latter. As it stands, the three new Trek movies are very much like the hated prequel trilogy of Star Wars. Lots of style, not enough substance. Give me a low budget Trek movie that doesn't have to make huge money to break even. Give me a story that doesn't have to be appealing to a general audience. Arrival's budget was $47 million yet it managed to have cool spaceships, cool aliens, great actors, and a great story. Star Trek Beyond had a budget of $185 million, which is ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this video was posted four years too late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian is only my third language but it feels like the word order is pretty awkward, too. I think this was definitely the work of someone using google translate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is the celebrity I most associate with wearing too much makeup all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have this set as a ring tone for certain contacts and to this day whenever I hear that coin being tossed into the phone I get a cold chill down my spine thinking my ex is calling me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now you're making it about race? Can't black people enojy Power Rangers too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but 118/120 does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trailers often show unfinished effects. And the trailer is 2 minutes long, while the actual movie is 2 hours. So it stands to reason that the money went a) into actually finishing the effects we got to see and b) the 98% of film we haven't seen yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wouldn't it be funny if this movie totally bombed at the box office?

What, specifically, do you find funny about the prospect of a studio losing money? Do you think it's amusing to them and the people working for them? You do realize people's jobs (not to mention future movies which might turn out to be good) are at stake, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he probably still made more than Paul Rudd and Evangeline Lilly combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in over 10 titles since Breaking Bad ended and he followed Godzilla with Trumbo, which earned him an Oscar nomination. So what are you even talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the cleavage is there for. Those breasts don't need to breathe and they don't need sunlight to survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I'm looking for movies like The Red Turtle (metaphysical, esoteric fables - doesn't have to be animation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty much what the title says - I'm looking for films that have the same atmosphere and style of The Red Turtle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are parody laws and where can I apply for parody law school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks more like popcorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the stakes felt incredibly real in this film. But knowing that Jackman is done with the role probably helped that a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel, man. I'm 27 so I've been a fan of this movie franchise for most of my life. I literally grew up on Hugh Jackman as Wolverine. And you know what? I couldn't be happier that he got a proper sendoff. Imagine X-Men Apocalypse was his final movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's your opinion, and I respect that, but I have to fully disagree with it. What you disliked about Logan was for me the best part of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is all that it was. But people just had to make a huge deal out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seventeen years ago the first X-Men turned Hugh Jackman into a star and ushered in the era of comic book movies that changed the landscape of summer blockbusters and is still as strong today as ever. Now Jackmans last movie in the iconic role gives us a new vision of what these movies can be. Not like Deadpool, with its over the top meme-like siliness, but an emotionally driven, self-contained personal drama with small scale action. The whole world is not at stake. There is no CG destruction. Instead, this is a stand-alone movie thats not concerned with any larger universe or previous movies or any  franchise baggage. Its just Logan, Charles and Laura against some bad guys. Dirty, ugly, gritty, tense, superbly acted and realistically violent. Simply put, the movie does not fuck around. Wolverine is a violent beast who kills people with huge claws and we finally get to see that without any PG-13 neutering. Jackman can be proud of his swan song and fans can only wish the previous movies were half as good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This showerthought should have an "already seen it posted a million times" button </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that must be a nasty toilet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there was some criticism surrounding the fact that Takei is gay IRL so they just shoehorned Sulu's husband into the movie as a reference to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always bothered me that they used some normal egg with a hard eggshell instead of the more leathery, slimy egg from the movie

Edit: Really? WTF are you downvoting this for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I want is a gay James Bond seducing dudes instead of the attractive starlets they throw into the plot just to have a pretty face on the poster. Now that would be progressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because most people DO give a shit when they find out that someone is homosexual, so it IS a big deal for gays and lesbians to be open about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sulu was briefly shown to have a boyfriend (or husband?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, Adventure Time has had a heavily implied lesbian relationship just casually thrown into the show for years. Friends had a lesbian relationship, too. Master of None has a lesbian character. Grey's Anatomy had a lesbian relationship. House had a bisexual character. Modern Family has a gay couple raising kids. Everyone just fucks anything that moves on Game of Thrones. I hear Orange is the New Black also has  LGBTQ characters. The list goes on. TV is way more progressive than movies, despite the fact that a movie about gays just won best picture. But I get it from Disney. They are a studiou focused on kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn that Superman theme gets my blood pumping every time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> must be all that exercise on the bicycle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, in the movie Star Trek: Generations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/woahdude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fast and Furious franchise is an example of what happens when you want to make a big-budget action film but you're in the middle of the era of comic book movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a very strong desire for a Bond movie that:

* is set in the sixties, but without commenting on the era in any way, just portraying it realistically and matter-of-factly

* shows us Bond as an unparalleled master assassin like John Wick, but also exploring in depth what a killer like that would actually be like as a person in day-to day life

* has actual spycraft in it, like Tinker Taylor Soldier Spy, The Night Manager, and even its actual 60s iteration From Russia with Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to tell you OP that I really enjoyed this video and I agreed with almost everything. (Though I have a problem with Jane Bond, but not because of the fact that she's a woman. Rather, I don't like that people would turn it into a huge deal and the manufactured controversy would tarnish the experience no matter how good the movie would be.)

I must say I really liked the idea of two simultaneous franchises set apart in time. There is precedent for this, most notably with the X-Men franchise and its First Class sub-franchise, but also in a little something called Star Trek. The various shows coexisting alongside each other as (almost exclusively) separate stories is exactly what could work with Bond. Just consider this: there are *two* iconic starships *Enterprise* and *two* iconic Captains. And DS9's airdates overlap the air dates of both TNG and Voyager, proving that these separate timeline franchises can also work simultaneously and not just one following after the other as TOS and TNG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do cigarettes burn so slowly instead of immediately going up in flames? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (since they are basically dried leaves and paper, which is what you use to set a camp fire) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 questions:

* Millennia?

* Is the entire mountain made of marble or is this just like a pocket of marble the way you have with gold or coal or oil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably watch robots vs anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone with a social studies major is just too happy they're not serving fries so they went overboard with the review </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I get that but this is another problem I have. The movie is praised for depicting life in Iran. So basically people value the fact that it's exotic. But that's not a merit of the movie. It's not an achievement of the filmmaker. That's just the circumstance that the film is Iranian and you are not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> risky click </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw you had no comments on your post and I liked Wild Tales a lot, too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Tale of Two Sisters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try [Taxidermia](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0410730/?ref_=nv_sr_1), a triptych of even weirder stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with this movie is that I went in expecting a drama about a divorce (or separation, whatever) but instead it's about a man with anger management issues who has to care for his father who has Alzheimer's and at the same time deal with a woman who accused him of causing her miscarriage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   disappointed in Alana for jumping on Hannibal's dick

Let's just take a moment to appreciate how you worded that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And I saw it years ago when it aired.

I forgot how long ago that was. Feels like yesterday. I guess that means I'll have to rewatch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally the love child of Hannibal and Zodiac! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did even work, with the thing still spinning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giant robots versus werewolves is something I would definitely watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently watched it again (on DVD) and boy is it accurate and relatable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't be the only one who finds this [very similar to the Doctor Strange poster](http://i.imgur.com/Pdd4CnT.jpg), right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright alright alright is his trademark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adrien Brody needs to have more screentime in movies where he is supposed to play the lead role </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally have never experienced a feeling of aslept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was bigger than John Goodman in that movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A little-known soap and sitcom actress, she had scored a major breakthrough in spring 1992 at age 27 with My Cousin Vinny, a slapsticky sleeper comedy about a personal injury lawyer from New York

How is My Cousin Vinny slapstick?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she was consciously trying to blame someone. Probably just a poorly phrased sentence from someone caught in a confusing situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a couple hundred depending on how pro you want to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even have a TV set. I just hook up my laptop to a projector and have instant home cinema.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 11:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I do not understand how Naomie Harris didn't win Best Supporting Actress.

because she lost to a leading actress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short article (or shorticle) is any length of text on the internet that isn't tldr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are some things water soluble while others are not and does entropy not dictate that even a diamond would dissolve in water if given enough time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel like for some people the liveliness of La La Land or atmosphere of Arrival is unbeaten this year.

I think this is the main issue. I really liked Manchester a lot but there is no way I'll ever watch it again. Too depressing. But I've already seen Arrival twice and I can see myself returning to La La Land whenever there's an opportunity. I guess that rewatchability isn't a real factor but many people will consider it nonetheless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Knight and Day kind of satisfies that craving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House number 9 on the street where I work has an overgrown stone wall with a neat gate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are arranged beautifully. I absolutely love it, good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The name and password to your secret porn account is probably your most guarded secret </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the Tom Cruise approach to life.  As in: my job is to ride motorcycles, kiss beautiful women and climb the tallest building in the world. Why would I want to do anything else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But where would we get all those hilarious gifs without current Bollywood action standards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why just indie filmmakers? Directors working in Hollywood right now should watch and take notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, uh, it's a stencil font. Never seen that before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! If you like it, share it with friends, please. The more people participate, the more accurate it will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  An undercover MI6 agent is sent to Berlin during the Cold War to investigate the murder of a fellow agent and recover a missing list of double agents.

I'm getting all kinds of vibes from this poster but that plot summary is not one of them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never believe anything I see on TV ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look like a fleet of starships from Star Trek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I haven't seen JW2 yet but in the first movie Wick actually got his ass kicked a couple of times and I wouldn't call all of his kills effortless. Also, I really consider JW to be essentially like a comic book movie, or definitely at least a sort of heightened reality. It has its own mythos and style that isn't really going for realism. Whereas I think the two Fallen movies were going for something gritty and more realistic at least in terms of depicting terrorism instead of stylized international assassins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the title is very appropriate if you know [what it means](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fifth_Estate) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bad for original movies but I get it. The movie just wasn't very goood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the idea for this website, then [check out the beta version we just launched](http://trailerhunter.tech/)
Now we need users to watch trailers and vote on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a biologist who sees a fugly extra terrestrial snake and talks to it like it was a puppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
