<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know if any of these games would require an update before they can be played? I know when I used to have a ps4 and get a new game sometimes the game would day my system didn't have the latest update and I couldn't play until it updated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't use it enough to justify the cost.

I wouldn't even be getting another ps4 but these 4 games are calling to me. 

Now I'll also have to get a tv... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metamorphosis by Kafka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never met anyone who's ever even heard of communion lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever read a cyberpunk book before, just looked this guy up and I think I'll be getting me a copy of Nueromancer, it seems to be the one he's known for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to go with War and Peace here, though I've never meet irl anyone else who has actually read it. But I will say that people get it wrong for a couple of reasons. 

1) most people who haven't read the book, don't even know what it's about, not even a basic concept of it, they've just heard it's really boring.

2) people who do know what it's about, think that's it's all about war, and it's not, not even close.

So, yes there is war, and yes it's a catalyst for the story, but the title is symbolism. The "War and Peace" in War and Peace is the internal struggles of the characters, basically, being a human being, having your ups and downs and the complications of life and loving and love and loss, disappointment, pain, struggles, sorrows, sacrifice, you name it it's in there. And it's also about his philosophy and the struggle he has with history and the way things are told and the complications of telling of these leaders and how things have been played out and how things will shape the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told myself I was only go read 3 discworld books, there is no way I can get invested into something that huge lol, so the three I picked up were

Guards Guards

Mort

Small Gods

I am excited to read them at some point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I love the "Story" part of story, and even his thoughts on history I didn't mind. But what left a sour taste, and don't worry no spoilers, was that I was so connected to the characters that when I finished the first epilogue I was thankful that I could have a little more time with everyone in epilogue part 2, but no, the second epilogue is just his philosophy on history. Which if I would have know the story story was done at the end of the first epilogue, I would have tried to hold onto it a little longer.


So OP if you want the story part, only read the first epilogue :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gifted a ton of his books, though I've only read The Shining and The Stand, I liked the shining much better. 

I'm more interested in his short stories and I traded in like 15 of the books which I didn't think I was going to read :/

But I'm excited for Dark Tower, I liked the comic, the next of his actual novels I'm going to read is IT, also I just bought 11/22/63 for like 3 bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I read a really long book and then several smaller books, I just finished War and Peace earlier this year, it's like 1400 pages, took me 3 months to get through it, I'm halfway through Imajica (850 pages) and I've only been reading it for about 10 days. 

Which is dumb because I read Flowers for Algernon in one day (300+ pages) and it's taken me 10 days to do that with Imajica, which is even more dumb because if I could do 300+ a day War and Peace should have only taken me like 5 days.

But what's even more dumb, is while I was reading War and Peace, I read 5 other books as well.

So, I think it all depends on if you're into the story or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The abortion scene was the most evil thing in that book to me lol. It didn't have any blood or gore, but it showed how vile he could be and his mockery of the girls suffering by leaving baby items, it still make me wince thinking about it.

Though, I loved the book and when it got extremely gross and disturbing I honestly was cracking up at a lot of the ridiculousness of it all, and thankfully I read it after I saw the movie so Christian Bale was in my head the entire time, which was amazing.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankenstein was really got me into reading, but recently Flowers for Algernon might have topped that, it was the first full length novel that I finished all in one day. 

One thing I like to do is read books that they've made movies out of and then spout the differences, I just recently read Psycho and it blew my mind how amazing it was. Also I have Jaws, The Exorcist, First Blood (rambo), Jurassic Park, and several other big movie books, they're quick and fun.

Also Brandon Sanderson really got me into fantasy so maybe check out some of his stuff.

And Richard Matheson and Clive Barker really got me into short stories, also Clive Barker is probably one of the most amazing writers out there.

Also Haruki Murakami is really good, and I think Cormic McCarthy is considered one of the greatest living writers right now.

But, here's a list of books by everyone I mentioned and a couple others that you might like.

Weaveworld - Barker

Imajica - Barker

Books of blood - Barker

Norwegian wood - Murakami

Windup Bird Chronicles - Murakami

The Road - McCarthy

Blood Meridian - McCarthy

Mistborn trilogy - Sanderson

Hell house - Matheson

I am legend - Matheson

The collector - John Fowels

Do androids dream of electric sheep - Philip K Dick

Dune - Frank Herbert

Frankenstein - M. Shelley

Flowers for Algernon - Daniel Keyes

These should be fun reads, for me at least they were, just a simple start.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the sci fi stuff is pretty short, I'd say most around 350 pages, I can knock those out in a couple days, so maybe besides the Stephen king stuff and big huge books I have, I can get through most of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you read all the books you own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently discovered I have over 100+ books I own that I haven't read. So I've cut myself off from the bookstore for the rest of the year and hopefully will knock out a lot of the smaller stuff. I feel this is ridiculous for me not to have read everything I own and I want to know if other people do this as well, maybe not to point of 100+ unread books, but still. Or does anyone have more than me that they haven't read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old man and the sea, because Hemingway writes like a child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just skip the whaling bits and focus on the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game of thrones, it's been like 2 years....I've only got 250 pages left...But I just never seem to get around to finishing it off...and I still have 4 or 5 more books to go in the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Moby Dick, though I didn't like the whaling chapters, I wanted the story not the context on how things are done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sky Rider, watercolor, wc paper, 8x12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So....what is the price of a switch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I think the price is $300 but every website has it listed somewhat differently, so I thought I'd check gamestop because even sold out they'd at least have the price up, well gamestop's website only has a $522 bundle listed and I think most the stuff bundled isn't even out yet. Amazon has them listed for about $400 and I stopped checking after that, Nintendo's website says $299,  but the retailers all have different prices and Nintendo doesn't have a way for me to just order off their site.

The sucky thing is I'm not even trying to buy one right now, I'm literally just trying to window shop. I was thinking maybe in May, but now lol I'm kinda over it all. I just wanted something that wouldn't require me to have a tv, might as well get a vita and just play ps1 games lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember color theory, you just use the primaries, yellow red blue, you can make almost everything from those, minus white.

To darken say red, use green, to darken yellow use purple, to darken blue use orange. To make black mix all to make brown then mix in more blue. 

Drawmixpaint made a good video about limited palettes. 

With watercolor though I use several different reds, blues, greens yellows and browns, it's a little too much to do all your mixing with the watercolor. 

But with gouache or oil, I only use the primary colors, if you look at my past posts I did a Nightcrawler painting that only used primary colors.  

Edit:
https://m.imgur.com/82zN1YE

Here is my Nightcrawler painting, only used primary colors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just made the characters up, so I'll be making prints before too long, I'll post again when I have them ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instagram jqstringer though not much fantasy stuff is on there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my thank you to r/fantasy, I didn't realize my little mice were going to be a hit and now I'm working on a story for them, so I'm going to bid you all farewell for awhile while I go and work on this. I'll see you in the fifth dominion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Mice can't dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even have internet at home, just my phone, but I'll have to check it out, thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be 3 total pictures I've posted on here of my little mice characters, and the band genesis lol, just a kind of fan shout out thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions for Brandon...If he reads this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or anyone else I suppose, so lately I've been posting some fantasy art on here of some little mice characters I've made up, and people seem to enjoy than, so I've been coming up with a story idea and I was just wondering if I could get any tips on how to bring a little mice world alive. I've got some general ideas for the overarching story, what the purpose is for why things are happening, the world the little mice are in and all that, I just don't know how to push it into more than an idea. 

So Brandon, if you read this, lol would you mind talking to me a bit. If you don't read this, would anyone who is familiar with his work and world building have any good resources or ideas on how to build a story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the spider's  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No only what I've posted on here, I'm actually now making a story of them, so I'll probably be away for awhile, but I want to do one more, a genesis inspired one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The salt elder, watercolor, wc paper, 8x15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] The spider queen, watercolor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] The spider queen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I mention Jonathan Livingston Seagull to someone they've never heard of it, though I think it was pretty popular.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice copy of Dune </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking about buying one of Stephenson's book, cryptonomicon, I always see it but I'm not sure if I should </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Guts from Chuck Palahniuk? The main character in that story is a teenager, does that count as YA?

http://chuckpalahniuk.net/features/shorts/guts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most expensive book you've bought? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I do most of my book buying at half price books I'm usually saving a pretty good amount on my reading material and I don't know if I've really ever bought a new book. I usually think about $10 is on the high end and I'm usually reluctant unless it's something I've really been looking for. Though I paid $50 for the ASOIF set new from Barnes and noble, they had it on sale for 50% off, the little leather bound set, but for one single book I think the most I paid was $18, and it was for the three book version of 1Q84. 

What's the most expensive book you've bought, or I guess even just own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
