<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people who show up just to check it out but not really participate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is! easily the most interesting dance floor in Madison

It's a really nice venue. MUCH nicer bathroomslol. Bathrooms at the Inferno could be an adventure when it was crowded.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It felt like it's what would happen if Lars Von Trier suffered a stroke half way through making a movie, then the editing staff just released the loosely edited remnants.

hahahaahaha! Okay that's pretty funny right there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, yeah I forgot about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rogue One: So you're telling me a person can hit a storm trooper on the side of their HELMET with their BARE elbow, and trooper crumbles like a sack of potatoes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 01:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 01:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so how does this affect the seeding  depending on if the Packers win and/or lose tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're completely full of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it's hard to keep track of who currently hates Mike Shanahan

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google "psilocybin mushrooms + migraines"

Seriously, people do MICRO dose mushrooms and completely cured their migraines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as I said I've read at least 3000 NDE accounts. One of the things is very striking is that when people leave their body, sometimes they travel around and visit loved ones. They hear conversations and watch what people are doing.

Then when they come back into their bodies they tell those people what they were doing and those people are absolutely stunned that they somehow knew that

 the characteristic effects of NDE were shown to be reproduced by using the drug Ketamine.

Absolutely not. Nobody's having the very specific type of NDE phenomenon while on ketamine. For instance I've never heard anybody say they had an absolute 100% holographic recall every single moment of their entire life while on ketamine. That's just one example
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most of the transcendental religions hold this to be true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 03:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> except it does contribute

It's constructive, worthwhile, criticism of this sub Reddit. Criticism that people need to hear, and hopefully take to heart.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 03:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very very true

On this sub for sure. Also any time you make that point you instantly get down voted, as you are here

women get tons of sympathy in this sub, men get very little. That's just how it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been studying the NDE (near-death experience) phenomenon for about 10 years now. At this point I have read over 3000 NDE accounts.

I now have absolutely zero doubt there is an afterlife none whatsoever. Over and over and over again different people with different religious backgrounds different ethnic backgrounds different belief systems experience the same thing when they leave their bodies. They described the experience as the most real thing they have ever experienced, and that this life on earth is in fact the dream, the spirit world is the real world.

Now NDE accounts don't support a fundamentalist Christian viewpoint, but they most definitely 100% support pretty much all of the teachings of Jesus Christ. I.e. the most important things in life are to love your neighbor as yourself, things like that

I suggest checking it out.here's a great place to start

http://www.nderf.org/Archives/exceptional.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

tthe mustache is still around? Why did they change their name? Those guys are pretty good actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just a joke. I might crack one about Carrie Fisher if you stick around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay somebody please tell me what the hell is going on Adelaide?

Seriously, I hear weird creepy stories about that city all the time.

There is some kind of weird shit happening here. and I just imagining this?

EDIT: just found out somerton man is from Adelaide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah,being forced to go to the south of France to assuage your depression sounds awful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whatever. That's what it AutoCorrect into I'm not changing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, should I? I literally don't listen to sports talk at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because Ted Thompson is going to hold onto every fourth-round draft pick like starving man holds onto his last power bar

Same reason he didn't trade for Marchan Lynch

he makes both of those trades and the Packers have at least one if not two more Super Bowl rings

then again TT is the one who drafted Aaron Rodgers, the best player in the entire universe right now

What can you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's good to know about the blue moon. I will check the place out

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hayward was consistently great in coverage his entire career

And he wasn't even asking for a lot of money. personally I think it was just a terrible terrible decision </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool, thanks for the tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a really weird idea for the Chicago Bears

Instead of drafting really good players and then trading them away for peanuts or letting them go in free agency You should keep them!

I know what you're thinking, totally nutso! But you never know it could work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh has a lot of nagging injuries all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and he is going to continue to improve. It was the right move ultimately.

Letting Casey Hayward go however  was one of the worst off-season moves in the entire NFL unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> except not really because Josh would have spent the considerable amount of time on the bench due to injuries, just like he did in Chicago

That was one of the reasons he got cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apparently so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well?

are you going to clue us in on these locations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check out the fish fry. Just be aware it's absolutely slammed most of the night. Wait time can be 2 to 3 beers or more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how is it possible the village Tap's $8 cheeseburger is better than most of the $11  $15 gourmet burgers in this town? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the villa tap is a neighborhood bar off Packers. they serve great food from teeny tiny little kitchen. Their fish fry is fantastic. They serve a no-frills nothing special eight dollar cheeseburger that taste better than nearly every single "gourmet" expensive burger I've ever had in the city.

I just don't understand how that's possible?

I'm talking specifically about the Patty itself. It's rich and flavorful. It tastes like beef You know?

I've had plenty of expensive burgers in this town where the Patty tastes completely neutral. Like nothing really.

Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay great. So you believe man-made climate change is real.

Excellent. So What should we do about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay then, let's discuss something rational.

do you acknowledge that man-made climate change is a real thing?

Or do you agree with Donald Trump that it's a Chinese conspiracy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you are debating me, but you don't have time for a debate

sounds like you can't name five good things about Trump. Oh well, I didn't really think you could anyway



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you can't name five major positive things about Trump being President, you've been manipulated to feel that way and aren't thinking rationally.

well? Go ahead We are waiting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also the reveal is pretty cheap.

agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right, the first half set  up something intriguing. You were wondering where they were going what was going to happen

and then, in the second act everybody started acting like dumb morons and doing dumb moronic thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TT snatched up Jason Spriggs quicker than shit when he fell

He's played fine for us, but not fantastic. Still, he has great upside. No idea what Schneider was smoking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because I assume he knows the business, and he has connections, and he can find a script that doesn't make people do moronic things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILERS



But when this Creature Who has already killed multiple people is rolling right at you and you just wave the gun around and say "excuse me please stop" and refuse to pull the trigger and then you get killed You are an idiot.

It makes me think that the person who wrote the script is also an idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Giamatti, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Brian Cox

Those are all fantastic actors, in my book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Morgan" (2016-new to DVD): how can a movie with this many talented people involved be this bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morgan is about a corporate risk-management consultant who must decide whether or not to terminate an artificially created humanoid being. 

Sounds like a good idea for a movie doesn't it? Intriguing. Lots of potential Right? Here's the cast

Kate Mara, Michelle Yeoh, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Paul Giamatti, Brian Cox, etc.

Directed by Luke Scott who is Ridley Scott's kid

fantastic cast and crew right?

Here's the problem. The characters in this movie repeatedly do things that are mind numbingly stupid. More than once I'm staring at the screen screaming "why are you just standing there? Why don't you _________?"

Also the humanoid being takes a series of actions that they never ever explained why she did those things. There's simply no motivation. It's just like she starts doing these crazy things For no reason. Why?

Also, there is a twist at the end of this movie. A twist that you probably saw it coming about one third of the way through the movie because they blatantly foreshadow it.

a couple of innocent characters die in this movie and I just sat there thinking "you kind of deserve to die for being so incredibly stupid you moron"

I can't believe all of these talented people looked at the script and thought "yeah! This looks good!" Because honestly this is a TERRIBLE script.

This movie is very similar to ex machina. In fact, just watch ex machina and skip this one altogether </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How I got paid to be an extreme adventurer And how you can too!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> our current Secretary of Education is an Amway sales lady, who inherited $1 billion, who wants to gut the public school system

So Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Why do people act like this is somehow a new development?

The right wing and their media allies have convinced millions of Americans that the rock solid science of climate change  is a big huge liberal conspiracy. And people acted like this was somehow normal and okay

Nobody really call them out. The news media treated the issue as "climate experts say one thing  but climate skeptics (who are almost always on payroll oil companies but let's pretend that's not happening) say another! Who can know who is right?"

Not to mention many of religious Americans stands on evolution, and a literal belief in a six-day creation, a literal belief in a flood that destroy the world despite zero geological evidence of such a thing, etc. etc.

This is been going on for a long time and it's only going to get worse. Once again Donald Trump just ratcheted up the volume to 11  on something that already is happening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL dying is bad for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kristin Schall seriously just gets on my nerves in everything she's on

I don't even know what it is! I absolutely cannot verbalize WHY exactly I can't stand her.

For one thing though her voice. That little baby voice she does all the time Super annoying! other than that I don't know. Just absolutely 100% cannot stand her at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what kind of restaurant were you working at where customers were giving servers sexually-transmitted diseases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by far and away the most popular word in all of the NFC North's word clouds combined is "Packers"

In fact it's not even close

it's probably because Aaron Rodgers is such a humble likable down-to-earth fellow

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so what he is saying there are things that ARE zen, and then there are things that ARE NOT zen

Okay great.

Could somebody make two lists for me? One list is all of the things that are Zen, the other list is the things that are not zen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very sexy!

the girl doesn't look too bad either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is not "duping" the media

He is giving the media EXACTLY what they want!

The media loves this twitter Fest as well as the various groups freaking out every time he tweets

The 24 hour cycle news media needs fresh content literally every hour. Donald Trump gives them that exact thing. So they roll with it.

The media is literally addicted Donald Trump and his wacky disturbing psychotic antics the same way a high school girl is addicted to the "drama" she claims to hate

The media and Donald Trump are literally a match made in heaven. They give him the attention he craves, he gives them  something stupid and idiotic to freak out about every 24 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nobody ever talks about banshee, but what a great show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banshee

Very little fanfare but what a great show! Be aware there's lots of fighting action scenes that are over the top, but also plenty of interpersonal drama.

The thing is you're not supposed to take the over-the-top action scenes too seriously. More like fun comic book violence

Two or three episodes in and you will be hooked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh, that's actually a good point!

our o line got a lot better after he left.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, can't help myself commenting more.

"Abaddon" and "Gog" are both mentioned in the book of the Revelation in the Christian Bible as harbingers of the apocalypse

cheron is the person who ferries the boat across the River Styx, and Cerberus is the three headed dog that guards the gates of hell

mot is probably a play on the word maat, the Egyptian concept ofbalance order and harmony

I could go on but you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also note the symbol labeled "satyr" is the phi symbol, a.k.a. "the Golden ratio"

https://www.goldennumber.net/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also, the symbol labeled succubus is the same as the astrological symbol for Taurus

Again why would you give a demonic name to a pre-existing symbol that has nothing to do with it? again Weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a bit annoyed that they took a beautiful symbol like the vesica Pisces and named it after Moloch

Moloch was a real ancient Middle Eastern God demanded human sacrifice, specifically sacrifice of children. Archaeological evidence continues to mount that this really happened.

Why would you name a beautiful symbol like the vesica Pisces after that? weird

http://sacredgeometryinternational.com/the-meaning-of-sacred-geometry-part-3-the-womb-of-sacred-geometry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's the thing This is EXACTLY what we would expect from man-made climate change!

The climate is destabilizing. That means we will have more extremes of on both ends. Extreme cold immediately followed by extreme warm is exactly what you expect from climate destabilization

So yes, if you stick around Chicago expect more crazy cold, crazy warm fluctuations during the wintertime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> so does the outcome of the Detroit/Dallas game even matter? Next week's game still determines division champ Right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> somebody fill me in here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed. This is legitimately shocking to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey, is Doogie Houser McClintock (or whatever his name is) still playing?


How does he look? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sso this dude is going to avoid calories by putting back the chicken wings and eating potato salad instead?

Alexa you are stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know we could really use on defense?

A guy like Casey Hayward. he plays for the bolts, not sure if you guys ever heard of him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's always a 50-50 chance if they are ever going to add you in this situation I have found </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously though how bad does the defense have to be before there are legit calls to fire capers?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this secondary is going to be the death of this team this year

offense is as good as any football team  in the league. Secondary is as awful as any secondary in the league

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, fair point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILERS!!



Right, she released the turtle that he gave her. So does that mean she's over him now? Or maybe not? I have no idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you're saying but you never really got a answer as to what Shia's character intentions were </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought too many of the situations the lead character got herself into were similar. The movie was repetitive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have a valid point, and I am not the one down  voting  you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> , yeah, you're probably right 

But that's what people in the movie called themselves, so that's what I'm calling them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you but there was very little actual character development

 Shia's character was basically the same person the whole movie, and then it ends and you still don't know if he has changed at all

If you're going to make a character-based movie, then there damn well better be actual CHARACTER DEVELOPMENT in your movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use that term because that's the term they use in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly. He's that boring guy you meet at a sports bar one night, have a beer and a short conversation, and then forget he ever existed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "American Honey": So many elements of a fantastic film, but holy shit! Did this movie ever need a good editor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "American Honey" is about a young dirt poor white trash girl who joins a roving band of similarly white trash people who go from town to town selling magazine subscriptions. Shia Labuff (spelling?) Is her love interest.

The film oozes authenticity. every character in this movie feels real, every situation is completely believable. Absolutely fantastic job on this. The movie really opens a window into the life of a poor young white trash American. (The movie uses the term "white trash" and that's why I'm using it)

the lead actress is great, it's her first feature film and she's fantastic.

Some of the cinematography also is awesome..

the initial story is involving, believable, and endearing.

The soundtrack is absolutely on point.

The problem?

Holy shit this movie is soooooooooooooooooo long! Way way way too long. it's two hours and 43 minutes, again wait too long Especially for a movie with a paperthin plot that never really goes anywhere.

Absolutely desperately needed a good editor. They could've chopped one hour out of this movie and it would've made it a better movie. there are at least five scenes of these people riding around in a van lip-synching to music. it got old.

My other problem with it is it's sort of eends abruptly  with absolutely no plot resolution of any type. Ugh! Now some of you may like that, and that's fine. I personally like a movie to tell me an actual story. This movie starts telling the story, gets disinterested, then wanders off and peters out

Overall the movie is still worth seeing, just be aware of has serious problems.

Despite this I still recommend it, if only for its raw authenticity that is so rare in movies today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HATE Jim!

Seriously, soooooooooo smug, so condescending, and so self congratulating in his little smug clique he has with Pam. The way they use Dwight, the way they torment him, all so they can feel better about their own overwhelmingly average lives

I don't understand why people like that guy so much. Dwight would be 1000x more interesting to have as a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?

That's it? That's the reason you dislike the guy?

I mean God for bid a football player should be an actual human being </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but has he ever growled to himself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moore spent months during the 2016 election explaining why Christians should refuse to accept the either-or choice of Hillary Clinton versus Donald Trump. He continually used his platform to encourage Christians to raise the level of public discourse and expand the approach to pro-life issues beyond simply ending abortion to including care for the immigrant, impoverished, refugee, and incarcerated.

So he wanted to apply actual comprehensive Christlike principles to these issues instead of simply stopping your feet and demanding "no abortions!"

So it makes no sense that a sharp controversy is now brewing in the Southern Baptist Convention over Moores leadership.

agreed, this makes no sense. This is theoretically a Christian organization, why are they upset that this man is applying Christlike principles to politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would not want to have a trip anything like what is portrayed in this video. But that's just me

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reaction to your trip

First off you saw the crazy clowns that they talk about in "the Spirit molecule". Very common.

Secondly, using somebody as your anchor who actively disapproves of psychedelic use is a really bad idea. You are setting yourself up for a bad trip before it even starts.

Set and setting my friend. Yours was all wrong. Your girlfriend was fighting with the spirit of the DMT, you were fighting with your girlfriends psyche, and meanwhile the DMT could not teach you any lessons.


next time, make sure you trip with somebody who actively support you, make sure your mind is calm and clear, and go into it with a good psychological framework. This will really help
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the combination of the music and the images very disturbing

the constant strobe effect, combined with the odd descending bell like sounds in the background give the whole thing a disjointed and cacophonous feel, the product of a disturbed mind

I like the flower of life tattoo he has, but the rest of the video and song to be dark chaotic and depressing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, I'm not a big beer connoisseur so this isn't really a big issue with me either way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interestingly enough after my 2 bad experiences I looked on trip advisor to see what other people were saying, and many of them mirrored my experience exactly

https://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurant_Review-g60859-d8753742-Reviews-Cafe_Hollander-Madison_Wisconsin.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I gather that the thing to eat there is the breakfast, which I have never ordered. Maybe I'll try it. Also maybe not.

The waitstaff was just so incredibly indifferent and slow it makes me not want to go back there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you actually order the hamburger and you are okay with McDonald'stier french fries at a high-end pub?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah,that's pretty much my exact experience at the place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caf Hollander (Hilldale): high prices, subpar food, and an indifferent waitstaff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to Caf Hollander at Hilldale two times now. Both times it was the same thing.

The waitstaff is disinterested and unfriendly.

I got a burger both times. The patty was good-sized, but completely bland. The french fries are the same generic fast food fries you get at McDonald's or Burger King.

And on top of this the prices are high.

The great dane is a block away, has better food, better waitstaff, and slightly lower prices. I cannot imagine a single reason anybody should go to Caf Hollander

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather have us tackle domestic hunger and poverty with that money.

You are living in fantasyland you think Donald Trump and his merry gang of billionaire corporate fascists are going to use that money to address hunger and poverty

$2 billion is a drop in the bucket. the Iraq Afghanistan wars cost us $6 trillion and nobody even blinks an eye, and yet when it comes to spending money on disease research suddenly everybody's a miser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not how I see it all

He's not questioning the $2 billion, is questioning whether or not the government should spend even a single dollar on researching a disease that causes brain damage

Furthermore he claims to be smarter than all of the scientists studying this and doesn't even think this disease causes brain damage in the first place

This guy is a disaster, Trump is a disaster, there's no getting around it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> come on dude!

Did you even read the article?

they print the ENTIRE Facebook post where he discusses this, you can read the whole thing within its own context.

It is OBVIOUS he is questioning whether we need government research into diseases that cause brain damage like zika at all.

He then goes on to explain that he, Mr. budget director, is smarter than all of the scientists who have studied zika and he declares that it probably doesn't cause brain damage and everything is fine

You have a PhD? And you're claiming this is fake news? And you haven't even read the story?

Come on now I know you're better than that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montgomery may be one of the best running back/wide receivers who wears number 88 in the entire league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 19:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike McCarthy LOVES slow developing run plays on third and short

GAH!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how exactly is the establishment getting wrecked?

Please explain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so a website ran by our billionaire president's closest adviser is telling us about how the "establishment" is losing control?

This is a president who's chosen a cabinet full of billionaires from the likes of Goldman Sachs and Exxon Mobil.


And they want to tell us about "the establishment" is faltering?

That's good. That's rich. That's quite hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 23:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it's almost like the military-industrial complex feeds various factions money and guns in order to propagate conflict, which the US then has "no choice" but to intervene, meaning more money and resources get poured into the military-industrial complex

It's almost like it's a self propagating entity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 22:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but the internal political situation in Syria has definitely been covered

But the major media outlets NEVER explained that the whole thing started because of a gas pipeline project from Qatar to Europe, and the Russian response etc.

It just never gets discussed and it should be discussed because it's a major contributing factor. It's not just a civil war, it is a proxy international conflict </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best succinct explanation of the Syrian conflict I've ever read. It started out as Europe's desire for a natural gas pipeline from Qatar in order to avoid dependence on Russian energy and spiraled downward from there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you so much for this.

Wars and geopolitics are almost ALWAYS ALWAYS about natural resources, energy being the major one. all the rhetoric about "freedom , democracy,  patriotism, fighting for the oppressed, blah blah blah" is just what governments have to say to motivate their citizens to go murder citizens in other nations

Secondly when it comes to the Middle East it almost always comes down to either Israel versus Arab states Or Sunni versus Shia or some kind of mix between those two.


And Sunni versus Shia is really Saudi Arabia  (backed by the West/US) and their allies versus Iran and their allies

So once you see the Syrian conflict in this lens it makes much more sense.

Overall great post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Sauna use (4x/week) reduced Alzheimer's   dementia risk by 65%. Also reduced risk of heart disease and overall death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cook, tnx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but most of it is very very dishonest

Up to just recently many of these so-called "skeptics" absolutely denied that there was any global warming going on at all. They did the usual obfuscations and cherry picking facts to "prove" there was no global warming.

Then finally the evidence of global warming was so absolutely overwhelming these same "skeptics" suddenly decided that "okay well I guess the earth is warming But people definitely are NOT causing it! Here's some cherry picked facts to prove it!"

These are not skeptics. These are people who have already reached a conclusion and desperately cherry pick facts to back it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay fine but what did you think of the force awakens?

Was it not as good, as good, or much better than that?

PS: I thought force awakens was incredibly average </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hold on! You forgot to accuse somebody of being abusive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> part of it I did actually copy and paste from IMDb

Nevertheless, it is really a good show. Check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting. How much exactly did you make it you don't mind me asking?

I've got some great ideas for some articles, I would like to know how much it's possible to make with this type of thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the mom is just great. Absolutely perfect dead ringer performance. The whole show is really well cast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well if you like her I would be shocked if you didn't like this show. Great show.

Can't believe I'm not hearing more about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Behavior on TNT is an absolutely great show! Moody, involving, great writing, great characters, with plenty of suspense and action. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe the show has float this far under the radar. I'm not hearing any chatter about it all. But let me tell you it's fantastic!

Michelle Dockery, previously seen on Downton Abbey, is an absolute revelation. Perfectly cast as Letty Raines, a thief and con artist who is always one bad decision from implosion. Fresh out of prison, she's attempting to stay afloat. But when she overhears a hit man being hired to kill a man's wife, she sets out to derail the job, sending her on a wild collision course with the killer.

this show is moody, involving, with excellent writing, excellent acting, and plenty of suspenseful action scenes.

I really like that the main character is deeply flawed. This is not a "good guy" who always does the right thing. Rather Lettie is deeply flawed, and yet very very human, and we pull for her despite the fact that she does ssome really really fucked up things.

Seriously, check it out. this is easily TNT's best original show they ever produced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michelle Dockery, Good Behavior

fuck yeah!

Great show!

It's gotten virtually no press and no publicity whatsoever but the show is rocking it! Highly highly recommended. Please check it out because this show needs ratings.

Great characters, great writing, unique and involving. Can't believe it went this far under the radar.if you don't like it I will personally refund the time you spent watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so true!

Jeopardy contestants are heavy on knowledge, but their light on game theory and strategy

So many simply have no idea when it is smart to wager big on the daily double, and when it is smart to play it safe and wager small.

Another thing, too many contestants just throw a half assed guess it a difficult question at the drop of a hat. WTF? If you don't know the answer don't guess! Eight times out of 10 you lose out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> personally I'm a bit fed up with the guy

Doesn't take his weight seriously, spent an entire freaking off-season yammering on about how he was going to lose weight and then he shows up about the same weight as he was before!

Also he takes forever to get the hole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing chafes my undies like elite scientists!

Ensconced in their goldplated mansions, driving around in their Lamborghinis, sniffing high-grade cocaine off of $5000 a night escort asses! and the whole time they've been manufacturing this fake climate change crisis! Just the thought of it burns me up inside!

I hate them so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know what I really like about Christine Michael?

Dude hits the hole QUICK!

Eddie Lacy takes about 43 minutes to get the handoff and actually rumble his way through the initial hole. Don't get me wrong, if he makes it through that hole he is a load and difficult to bring down. But he hits it so damn slow!

I'm fine with bringing Eddie  back, I'm also fine with letting him go, keeping Michael and Monty and drafting a rookie or two

also,  James Starks is toast. We can't have him on the roster next year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but it's because we have a guy at quarterback is just stupidly good.

If the Packers had just an average quarterback over that same amount of time they would not even be an average team they would be a crap team. They would be a 4  12 type team, possibly worse.

The lack of talent at linebacker is just a joke, year after year after year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you

This is actually a really great critique of the Packers front office

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in Green Bay land we call that "doing the Finely"

Also, fuck you J-mike for trashing AR like that couple weeks ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha! Okay there

I think I made an excellent point here. That point being "don't simply tell somebody who got nothing out of therapy to get more therapy. Try to be more helpful than that"

I'm not really interested in your psychoanalysis of my comment history, but thanks for the attempt anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really did not mean to "crucify" you. I'm just pointing out that if you tell somebody who got nothing out of therapy that they need therapy, that's not super helpful.

Perhaps explain WHY or HOW that happened, and how they might get something out of therapy in the future. You see my point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP says

I saw a therapist weekly for about a year and a half, but I got nothing out of it 

so then you advise her

You desperately need therapy

okay well? How about you address the fact that she was in therapy for a good while and it didn't work. Telling somebody who was in therapy for an extensive period of time and got nothing out of it "you need therapy" is not really helpful.

perhaps address  this fact, and explain to her how and why she didn't get anything out of therapy in the first place and how she can actually get something out of it if she chooses to go again.

otherwise it feels like you didn't even really read the OP





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  
 
 
 
 Plus, in an interview, Nolan states "oh, he's dead."

lol, ok then, thats that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Ford created a copy of himself and it was the copy that got shot in the head?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's having an impact on moviemaking technology

That is specifically NOT having an impact on the culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the secondary has been truly atrocious since we lost shields and multiple other players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hate to say it, but the o line looked perfectly decent last night.

Also, Russell is going to pick apart this secondary like the death Star destroying Tatooine. Yesterday I saw all kinds of open wide receivers, and the either drop the ball or Brock overthrew them by 20 yards. That's not going to happen with Russell.

The Packers only chance is to match them point for point

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have anything to back that up? A link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my argument is really really really really really really really really clear

Sad you can't understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so what? Big deal

I'm glad that you feel you are so much better than other people, however that does not give you the right dismiss them as literal human piece of shit

Criticize their ACTIONS and WORDS. Do not dismiss them as human beings


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you just have given up on anybody who's reached the age of 23 and still treats other people inappropriately?

Very sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's sad that you and others would actually support this concept.

Maybe when you look in the mirror you see a piece of shit and now you feel the need to project that onto other people? I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well guess what?

Sometimes 23-year-old guys also have had bad parenting and don't understand boundaries

Dismissing people as pieces of human shit, says more about you than it does about them, as I said before.

also, since you seem to be on board with this, at exactly what age can we start calling people human pieces of shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> regardless. I don't think we should be calling other people human pieces of shit

How is that constructive or helpful in any way shape or form?

What if somebody posted about their boyfriends six-year-old ddaughter acting inappropriate and I called the little girl a piece of shit? Would that be okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend is a piece of shit

one thing I don't understand about this sub is how quickly people are to label other people literal "pieces of shit". I see here quite often.

Almost all the time it's a man. In fact if you try to use the words b---- or c--- your post will get automatically deleted. But somehow it's okay to run around calling men pieces of shit because they're acting grossly inappropriate in a relationship.

This guy is 23 years old. He's young, stupid, inappropriate, offensive, and just plain wrong. But you know what? People can change. They can grow. Don't get me wrong, OP probably should break up with this guy.

But when you throw people away by calling them human pieces of shit, not only are you breaking the rules of this sub Reddit, you're being incredibly judgmental and dismissive and not giving people room to improve.

So please use other language. I don't think this language is constructive in any way shape or form,and it also says quite a bit about the people using it.

criticize people ACTIONS and WORDS. Don't dismiss them as human beings

EDIT: I love it! Bring on the down votes. 100% stand behind this post even if it gets downloaded straight to Hades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 19:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you are going to eat at Buffalo wild wings, ONLY get the chicken.

All of the other food is overpriced, completely generic, and totally not worth it. I mean honestly how hard is it to make a good quality burger anyway?





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At what point does accepting this because it was the legal outcome become outweighed by our moral obligation to protect the people around us?

you want a real answer?

The real answer is When it affects their pocketbooks. When the economy takes a dive and suddenly people will be like "golly Gee! This man is not a good president!"

And then suddenly they will get outraged at all of the outrageous shit he is constantly doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a bunch of horse shit

The purpose of talking to the media is that if you spout total and complete BS, somebody in the media is supposed to say "yes but Mr. Pres.! What about XYZ? How can you say ABC when clearly"

The press SERVES a FUNCTION! Donald Trump sitting on his golden throne in Trump Tower tweeting cannot substitute for holding it freaking press conference

Not to mention the Republicans were throwing fits about how few times Hillary held a press conference. Then again, I guess it's only bad when Hillary does it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have ever encountered a person truly in need, and you gave to that person with pure intent, you conveyed unconditional love that person Then you have met Jesus

The King will reply, Truly I tell you, whatever you did for one of the least of these brothers and sisters of mine, you did for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it's just so pointless

Two really talented people now are dead because of what? Because of ego? Because of arrogance? Because of the infatuation with violence?

so many YouTube commenters praising this song like it's the greatest thing ever. This song helps to end an era of hip-hop, and usher in the new corporate safe hip-hop were all stuck with now

Oh well I guess
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so what you're saying is you don't really know how bad it could get. You fully acknowledge climate change could be utterly  destructive and devastating to modern civilization, and caused millions and millions of deaths. You acknowledge that is a possibility, while also acknowledging maybe that won't happen But maybe it will.

And yet you think anybody who was concerned enough to be scared is part of some kind of bizarre cult

Sorry, but I cannot agree with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> consequence free?

Is it though? Is it really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Westworld is so far beyond a cartoon videogame it is not even funny

Which is kind of the point of the show I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes because at one point he actually was

When sitton lang and beluga whale were all playing it all pro levels he was definitely the weak link

But he just kept improving year after year and now he's rocking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the way he treats the hosts might not be a direct analogue to how he treats people, because he clearly doesn't think that hosts are people.

No, how he treats hosts is how he would like to treat people but he can't because there are things like laws and police.  He's legitimately a bad person in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the heck, even some fat would not hurt! LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Challenging situation! But also a learning opportunity 

I find when you are dealing like people like this, the Bible is your best friend. Logic, reason, appeal to their good side etc. doesn't work for the most part.

So you need to go in armed with multiple Bible verses. Not Bible verses that say "you are wrong, I am right here's why according to the Bible", no. Rather memorize a few Bible verses that encourage them to communicate in a healthy loving manner.

_________________________________________

 Ephesians 5:4 Let there be no filthiness nor foolish talk nor crude joking, which are out of place, but instead let there be thanksgiving. 

Ephesians 4:15  Instead, speaking the truth in love, we will grow to become in every respect the mature body of him who is the head, that is, Christ.

Ephesians 4:32
Be kind to one another, tenderhearted, forgiving one another, as God in Christ forgave you

Proverbs 16:24
Gracious words are like a honeycomb, sweetness to the soul and health to the body. 

_______________________________

For instance you could say "uncle  _______ the word tells us in Ephesians chapter 4 'Be kind to one another, tenderhearted, forgiving one another, as God in Christ forgave you'. have you forgiven these people you are complaining about right now? if not Why not? can you talk about them in a tenderhearted manner as Paul implores us to?"

Never say "you are wrong because of XYZ" it just won't work. Use the Bible to convict them in their hearts while remaining as neutral as you can emotionally
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spriggs is playing just as well as bakh did in his rookie year.

He just needs to put on some muscle mass, and learn how to deal with the bulrushes. He's going to be good  I have a feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this guy seems confused

You are supposed to have your BEST season during your contract year, sign a big fat contract, then fall off a cliff.

I guess he didn't get the memo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he makes a lot of sense for a man who secretly bombed Cambodia and helped pol pot rise to power. A man who would go on to murder millions and millions of his own citizens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this sounds disturbingly like what all of those ultra right wing Breitbart-reading Trump supporters say about the "liberal media"

I'm not even kidding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  so it's not like he can turn back time 100 years and our cities will be chocked with black soot again.

actually yes he can
http://www.cleveland.com/weather/blog/index.ssf/2016/11/trump_chooses_top_climate_skep.html

so he chose a climate denier, a person who is enthusiastic about destroying our life-giving biosphere, to head up the EPA

This is a person who wants to roll back pollution regulations, enthusiastically.

Trump has said he wants to "clean the air, clean the water" 

Donald Trump is a long time conferred sociopathic liar. Do not pay attention to the lies that lying liars tell, pay attention to what they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 07:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh boy. Highly trained in science AND mathematics?

not bad. Also, how many confirmed kills did you have while being a special ops soldier in Iraq?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
