<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6816</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because those people are more akin to the Pharisees than they are to being Christ-like. Jesus himself flipped out on the Pharisees regularly for focusing too much on "the rules" and missing the entire point of Christianity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expedition* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The list with trucks excluded: https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--aCEo4tm7--/c_fit,fl_progressive,q_80,w_636/qf7biiw1qrkihasayf6y.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Are The Cars That Are Most Likely To Go Over 200,000 Miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point regarding the need for more drivers to pull this off. I would imagine this will be way more feasible once autonomous driving is advanced enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we put more thought into the optimal size for buses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in NYC, I've noticed that the streets as they are, are not optimally designed to accommodate the size and turning radius of buses at all. They accelerate slowly, which slows down traffic behind them, and take very wide turns that causes them to take up a lane and a half in the process.

Since widening all of a city's lanes to accommodate buses would be a huge undertaking, wouldn't it make sense to rethink the optimal design of a city bus? I'm starting to like the design Elon Musk [put forward](https://www.dezeen.com/2016/07/28/elon-musk-vision-autonomous-buses-updated-tesla-master-plan-part-deux/) a few months ago:

 "With the advent of autonomy, it will probably make sense to shrink the size of buses and transition the role of bus driver to that of fleet manager," said Musk. "It would also take people all the way to their destination."
 
 Buses will be completely redesigned to make them use space more efficiently, with central aisles and entrance ways removed. These smaller buses would also help reduce congestion.

In other words, it would make more sense to create buses that have a similar box design that maximizes space utilized by passengers, but on a smaller scale that holds say 10-15 people, rather than the 40+ that a typical city bus holds. Because there's no central aisle, these "buses" would instead open up gullwing style and allow each passenger to sit directly into their seat. 

This would make entry/exit much faster and less cramped, and having a larger number of these smaller buses would mean more frequent service. This kind of bus wouldn't take massive turns and accelerate just as fast as a regular car, especially if its electric, allowing it to move with the flow of traffic much better. 

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
