<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8479</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyyy, I'm looking for feedback on my ["Still Alive" (Mirrors Edge) Future Bass Cover:](https://soundcloud.com/heroplanet/still-alive)
-------------------------------------------------------
FEEDBACK:

[reddiitor101](https://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/5036cr/feedback_thread_august_29/d70z8z3)

[Plumfruit](https://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/5036cr/feedback_thread_august_29/d70zl8p) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 11:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "no"!! this makes me furious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 12:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's OP supposed to ask clever questions if can't event answer his dumb ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had trouble doing this since I was a kid. Is music theory a thing you can learn unconcious/unintended or am I just not as good as I think I am? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 09:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 09:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in this case I think software like MuLab is perfect for just playing around and to find out if producing is something that might be fun to you. Don't expect to be even close to productive for the first several weeks/months (depends on how much time you invest) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 01:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like you're looking for something like [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JMpAgzNTkV0).

I've never used it, but was told it's the best and easiest DAW you can get for free.

But honestly I think if you're not willing to spend money on it, you're not very likely to put in the effort it takes to get some decent results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 12:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to go! I think it's a chill track, but the mix isn't very great. It's missing energy. Also the kick (maybe drums in general) could be a little louder and punchier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 12:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super funky, sounds great over all. Definitely something I would listen to repeatedly. Maybe it's just my headphones but I feel like the snare is missing something in the mid-high section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
