<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9440</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Official Synopsis released a while ago.  Its on [Wiki](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kingsman:_The_Golden_Circle) and IMDB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Good Son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither one of these are Fictional or ran by Julianne Moore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pig Fucker One, I don't remember the name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White Christmas wasn't the pilot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try the second episode.  Most of them aren't like the pig fucker one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got to Media in the book.  Didn't expect Gillian Anderson to play her.  Thats an interesting choice.  I wonder how her Lucille Ball is? She had very specific mannerisms that couldn't be easy to emulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandma has it.  I went over to see her the other day and she told me to get out of her house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3124 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](#s "---Roy---") hasn't been ruined yet.  So at least there is a surprise left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wanted it to be a surprise.  Clearly the CW heads made Amell tweet his return for a ratings spike.  It worked by the way, Manu coming back was huge news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what the movie is about.  There's an American version of the Kingsman called 'The Statesman'.  They have to team up to stop a criminal organization called "The Golden Circle." Channing Tatum is the Colin Firth counterpart and Bridges is the Caine counterpart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : Alan Tudyk (K2S0) improvised the majority of his lines in the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing happened to me Tuesday night.  I fell asleep on my couch and woke up to this show "Crashing" starting on HBO.  I kinda sat up and saw Pete Holmes was in the show.  I loved his talk show so I decided to watch his bit.  Turns out hes the star and it was a marathon.  I watched 4 episodes before I finally went to bed.  1:30am and had to get up at 5:30am for work.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have taken them to Twin Peaks, its better.  Especially on lingerie or bikini week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #YYYEEEEESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to watch several more seconds it gets way better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should look into investing.  Even 3% would be significant.  You won't really miss it once you start and its good to have a nest egg.  Especially since we might not have our Social Security by the time we retire.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McAfee did the same thing.  They wanted to start charging for antivirus subscriptions so they released a virus specifically to force people to upgrade to their new version.  It didn't do anything malicious just made the older version flag it as a virus that couldn't be removed.  When people called for help, they were told to buy the latest version of the software. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 Days after its over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lex made no fucking sense.  He spent the entire movie and months carefully setting up dominoes only to give up his plan *WHILE ITS HAPPENING* and create a stupid monster.  I also have no idea why that wasn't Bizarro.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss the stunt series.  Loved seeing the previs fight scenes with the stunt team.  Hearing how they accomplished some of the shots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](#s "Evil Rip was a lot of fun, though.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does that liquor store look like the DMV?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true though.  This world would be a lot different if we weren't on top of the food chain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Produced by Lorne Michaels.  
Written by two SNL Writers.   
Starring Former and Current SNL Cast Members.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flying Lifeguard : That guy is drowning!  
Lifeguard : Where?  
*Fires gun at drowning man*  
Flying Lifeguard : Uh...  Nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Tits! Flag! Gun! Boat! Horsepower! 
  
ROCK FLAG AND EAAGGGGLLLLLLEEEEEEEEEEEE!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second episode didn't deal with Flashpoint.  It dealt with lies and what Eobard did to fix things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caity Lotz was played by a man in the resurrection scene?  Thats so wierd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Arrow -- Behind the Visual Effects (HD) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better Off Ted.  
  
The Good Guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy Boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Forte is so great on 'Last Man on Earth'](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EXaOjgGRwDw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invest that in a ROTH IRA.  Keeping it in a jar or bank is pointless anymore.  I put 6% of my income in a ROTH and in 4 years its already well over $35,000.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, damn.  My monitor is older and hid the screen from me.  My bad.  Nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Heres a good 1080p source w/ Download](https://m.vporn.com/latin/gianna-nicole-eye-contact/986234/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I read the dev kit had an LED screen on the front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I gather, Season 1 isn't as bad if you binge it. So you could just give Season 1 a shot and see how you feel about it.  Just remember it does get ridiculously better.  That said, I bet if you watch the other shows and are familiar with the universe you should be fine starting with Season 2.  There's a previously on thing that recaps the first season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day the new Ghostbusters started on HBO.  I decided to see what it was like since I didn't have to pay for it.  It was absolutely terrible.  I don't know how Sony allowed that film to be released.  The thing that really got me was how bad the cast was.  I'm pretty sure they cast this movie based on popularity instead of chemistry.  They just didn't work together.  	 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its his attitude.  What he lacks in conventional Superman looks he makes up in spades with his Reeves like Attitude.  I liked him the moment he was on screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet DC forced that look so people couldn't compare him with Cavil.  They have always been terrified of the TV world doing their character better than the films.  Thats why won't allow Batman on TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does Felicity not know who she's talking too?  I really hope she takes an arrow in the leg.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrow.  The final three episodes this year will be probally the best episodes of the entire series.  Something ridiculously amazing is going to happen.  The fact that Oliver apparently is [](#s "getting Slade, Captain Boomerang, Nyssa, Malcolm Merlyn and Roy Harper") to stop Prometheus is just fantastic.  I just cannot wait to see whats going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here is another example on how these event episodes should be longer.  Like the Mr Mxyzptlk episode or Music Meister.  Hell its the same with the other shows.  Arrow's Tortue Episode or The Climb.  Flashpoint.   You can't do these stories in 40min with time removed for BS subplots.  
  
Hell, to further elaborate my point...  Bam Bam came out and said [this fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hgp0rc0Y2yw) was much more elaborate and longer but was cut for time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had a conflict in his schedule, so they had to work around him.  Personally, I like his arch this year.  He'll also be back for Season 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **How to film a climactic moment.**  
  
Be Sam Raimi and spell climatic correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the returning cast members for the finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She accidentally tweets nudes of herself.  So many people follow her for the next accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they have been testing it this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that Raven? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 is the best.  They wrecked 260 cars at the end of that movie.  I think its the current record holder.  
  
Edit : Nope, Transformers 3 is the current record holder at 532.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : She got on Parks and Rec from her audition.  She walked in and basically just stared at Michael Schur.  He was so creeped out he went home and added a character to the script for her. [...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BTn3BIPhMRs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the news today, I really hope she gets decapitated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One little massively important thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY!  THAT PSYCHIC SPACE OCTOPUS WAS FANTASTIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't great, but it was really bad either.  Most of the characters were fun enough to keep you interested.  I personally kept watching specifically because of Sara Lance.  Shes fucking awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Anna looks high maintenance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun -10?  I guess OP never shaved his balls before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, they were trying to start [their own](http://nerdbastards.com/2016/01/12/the-cw-flirts-with-starting-its-own-streaming-service/) paid streaming service. Netflix just basically talked them out of it and gave them bags of cash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Jabronies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CW streaming rights ended.  They wanted to start their own service and Netflix paid them so much it stopped them.  The new deal lets Netflix get the show eight days after it ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legends of Tomorrow Season 2 hits Netflix Tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legends of Tomorrow's first season wasn't great.  They shackled the story to two similar uninteresting baristas and a villain that made no sense.  Most people watched a few episodes and just gave up.   
  
The second season, is one of the most fun TV shows I have ever seen.  They got rid of the dumb hawks, fixed their villain problem and added several new characters that add to the show instead of dragging it down.  Its not only better than Season 1, its better than most of the stuff on the CW.  You really should give it a chance tomorrow.
  
[This is how Season 2 starts.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jA5pSHzhTCI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adrian Chase is Vigilante in the comics.  So naming him Chase and making him Prometheus wasn't obvious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new head of ABC openly hates the show.  But then again ABC is owned by Disney, so who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes not listed on the instagram.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a dragon ball z character farted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do it.  Heres what happened. 
  
[](#s "Dhark planted corn and killed Laurel.  She had secret last disappointing words.  Malcolm lost a hand.  Felicity nuked Havenrock.  Oliver punched Dhark to death.")  
  
Thats it.  Now just start Season 5 and never watch 4.  Just don't do it.  It's the fucking worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres already leaked pictures of fully geared up Deathstroke on set.  
  
Edit : [VERY HEAVY SPOILERS](https://www.instagram.com/p/BSuTt6tgbTN/)  I didn't want to post this because it spoils multiple other characters for the finale.  Not just Deathstroke.  I would suggest you don't open it, save it for the finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and Merlyn.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oliver brings it with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can say "Comma" "Period" "Weird Mexican Question Mark" and it will put them in for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slade's a Wild Card?  I really hope this season ends with Slade planting C4 on Ollie's chest, putting on a cowboy hat and screaming "WILD CARD BITCHES!" as he jumps out of a limo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going back *for* Arrow.  Hes going back *to work with* Arrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DF dude said they took every major engine used by these devs and tested their hardware for bottlenecks.  That's significant.  Based on that statement and what we've seen that would include Rage, Creation, Frostbite, Ubisoft, Unity and Unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bioware Austin, not Edmonton.  Edmonton is the A team as far as im concerned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's lots of stories about Scarlett Johansson.  The most famous one was meeting Benicio Del Toro in an elevator and breaking a fucking bed in his hotel room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes wearing armor and a helmet so Thor can knock it off during the fight.  When you have two gods throwing down, you need something to show the audience who's winning.  
  
Like the Iron Man v Hulk fight.  Remember?  Veronica kept losing shit through out, it showed you who was winning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Gilmore : "HERE!  JUST... WEAR THAT!  LEAVE US ALONE!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone notice Loki is hanging out with Jeff Goldblum?  I guess he whammed Banner somehow to keep him hulked up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several major players at Microsoft are on r/Xboxone.  I think that's why the mods are so goddamn anal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shes my new favorite porn star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.  Which means no three way between Deadpool, Thanos and Death.  Such a bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox owns Death.  She came with the X-Men purchase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder when they filmed it because Benny Cucumberbatch is so hard to lock down they are filming both Avengers with a stand in.  They are going to film him seperately and paste his face on like they did with Scarlet in Ultron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Shia LaBeouf, he convinced Megan Fox that they needed to have sex for their on screen chemistry to work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it only took 3 movies to do him justice.  
  
Although, Cap and Thor teamups in Ultron was fucking incredible.  Hands down the best part of the movie.  Every time those two fought together it was just so great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this Thor movie have such fun and style all of a sudden?  Thor 1 was terrible, and Thor 2 was alright.  I wasn't expecting anything like this.  This is just, wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops.  I thought it was the Badlands dude.  My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dude was the fucking best in Rogue One. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Laurel, it's already been confirmed she's back for the final episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how many months has it been out?    The RRoD took almost a year before it was a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are multiple pictures and tweets.  Its real.  The TV mode overclocks the processor and it heats like your cellphone when you use it too long.  The dock doesn't have proper ventilation and traps the heat next to the device.  Over time this is causing problems.  People are playing Zelda for hours on end in dock mode and the heat is damaging the device.  Warping is just the noticeable issue.  That kind of heat could severely damage the internal components.  The more people use a Switch, the more this problem will show up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and some people's X-Box 360's never Red Ringed, still cost Microsoft Billions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never played it either and am really enjoying it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, keep it out of the dock.  They are melting SD cards and warping.  Some are already dying.  Were on the cusp of another RRoD.  
  
Edit : Look at all the delusional fuckwits downvoting me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a freaking long gif, and its got sound?  Is this some kinda new technology?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would this shit charcoal give the food a hearty poo flavor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else think its wierd there was no Thomas Middleditch? Hes the star of Silicon Valley.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know damn well that their customers love instant gratification.  They release the trailer a few weeks before the show, that way its fresh in peoples mind.  It works better.  Only the really big tentpoles get long advertisement campaigns.  (Daredevil, Stranger Things and House of Cards... etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I snorted a pikachu once.  Woke up 3 days later married to a lamp post in Las Vegas.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that 88% was the peak, and this was unoptimized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's looking more and more likely that Frank will appear in Defenders.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really don't need AA at 4k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : The script was so confusing to Hollywood types that the Wachowski's had to attach blue pages to the front of the script explaining what its about. The confusing nature of the script is how they lost several big name actors including Val Kilmer who was being courted to play Morpheus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Xbox One? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had an unlocked framerate which made the game run terrible.  Also the Xbox One had trouble hitting 30 constantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one is mostly negative space for heat distribution.  This is how the S is 40% smaller.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they ever fix the issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sleeping now, that thing will be waiting for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They went there for the spear not just the blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda want a warped reality version of him yelling about what they did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this tech kick the back of my chair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should do a supercut of him saying 'remarkable'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day I went to history class and the teacher was going to get us to watch some chick flick that had nothing to do with history.  I blurted out "What does this have to do with history?" I intended on just thinking it but somehow it came out of my mouth or was telepathically projected across the classroom.  Anyways, the teacher heard me, shut the movie off and forced us to sit in silence for an hour until the class was over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Terminator he spent 50 Million of his own money building a fully autonomous metal T-800 Robot and fought it for months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So our accounting software should automatically gleam where our employees went for two weeks?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes not directing?  Well there goes my interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the first death scene in Death Proof.  Tarentino should do a horror movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sequel is coming. :o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved him in Walter Mitty.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What network is that on?  I have never heard of Audience Network Series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might be a premium skin. They just showed Reverse Flash and Flash.  Both running on Flash's model.  [Link](https://youtu.be/fYB-lmruF98) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Xbox is back!](https://youtu.be/LaTGrV58wec) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is your favorite season?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im with a service company.  You have to bill the time to the individual work orders.  Its how we turn around and charge the customer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite opening.  Every re-watch im always patiently waiting for Season 2 to start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't going to debut the new Forza game in this venue.  It's being saved for E3.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Project Cars and Just Cause 3 will actually be playable now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24
  
I woke up after a late night of drinking.  Blinds were drawn and I was still achy from helping my buddy move the night before.  Rolled over and grabbed the remote for my TV and started flipping.  I was desperate to find something because I didn't want to get up.  I see Kiefer Sutherland with a gun and think this will work.  Then he says, "We're going to have a big enough firefight that they can see us on the thermal satellite." and I was like "What the fuck is this?" then he starts killing everyone.  Guns, Knifes and general extreme bad assness. It was a marathon of Season 4 and I layed in bed watching it until the finale.  The next day I went to best buy and bought Season 1 and 2 on DVD.  Funnily enough, if it wasn't for the marathon I wouldn't have liked Season 1 and watched any more of it.  Jack doesn't really kill anyone in that season.  He spends most of the time running away.  Jack really isn't Jack until Season 2, which is easily my favorite season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tea Room?!? People have a room just for tea?  Do you store the tea in there or just drink it?  Is there a separate tea storage room?  I'M SO CONFUSED!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head of X-Box said he doesn't like modular consoles, doesn't want the user using a screwdriver or shipping the console with an allen wrench.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its going to be around $500. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they compared it to PC when its not one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cotton candy, sweetie go, let me see the Scorpio!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you know who High Jackman and Patrick Stewart are, you good bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should do Monarch, I want to see Dr Girlfriend in live action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last month I got a bill from my Patella.  $3,500 dollars for a hot tub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of one our old employees that quit in a week.  I had to show her how to do payroll and she instantly said "Wait?  I have to type every single work order number they did? Every week?  There's not a simpler way to do this?" I did the first employee to show her, then I told her to do the next one.  She quit halfway through.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its impressive he did this sans safety wires.  I remember a story about the first Rush Hour.  The insurance people wouldn't let Jackie do his thing and at one point demanded a fake tree for him to climb on.  Jackie agreed so they would leave, then he did the scene anyway behind their backs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are working on a multiplayer shooter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two main characters are literally nobodies. I never said they hired pieces of shit off of the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A specific link... uh... im not sure if I can find it.    Are you wanting a link on the other deals not going through or the Japan thing?  
  
[Japan](http://movieweb.com/marvel-spider-man-movie-song-deal/)  
  
I can't find anything specifically mentioning the other deals but they tried very hard to get him in Avengers 1.  The cameo would have been when Stark falls.  The other mention was Oscorp in the skyline.  Sony outright denied the cameo appearance, they approved Oscorp after ILM locked the skyline FX and at that point it was too late to change it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't targeted towards pre-teens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its sad that I like action shows?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 35. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all bullshit.  
  
a) The Sony/Spider-Man movies stopped because Sony *JAPAN* demanded that they stop dishonoring the character.  They were the ones that proposed the deal.  Sony Pictures would have never done this deal and have denied Marvel negotiations for years.
  
b) The Spider-Man deal was so convoluted and drug out that we almost didn't get Spider-Man in Civil War.  If they didn't push the airport fight all the way in the back of the shoot and actively plan for the character that wasn't guaranteed it wouldn't have happened.  Several producers and people on the crew thought it wouldn't happen in time.
  
c) This is the woman that said, "We will *NEVER* give Spider-Man back to Marvel."  
  
Edit :  
 
d) Michael Keaton almost didn't happen because Sony didn't want to pay for him.  Its rumored that Marvel had to pay for him outside of the deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dudes feet are blue.  fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Red Dead 2, Witcher 3, Halo 5   Forza 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dog : I want too pee on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Booster Gold is off limits, just like Blue Beetle.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I buy Microsoft, they have the best software engineers on the planet.  The developers don't have to make the game run on all three consoles, all they have to do is one and the consoles will automatically scale down or up.  Every single game out right now will *AUTOMATICALLY* work on Scorpio, and just like the BC games they will run better than they do on The One.  This is out of the box functionality.  On top of this, the publishers will be giving out updates that make the games work even better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hud doesn't work, the voice acting is terrible, the facial animations and characters look funny, they reconned their own established universe and all the technical glitches.  I saw all of this in the first few hours of the game, hence "its garbage".  
   
I also wouldn't watch a TV show that killed my DVR or constantly glitched out on me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks ridiculously expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVED this game.  Great storyline.  I also liked the combat mini game of just swinging around beating ass.  Made me feel like Spidey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a difference between thinking and knowing.  I played ME:A on the trial, and it is garbage.  Most of the people who think those shows are garbage haven't actually seen them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand, the asian countries didn't have a big movie theatre demand.  It just wasn't as prominent as it is in the US.  But that has changed and now more movie theatres are opening up over there.  So Hollywood has essentially been exploiting this new naive audience to make easy money off of this unsuspecting group of people.  Also because of the laws in Japan and China they have to specifically fund those movies or they can't get a release.  So on top of exploiting this new audience they aren't even paying for most of the production.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, Season 1 Oliver was a straight up nightmare when he started.  He killed security guards and randos all the time.  People just doing their job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] So... new Villain next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I guess we're getting a new villain next year?  Im kinda sad the Legion of Doom is gone.  They were exactly what this show needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't hire any known actors for the characters like the original trilogy.  This game was made on the cheap and shoved out the door before it was finished and people are still defending it.  Idiots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Microsoft's stance on the Scorpio is that you don't have to rebuy games.  They all work across all platforms.  The 4K stuff could easily be an update.  That said it probally will vary considering publishers and added content.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent 28 hours one weekend bringing our server back from the dead and all my boss said that Monday was "Why are you 10min late this morning?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Max Payne 3.  This weekend I held a gun to my One's head and demanded it play the disc but it knew I was bluffing and just sat there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet like a week ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and not every 360 RRoD'd.  Still cost Microsoft billions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **IT WAS US!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow!  How is Arrow going to top this episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz she dirty.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey look everybody this guy thinks Eobard is dead.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next Video...  
  
Cleanliness.  When slicing a man's throat, make sure you wear a poncho and remove any articles of clothing you can.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
