<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8764</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 07:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Mizzou fan, I don't know where to start. 

Actually, yes I do. 

What if Mizzou hired Bill Self as head coach in 1999 instead of Quin Snyder? The three finalists for that job were Self, Snyder and some guy named John Calipari, who recently got fired from the NBA. Calipari pulled out of consideration at the last minute. 

So many interesting parts to this:

1. Does Mizzou become the top program in the Big 12? Self's track record against Roy Williams makes me think it was possible. Self recruited a lot of guys to Illinois and Mizzou is a pretty similar program in terms of geography. 

2. Who does Illinois hire in 2000? Does Illinois even sniff the Final Four without Self bringing in that talent? Do they somehow find a better coach who stays there for years and years? What if's go both ways. 

3. Who does KU hire in 2003? Help me out here KU fans, but wasn't Self the slam dunk top candidate? Do they find someone who continues to win like Roy did? Do they hire a Matt Doherty/Steve Lavin type that sends that program into the ground? 

4. Where is Self coaching today? While I'm a diehard Mizzou fan, I'm a realist and Mizzou certainly would not be Self's last coaching job. Does he take the Oklahoma State job when Sutton retires? Does he take over at Kentucky or Indiana at some point? Or, oddly enough, maybe North Carolina if Self took Mizzou to a Final Four before 2003? He said in his book that he wouldn't have left for KU if he was offered the job had he been Mizzou's coach. I could maybe see him pull a Pitino and take an NBA job and later be hired by KU if he failed in the NBA. But he certainly would not have replaced Roy. 

I honestly think this is the biggest "what if" of the past 15 years in college basketball consider Self's success at Illinois and KU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 05:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim Anderson

Strength 1: He has a history of winning. Is it in D1? Nope. But he's won a national title and he's won big games at his level. This suggests that he knows basketball and can coach well. That doesn't mean Mizzou will win a title or anything like that, but he has a pedigree of success. 

Strength 2: I think his teams will be a lot smarter than those Frank Haith had. So I think he'll bring some fundamentals back to this team. 

Weakness 1: No D1 experience. Bo Ryan demonstrated that you can go from one level to the next and do well. Still, it's a HUGE question mark and it's why I wasn't so excited about the hiring. 

Weakness 2: I won't say this is a weakness necessarily, but can he recruit enough talent to compete against Kentucky, Florida, Arkansas, ect.? Haith was a good recruiter. Can Anderson and his staff bring in some talent?

_____

Mike Anderson (I'll pick Arkansas as Mizzou's SEC rival in basketball)

Strength 1: Defense. When his team has the right talent, but they can create havoc on defense. 

Strength 2: He's good at stabilizing a program. I know most Mizzou fans don't like him now, but he took over a dumpster fire from Quin Snyder. Anderson did a nice job at making Mizzou respectable again and by all indications, he's a class act and he can recruit well. He's a good "Face of the Program" type and I think Arkansas will get good again. 

Weakness 1: He's stubborn as hell. I loved the guy, but if he's coaching against a team with better athletes, he gets rolled all the time and will not adjust from his system. See what Bill Self and KU did to him most years when Mike as Mizzou. He's not great at adjusting his defense.

Weakness 2: His half court offenses were average to below average most years at Mizzou and whenever I watch Arkansas play, they seem to struggle there too.  

That said, I still respect the job he did at Mizzou and thankful he coached there. Now Kim Anderson has to clean up a bit from the Haith Era . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 03:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to Melo. He helped Denver climb out of the NBA hole and his trade helped stock Denver for a few winning seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 03:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a sneaky suspicion Sanchez will do well. He helped take the Jets to two straight AFC Championship games. His quarterback rating in the playoffs is a very respectable 94.0. He outplayed Tom Brady in the Division Playoff Round. I also think Chip Kelly is someone who's very good at getting the best out of his offensive talent. He's familiar with Sanchez since both were in the Pac 10. 

If you were to compare situations, I'd take the Eagles over the Cowboys when it comes to back-up quarterbacks. Philly will be OK I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 00:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 00:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never thought I'd take such joy in watching the Patriots destroy a team, but I am today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 23:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. If you have an opposite opinion than someone else, it makes you a bad person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 23:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've voted for Roberts in the past, but I've never seen a political candidate more desperate than he is this year. He did some sleazy things in the GOP primary, though his opponent didn't help himself either. He's brought in every major Republican in to campaign for him, which is bizarre in red-state Kansas, as the election is usually wrapped up in the summer. It wouldn't surprise me if this scenario is the way it really happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 23:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to give one Mizzou related one and one CFB related:

- For Mizzou, last year's game against South Carolina. Even with the loss in the SECG, they're probably going to a BCS bowl if they finished the regular season undefeated. That was a kick in the balls loss. Mizzou had a handful of chances to put that game away and it failed. Credit to Connor Shaw's gutsy performance. 

- General, I'll say K-State losing to Texas A M in the 1998 Big 12 championship game. K-State's a rival, but even I felt sick for them after that game. A M was down 15 late and somehow came back. If K-State wins that game, I think they handle Tennessee in the national title game and Bill Snyder goes from worst to first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 22:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Georgia 34, Missouri 0
- Missouri 42, Florida 13
- Florida 24, Georgia 7 (so far)

Sports are real dumb sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RAIDERS RELATED: What if the alleged trade that brings John Elway to the Raiders in 1983 wasn't allegedly blocked by Pete Rozell? Are the Raiders still in LA? How about a backfield of Elway and Marcus Allen? Or later, Bo Jackson? Do the Raiders win two more titles in the 1980's or early 1990's? What happens to the Broncos? Elway was in my mind the greatest quarterback ever. Forget the Tuck Rule: That's a huge WHAT IF for the Raiders.

REST OF THE LEAGUE: What if Jimmy Johnson and Jerry Jones would have worked out their issues and stayed together with the Cowboys? I know Barry Switzer won the Super Bowl a few years later with that team, but I think that team wins five or six Super Bowls in the 1990's if Jimmy was still there. Along with being a better coach, I think Jimmy would have done a great job in drafting and trading for talent to keep that team going a few extra years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 22:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This...and the fact he's the DH and he played just four games in the World Series. It doesn't make sense to pay someone 12.5 million as a DH. Just my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 08:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not taking anything away from Bochy. He's going to the Hall of Fame because of the three rings he won. 

I think baseball managers are very overrated. The Royals were two more runs away from making Ned Yost a World Series champion. Baseball depends on players more than any sport in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 08:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in Kansas City so I've always been a Royals fan.  While in my early teens, I lived in Colorado. During that time, the Rockies came, so I adopted them as my "NL team." It was an easy decision, though I kept track of the Royals via the Internet. 

If they ever played in the World Series, I'd root for the Royals to sweep the Rockies. But I pulled for the Rockies hard in 2007 when they made their run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 08:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disappointed they didn't win, but I'm not in pain over the series loss. The Royals ran into literally the best pitcher in World Series history and settled on one of the best defensive plays in Game 7 history. 

It's not like the series was decided on a Bill Buckner play. The bullpen didn't blow a lead in Game 7. There was no choke job. There was no weird fluky stuff like Steve Bartman or Bucky Dent. 

The Giants were a pinch better than the Royals. If they played 10 times, I think they'd split them. Unfortunately, there are only seven games and the team with the best pitcher won. 

I can't lose too much sleep over this loss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 08:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Madison Bumgarner is warming up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 04:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talent wise, the 1989-90 team. Accomplishment wise, the 1993-94 team. My personal favorite was the 08-09 team. They won the Big 12 conference title and their win over Memphis in the Sweet 16 was probably the program's single best performance ever. That Memphis team was loaded and Mizzou just blitzed them that night. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 04:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1997 and 2008 teams were the best I've seen as a Mizzou fan. Beating KU in '97 was one of the most inexplicable wins I've seen a Mizzou sports team pull off. 

The 2008 team had a lot more depth at the guard position. I think that's why they won it all that year and not in 1997.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 00:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like the NFL version of Gregg Popovich. You really do your best to not like him.....but you end up liking him anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 00:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know if anyone here watches the NBA, but it reminds me when the Pistons fired Rick Carlisle in order to hire Larry Brown. Carlisle had done a pretty good job there. 

But Larry Brown was Larry Brown....and the Pistons won the title his first year there and would have won a second title if Robert Horry did not exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 00:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 00:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I like Ned as a person and I think the players get along with him. But good lord were his decisions bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 00:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least the Cubs young prospects aren't pitchers. He won't murder their arms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 20:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The silver lining here for Renteria is at least he'll get paid for the remaining two years. 

I don't blame the Cubs one bit for doing this. Hell, my team's manager just made the World Series and I'd be tempted to do the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 10:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention Nefi Perez for Jermaine freaking Dye earlier in that decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 09:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, technology allows you to follow the game a lot easier today than even five years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 08:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He made great trades and with a little luck and a little health, the A's would have made a strong playoff run. You can still be a fan of what he did even if the A's stumbled a bit. They were the right moves at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dan Duquette. The Nelson Cruz signing was huge for the Orioles and Andrew Miller was great for the Orioles after they traded for him. They won the division this year and were a handful of runs away from winning the pennant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 04:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously no guarantee, but here's what I do:

1. Let Shields and Butler walk. I appreciate James Shields and what he did to help transform the culture. But the Royals are a small market team and I wouldn't give a 33-year-old pitcher a $100 million deal. I wish him well, but the Royals need to be thrifty with the $30 million they'll have to spend. Plus, I think a healthy Duffy and a more experienced Ventura would help fill the gap. Add in Vargas and Guthrie and you have most of the starting rotation from this year.

2. Make a run at a right fielder. They've mentioned Torii Hunter, but I'd prefer Michael Cuddyer. He's hit reasonably well at The K, averaging .280 with 13 homers in 58 games. Cuddyer wouldn't be a big, big bat. But he'd be a nice position upgrade. And I'd prefer him over Hunter due to age. 

3. Look for another starter somewhere. Maybe a Brandon McCarthy? Don't know. 

4. Look for a decent back-up catcher. Salvy Perez needs a reliable back-up after this year. 

I know there's buzz about trading one of the members of the HYDRA bullpen, but I'd wait for the trade deadline. If the Royals are struggling badly, then swing a deal. However, that bullpen is too good to break-up until it needs to be. It needs to be a Godfather like offer to move any of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 04:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Welcome to the Worst World Series Ever." ---- ESPN.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 21:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be my choice if I were him. Going to the American League would allow him to be a DH when he gets older. He's already won three titles with the Giants and why not cash in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even as a Royals fan, I definitely understand your point. However, I believe both the Giants and the Royals were built for the postseason and deserved to be there in the end. 

Bumgardner is literally the best World Series pitcher ever and a short-game series allows the Giants to use him more. The Royals' bullpen this year was the most dominant baseball has seen in a long time. It almost was enough to win the World Series. 

The postseason allows teams to shorten their pitching staffs, meaning the fourth and fifth best pitchers of the staff don't start unless there are injuries. I imagine teams with a great regular season record had fun when teams threw out their fourth or fifth best starters. 

Plus, the Royals won 102 games in 1977 and failed to make the World Series. They won 97 games in 1980 and failed to win the World Series. Weird things happen in October and I'm not apologizing that the Royals made it in the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look out, MJ....he has drones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 19:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should give him all four wins just to be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you like it! There are some old games on YouTube, including Game 6 and Game 7 of the 1985 World Series....games I've watched over the past few weeks for obvious reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rooted hard for him to get a ring in 2002 and 2003. It's almost unfair the Giants have won three after he retired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As unpopular as it is to say in Kansas City, I'm still not quite sure on Moore either. I think he's a decent GM that's been a little bit lucky. Wade Davis was terrible early on and then he morphed into Mariano Rivera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest play of the series. Royals had all the momentum at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I disagree with the decision to send Gordon. He's out by 20 feet if the third base coach sends him. I do think Gordon scores if he hustles, but it's hard to blame him too much.

2. Perez had bad swings all year. See the Wild Card game. Even his game winning hit was ugly. I don't think him getting hit was a factor in the final result.

3. Hard to know. You could make an argument either way about the Royals making a comeback. Either way, Bochy made the right and even if the Royals tied it, it was the right call.

My big what if of Game 7 is the double play. If the Royals took the lead, I think they win. My big what if of the series is if Duffy was fully healthy. The Giants were missing Cain, so it balanced. But Duffy was the best starter ERA wise this year and perhaps Game 4 or Game 7 goes differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 08:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That double play was the biggest play of the game. If the Royals get the lead, I think they hold on and win it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 05:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, since Watson is from Kansas City, that's a GREAT comparison to this series and the run the Royals had.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 05:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never gotten the Cardinal hate. There are some annoying Cardinals fans, but all fan bases have annoying Cardinals fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 05:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the laugh, AL Central Bro. I needed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 04:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to all the Giants fans here. Your team is a class act and while I hate losing in the World Series, at least it's to a class organization. 

This was the greatest month of my life as a sports fan. I'm still very proud of this team and it made baseball fun this year for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 01:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Royals are up big in the late innings, it's happening. And it should.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that nothing's a guarantee. 

But when you add one of the top three or four managers in the game to a great front office, a big market and a lot of young talent, I can see why Cubs fans are delirious right now. 

I felt the same way about Dayton Moore's hiring, though that took some time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And possibly James Shields. Or Max Scherzer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To resemble the Yankees, you can spend $200 million a year like they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 00:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats, Cubbies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it's 2001. Randy Johnson, Curt Schilling, Roger Clemens and Mariano Rivera all pitched in the game. Soriano hit a home run that appeared to win the game, only to see Rivera blow the save.

For history purposes, 1955 also comes to mind as Brooklyn finally won a title. Sad they left two years later but at least they won it all before leaving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 20:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The earlier, the better. That means Hudson got shelled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think both teams come out swinging tonight and the game is higher scoring than most think. I think it'll be an 8-6 type of game.

I'm not sure who gets the 8. Guthrie has been performing very well as of late but he still makes me nervous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 19:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need to know about the NCAA and the folks who run things in college football: Reggie Bush was stripped of his Heisman, while O.J. Simpson was allowed to keep his. I know the Heisman Trust was the group that officially vacated the trophy, but that says a lot about the college football world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 07:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - 2001 World Series. Fantastic World Series that featured drama and a lot of Hall of Famers performing like Hall of Famers. 

- 2003/04 ALCS. Both of these series were fantastic and it's almost a shame that the 04 series overshadowed the '03. Great series featuring the best rivalry in the sport. 

- 2004 NLCS. The '04 ALCS also overshadowed this great series between the Astros and the Cardinals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 07:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this one. Not to sound too corny, but that World Series helped me move on a bit from the events of September 11th. That was a great World Series and the games in Yankee Stadium were incredible. 

It's the one time I wish the Yankees would have won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Giants were playing any other team in the World Series, I'd root for this scenario to work in a big way. Would be a great redemption story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take it! He's gotten his big hits in bunches this year and hopefully it carries into tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 00:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humble pie, Hitler.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 07:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching/reading interviews about Roy, part of me thinks that he wishes he never left KU. I think if it wasn't for restoring Dean Smith's program, he would have stayed at KU. 

That said, it's been a win-win for both schools. Carolina returned to the top and Self has done historic things in Lawrence. One more national title and he may go down as the best ever at KU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 05:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....you talk to your nephew about how great Michael Jordan, Magic Johnson and Larry Bird were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's either him or someone from the Royals bullpen at this point if the Royals comeback. I'm not sure if there's a hitter who deserves it at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tip of the hat to Bumgarner. Hell of a performance that solidifies him as one of the best postseason pitchers ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 01:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barring a scenario in the Raiders somehow getting Jim Harbaugh, I think he'd be the best possible hire. High profile name and he turned around the Raiders once. I know his time in Tampa Bay ended on a bad note, but he did get them over the top. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 08:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Richt has lost control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 07:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree with you about the Saints. I thought that was the best team of the Brees/Payton era but Alex Smith just went nuts on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 07:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish ESPN would make a 30-for-30 about those early 1990's Dallas Cowboy teams. Good lord I bet there are A LOT of great stories about that team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 07:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked the Nets to win the East before the season started last year. Even with Kidd coaching, I really liked the veterans they had and I believed they could have squeezed out one good run together. 

Oops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 06:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of this point, I"m not sure Mizzou has anyone they can put on the block. Can we wait for the theoretical trade deadline? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 06:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish him the best and hope he's healthy so he could scare the crap out of me each time he's at bat against the Royals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 04:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree 100 percent with this. A lot of NFL/NCAA coaches have called a play in that situation over the years. 

The blame is Bo Wallace's and only Bo Wallace's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 04:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree about the delay of game penalty. That's inexcusable. 

I do agree with the decision to run a quick play with nine seconds left. I've seen a lot of NFL, NCAA and even a few high school coaches call a play in that situation and have it work. The blame on the final play is Bo Wallace's. A 47-yard field goal in arguably the toughest stadium in America is a tough get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 23:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll also say that if this was happening to Kentucky, I'd bet my life's savings that John Calipari would not be getting the same free pass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 23:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry....but after the way Joe Paterno looked the other way on the Penn State scandal, I'm giving no coach the benefit of the doubt any more. If evidence comes to light that shows Roy is innocent, than he is innocent in my mind. If evidence shows that he's guilty and took part in this, he's guilty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 22:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notre Dame let its grass grow in the stadium the week of the USC game when Reggie Bush was there. It was thought the longer grass would hurt Bush, but USC still won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 21:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. I don't know how Yankees, Cardinals, Tigers, Angels or Red Sox fans can deal with this. And like you, I had a bad feeling entering the 9th inning. Glad I was wrong. 

As for the game, the Royals have a great opportunity tonight. Here's hoping they're loose and they have fun while on the field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 07:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops...meant 2003 World Series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 07:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before it started, the two World Series doppelgangers I thought this series could turn out like is the 2003 World Series or the 2007 World Series. 

The 2003 World Series, like this one, featured a previous world championship team (Yankees, Giants) and a "What the hell" team (Marlins, Royals) that ended with the younger and unexpected team winning the title. I know there wasn't a Bartman situation for the Royals, but that Marlins team had a lot of comeback wins, late-inning victories, timely hitting, great defense and a couple fluky breaks like this Royals team has. 

The 2007 World Series had a similar storyline, except this time the Cinderella was overwhelmed by the more experienced and better team. Admittedly, I had a flashback to the 2007 World Series after Game 1. 

There's still a long way to go. The way this postseason has gone, I wouldn't be surprised by any outcome at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 00:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sox went from dead last to championship in 2013. The Royals have made the World Series after being a joke for nearly 30 years. 

Why not the Cubbies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 23:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't happen, but I wish Brooklyn would get a team back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 06:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, let me say that behind the Kansas City Royals, Missouri basketball is my favorite team. I like them more than Mizzou's football team even with Pinkel's successful 15 years. 

I agree with you about the arena. I loathe that place. I don't get how Mizzou's record has been so great there the past five years. There's little energy in that building and I miss Hearnes. 

That said, here's mine: The "Norm Stewart was God" segment of the fan base. Norm is a genuinely nice man and I'm thankful for his time. But some fans think he was the greatest coach ever. Let the record show he never made the Final Four and he had his share of tournament flame outs. Norm would be the fifth best coach at KU with that record. 

While I'm warming up to the Kim Anderson hire, the fact he was #1 on so many fans' lists (at least here in Kansas City) was depressing, especially with Howland, Gregg Marshall, ect. out there. 

Remember Norm fondly. He had a good run at Mizzou. But he wasn't John Wooden or Bear Bryant. Let's not look back to the past when we're looking to the future. I wish Kim Anderson well, but if he wasn't a Norm Guy, he doesn't get that job.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 04:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal Foul, for being mean. 15-yard penalty. 

Automatic first down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to the two-minute drill, he's the second best Broncos quarterback ever. Sorry, but I'll still take Elway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't be too surprised that Denver got that call in Mile High.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but so what? Usually teams in the Midwest don't get a homer on TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
