<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7184</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came to say this.  It's so weird how you just know, but you do.  Something about the intensity or, idk...you just know.  And if it's just being off a bit b/c of the ear infection, it will eventually go back to normal :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wait, wtf, somehow this was your fault?  B/c otherwise, wouldn't the other driver have to pay for you?  I'm sorry, I haven't been driving that long so I'm not sure how these things work, and I know they vary from state to state, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sylvinis is just so great and powerful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really cool.  I can't wait to see what other changes they are going to make.  (For Shaman!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be too low/high to queue for instances, but maybe you can get a group of friends to run it with you a couple of times to get the requirements you need.  Or, you can do a couple of quests or buy some gear on the AH.

I've never not had this problem when leveling, unfortunately.  Especially, I think, b/c I use the heirloom gear and that ilvl isn't always comparable to the gear that actually drops out of instances, even if it is "better."  Usually I get stuck around MoP though.

Good luck, though!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even know he had a daughter _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was nice of someone :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they are minimums anymore.  Just "get what you can" and the only way to min/max your character is to frequently Sim yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, what about emersion?  Don't all of your characters deserve to feel it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can level really quickly w/ instances, once you unlock that feature.  But yes, questing until then is the quickest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mods of this forum gifted me with the  symbol.  I like to think it's b/c I'm dangerous, but it might also be b/c I'm usually nice until I get hungry.  We may never know ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For breakfast (it's prob my fav meal of the day) I like scrambled eggs with some kind of veggie combo of mushrooms, onions, asparagus.  For lunch I usually make a salad - lettuce, onions, carrots, celery, mushrooms, some kind of meat, oil   vinegar for dressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mods of this forum have granted me this magical sign.  I like to think it's b/c I'm Savage   Dangerous AF.  Or possibly b/c I'm usually peaceful until I get hungry.  One will never know ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had very bad migraines for the first week I when I re-started.  It was b/c I was not taking my potassium and magnesium supplements, and I had no idea until I went to the dr ._.  So, I would start there, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations!!

Based on the info you provided, your BMI is 30.25, which means you are super close to not being obese anymore!!  It's a wonderful feeling to get there.  Though honestly I think clothes fitting super lose is even better!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg this is so adorable =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SV] Lost 35 Lbs!!! (  My Intro - AMA!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

I am new here.  Just found this sub and I've been lurking for a week or so.  I started doing a keto diet in April of last year.  I've gone from super strict to kind of loosely following it and back to strict again, and in that time, as of today, I have officially lost 36 lbs!!  It's amazing, and I'm thinner in a way I never have been before.  Though I have weighed less in the past, my measurements are much different!  It's shocking and amazing.

I started my journey doing Transformation 360.  I had no idea that it was actually a "thing" outside of that program until my husband saw my success, wanted to join in, then found and told me about this sub.  I'm really looking forward to reading more and getting some ideas about different things to eat.

Thank you for this community, and for allowing me to be a part of it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeahhhh this was me on Monday, too.  Worth it but not.  Crazy how you "evolve" into this way of eating vs the old way, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded the app and I'm excited to try it out.  I've been looking for something like this, b/c I'm getting tired of eating the same foods all the time!!  Looking to be creative! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I will buy that.  It's probably really stressful being in that situation.  I know I wouldn't be able to handle it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pieces of shit that kicked me out of the house when I refused to kill my grandpa so that they could get what he left for them. The ones that refused to give me a single cent when I called them and told them I was starving.

But, the previous story said
Im homeless because I was a stubborn twenty-year-old trying to make it out on my own. I had family waiting for me back home, but I wasnt ready to crawl back to my family yet. Like I said, Im a stubborn guy. I would rather die than beg my parents to take me back.

So I'm really confused :/  Have you gone crazy, OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swore up and down that I was not going to cosleep.  Yeah.  That goes right out the window at 7am and you haven't had more than 2 hours of uninterrupted sleep in a week.  Good luck, mama.  I swear it gets better, even though hearing that doesn't help you right now in the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I kind of think it's slightly rude not to invite you.  I've done almost the same thing with my mother several times (she will pay the entry fee and for a couple of extra cards) and when I've won and she didn't, I at least paid her back the $ she spent on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow times sure have changed from when I was playing the sports at a young age.  We used to have 1 child's parent orange slices per game.   That was it.  We even had to bring our own water/Gatorade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf.  I just don't understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should have your own separate checking account where your $$ gets direct deposited, and then you move the money for bills into your joint account b/c you're responsible.  He should have his directly deposited into your joint account.  It's not fair to you that he bascially has free reign over your money.  (Well, seemingly free reign b/c he keeps just spending and spending w/o a care in the world.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Nooooooooooooooo!"*

I'm sorry, BabySpawn, but you can't roll off the changing table.  It's generally frowned upon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!!!  Also post a photo of that shawl when you're done :d  I'm the world's laziest knitter.  I start 1,000 projects and I have finished 4 in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to say this.  Some religions even say that you are entitled to sex with your wife simply b/c she is your wife and that's her duty as a mate.  Smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I usually try to make coffee without adding grounds at all.  Spoiler alert - that doesn't work xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're not sure he'd tell you the truth if you directly asked him what if you asked him in a roundabout kind of way?  "Honey I was thinking of changing the way we eat, trying to be more healthy.  What do you think of me trying out this *insert meal here that you don't normally cook* for dinner?"  See how he reacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer, I obviously don't know your relationship.

But, I will say that we have made a "schedule" to fit in sexy time b/c we're both so busy with our hobbies, family, job.  We need to do it b/c right now it's hard to be spontaneous with a toddler xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really thought about this until you said something, and I agree with you!  Just something to make it more "real!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really cool :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WoW is what you make of it.  Your story begins when you first create your first toon, and you level him.  Most players will be working on max level things, yes, but you may find some value in going back and running older content for transmog gear, achievements, pets, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !Remind Me 6 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just when you thought you got out -- They pull you back in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an answer I pray I never find out.  I will probably weep salty tears when I see the ~~days~~ years I've sunk into this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the fire gives him a buff in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long was the time in between your drops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In theory, you'd encounter less players while questing and whatnot, but I believe most zones have cross-overs now so it doesn't really matter.  I was leveling a new alt last week and I saw several people from many different realms in the starting zone.  (And no, my server wasn't merged with another.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how does one get you nominated for President of the World? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has to use turn signals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay thank you for your time!  I'm thinking I will rewrite the last bit, maybe elaborate with what he actually does to each coworker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, It's a "Non-Story" and Idk Why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will pretend that I understand what you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I always think the same.  It's true xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing you can do is SIM yourself.  In my case, sometimes the lower ilvl item is better than the higher one.  I usually keep both items in my bags, though, b/c you really should re-SIM every couple of ilvls or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this struggle T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am generally never a bully or jackass to anyone b/c I like to think I'm a decent human being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that sounds fun :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be totally honest.  I would like to see more "slut-mog" tier.  I don't like how covered up my tier has been lately.  (Yes, yes, I know I can xmog it, but that's not the point.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg this is one of the greatest things I've seen on here.  I'm laughing so hard right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Just Accept Me - I Don't Want to Be Alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo, plot twist, my WoW toon is also named Pebck ;)

Do you still play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok.  So, does he like video games or something like that?  You could treat his homework like a quest.  "Turn in Assignment A and receive insert a small, desired bribe here - Fail, and lose privilege here for x amount of time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, can you send me a referral?  (If they have that sort of thing, idk.)  Also, I love your UN :D

PS - I had 1 pair of leggings that ripped after 1 wash.  I contacted LLR directly and they were actually very nice.  So maybe they've lived and learned.  Idk, I am not totally drinking to Kool-Aid on that one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on your weight loss and your confidence!!  That's just a great feeling.  I wish you more success and happiness on your journey!!

As far as Lularoe, I hated it -- at first.  I thought all of the patterns were ugly (  this is coming from someone who has a very unique and funky style sense) - UNTIL ONE DAY I found a pair of Space Invader leggings.  WELL, now it's my personal quest to find all the leggings like that xD

I don't like/wear any of the other options, but some of them are cute.  Actually in one of the groups I'm in shows one of the dress-things as work-wear.  I guess it's all in how you accessorize lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he doesn't feel challenged enough and he's bored, so he's skipping it.  It's just odd that he's only skipping that 1 specific class and none of the others...have you asked him why?  Maybe something is up with that class/teacher/a student.  It's a hard time, being 13.  (I think.  It's been a while :P) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it will be a few days to a week of adjustment.  BabySpawn would look for his nighttime bottle as I was putting him down.  (This was the last bottle to go.)  Eventually it worked itself out and he didn't cry when I put him down in the crib. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well sure, but everyone's situation is different.  Some weeks I couldn't swing it, but most I could :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors, tell me your "luckiest" stories - What is the most improbably yet amazing thing that happened to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This creepy coworker of mine who looks rotten and has a personality to match.  Ugh, plz don't even look at me or speak to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I entered a female-only beer chugging contest and I finished my glass first without spilling the entire thing down the front of my shirt (like everyone else did). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to save 20% of your paycheck in a savings account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defenestration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're flying for business, you might be more likely to go for the "first class" upgrade since you're probably not flying on your own dime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write underappreciated stories for /r/NoSleep
xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marshmallows and cheese doodles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AIM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best fashion designer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A picture frame or mug with a photo of Dad   Baby on it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in the day when AOL/AIM Instant Messenger was a very popular thing, I used to create wildly popular buddy icons with a "doll" theme for the masses.  I submitted on Imbum   Iconhell.  I ~~am~~ was PyroPrincess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Innocent people suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're lucky enough to live near your match, you should do it.  I wish I lived close to you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, there are in-game 2 person mounts.  If your friend has one of the flying versions, he could carry you around to do quests together.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so there you go, then.  You only need to suffer through the grind once! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought after 35, chances of complications rose exponentially.  I'm not sure, though, this is just what my dr told me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often wonder if I'd started having kids earlier (in my 20s) if it would have been easier or harder than having them now (in my early 30s) but who can say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say all of the exactly.

My husband wants to help, but unless I give him direct tasks, he kind of...disappears.  Once we both figured this out, things have gotten 1000% better around the house :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're SO mean! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I was thinking of that, too.  He keeps saying he needs new pants b/c he's lost weight but he's pickier than a woman when it comes to these things...AND he doesn't like to go shopping xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GUYS. I AM SO HAPPY. 

This.  Good for you! =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if your friends aren't doing anything with you and are leaving you to play alone, maybe you need new friends :(

Also, there *are* in-game 2 person mounts.  If your friend has one of the flying versions, he could carry you around to do quests together.

As far as alts, I thought flying was cross-account but I might be wrong.  I don't know, as I don't have flying yet, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you also updated all of the files on your computer?  I seem to remember I myself just had a bunch to download over the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awe congrats!!  That's adorable :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you doing when the game freezes?  Are you in a graphicly intensive area or standing by yourself in the middle of nowhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're remotely curious, you should definitely give it a try.  Download the trial version so you won't really be out any $$ if you decide you don't like it.

If you are going to play, you should join Korgath-US and be Alliance.  Then you should send me a PM on Reddit and you can join my guild.  I (along with most other guildmates) would be happy to have you and help you along the way.

Enjoy =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, if a character can use it.  For example if your main wears mail and you have 100 different mail chests, but your alt wears leather, you cannot xmog the leather to look like the mail.  Does that make sense lol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was happening to me whenever I'd try to exit the game.  Not sure why, but I updated all my addons and restarted my computer.  Seemed to fix it.  Might work for you, too.  Sometimes addons get weird randomly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exception would be running these with trusted friends or guildmates.  You *generally* won't fail this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can run instances and PVP if that's your thing.  You don't have to do WQ.  They are kind of like dailies.  I personally like to do the WQ while I queue for instances, since it's usually 20 minutes or more in between pops b/c I'm DPS.

You could also work on fishing, farm herbs or ore, go kill all the rarespawns, collect all the treasures.  So much to do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When BabySpawn is asleep, we both play World of Warcraft together.  While we don't always quest or do instances together, we are sitting side by side on our respective computers and occasionally chatting with each other.  If we aren't doing that, we will generally be watching Star Trek in bed with the lights out.

When BabySpawn is awake, we go for walks, to the park, or out to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, mom who did the helmet stuff here.

Firstly, I'm sure you know that having a flat spot does not in any way harm your son's brain.  He will be just fine that way.  Secondly, if your doctor said there was nothing to worry about, I'm sure he's probably correct.  Ours talked to us b/c it was pretty extremely noticeable.  (Even more so when we saw the "before" and "after" scans when everything was said and done.)  After all of the helmet and therapy we did, it's still not perfect.  We didn't expect it to be, but now it's not noticeable to anyone except us.  And the little it's off now?  Can be disguised with a haircut.  (Or not, b/c that kid has so much freakin' hair.)

Did you ever Google what some flat spots can cause kids to look like?  Sooo...I'm sure you're baby's head is nothing like that :P  And some flat-ness is extremely common these days b/c of the whole "Back to Sleep" campaign.  Additionally, most of that *does* correct itself by the time the kiddo is 3.

You'll be fine, and so will he.  Don't beat yourself up about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he has so much to say, that should write it all down in a journal.  Tell him he could write his stories down in there and maybe one day he'll be famous :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's perfectly fine to travel on your own once you're married.  You are still 2 separate people.  And yes,  I'm perfectly fine with him traveling w/o me, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, last night it was pretty much 50/50. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is and will always be what I think of when I see Maxis.  I still play Sims 2 on occasion.  It's so freakin' awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I used to only charge the customers who were being rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dying xD  I am literally picturing BabySpawn and Doggo.GIF playing tug o' war over a rubber bone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I just ask a question?

Why are the pictures not allowed?  I obviously understand that if there are threats why that's bad.  But.  What if a child took a vid of a teacher and said something like "Omg fav teacher in science class!" or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, see, I think THAT is rude.  And also kind of...interesting...that he had his mom make it for him while there was other food xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to say without knowing his reason for doing this.   But I like to hope that most people aren't total jerks, so I'm going to guess he just doesn't like chowder.  (Which is stupid, bc yum.)

Did you mention you were cooking chowder for dinner beforehand?  If he doesn't like it, I don't think it's rude that he doesn't eat it.

For example, I LOATHE tunafish.  Like, my throat will close off and I will gag and I just can't ew it stinks.  Nope.  Went down the shore w/ best friends.  Said I wanted to go out to eat in front of everyone.  Nobody said anything contrary to this, nobody said they were going to make dinner.  Dinnertime comes, and tuna salad is served.  I cannot even sit at the table b/c I cannot take the smell.  I mumbled an apology, and I left to get my own food.

I guess what I'm saying is maybe it's the same for him and he doesn't want to offend you?  And he thinks he's helping by making (  paying for) his own stuff?

I saw that you mentioned he doesn't clean up well - just flat out say you don't mind if he makes his own food, but just be sure to clean up after himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I have so much to look forward to _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  I worked for those assholes.  They have no Souls.  I would rather light all of my money on fire than bank there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you see Final Destination?  That guy tried to warn everyone, and they thought it was his fault at first that the plane crashed.  It's probably the same idea.  She didn't get on the plane, yet it disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol damn.  Tbh I was slightly concerned but I guess I'll worry about it more when/if it..uhhh...comes out the other end?  xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually came here to say this.  My aunt was scandalized that I was still moving around and cleaning in my 8th month.  But, I mean...plot twist BabySpawn did have his umbilical cord wrapped around his neck 2x sooo...maybe next time I won't be doing moving as much =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so very happy to hear this!  Big hugs to you and your fam :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ...D-did You EAT That? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BabySpawn is teething.  I get that.  He would rather chew on his fingers or blanket than anything else.  Believe me, we've tried to offer lots of other options.  But this morning, we discovered BabySpawn found something ELSE he really likes to chew on - his crib _

Yes, he decided to download his teeth into the natural wood frame and now has taken a noticeable CHUNK out of it (  I guess swallowed the splinters?!)  I tied some cloth around the spot to prevent him from getting to it again (it's only this one spot; I guess it was the most flavourful?) but like, WHAT?

On the plus side, I do feel little bits of tooth coming in on tops and bottoms, so hopefully those molars will be bustin' out soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
