<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7048</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 02:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rusty Axe cuts in 9 hits, just like the Modern Axe. Just checked it today. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 18:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rusty Axe

Or you can put a little more effort and make Crafted Axes which will cut down trees in 9 hits.

Crafted Axe:
Combine
- 1 stick
- 1 rope
- 1 rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It would be interesting if we had certain obstacles that would require building something to proceed with the story (With Examples) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 18:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a wild Forest, the path shouldn't be tidy for a survivor. 
I believe that if we had more interactions with the survival guide besides being a self-protection oriented structure crafting, it would give much more context and realism to the game. 

Like, imagine yourself in a cave, and you need to climb to a higher section, but you don't have a wall for the climbing axe, so the only way to progress would be constructing structures that could take your character up there. 
Or maybe a broken bridge above the abyss, an 90 degrees steep moutain, ...I think you get what I mean.
Adding depth to the crafting tools would give the players more options and versatility, and therefore make the exploration even more fun than it already is.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a Champion that everyone plays, or having one that wins the most? Do we have to answer?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it on NA tho?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major Game Changing Tip: You can close the games faster by clicking where the button appears even before the nexus animation starts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 01:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What finals?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok Thanks Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I remove the Orange nickname? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like brazillian president Dilma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody knows this song name in this LoL video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's contemporary, and not sure about the Youtube audio library. Heard a bunch so far and nothing close to the sounding!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT]I have the song link, but not the name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 02:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has no lyrics, just the melody. Even Shazam couldn't find it. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=06VftHnEwpE

Reminds me of Faux Tales. Still, I don't know if I'll ever find the name. Can you discover it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have the song link, but can't find the name! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=06VftHnEwpE
It's used in this video, but it doesn't gives any information at all. Shazam couldn't find it too. 

Help me!! Reminds me of Final Fantasy, and also Faux Tales (producer). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is Taric tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 07:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best reply I didn't read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 03:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in Summoners Rift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 03:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 02:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orianna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
