<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9117</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers examine the use of antiparasitic drug as new treatment for brain tumors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary: http://www.genengnews.com/gen-news-highlights/method-for-capturing-secreted-cancer-markers-developed/81254181
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rapid magnetic isolation of extracellular vesicles via lipid-based nanoprobes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary: http://www.genengnews.com/gen-news-highlights/viral-hemorrhagic-fever-treatment-developed/81254159
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers develop Marburg virus treatment effective five days after infection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a really great question that unfortunately the authors did not address in this study. Certainly not out of the realm of possibility, based on evidence gathered in the recent years. Since these results are so novel, I don't think the authors wanted to speculate too much on the mechanism of action, but if the data holds up in larger studies I'm certain that will be the next path researchers go down.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary: http://www.genengnews.com/gen-news-highlights/antibiotic-could-aid-in-the-prevention-or-treatment-of-ptsd/81254151 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Common antibiotic may help to prevent or treat PTSD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the pH portion is only within the realm of fiction as the body tightly regulates pH and minor fluctuations can cause serious issues or  even death.
HOWEVER! ;) Malaria was used to treat syphilis. more specifically neuro-syphilis (when the bacteria infects the brain). Julius Wagner-Jauregg won a Nobel prize in 1927 for this, in what was titled Malariotherapy. This technique fell out of favor due to the high death rate associated with it and the development of antibiotics. The theory was briefly resurrected during the height of the AIDS epidemic as it was thought the HIVvirus would bee sensitive to the extremely high fevers associated with malaria parasitic infections...this obviously turned out to not be true. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it would be reasonable to assume that it may work against other parasites that break down heme, such a trypanosomes (African sleeping sickness) and Leishmania...but I'm not sure if it has been tested widely on those organisms as of yet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries ;) I did a lot of research in malaria so  I always love discussing it! Artemisinin actually also works against Schistosoma (blood flukes), which are parasitic flatworms. Unfortunately, the method of action for Artemisinin is still not fully understood, but the most widely held theory is that it somehow interferes with the parasite's ability to break down heme (iron molecule) that it accumulates from digesting blood. This would be consistent with Schistosoma as well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary: http://www.genengnews.com/gen-news-highlights/cancer-targeting-triple-threat-microcapsule-developed/81254128
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers create triple-threat cancer-fighting polymer capsules for guided drug delivery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is mainly used to treat P. falciparum, since parasite drug resistant is highest in that strain. However, ACT (artemisinin combination therapy) has been successful in other parasite strains such as P. vivax.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
