<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8546</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quinoa genome has been sequenced, enabling genetic improvements for cheaper production and increased food security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> moderate drinkers tend to have better wealth, education, physical activity levels and diet.

Maybe I shouldn't be, but I'm shocked studies that didn't control for those things made it past peer review.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's [the study](http://journal.frontiersin.org/article/10.3389/fnhum.2016.00645/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting the line to be funny. Objectively I guess I think it was, but when I got to it I just felt sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children learn math better when physical activity is incorporated into instruction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first reaction too, but after thinking about it, "abusive" covers a range too, a range some of this behavior might fall outside of (especially depending on context). Probably better to use the broader, more inclusive term in this case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah. Not sure what their nerve/pain situation is, but looks brutal. "We suspect that they then seek humid shelter until the regeneration process has at least begun" -- sounds like a gecko burn unit. Can't blame them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [study](https://peerj.com/articles/2955/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New species of gecko that loses and regenerates giant scales is confirmed with 3D imaging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, from a cyclist's perspective, this is also the greatest weakness of human-driven cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perhaps the biggest challenge for self-driving cars to overcome is detecting bicycles. Here's a status report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like human drivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The study cites a correct response rate of 70% for the questions with known answers. Can anybody explain why it didn't work the other 30% of the time? Can this technique ever get to the point of being completely reliable? Or does it depend on the person and what's making them locked-in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's [the study](http://www.nature.com/tp/journal/v7/n1/full/tp2016280a.html). 

Looks like those living in highly polluted areas have 92% greater risk of dementia. And the authors estimate 21% of "accelerated cognitive decline and all-cause dementia" in the US is because of exposure to air pollution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People living in areas with high levels of air pollution are at greater risk of dementia, study of US women finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL people in the Civil War era would squeeze the contents of cowpox pustules into cuts on their arms as a primitive, but effective, vaccine against smallpox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some science is really exciting and probably easy (or at least easier) to get the public excited about. But a lot of smaller, less exciting studies happen to get the state of knowledge to the point where amazing results that make headlines happen. Do you think there's a good way to get the public to understand the importance of funding and protecting this more boring research? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [study](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature21072.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earliest known human ancestor has been discovered, the fossil of tiny sea creature that lived 535 million years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LSD causes brain receptors to fold over like a lid after attaching itself, new study finds. This explains why the drug takes so long to wear off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists create human/pig chimera embryos, getting one step closer to growing human organs in pigs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists create human/pig chimera embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my Slovakian friend: "Easter might not be the best time to visit; that's when we hit women with sticks." I thought he was joking. He was not. Apparently they don't hit them very hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peer review is a critical part of science, so why are women being excluded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Thomas Edison attempted to invent a "spirit phone" to talk to the dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists knit textiles that work like muscles. This could lead to external artificial muscles, worn as clothing for mobility assistance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a professor, but administered a study abroad program. Asked student to email me a copy of her passport. She scans the cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnily enough, this happened at the Japanese embassy in the US. But the stamps from the airport in Japan are straight as an arrow. 

The staple was removed by a border control agent in Switzerland. He gave me a hard time about it. I said I hadn't put it there. He said I should have removed it. Because you're not officially in Switzerland until you've been lectured by a bureaucrat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fecal microbial transplants improve autism behaviors 20-25% in clinical trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bureaucrat stapled documents to this exact spot on my passport. He gets it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Original study](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14142) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans, not climate change, wiped out Australian megafauna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this perspective. I saw this posted in /r/science and came here to see what the neuroscientists were saying about it. As an outsider, I was shocked by how dismissive of the field Kording seems in the [first article](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/should-neuroscientists-trust-methods-that-cant-explain-how-donkey-kong-works) I read about this a few days ago. But I guess if he has a good reputation and respect in the field, he can get away with that and people (at least some/most people) don't take it the wrong way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone working in neuroscience chime in on how this paper has been received in the profession? I've been wondering since I first read about it. These guys seem pretty dismissive of the field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that ants intentionally medicate themselves by consuming toxins to stop fungal infections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other news: water is wet. Just kidding, empirical validation of intuitive results is important, etc, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Female Space Sculptor Who Designed the Earliest Space and Aviation Helmets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [study](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v541/n7637/full/nature20801.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New modeling suggests competing plant/termite theories of Namibian "fairy circles" could both be true. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that in the future, when we understand more about how specific microbes and combinations of bacteria affect our body, that testing the microbiome and curating it with probiotics could be a standard part of a medical check-up? Or is it important for public health that each person have a slightly unique microbiome?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just took a look through Sarah Garfinkel's profile from the link, and I'm guessing they're referring to [this study](https://www.researchgate.net/publication/236073359_What_the_heart_forgets_Cardiac_timing_influences_memory_for_words_and_is_modulated_by_metacognition_and_interoceptive_sensitivity)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see a few of the images they used [here](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms13854/figures/2).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [study](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms13854).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are more likely to perceive black men as a threat in snap-judgements that coincide with heartbeats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study found that children in South Africa and Turkey were the most selfish of the countries they looked at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some inbetweens, e.g. vegetarians who'll only eat eggs if they're cage-free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really the first time though. For example, this pretty creepy [case from 1992](https://www.researchgate.net/publication/26344266_Outbreak_of_vampire_bat_biting_in_a_Venezuelan_village).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Breakthrough in the Search for Alpha Centauri's Planets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the older generations distinction is key. I think this is really changing. They said 95% they surveyed would be happy to share. Even if in practice it's less, it could help.

I once heard one of the scientists who did research on HIV with Robert Gallo (who discovered it and developed a blood test) in the 80s say in a talk that unwillingness to collaborate among labs really slowed progress in that area. BUT, he also said he was very pleased to see a much greater spirit of cooperation in younger scientists, and that makes him optimistic. I hope he's right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An oldie, but a goodie: [Lizzie Borden's parents](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lizzie_Borden).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my elderly mom said she was going gluten-free, because her friends told her that's healthier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why does that "insert" key that deletes your text as you type exist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consensus at work is that it's just annoying, and nobody could think of a way it'd be useful. Is it just a vestigial feature of some sort?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask this whenever I meet someone in a climate change related field, and this is by far the answer I relate to the most. Thanks for being so honest!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, the problem of climate change--especially convincing people to change their behavior--seems kind of hopeless. Do you ever feel this way? What keeps you motivated to keep working on this issue?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [original study](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14014).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study in mice shows how alcohol triggers hunger despite being caloric. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also important: medical applications. The study authors mention nerve regeneration after spinal cord injuries in [this interview](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/spinning-super-strong-synthetic-spider-silk).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really cool. Something this cheap (20 cents) that doesn't require electricity to perform all the important lab functions of a centrifuge could have some really exciting global health benefits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paper centrifuge can separate plasma in under 2 minutes and isolate the malaria parasite in 15. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
