<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9557</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be  in big trouble if we had a WC in town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't wanna feel like a jackass? They are the ones that screwed up your order. You payed your hard earned money and are a paying customer.  if you don't want to be a jackass then just don't be rude when you complain.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can contact them online and they often send you a gift certificate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time i take back food is when they screw up my order.  Which happens more then you think.  I stop going to the KFC here in town. They screwed up 80% of my orders.  Popeye's here is only slightly better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ricky Ross, one of Gary Webb's primary sources had spoken to Gary in the days before his death. Gary told Ricky that he had seen men scaling down the pipes outside his home and that they were obviously not burglars but 'government people'. Gary also told Ricky that he had been receiving death threats and was being regularly followed. It was also mentioned that Gary was working on a new story concerning the CIA and drug trafficking.

Gary described the men around his home as 'professionals' who jumped from his balcony and ran away when Gary confronted them


Original Associated Press reports stated that Webb had died of gunshot wounds (plural) to the face. This was later changed to 'single gunshot wound' when people began to question how or why a man would shoot himself in the face twice. This represents a concentrated effort to cover up the nature of Webb's death. There have also been reports that the coroner on the scene had originally reported 'multiple gunshot wounds' but later changed his story.

Newspapers also reported the fact that Webb's body was found by removal men without questioning why a man who was about to commit suicide would plan a house move.

Former DEA agent Cele Castillo concurs that Webb was murdered and that in such a 'revenge hit' situation it was common in his experience that the murderers would have likely talked to Webb at length about how and why they were about to kill him.

In a death of this nature a homicide investigation would be par for the course but the media is complicit in bleating like well-behaved sheep to the acceptance that this was a suicide."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PR Costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that Box Office Mojo lists production costs. Is there any other resource that shows how much they spent on Advertising/PR? I have heard some people say assume they spend the same in advertising that do in production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that it will make around 40 mi. If opens at 40 then it wont make more then 80 million.
I mean 40 mil+20 mil+10 mil+5 mil+2.5 mil = 77.5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Weaver: State wont start school year without a budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MD's Big Tasty Bacon Burger was great but they stopped selling it after selling it after a few years.  It had grilled onions. But nothing else worth talking about. I keep reading articles about all these food they are trying out but nothing ever happens. They are testing deer burgers in Texas. They were testing a bacon BBQ burger, even a greek burger with feta cheese.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is their sauce. Its too salty and they don't put enough on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they still open? I haven't seen a friendlies in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never had a really good fish sandwich from the big chains.  Funny enough though there is gyro place in town does makes a really good fish sandwich. You can have it topped with cucumber sauce, tarter sauce, or mayo.  we either eat there or get a shrimp poorboy from Popeyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subway shouldn't be allowed to call the product they sell a sandwich.  There is not enough meat in them to call them anything but plain bread. I wouldn't eat there if they paid me to. Even casey's general store subs are better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Panda Express here in town is discussing, the food is always soggy like it was made days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't about the amount, it was that TB was out of mild.  She  was blocking the drive-thru until they gave her a 50% discount for not having sauce. So TB called the cops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SOUTH EUCLID, Ohio - A very saucy situation brought police to the Mayfield Road Taco Bell on March 12.

Employees were concerned when a disgruntled customer held up the drive-thru line because she didn't like the choices of sauce available to her. So, they called South Euclid police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks - Vault 7: Projects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats in the future of local shopping malls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Payless Shoes to File for Bankruptcy Next Week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beer Town: Finally in Georgia, youll be able to buy a beer at a brewery | Atlanta Restaurant Scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17,000 AT T technicians and call center workers go on strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17,000 AT amp;T technicians and call center workers go on strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17,000 AT amp;T technicians and call center workers go on strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Massie: Obamacare-Lite Is Dead; Ive Spoken to 29 Colleagues Who Will Vote 'No' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers blackmail Apple over 200 million accounts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-sustaining, solar-driven bioelectricity generation in micro-sized microbial fuel cell using co-culture of heterotrophic and photosynthetic bacteria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bomb squad called to Parliament
Posted at
11:10
A planned evacuation of Parliament has been halted after an announcement was made saying there was a suspicious package in a vehicle and the bomb squad had been called.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is in it besides bread and cheese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I removed r/popular? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost as good as Joe Biden's medal of freedom doing nothing more then any other VP does. I swear he really got it for not running against Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about Crew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started playing last night.  I am not level 5 yet. What can you tell me about crew? Do you buy them once or do you pay them a salary? Do they level up?  what kind of buffs do they provide. How members can a ship have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Light Torpedo Clipper is a ton of fun to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! They will just put video gambling machines at every city owned building. That way it doesn't feel like a tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The effect is achieved by a process known as "volumetric capture." Up until now, real-time 3D imaging hasn't placed much stress on this resource-hungry technique. As tempted as I was to stick my nose up at its gimmicky nature, a mind-blowing demo (not the one with Aldrin) changed my tune. Virtual reality offers a particular use case that breathes new life into the conceptand in a scratch-my-back kind of way, VR has good reason to embrace the standard, however proprietary it might be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The effect is achieved by a process known as "volumetric capture." Up until now, real-time 3D imaging hasn't placed much stress on this resource-hungry technique. As tempted as I was to stick my nose up at its gimmicky nature, a mind-blowing demo (not the one with Aldrin) changed my tune. Virtual reality offers a particular use case that breathes new life into the conceptand in a scratch-my-back kind of way, VR has good reason to embrace the standard, however proprietary it might be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is too good for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least SOME criminals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right they should be flayed on Facebook like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 15-year-old girl in Chicago was reportedly recently sexually assaulted by five or six men or boys on Facebook Live, according to the Associated Press.
This is the second such reported attack in Chicago that was broadcast on Facebook this year alone. In January, four teens were arrested in connection to a torture video. The Chicago Tribune reported Tuesday that this attack marks "at least the fourth Chicago crime caught on Facebook Live since the end of last October." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 15-year-old girl in Chicago was reportedly recently sexually assaulted by five or six men or boys on Facebook Live, according to the Associated Press.
This is the second such reported attack in Chicago that was broadcast on Facebook this year alone. In January, four teens were arrested in connection to a torture video. The Chicago Tribune reported Tuesday that this attack marks "at least the fourth Chicago crime caught on Facebook Live since the end of last October." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago teen reportedly gang-raped as 40 people watched on Facebook Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the new policy, which was announced Monday, the grace period for Chicagos red lights will move from 0.1 seconds to 0.3 seconds. This will bring the Windy City in line with other Americans metropolises, including New York City and Philadelphia. In a statement, the city agency said that this increase would maintain the safety benefits of the program while ensuring the programs fairness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the new policy, which was announced Monday, the grace period for Chicagos red lights will move from 0.1 seconds to 0.3 seconds. This will bring the Windy City in line with other Americans metropolises, including New York City and Philadelphia. In a statement, the city agency said that this increase would maintain the safety benefits of the program while ensuring the programs fairness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the new policy, which was announced Monday, the grace period for Chicagos red lights will move from 0.1 seconds to 0.3 seconds. This will bring the Windy City in line with other Americans metropolises, including New York City and Philadelphia. In a statement, the city agency said that this increase would maintain the safety benefits of the program while ensuring the programs fairness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red-light camera grace period goes from 0.1 to 0.3 seconds, Chicago to lose $17M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red-light camera grace period goes from 0.1 to 0.3 seconds, Chicago to lose $17M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red-light camera grace period goes from 0.1 to 0.3 seconds, Chicago to lose $17M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SALT LAKE CITY (AP)  Former CIA and National Security Agency Director Michael Hayden is denying allegations from a former Salt Lake City mayor that the NSA conducted a mass warrantless surveillance program during the 2002 Winter Olympics in Utah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SALT LAKE CITY (AP)  Former CIA and National Security Agency Director Michael Hayden is denying allegations from a former Salt Lake City mayor that the NSA conducted a mass warrantless surveillance program during the 2002 Winter Olympics in Utah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SALT LAKE CITY (AP)  Former CIA and National Security Agency Director Michael Hayden is denying allegations from a former Salt Lake City mayor that the NSA conducted a mass warrantless surveillance program during the 2002 Winter Olympics in Utah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA officials deny mass surveillance during Utah Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA officials deny mass surveillance during Utah Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA officials deny mass surveillance during Utah Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to Visit Brussels in May to Meet With NATO Leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft provided Tim Cook with a Surface Pro 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but all they are going to have is a picture of person with a mask on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All they really have are cameras.  That's only going to work so well.
You would almost have to have a turn-style door that only allows customers that have had some sort of background check. If a person then steals then can be barred from the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Running Out of Time to Change Work Visas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Running Out of Time to Change Work Visas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point in the evolving history of video-game economics, we're used to free-to-play games that make you pay exorbitant sums or grind for a ridiculous number of hours to unlock a bunch of digital trinkets. But Ubisoft's For Honor is the latest game to add a ridiculous number of paid and/or grindy unlockables on top of a pay-up-front games. It asks for over $730 or over 5,200 hours of gameplay to unlock everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any other sources for this?  I am not a big twitter fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why min age should not be 15. I am sure they are working on an automated pizza cutter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next month, Tesla will no longer offer the Model S sedan with a 60 kilowatt-hour battery pack  the cheapest car it sells. With the change, the Model S will start at $74,500 with a 75kWh battery before any state or federal tax incentives, up from $68,000 currently. Of course, Tesla will launch the Model 3 later this year, which will be much cheaper still, starting around $35,000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla is discontinuing its cheapest car, the 60kWh Model S </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tastee Freeze had amazing soft serve ice cream.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoney's At its peak it had over 1300 restaurants now it is down to 230 

Roy Rogers went from 650 to 51

Kenny Rodgers Chicken  Had 425.  The last Kenny Rogers Roasters operating in North America was located in the Ontario Mills mall in Ontario, California; it closed on December 31, 2011

Rax Roast Beef went from 504 to 8

Hot 'n Now went from 150 to 1

Arthur Treacher's went from 800 to 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most successful American rocket launchesfor one of the last times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Developer gets a Game Boy emulator running on the Apple Watch, because he can </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheerios Has A Plan To Save Honey Bees in Canada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheerios Has A Plan To Save Honey Bees in Canada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After years waiting for Google Fiber, KC residents get cancellation e-mails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://arstechnica.com/security/2015/08/highway-to-hack-why-were-just-at-the-beginning-of-the-auto-hacking-era/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total Recall has aged better than many sci-fi movies from the 80s but in my opinion Empire Strikes Back and Predator aged better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Maps adds a sweet new parking spot saver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 100 people took part in the drills, which included transmission of information across "J-Alert," a national emergency alert system that can transmit urgent messages nationwide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK government halts its YouTube ads after some appear on extremist videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan conducts evacuation drill for North Korea missiles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel intercepts missile fired at its air force in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wont rule out just means it is an option on the table.  I bet it is just more saber rattling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you haven't read all the articles of their missile test fires. The last one landed in the Sea of Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are US soldiers and wont arrested by the locals.  I the Army job to arrest and court martial them.  They probably will end up in a military prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson Doesn't Rule Out Preemptive Strike on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you sure it is the transmission? Many times it can be a sensor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A US ally means it was not the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kobe steak and emu eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accused Pizzagate DC shooter negotiating plea deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The payload was to heavy to be able to land the stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US didn't fire the missile and they have a drone jamming system. that disrupts is communications.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A US ally shot down a $200 drone with a $3 million Patriot missile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will launch EchoStar 105 in May. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building a Mars Colony? You'll Need a Team of Astronaut 'MacGyvers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building a Mars Colony? You'll Need a Team of Astronaut 'MacGyvers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been that way for a very long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it was her turn.. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't wear armor on a ship. You can't swim in armor. Also salt water would quickly rust the armor. They had enough problems just keeping the cannons from rusting away. Rich Merchants used bronze cannons. They didnt rust as bad and didn't explode 

Also could you imagine how hot that armor would get in the caribbean sun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike the majority of SpaceXs launches over the past couple years, this mission did not include a rocket landing post-takeoff, as CEO Elon Musk originally announced in a tweet in January. Thats because EchoStar XXIII is a particularly heavy satellite thats going to an orbit about 22,000 miles above the Earths surface. Those two factors combined mean the Falcon 9 needed a lot of fuel for the launch, leaving little left over to perform a rocket landing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike the majority of SpaceXs launches over the past couple years, this mission did not include a rocket landing post-takeoff, as CEO Elon Musk originally announced in a tweet in January. Thats because EchoStar XXIII is a particularly heavy satellite thats going to an orbit about 22,000 miles above the Earths surface. Those two factors combined mean the Falcon 9 needed a lot of fuel for the launch, leaving little left over to perform a rocket landing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike the majority of SpaceXs launches over the past couple years, this mission did not include a rocket landing post-takeoff, as CEO Elon Musk originally announced in a tweet in January. Thats because EchoStar XXIII is a particularly heavy satellite thats going to an orbit about 22,000 miles above the Earths surface. Those two factors combined mean the Falcon 9 needed a lot of fuel for the launch, leaving little left over to perform a rocket landing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX successfully launched a communications satellite on its Falcon 9 rocket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX successfully launched a communications satellite on its Falcon 9 rocket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the age of the manufactured meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is why I only ever drink beer now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get caught up in Lexus LIT IS's mesmerizing light display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get caught up in Lexus LIT IS's mesmerizing light display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonalds is now testing mobile ordering in the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, Trump with nukes or Daleks with disintegration beams. Tough call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here just to say that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Architects will have five days to submit proposals for Trump's border wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Architects will have five days to submit proposals for Trump's border wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IKEA switches to furniture that snaps together in minutes without requiring tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somali pirates hijack first commercial ship since 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the problem with cabbage is if you even slightly over cook it you get retched sulfuric stench.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what did they try to pair it with?  Bud light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks hurts CIA's relationship with Apple, Google, Microsoft and Silicon Valley, former director Petraeus said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks hurts CIA's relationship with Apple, Google, Microsoft and Silicon Valley, former director Petraeus said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the heels of Zika comes its deadlier relative, yellow fever, experts warn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the heels of Zika comes its deadlier relative, yellow fever, experts warn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a terrible web page. Even sell playing ads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are using the wrong ad-blocker.  Mine works fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 26-foot statue is made of quartzite and could be up to 3,000 years old. The Antiquities Ministry in Egypt is hailing the discovery as significant. The remains lack an inscription bearing the pharaoh's name, but the discovery's proximity to a temple devoted to Ramses suggest the statue is of his likeness, the ministry says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive Statue of Ancient Egyptian Pharaoh Found in City Slum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flippy The $0-An-Hour Burger Flipper Is How To Make Fast Food Wages $15 An Hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flippy The $0-An-Hour Burger Flipper Is How To Make Fast Food Wages $15 An Hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks offers tech companies exclusive access to CIA hacking tools | VentureBeat | Security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks offers tech companies exclusive access to CIA hacking tools | VentureBeat | Security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just called someone a Mongoloid so you are an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caterpillar machinery is the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like shit graphics to me but I am a pc gamer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos of the 11ft-diameter Hyperloop test track under construction in Nevada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbus reveals a modular, self-piloting flying car concept </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This House Was 3D Printed in Less Than 24 Hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This House Was 3D Printed in Less Than 24 Hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Feds Would Rather Drop a Child Porn Case Than Give Up an Exploit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Feds Would Rather Drop a Child Porn Case Than Give Up an Exploit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "By the end of 2016, the CIA's hacking division, which formally falls under the agency's Center for Cyber Intelligence (CCI), had over 5000 registered users and had produced more than a thousand hacking systems, trojans, viruses, and other "weaponized" malware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "By the end of 2016, the CIA's hacking division, which formally falls under the agency's Center for Cyber Intelligence (CCI), had over 5000 registered users and had produced more than a thousand hacking systems, trojans, viruses, and other "weaponized" malware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "By the end of 2016, the CIA's hacking division, which formally falls under the agency's Center for Cyber Intelligence (CCI), had over 5000 registered users and had produced more than a thousand hacking systems, trojans, viruses, and other "weaponized" malware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA planned to hack cars and trucks to carry out undetectable assassinations claims WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA planned to hack cars and trucks to carry out undetectable assassinations claims WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On its support page Nintendo states, "Small numbers of stuck or dead pixels are a characteristic of LCD screens. These are normal and should not be considered a defect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On its support page Nintendo states, "Small numbers of stuck or dead pixels are a characteristic of LCD screens. These are normal and should not be considered a defect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On its support page Nintendo states, "Small numbers of stuck or dead pixels are a characteristic of LCD screens. These are normal and should not be considered a defect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo: Switch Screen Dead Pixels Are Not a Defect | News   Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo: Switch Screen Dead Pixels Are Not a Defect | News  amp; Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or both, I find My safety razor does such a good job that I just touch it up with electric the next day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switch to a merkur safety razor. You can buy a 100 pack of Astra Platinum Double Edge Safety Razor Blades for $11. Each blades costs me 11 cents and lasts about 2 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just too much work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well if they fail with the Switch like they did with the WiiU they are so screwed. I actually feel bad for WiiU owners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whom exactly made this comic.  I smell a shill.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dick Durbin must be off his meds. The Senate's H-1B is SOOOO much better then Trumps.  The senate bill will double minimum wage and give power to police the system. Trumps plan is to auction the Visas to the highest bidder.  Why the hell would Durbin want Trump to Act? There is even talk about adding more to the bill that would stop a company from contracting their visa workers to other companies.  Companies like Infosys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they plan to grandfather in H-1B visa workers already here.  I hope so,. If they don't then many families will have to leave.  At least give them a year or two grace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bill, a companion to the Senate's version already being worked on. The bill proposes to prohibit employers from outsourcing H-1B and L-1 visa holders to other sites unless the employer obtains a waiver which is available only in limited circumstances when the rights of American workers are protected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second Bipartisan H-1B, L1 visa reform bill introduced in US Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bill, a companion to the Senate's version already being worked on. The bill proposes to prohibit employers from outsourcing H-1B and L-1 visa holders to other sites unless the employer obtains a waiver which is available only in limited circumstances when the rights of American workers are protected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second Bipartisan H-1B, L1 visa reform bill introduced in US Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to do Far Cry and elder scrolls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk Agrees to Hold Contest for Fan-Made Tesla Ads, at the Urging of a Fifth Grader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intel may cut prices in response to AMD's Ryzen 1700, 1700X, and 1800X launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a statement sent yesterday, UPTE-CWA says the layoffs could spread, since the HCL contract can be utilized by any of the 10 campuses in the University of California system, the nation's largest public university. "US taxes should be used to create jobs in the US, not in other countries," said Kurt Ho, a systems administrator who was quoted in the union's press release. Ho was required to train his replacement as a condition of getting his severance pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a statement sent yesterday, UPTE-CWA says the layoffs could spread, since the HCL contract can be utilized by any of the 10 campuses in the University of California system, the nation's largest public university. "US taxes should be used to create jobs in the US, not in other countries," said Kurt Ho, a systems administrator who was quoted in the union's press release. Ho was required to train his replacement as a condition of getting his severance pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public university lays off 79 IT workers after they train outsourced replacements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public university lays off 79 IT workers after they train outsourced replacements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caterpillar shares fall as feds conduct searches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The researchers propose a "humanoid-bioreactor system" with "structures, dimensions, and mechanics similar to those of the human body." As the robot interacted with its environment, tissues growing on its body would receive the typical strains and twists that they would if they grew on an actual human. The result would be healthy tissue, grown for the exact area on the body it was destined to replace. Mouthuy and Carr note that this would be especially helpful for "bone-tendon-muscle grafts... because failure during healing often occurs at the interface between tissues." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The researchers propose a "humanoid-bioreactor system" with "structures, dimensions, and mechanics similar to those of the human body." As the robot interacted with its environment, tissues growing on its body would receive the typical strains and twists that they would if they grew on an actual human. The result would be healthy tissue, grown for the exact area on the body it was destined to replace. Mouthuy and Carr note that this would be especially helpful for "bone-tendon-muscle grafts... because failure during healing often occurs at the interface between tissues." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get ready for robots made with human flesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get ready for robots made with human flesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IGN is the last place I go for reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois Senate cancels budget votes; leader blames Rauner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo Switch: Friend Codes Return In Day One Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my father is a plumber does that me a plumber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how much filler are in their meatballs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elvis was a big fan of fried balona </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's looks good.  Extra points for not overcooking the burger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is is a place in town that makes an apple crumble pizza. It is an amazing dessert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm anchovy and pineapple pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers grow electronic rose complete with wires and supercapacitors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few people not plenty.  The writing was terrible there wasn't even one memorable quote. Apocalypse was terribly done.  The whole movie was just chain of cliches.  We even got so a giant bridge destroyed again.

Psylock was terrible pick for a horseman she has not real ranged attacks. Horse men were supposed to be the most powerful mutants on the planets. The only reason they picked her was because they were trying to get more people in Asia to watch the movie.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Batman   Robin (1997) -  "Let's kick some ice!"  " Stay cool, Birdboy."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one liked Apocalypse becaue it was terrible.  Now it was not as bad cat-woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped trusting rotten tomato a long time ago. After watching the miserable Wolv 2 I have no interest in watching Logan. why did they add X-23 to the Old Man Logan story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cutting Rigging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you cut enemy rigging whith a sword?  If not, is it something the Dev's are considering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rifle Range </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What ranges do the rifles in this game have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if it is more expensive then real beef. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How article are we going to get on lab grown meat that no new information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neurons recall place-related memories if you just get close </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New $10 Raspberry Pi Zero comes with Wi-Fi and Bluetooth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course this can change depending on who is writing the comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart's New Plan to Set Prices in Face of Discount Chains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We never had a 'Players vs GM' problem because we all took turns being GMs.  The TPK was not planned.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gigabyte Announces AORUS X370 And B350 AMD AM4 Ryzen Motherboards For Enthusiasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure they are all dead or insane in first hour of play.  Best just to get it out of the way first! That what happened my first COC game. (..and second)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better understanding the structure and properties of beetle exoskeletons could help scientists engineer lighter, stronger materials. Such materials could, for example, reduce gas-guzzling drag in vehicles and airplanes and reduce the weight of armor, lightening the load for the 21st-century knight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better understanding the structure and properties of beetle exoskeletons could help scientists engineer lighter, stronger materials. Such materials could, for example, reduce gas-guzzling drag in vehicles and airplanes and reduce the weight of armor, lightening the load for the 21st-century knight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better understanding the structure and properties of beetle exoskeletons could help scientists engineer lighter, stronger materials. Such materials could, for example, reduce gas-guzzling drag in vehicles and airplanes and reduce the weight of armor, lightening the load for the 21st-century knight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
