<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 01:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't too sure about putting the Aldo knockout there, but I thought it went well with the lyrics around there. That and the Mendes knockout timed to the word "power". I appreciate the criticism though, I've got plenty of areas to improve on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 22:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about that actually. If I flipped the footage would they still be able to issue a claim?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'll make sure that it will be!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol and true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all a bunch of masochists, aren't we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like so long ago... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I feel like Keyboard Cat is the only thing Chloe can play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I fully intend to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 19:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People seem to watch them. Seemed like as good a place to start as any.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Started learning video editing, figured McGregor highlights would be a good place to start: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 19:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 02:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta pick Max and Chloe reuniting in Chloe's room in Ep4. I made a lengthy [post](https://www.reddit.com/r/lifeisstrange/comments/3zwkx6/ep5_spoilers_your_favorite_moments/cypxp7g) about this scene earlier and why it's favorite scene in the entire game. But the pool scene is a very close second (on the Pricefield barometer). *Very* close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 02:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Frank. He's a good guy, but he feels threatened. He's at the bottom of the pecking order, and people spit upon him and spur him like a stranger cur (Shakespeare reference, woo). He kind of has to behave prickly, otherwise people would just walk all over him. But he's a good dude. He loved Rachel. He loves Pompidou. He loves beans. Even though their relationship gets off to a rocky start, he eventually comes around to admire Max as a person (if he doesn't die). He's a good guy at heart. He's just in an unfortunate position, and whether it's by his own doing or not doesn't change that. 

As for the morality of selling drugs for students...

A man's gotta eat. I don't think Frank sees any other options for himself. Being at the bottom of the class pyramid can often rob you of hope. If Frank could get a job doing something else, I'm sure he'd take it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I thought to myself, "I wonder just how easy it would be to look vaguely like Chloe."
Turns out...pretty easily!

You....might need to shave... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chloe cuddles are probably the best cuddles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't bear all these puns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 21:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, that is awesome. Even with the sleeves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 21:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he looks best with his 194 cut and neatly trimmed beard, but his 189 hair and beard had a charm of its own. The lack of grooming (and how deathly pale he was) made him look like a fucking crazy man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of want this to come true, because I'm still not convinced that Conor can't fight off his back. I know he was getting dominated by Mendes for almost two whole rounds, but I just don't believe that's all he has to offer on the mat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To me Conor looked pretty tired, he wasn't light on his feet, he went completely flat footed and was breathing from his mouth. 

He did. But he looked pretty off his game right out the gate at 189. I distinctly remember watching that fight and thinking Conor looked really, really fatigued from the jump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad that you mentioned stepping onto the campus for the first time. The serene moments like that were awesome. They weren't serene and peaceful because they were still, they were peaceful because they felt genuinely alive. You look around the beautiful school grounds and see an assortment of characters all doing their own thing. A lot of games are described as having worlds that feel "lived in", but LiS is the only game world I've ever been it that feels like it is *being* lived in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How's it going time tripper?" is one of my favorites (Episode 3, bathroom mirror in Casa del Price). It's a super cute little moment, due almost entirely to Hannah's delivery of the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite moment is when you return to the original timeline in Episode 4. The scene is *incredibly* well done. The muffled music, "In My Mind" by Amanda Palmer, playing in the background begins sounding creepy and a little ominous and soon changes into the most joyous song you've ever heard. The opening shot of the pirate drawing is initially confusing, a little unfamiliar, but as it comes into focus it evokes a feeling of nostalgia. The scene still hasn't been set, and you're left wondering what's going on and whether or not you've fixed everything. The camera turns to Max, looking as disoriented and worried as the player. Then the camera slowly pans up. The music comes into focus as soon as Chloe's blue hair enters view. The swell of the music is times perfectly with the grin that spreads across Max's face as she turns around, as well as the swell of our own hearts. Max runs to Chloe and wraps her in a tight, awww-so-sweet hug. And naturally, Chloe responds in the best way possible: with her trademark dry humor and sarcasm, "that beautiful pissed off face". It's the perfect way to assure us that we're finally home. The scene instantly transitions into one of the game's awesome sit-down scenes where you can stay frozen in time for as long as you want. The warm colors and morning sunlight streaming in from the windows reinforces the feelings of hope and home. It's one of the best executed scenes in the entire game. 

And for me, it was also *the* most emotional moment in the game. I've talked about how the main takeaways and emotional effects I got from the game are positive, and this scene takes the fucking cake. I remember the sheer emotional brutality of the first act of Episode 4, and I was *so* worried that I'd never see my Blue Chloe again. The scene opens and builds the tension like I described above, but then it all dissolved the second I saw that blue hair. It was the most relieving moment for me in the entire game, even more than saving Kate. I remember just sitting there grinning from ear to ear for minutes and minutes on end, even after the song ended. In that moment, everything else melted away. Rachel, Kate, Nathan, David, the binders, the alt-timeline, as well as everything going on in my own life, it all just disappeared as I got to bask in this moment of pure unadulterated happiness. It wouldn't be an exaggeration for me to say that it was one of the happiest moments of my entire life, and it's not like I've had a shitty life or anything (a relatively short one maybe). I can't remember ever smiling so hard (my face hurt). It's something that I won't ever forget about. It was also the moment I swore to never let Chloe go again. 

Even if you didn't read through that whole blahblahblah (understandable), I'm sure my excessive fawning over the scene shows just how much I love it. 

RUNNER UP: This is a funny one. The scene when you return to the Blackwell campus in Episode 4 and bump into Mr. Jefferson is fucking awesome. It's a scene that really highlights the quality of the dialogue and characters. It's the first real instance where Jefferson seems like a real person, and a genuinely likable dude at that. It's another positive moment where I forgot about all the darkness surrounding Arcadia Bay. The scene contains the single spoken interaction between Jefferson and Chloe in the whole game, and it is AMAZING. The light flirting, while creepy in retrospect, is hilarious. Chloe telling Jefferson that she's Max's date for the Vortex Club party is one of my favorite lines in the entire game. And of course this line: "Besides, you don't want to see the old hipster trying to keep up with the kids." This scene is just awesome. Then the subsequent banter between Max and Chloe (fighting over the sexy teacher) is also super cute. It's honestly one of the most human moments in the entire game, and that's saying something! Makes me long for a timeline where Jefferson isn't secretly Jefferdouche.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 23:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Oh deer.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. If I didn't just replay Episode 3, I probably wouldn't get it. But I did, so it's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Always take the shot .. ahem ... opportunity!"

That could've been real dirty. 

But in all seriousness, good for you. It's awesome to hear both you and /u/LegendPT's stories. This game and community are so fucking awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So *"Let's thrash this place!"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16,184 Shaka Brahs, *113 ready for the mosh pit* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Carlton too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather have us go by "Shaka Brahs".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a dark blue beanie in the background... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *rage boils over* 

Jefferfield is probably as taboo as it gets around here. Though if you start preaching Grahamfield/Wax/Marren you might create a sizable hullabaloo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would've been a ballsy move, and methinks potentially a lot more meaningful. But at the same time, it wouldn't be right to take the game's most important mechanic away from us during the final choice. If Life is Strange's choice mechanics were more passive and not bound to "pick A or B", then it might work. Games that have good and bad endings attached to kill counts kinda work along those lines; you're (generally speaking) not actively making the decision to get the good or bad ending. But for an entire game where we've been presented with this very specific and binary, active, method of making choices it wouldn't work to remove player agency at the very end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am all aboard the S.S. Princefield

uh...

 S.S. Princefield

...

 Princefield

*rages uncontrollably* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want them to get hung up with the concept of the storm; that was never the main focus of the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 16:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS IS SO AWESOOOOOOOOOOOMMMMMMMMEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 16:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 21:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-posted because there was something wrong with the initial video upload.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uncharted 4 Trailer: Fury Road (fan edit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 21:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 20:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom sounds pretty cool. Perhaps even hella cool. Her take on accepting Chloe's request was very interesting to read; I accepted, but I wonder if I would've been able to do that in real life. Realistically? Your mom's right, I probably couldn't.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 20:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cork, Ireland! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 23:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's after the credits for Kinda Funny live. It's just the four of them eating burritos in complete silence. 

[Link](https://youtu.be/cF8Y2zWdDTM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 00:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me that Rachel was just confused and stuck at crossroads. She falls in love with Frank for the content of his character. She falls for Jefferson because he's the key, or maybe the door, to her success and career as a model. Then her best friend Chloe becomes infatuated with her, and when Rachel doesn't feel the same way she fears hurting her best friend. The Nathan Prescott becomes infatuated with her. Looking at it this way, I think she was just in a really difficult position where there was no right answer. I don't think she was a manipulative bitch. I think she was just like everyone else, she had problems in her life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 21:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what'd be the point of that? There are plenty of interesting situations they could put Max and Chloe in, but most of them would be pretty pointless in regards to their evolution as people. Let's take your idea: Max gets kidnapped, Chloe has to go all super-Chloe and save her. What's the message? What's Chloe's character arc? The point isn't to write them into a story, it's to write a story *around* them. 

Also, I'd say that Chloe has very much grown over the course of the game. At the beginning, she's bitter and wants to "drop a bomb on Arcadia Bay and turn it to fucking glass". At the end, she tells Max that there are so many people in AB who deserve to live more than she does. If that's not growth, I don't know what is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're 100% right. As much as we want to see them again, Max and Chloe's story is done. It wouldn't be worth bringing them back just to get another five episodes out of them (though I would definitely enjoy that). That said, I'm not really sure what the second season would be about. I can't see how or why Dontnod would make a sequel/second season that is still Life is Strange. I feel like a second season with a new cast would essentially just be a new IP in the same genre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to close the tab. I'm not going back there again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max is sitting up a little too straight. She tends to hunch just a little bit. But I really like the overall feel of this pic. Super chill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 14:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't be long before your expression of amazement is "wowser" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy new year to you as well dude! Looking forward to 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's awesome to hear that this game gave you closure. It's also awesome to see you using the word "hella".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dustin's actually got a pretty nice straight left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Errant Signal. He's one of the most critical and level headed reviewers out there. Whether you enjoyed his criticism or not, he makes some very good points about the game. He's not nearly as opinionated as some other reviewers, and that's something I can genuinely appreciate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says it at the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's awesome. I've only been a real part of 3 or 4 other communities of this kind before, and they were all pretty...not nice. Even if they started out super constructive, they all devolved into douchery pretty quick. But this community has been super cool. The people are very nice, very welcoming, usually very open minded. There's a lot of energy and enthusiasm here as well; there's so much damn fanart and so many damn fanfics and people posting pics of their new blue hair, ugh, it's beautiful. I love this community so much. 

Also, thank *you* for these Daily Topics. They're a super awesome contribution to this wonderful sub. /u/armis37 the real mvp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2015 has kinda been the best year of my life. Everything finally started to come together for me and I feel I discovered who I am. I had a lot of great experiences this year, but experiencing Life is Strange and this community was definitely the best one. I want to thank everyone here for being super welcoming, civil, and often hella goofy. I've said it a lot before, but it has genuinely been an honor to join all of you on this wild ride. You are all Arcadia Baes. 

Here's to 2016, fuckers! Happy New Year :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally don't give a shit about the reset; narratively I actually quite like it. Both endings are "resets" when you think about it. It was never about the whole week being for nothing; Chloe says it herself, but the memories of the week *are* real, and they always will be. That won't ever change. I just couldn't let her go. I refuse to surrender myself (and her) to fate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 23:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For Chloe, her story ends in a bathroom of a high school she was expelled from, after a father whom she loved was killed in a car crash, with a step-father that she hated, whilst oweing a drug dealer money that she borrowed in order to try and find Rachel, the love of her life that she doesn't even know is dead, and, to top it all off, without ever again seeing the friend who seemingly abandoned her all those years ago.

This was precisely why I couldn't make the choice to let her go. Chloe deserved better than that. Yeah, everyone in Arcadia Bay didn't deserve to get obliterated by the storm, but I couldn't and still can't bear the idea of Chloe dying alone in that bathroom. Alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 22:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm playing on my new PC and can run it maxed out at 60 fps

*Maxed* out? You'll fit right in here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 22:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really *heartfelt* picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn. Oh damn. Oh damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JESUS FUCK WHAT IS GOIN ON

This has got me hooked already. Let's see where this goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't. Not because I think the season pass was a rip off, or the DLC wasn't fun, or it wouldn't be worth it. I just don't have the time anymore. I haven't got the chance to play the Arkham Knight DLC since late September. I really liked the images of the skins and Batmobiles I saw, and the Season of Infamy missions looked pretty interesting, but I haven't had the chance to try them out. I wouldn't lay down another 40 bucks for a bunch of DLC I won't get around to playing. If I had time, I most certainly would. What I *did* play of the additional content, I had a lot of fun with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 19:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shy/introvert posture comments are probably right. Dontnod put lots of work into characters' mannerisms. For example, without talking to her you can see Chloe's confidence (and that it's probably a defense mechanism) from how she carries herself. The way Max holds her arm, and often anxiously looks around while she's doing this, does point towards introversion. And we already know that she's an introvert, so that's that. 

Buuuut coming at this from another angle, your comment that pose having to do with shoulder pain got me thinking. Max is a relatively skinny and frail looking individual. Her clumsiness, build (compared to Chloe's more lean and muscled frame), and awkward running suggest that she isn't a particularly active or fit person. And if you look at Max's posture, she tends to slouch a little. Not drastically, but a little. Her shoulders tend to hang forward, and her back is often bent. This is the case with most people. Most of our lifestyles (even regardless of how often you work out or whatever) involve a lot of sitting down, hunching over computers and books. In the long term, poor posture can lead to things like back pain and shoulder (rotator cuff) pain, but even young people can suffer minor irritation of this kind. So based on these assumptions (which is really all this is), it's very likely that Max Caulfield might actually suffer from some kind of minor/moderate shoulder pain. It doesn't help that the weight of her bookbag is constantly coming down on that shoulder. 

BUT, that's probably not what Dontnod was going for when they worked on Max's animations and mannerisms. Go with the introversion. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 19:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. McGregor's cleared out the division *except* for Frankie. I don't think that detracts from what he's done though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 18:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago you would've received lots of upvotes for this comment. Huh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 14:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The final choice, then, is a culmination of that idea: is your version of adulthood about sacrificing the things that matter to you (sacrificing your dreams so you can get a good job/raise a kid/whatever), or are you willing to be more selfish in the pursuit of the things that you really care about (in this case, Chloe)?
Personally, the latter resonates more with me. I hate stories like Knocked Up, that endlessly reward their protagonists for giving up their individuality in the pursuit of "real" adulthood, which always means giving up all the shit that matters to you so you can be a True Man Who Takes Care Of Shit.

Wise words, whether you agree or not. Personally, I do. 

 Also, I'm not gonna let my sister die in any game where she's a character, so there's that.

Even after Ash has shot, maimed, abused, and turned Anthony into the subject of a Schrodinger's Cat experiment in the bathroom. Dawww. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 14:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I didn't even realize that you were referring to the bullet hole. I was thinking, "why are these neck worms symbolic?" I get you now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really starting to get invested here. Good to see a longer chapter too. The moment when Max passes out at the top of the stairs was pretty fucking emotional, nice work! The one criticism I have is that it's hard to tell who's who in that final exchange between the Caulfields and the Prices. I know Max can't see them, but she *can* hear them. A little bit of clarity when it comes to who's talking when would've helped. Loving it otherwise, excited for the next one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 22:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of what exactly? I'm not the sharpest knife in the drawer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 22:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't throw him that homecoming after 194 either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Question 5:**

Where Max's powers came from is never really revealed. Some people say it was the universe giving her more time to be with Chloe. The visions of the storm would be the universe reminding her that, at the end of the week, she would have to let Chloe go. That only really applies to the Sacrifice Chloe ending though. It's quite poetic and touching though. 
There's also the possibility that the whole week happened in her mind, and dreaming up a last week of adventures with her best friend was Max's way of coping with her death (and her own guilt). That would mean the rewind powers never existed. 

I think that the powers and the storm are metaphorical, and we aren't supposed to take them literally. I don't think the week was all a dream though. I think the game is about Max deciding what kind of person she wants to be, "coming of age", and I think using time travel powers was the best way Dontnod had to tell that story. 

Then there's the possibility that the "spirits" of Arcadia Bay gave Max the powers, hoping that she could save the town. Arcadia Bay had gone to hell in the 5 years Max was away, under the effects of the Prescott family. Maybe when Arcadia's favorite daughter finally returned, and reunited with her partner, the spirits gave her (them) the power to save the town. Or, if the cost was too great, to save themselves. This could also explain the visions; the spirits were warning her of the impending storm so that she could prepare. There are a lot of references to spirits and Native American legend in the game, so something like that really wouldn't surprise me. I'm being vague as hell, I know, but that's all I got at the moment. 

The last two are the ones I like best. I may have also pulled all of these out of my ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you, or I, will ever disconnect from LiS memories, but you will probably move on in time. I'm still always thinking about LiS, Max and Chloe, listening to that soundtrack, but I'm not a wreck anymore. 

Then again, I got the "happy" ending. That might make my experience very different from yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if he can do both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nathan said in his struggle with her that no one would remember her; he couldn't have been more wrong. The people at the funeral remembered her, Max remembered her, and I honestly don't know for sure that I will ever forget her.

The tears be fallin'. Well said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't have said it any better. Well, maybe you could've. I couldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 16:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. But there's also money involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 13:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Followed by going downstairs and eatings some are you cereal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 13:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be nice, but it sounds a bit unrealistic. Two separate Episodes Ones I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 02:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the Bae ending sort of symbolizes defying fate, making your own destiny. Earlier in the game Max also asks, "who ever said we only have one fate?" I think she molds her own fate, and the Bae ending represents this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super pretty! I like that it isn't just one solid shade of blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, that was...a lot to take in. Nice work Tinny. Incredible work even.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 19:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see them releasing the first episode in the fall; that'd leave it to January/February 2017 or Jan/Feb 2018. If you were to place a bet...

...don't. Gambling iz bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 18:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conor should walk out to The Next Episode for his next fight. 

With his rendition of "It's the motherfuckin D O Double G" dubbed in of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 18:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't actually know that. But still, I can't see them putting out Season 2 in 2016. That's way too soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I prefer weed and chill](http://i.imgur.com/ZJTb8vc.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were a lot of people who were very active here in say, June or July. Don't see them here anymore. :( Makes me kinda sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cute! Love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *WHAT REALITY IS THIS* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God DAYUM that's amazing. I love how one side of Max is highlighted in blue and the other in red.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt they'd retcon the endings to Season 1. There are more ways of preserving the endings without rendering them meaningless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was no way that we'd see Season 2 in 2016 anyways. 2017 at the soonest, though my guess would be January 2018. They've got Vampyr in the works and that's, at the absolute earliest, a holiday 2016 game. Max and Chloe or no, we never would've seen the second season in 2016.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hella dope. Even though the Spanish Sahara quote dissolved my soul when I saw it. Can't wait to see the finished journal. (I know it'll be a while, but keep at it!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 20:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about us. See you around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 14:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to say DJ. DC's a close runner up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 05:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOD DAMMIT ASH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 05:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you maybe take a screenshot of some of the playlist and post it here? I...don't have spotify. I'd like to know some of the songs though, that way I could look them up somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 04:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spoilers? Is this still necessary? Let's be safe.]( #s "I'm going to say Jefferson. Not because he's the villain, not because he's a douche, and not because he's too pretty. I just think he's the most shallow character in the game. The funny thing is that before Episode 5, I think he's much more 3 Dimensional. We see that he is driven, yet carefree. Supportive (of Max, he's an absolute turd to Kate), yet stern (in class). He's rumored to have had sex with students before, but when Victoria makes her proposition to him he outright rejects it. He's a hip, famous photographer, but he also calls himself 'an old hipster'. Pre Episode 5 he had a lot of charm and charisma, and I feel he had more depth as well. Then he turns out to be the villain and just...becomes a stereotypical villain. The unused dialogue hints at more behind his character, but what we saw was incredibly 2 Dimensional.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 04:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  More than anything else, Life is Strange is an incredible use of the medium to tell a story we dont really get to see in games. 

I'm always happy to see people write this about Life is Strange. One of the game's best aspects, if not it's best aspect, is that it tells a story that you couldn't effectively tell in any other medium. Being able to rewind time and change the choices you make works perfectly with the themes and fuses narrative and gameplay into one entity. It's a beautiful and refreshing thing to see in a time where games need to you commit dozens of mass murders before they can show you an emotional moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 02:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way I don't know why you're being downvoted, seeing as *you are contributing to this discussion*. 

It's not a dislike button, people. It's an "irrelevant/inappropriate" button.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 02:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look so cute in wintery gear. Love the color scheme too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 02:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This conversation has been a lot of fun. Thanks for, uh, conversing! Hopefully we'll be seeing you around this sub in the future. 

There's no other game quite like Life is Strange. If you're looking for games with moral choices/conundrum's, play *The Walking Dead: Season 1* or *The Wolf Among Us*. If you're looking for the nostalgic vibe of LiS and a Pacific Northwest setting, try *Gone Home*. If you want a game with an atmosphere as rich as LiS (though different), play *Red Dead Redemption*. And if you want an equally strong story driven my the relationship between two characters that also poses some really deep morality questions like the one we talked about, play *The Last of Us*. And for a story about the touching friendship between two girls, play *The Last of Us: Left Behind* (*Gone Home* also falls into this category). Those are the best recommendations I can give you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 01:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For me/my Max, it felt the complete opposite. Sacrificing Chloe made me feel guilt, a deep sadness, but no regret. I think that, in the final ending, as she stares out into the sunlit bay, Max feels a deep sadness, but does not regret her choice. She feels sad, but in a way, contented.

I believe guilt is related directly to morality. When I (or rather, the user I quoted) say Sacrifice Bay = Guilt, I'm suggesting that Max feels that she has made the morally wrong choice. Which, in the grand scheme of things, she has. But if she sacrifices Chloe she doesn't necessarily feel guilt, because she has made the morally right choice; she feels regret. Regret is more personal, and in this context maybe more selfish. She'd regret giving up Chloe because it is worse for herself. 

I totally feel you your last point. Every single character in the game feels like a real person. Almost everyone has some kind of character progression and some kind of life that goes on independently of Max's, and also everyone has secrets that they hide. It makes them feel incredibly three dimensional. So yeah when that final choice comes, it's hard to think of Arcadia Bay as a bunch of lines of code. It feels like a real town filled with *real* people. I also feel you on the point of Max being able to easily empathize with others. Especially with her powers. She can see the different sides to everyone. She can see the good, the bad, and the ugly in everyone. If anyone, Max would have the resolve, nay-the ability (did I really just say "nay"? I feel like Prince Hamlet right now) to make the selfless choice. 

But to be entirely honest with you when I look at Max, from my own lens or from a distance, I don't see this perfect and selfless heroine. The fact that there are so many choices in the game that can be broken down to "selfless vs selfish" is reasonable proof that Max is internally conflicted about her morality. She stops and considers different options, justifying each for herself. Her moral compass isn't definitively righteous. She's not a superhero. She's a very real person with normal character flaws. She often wants to take the selfish route but knows that, based on everything society teaches us, it is right to take the selfless route. The age old conflict of feeling vs thinking. (It's worth mentioning for your side that when she initially gets her rewind powers but doesn't have a personal stake in the decision, Max acts selflessly and heroically in the bathroom in Episode 1. Being selfless is Max's true nature. That supports your side, and I'd be a doofus to deny it.)

It's a very complex issue, and it goes far beyond the confines of our monitors. It's a hella deep morality (and even psychology) conundrum. All arguments about it run in an infinite loop, as this sub has most certainly seen over the last two months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 23:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greg's a notable personality in games media and the games industry, so I figured it was worth mentioning that he's finally got around to playing the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Miller (Podcast Beyond, Kinda Funny, PS I Love You XOXO Host) hops aboard the LiS train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 23:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
