<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Walk daily for minimum 30 minutes even if you don't want to. A walk can drastically make positive influence over a period of time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basic needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they keep secrets and talk only about themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because killing myself would mean a painful death because I am young.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if you were a cute kitten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you like about introverts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of losers claiming to be wise or intelligent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People complimenting my looks but the self esteem is still quite low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is so absurd that everything seems so amusing sometimes. Like what matters right now won't matter ever in a few minutes/months/years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad grades, no fun, depression, unable to concentrate on studies, not knowing what I truly want, not knowing what I want after graduation, bad career prospects after graduation, long commute etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seminars/Webinars to highlight the importance of majoring in something that will give you good career prospects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which sports should be banned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the pollution and overcrowd can drive you mad.  
Source: I'm an Indian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are your favorite cricketers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell people you have a crush on them. If you're a guy and a pretty girl says yes then you got a date otherwise just yell "APRIL'S FOOL!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what, just say "Your mom". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People telling others to break up over trivial things while giving relationship advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do during evening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost fucked my friend's ex but I did ask for my friend's permission before. Ended up not doing it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pet cat of a millionaire! Mew Mew Mew! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/unexepected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still fascinating!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To observe those creatures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got the fucking gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 19 so there aren't many but trying to turn an okay friend into a lifelong friend has been a mistake. He's just not the kind of person who can have long term friendships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which books are a must read for a young adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recording dreams and playing it later for our amusement or getting clues about our unconscious desires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally got my first gold for asking it. Someone had put a question as to why you want gold and I said I want to say "thanks for the gold, kind stranger" and the user gave it to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counter Strike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A place for mostly losers who have no life but to read and answer stupid questions and reading made up stories where 99% of stories are just not true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got jealous as hell whenever I looked at the photos and the people starting their own YouTube channel. That happened because people were having what I want and I knew I couldn't have those things no matter how badly I wanted them. I have unfollowed a bunch of people and I don't visit the site as often now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not talking to girls more and letting parents decide everything for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter. Severous Snape. Goku. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing as Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and few friends were fighting for fun. Suddenly, one of the friend got in a fight with a kid we didn't know and he punched that kid with a blade around his fingers. This was when we were 11 year old. Around 8 years ago. At that time I really got mad at him because it wasn't  supposed to be a serious fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Embarrassing.  
Occasionally.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the God made it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you describe yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, gotta make some change. Man in the mirror by MJ inspires me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good sleeping routine, exercise, study, be social, love someone passionately, work hard and smart, love myself, have good hobbies, play more sports, hangout more often, try new things etc. Too bad I'm too apathetic to try these stuff now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleep and I am determined to believe I am a loser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What to do when both of your parents have mental issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fulfilled my best friend's wish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has always been an enthusiastic and charismatic person. Ever since we both turned 17 I found a rejuvenated admiration for him in my heart.  No, I didnt think of him romantically. He was just like a brother from the other mother to me. Sounds clich but its the best description I could give. Wed do everything together. Wed sit in class with each other, would hangout after school, would play basketball sometimes, would talk about new YouTube channels we started watching. Heck, once there was a widespread rumor about us dating each other which always annoyed me because I was straight. I even had a crush on one of my classmate and she was beautiful and had been my fantasy for months.  

I ignored those rumors because I cherished my friendship more and I wouldnt give it away for a stupid rumor. We still played basketball with each other, discussed our favorite YouTube channels, sat in class with each other and didnt care about what anybody else thought Or so did I think. His behavior was odd for the past few days. Now that I was sitting in my room alone pondering over what happened during the week I realized things were not quite the same. What was going on? Why did it feel so different talking to him now? I tried to think about something else and brushed this feeling off as overreaction on my part.  

Just as I was about to go watch TV my phone rang. It was him. Bastard will have a long life I guess. I picked it up and he sounded upset. He told me to come over his house because he wanted to tell me something extremely important and he couldnt resist anymore. So, I walked over to his house which was a few blocks away.   

Hi, Mark! Good to see you. What do you want to tell me?
Sit down. It might not be easy for you.
Wh..What happened? Alls well?
Well, I have been pretty upset about those rumors you know. People tease me every day. They ask me how does it feel when youre in me and make nasty jokes. I am tired of this. He concluded as he sighed.
What do you want then? I asked sternly.
I want to get away from you. It is depressing to be made fun of by everyone. Look, youre like a brother to me. I would wish death over abandoning a great friend like you but its not healthy for me emotionally to continue this friendship. He was looking away as if not having the power to look me in the eyes and say it. 

Without saying a word I got out of his house and promised I would never bother him again. Few days passed but it was so awesome when we spent so much time with each other. I kept thinking about the old days.   

I thought and thought and decided I will see him for one last time. I called him and asked him to see me one last time. I told him I wanted to give him a present before we finally parted our ways. He reluctantly agreed. I got in my car and went over to his house.  

There he was, sitting on his couch, having no idea what goodbye present I was to give him thatd vanish all his depressive thoughts that he had been feeling these days. I told him to close his eyes and wait for it. He closed his eyes and I waited. Ready? I asked.  Um, yeah. With a cracking loud noise he fell to the ground. I had figured out shooting him in the forehead would give an instant result and I was obviously right.  

I kept repeating his words in my head. I would wish death over abandoning a great friend like you he had said. I had vowed to never bother him again. Well, Ill never bother him again. Its not my fault though. He had wished it over abandoning me. I just fulfilled his wish.   

If anything, I am proud to help my friend. After all, friends are there to help you, to help you turn your wishes into reality. I just turned his wish into reality.   

Police has been investigating his house to find a clue about his murderer since this morning. But why are they doing it? A friend has helped indeed to a friend in need. I did nothing wrong. I just fulfilled his wish. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am similar.  
I actually dropped out this semester and the anxiety I get about future is horrible. I just don't know myself. I was declared a loser by most people but now people tell me I should believe in myself and work hard for success. I don't know what to believe. Am I a loser or not? If not, why everyone around me convinced me I am one for all these years? Why did they always point out my flaws? Why did they never believed in me? But now they imply you have only two options in life:  

1- Work hard and be successful.  
2- Be a loser and let the system decide your fate.  
Well, if that's the case shouldn't I had started working harder earlier in life instead of perceiving myself a loser? It's just so hard for me to know who I am now as a nineteen-year-old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you let your friends makes your decisions for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one thing to get suggestions but I often feel my friends try to make decisions for me. Like, recently I dropped out of college due to many reasons. I took a long time to think about it and analyzed everything and concluded dropping out would be the best idea. Also, I was doing psychology so it isn't like I was sure to get a job after getting the BA. I knew it was the best decision for me because of my situation yet my friends would go like "OMG! don't drop out. Get the BA". Like it's the end of world if you drop psychology. It's quite annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sahara desert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mayhem..chaos..destruction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things don't always go the way you want them to go. Try to be happy even in arduous times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not believing in myself earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am your real father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]How do you deal if everyone around you seems successful and you're not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fulfilled my best friends wish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's sick. Don't hurt your boyfriend. Get away from him for fuck's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jay Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to turn an okay friend into a lifelong friend. We're friends for 6 years but lately I realized how awful I feel around him. He keeps secrets, tells lies etc. Whenever I want to talk about me he just doesn't want to listen. He keeps talking about him and I started to feel as if I am living his life not my own as evident by the fact that I started thinking about same dreams as him but my life and his life are very different. I sort of feel I have wasted a lot of time with him when he clearly isn't the type of person to keep as a lifelong friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heartbreaks, getting taken advantage of, neglect, materialism etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logging into my facebook account...*once again* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friday by Rebecca Black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. But I also think people like us  just don't have any great raw talent to work with and/or we just don't have right resources and/or there's literally not a single person who'd help us in achieving our dreams/goals.  
If you take out any famous or successful person you'll see they always had sheer luck or people helping them or natural raw talent to work with.  
Basically it's our fault but not entirely. Luck is a huge factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a liar. Your mom was with me last night and she enjoyed every minute. I'll do her again tonight. Hence your question is answered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah! Your mom was pretty satisfied. Why don't you ask her for proof? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll use a condom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I am better than everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do cats bark and dogs meow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constant neglect and emotional pain, poverty, losing a family member just to name a few. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of friends, loving family, a SO who loves me and doesn't cheat, lots of money, a little fame, good house and only positive things. Nothing bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are too many subreddits. I can't keep up with all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if you lose your home? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I feel as if I have read this answer before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I am The Mr. Experimenter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enough is enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the ways to make someone happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's genital area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one that wants everything to fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls stupidly falling for fame and fortune instead of emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By being sexist, racist, misogynist and making jokes about OP's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I accidentally sexted my teacher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite evening snack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a good face it is a good face. If it is a bad face it is a bad face. If it's a slutty face it's a fuckface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which sport can just fuck off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who in your life can just fuck off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a bad idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should a guy do if he badly wants to touch boobs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> India= looks innocent but horny as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't you quit Facebook? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't realize how lucky they're so they always assume you can have money if you want it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokingly kicking a friend when he had punched me first (jokingly). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age 11. Sixth standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But selling your soul can fill your tummy. So, it's always an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you answer a question that doesn't make sense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine yourself in a trap. You want to get out but you're locked. You can see other people passing by and you want to join them but you can't because you're bounded in that trap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people are unaware that with proper equipment nearly anyone can sound good. With some effort you can easily learn to make music these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I was a kid and didn't realize how severe it is to say something like this. My teacher was actually sorry I went through that. As I am getting older I am realizing how big an impact death can have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On footpath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would get boring at one point so when I feel it's done I'd pray that it ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing. I am 19 as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then any hot chick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if you were alone in a room with your crush for 53 hours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandpa died so I couldn't come to school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even your best friend might not be your well-wisher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singing. Chicks love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like any other. Hellish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actor or Singer. Embarrassing because I don't do either. I mean I don't even practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
