<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4131</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post, very informative. Careful with Sues Extreme, they are very fragile. I had a brand new one on a little table next to my front door and some guy knocked on the door, when I opened it he reached in and knocked over the sues extreme! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro gamers make more money than u could even imagine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I am not a father, I hope to be one someday.

Hey man, I realize we got into it a little bit back there, that's my bad. Thanks for the advice, I'll try harder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off I don't force myself in, I'll just reach in and if there is like a little table by the door I'll knock some stuff off, it's really no big deal

Second, if U had a friend U would know that friends help each other so I let my friend Carlos use my account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend Carlos posted that question about dating, he doesn't have an account so I let him use mine. It's called being s good friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's so great about ur life? U prob don't even get any girls or have a wife? Go back to the farm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever had a bad day? Wouldn't you have liked someone to make you laugh when you needed it? Dancing in front of the car is funny, and I also throw glitter in the carband sing! Most people think it's hysterical

Also that other question was from my friend Carlos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep telling urself that. Actually there is one difference, I went to college  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thx guy! I'll upvote your last 50 posts as a reward!

Edit: oops only 4 posts total, so 4 up votes it is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad I took a chance and asked for help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only difference between you and me is luck so you should get off of ur high horse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apply all the time and I went to college, there is just no work for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't cause any real damage, I'm just trying to bring a little entertainment to people's days. Most people understand and enjoy it, it's my wife that has the issue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I had a little bad luck and I have a hobby, I guess that makes me loser according to you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is easy to make fun of someone who has had some bad luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I missed my 1 chance to become a pro gamer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a professional Dota scout checking me out and my chances were ruined by other players in a ranked match. My persona involves that I ask questions either over chat or in the mic and I need the other players to respond with a"yeah yeah". For example, I'll be like "am I original?" They say "yeah yeah". "Am i sexual?" "Yeah yeah". The questions come from the song backstreets back. Anyway the other players would not say "yeah yeah" no matter how much I asked or explained. The scout said without that showmanship I can't go pro. How could fellow gamers refuse to cooperate like that, when it was so important to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wife calls me a loser because I enjoy gaming, looking for advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife is constantly calling me a loser just because I like gaming, particularly dota and the character Silencer, and am having trouble getting a job. She thinks she is so great because she is a lawyer and makes a lot of money. I like to wear a Silencer costume and go around town. I go into stores and dance around, knocking merchandise on the floor. I dance in front of cars so they can't move and the drivers get mad. I knock on houses and when they answer I scream in their faces and try to push my way in to smash their things. I like to entertain people and spread Dota awareness. I believe that is more important then making money. She yells at me all the time. I asked if we could include the Silencer costume in our lovemaking and she flipped out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about meeting girls IRL who you met in game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I feed, an open and honest discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first post to the Dota sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I feed the courier, an open and honest discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Everyone. I'd like to create an open and honest discussion about why people feed the courier. This is the second installment. This is a safe space for people to express their thoughts and feelings on the topic. Please no insults or flaming, and keep an open mind and open ears. Thank you.

I occasionally feed the courier. I am not proud of it, but I admit it. I do it primarily because it makes me feel good. For a brief moment, it feels like I control my teammates and they view me as a god. I'm not trying to ruin the game or anything like that. I also think people overreact to a courier feed. 1 courier feed hardly decides a game, and I think weaker players use it as en excuse for their own poor playing. Those are just my opinions, and I welcome yours. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a meme, it's called helping ur fellow man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro u need to take this seriously, Yourbunghole gave his number out and it was used by an employee of the company he gave it to to stalk him. The employee was a morbidly abuse man, and he eventually ended up sexually assualting him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't Dota players be happy for others success? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy playing Dota but I've taken issue with how few players are genuinely happy when others do well. When another player, my team or the enemy, makes a great play, I congratulate him, even if I died! Likewise, if another player has success in life, I congratulate him. I'm not interested in trying to tear them down. Yet when I play, I hardly ever get congratulated. Whether I made a great play or reveal my great new job(6 figures), all i get is shade. It's gotten to the point that I don't even want to tell other players about myself, my car (new black benz, fully loaded), or the girls I get. When will the average player learn to not be jealous but instead to be happy for others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful! As a reward I will upvote last 20 posts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone complains about Peruvians, but what have you done to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so tired of people complaining about Peruvians ruining the game. First off, yes they have bad internet and computers. So what? If they lose the connection just pause it. If they feed or spam, take the opportunity to try and help him mature. These people live in poverty, they need our help, not our disdain. I had a Peruvian on my team, and he died 5 times in the first 10 minutes. Did I freak out? No, I talked to him. I trained with him. I wired him money to help with his bills and family. A friendship formed. Now he is 6k MMR. I was invited to his village for his birthday, which was a great time. I ended up being intimate with a beautiful Peruvian woman. Be helpful, it pays off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a professional Dota scout checking me out and my chances were ruined by other players in ranked. My persona involves that I ask questions either over chat or in the mic and I need the other players to respond with a"yeah yeah". For example, I'll be like "am I original?" They say "yeah yeah". "Am i sexual?" "Yeah yeah". The questions come from the song backstreets back. Anyway the other players would not say "yeah yeah" no matter how much I asked or explained. The scout said without that showmanship I can't go pro. How do I deal with people who flat out refuse to cooperate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A thank you, from the ICONOCLAST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to thank everyone in this sub for their support and friendship. I just wanted to let u know that thanks to your support and my achievements here, a pretty huge opportunity has opened for me. I won't be posting for awhile as I begin this exciting new assignment, but don't think I've forgotten about you. I am, and always will be, ur iconoclast! Send me a message if U need me, but I won't be able to check too often! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's way better, not only r there mostly Americans on us servers, a lot of them r hot girls who will hang out with u IRL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA About when meeting girls IRL that you met in Dota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently went out on a date with a girl I met on Dota. She said shewas pretty and nice. I show up at the bar and BAMMO, she is a gross hog! I walked up to her and said that she should be ashamed of herself, that she was fat and ugly, and that she should leave the bar cause she was so gross it was bothering everyone. She cried and ran out. Turns out, SHE WASN'T EVEN MY BLIND DATE, just some hog girl sitting at the bar! My date showed up a little later and was pretty hot, I ended up banging her (and a friend of her's a little later!)! Be careful out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI Babu just copied your entire post, changed it to his contact info, and pasted it in at least 2 other Dota forums.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are, believe me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, you can't blame me. It's valves fault for letting me, and it's the other Dota players who look to me as an iconoclast fault for encouraging me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know yourbunghole irl and he's a transsexual. He got in trouble going into the woman's bathroom. That's why he voted for Hillary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All true brah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I missed my one shot at going pro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a professional scout checking me out and my chances were ruined by other players in ranked. My persona involves that I ask questions either over chat or in the mic and I need the other players to respond with a"yeah yeah". For example, I'll be like "am I original?" They say "yeah yeah". "Am i sexual?" "Yeah yeah". The questions come from the song backstreets back. Anyway the other players would not say "yeah yeah" no matter how much I asked or explained. The scout said without that showmanship I can't go pro. How do I deal with people who flat out refuse to cooperate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't you be happy for other people's success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It needs to be ranked for me to enjoy it. If there r no consequences then both serious games and feeding games r boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA be careful when meeting girls IRL who you met in Dota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently went out on a date with a girl I met on Dota. She said shewas pretty and nice. I show up at the bar and BAMMO, she is a gross hog! I walked up to her and said that she should be ashamed of herself, that she was fat and ugly, and that she should leave the bar cause she was so gross it was bothering everyone. She cried and ran out. Turns out, SHE WASN'T EVEN MY BLIND DATE, just some hog girl sitting at the bar! My date showed up a little later and was pretty hot, I ended up banging her (and a friend of her's a little later!)! Be careful out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly, that's annoying. Luckily as a 5K player, I can almost always stomp even if there is a feeder on my team  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If u don't take the rules of the discussion seriously please just move on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I'm serious, I'm trying to create a dialogue here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, throwing games isn't a big deal. It's a great way to blow off steam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I throw matches, an open and honest discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Everyone. I'd like to create an open and honest discussion about why I and others throw matches. This is a safe space for people to express their thoughts and feelings on the topic. Please no insults or flaming, and keep an open mind and open ears. Thank you.
I occasionally throw matches. I admit it and I'm not proud of it. However, I have my reasons. You see by skill I'm a 5k mmr player, but I like to play at the lower brackets. So for me to maximize my fun and not advance to the higher brackets, I have to purposefully lose some time. So usually I'll play a game for real and have a great time crushing scrubs, and I'll play a second game, and have a great time doing something silly, like fight for mid with someone else, feed the courier, carry kotl who pulls players back to base. Every game I play is fun. This is valves fault for not letting me choose my bracket. Since no one has reports anymore, there is no downside. So if this happens to you remember, don't hate the player, hate the game. Tell valve to let players choose their bracket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
