<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7937</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer silphroad's sliders because since there is a variable in guessing your mon's level pre-power up. silphroad's sliders make it easy for you to see both (sometimes three) potential IVs without having to retype another set of data: starting with the lowest possible level rate, got back and just slide the level slider up in whole numbers making sure the dust, cp, and hp stays the same and rate to see your other potentials pre-powerup. that's just me though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 19:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just name my mon with their IV appended after i manually calculate, no app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 19:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhh thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got three mons that don't seem to make sense (IV wise) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 09:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be after a pokemon "attacks" you? Maybe there's a roll when it attacks or jumps and if the roll hits you you'll unintentionally start throwing curves for a window of time depending on the roll when the poke attacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Is there a keyboard shortcut to "plus one/minus one" on while in a cell so you don't have to type in numbers while guessing levels and IVs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I should rephrase. Does the lucky egg have any affects on hatching "better pokemon"? Or does the lucky egg only affect xp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 07:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do lucky eggs affect eggs that you're hatching? I have a couple of 10k's was going to save them and time the lucky egg during hatching but if it makes no difference I'll start incubating the eggs now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ozark from walmart is manufactured in the same factory as yeti and everyone else so they're nearly identical except for the branding, best buy is the ozark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can try Appliance Factory outlet on 84th, they've got blemished items at sort of a discount  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice! here's my trio https://i.imgur.com/sJcAuGN.png  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a facebook cover for team Valor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's all i've really found in my limited time there. I hear utah lake in aurora is great for dartini farming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i run into magikarp pretty often along platte river near 8th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can't evolve a vaporeon, and i sure as hell didn't use any stardust, wonder what made it gain cp then...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever gain CP from visiting gyms? My Vaperon someone jumped a hundred CP without me using any stardust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do you make the stickers? ie equipment etc. just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Olde Town Arvada where the library is: three nights in a row where you can stand in one spot and be in range of three stops that (at night) are constantly lured. 20min walk and you'll run into about 20 stops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: new android version is out - update provides compatibility with nougat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there's anything else in this patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the animation but nothing shows in my jounal

 https://i.imgur.com/3M8H3uo.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game glitched when I hit 16 didn't get any rewards, did I miss anything else outside of the rewards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 23:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Team Valor. same damn thing happened to me https://imgur.com/a/Xrwer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 23:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Team Valor got three Vaporeons:

https://imgur.com/a/Xrwer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adobe after effects, xem youtube dday hoc/biet - tiem 'logo intro' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for all the luring in Olde Town tonight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 08:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw hilarious when I watched 30 people run for a gastley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 00:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made it for fun - have no idea what it'd be used for even if it were shorter hehehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 00:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just to erk you Mystic's out there hehehe go team Valor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  i'm actually team Valor (which i made first) and things got more complex as i made the other ones: Mystic had the most complex one due to the nature of it being the last one i made lol

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm actually team Valor (which i made first) and things got more complex as i made the other ones: Mystic had the most complex one due to the nature of it being the last one i made lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> team Instinct: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bnK9xGhJM6A

team Valor: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qocBChaCd9I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> team Valor: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qocBChaCd9I

team Mystic: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_hudx3e4Rg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> team Mystic: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_hudx3e4Rg

team Instinct: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bnK9xGhJM6A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a logo thingy for team Mystic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a logo thingy for team Instinct </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a logo thingy for team Valor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BIFL Request] Wind-proof umbrella. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 09:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more compact, the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 09:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come some pokemon have a blue hue behind it and others don't? I have two identical paras, they're both extra large, both with 80cp yet one has a blue hue behind it and the other one does not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 00:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could i have that ai file? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know how I can create sustaining water droplets?

I bought water-beads for a shot, it came out great but now I need to make smaller ones that affix to a product. I've tried using various ratios of glycerin and water and sprayed it on the product but the beads aren't quite round enough.

Looking to basically demonstrate an extremely hydrophobic surface. My goal is to create a macro shot of water beading at a somewhat exaggerated level.

Any help would be awesome, thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know how I can create sustaining water droplets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any programs out there that will queue up print jobs for different printers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Info:

I've got two hp laserjets that I manage - I print about 100-150 different documents a day. Each document has specific settings due to certain documents needing to pull from different trays using different media. Oh and the copy count of each document is different as well.

I'm looking for software that I can queue up jobs so I can run like a giant list of different files with different settings so I can walk away from the printer for a while. 

Currently I'm just using Acrobat Reader to print as it's the only program that reads Adobe Illustrator files correctly without actually having to open Illustrator.

Any advice is greatly appreciated, thank you ahead of time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 23:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> another lucky bastard with a SCAM spinner... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Maui Jim](http://www.mauijim.com/) sunglasses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 22:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing people put their index finger along the spine of a chef's knife instead of gripping it properly drives me utterly insane when I see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone remember that rumor way back when about Disney opening up a park but then FocusOnTheFamily stopped it? Was that legit or just some crazy lie that spread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 17:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was looking for an article to back it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anyone planning to create a hybrid/stock-water-cooled option coming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No longer a drinker but I had dinner at the School House in Olde town a bit back, caught a glimpse of their bar/lounge, looks quite nice - not really a dive bar, more like just a regular bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I impulsively bought a steam link, should have done a bit more research before pulling the trigger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really hoping that the steam link would basically stream steam so I could just do other things on my PC. Alas after a few minutes with the steam link and a quick search comfirming it's just an over-glorified interface that mirrors my display (which I already have the capability to do with my 50' HDMI cable), I'm severely disappointed.

I guess I'll just save it given the very off chance I want to play in the bedroom.

Does anyone know if the hardware is even capable to stream steam separately in a future software update? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The SO snapped this pic in Winter Park this past weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 21:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 19:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when the high sparrow hits over 9000! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 06:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King of the North!
https://i.imgur.com/odux3MX.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 06:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BURN BABY BURN!!!
https://i.imgur.com/VyEVman.gifv

awe.
https://i.imgur.com/YMQMOaP.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 01:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two cakes with the EXACT SAME message though - what I'm saying is that it's unoriginal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 23:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this some sort of template? already happened back in april:
https://i.imgur.com/rCOmrGT.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nevermind, figured it out - just needed to up my blend steps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illustrator file can be [downloaded here](https://www.dropbox.com/s/uqacji6she4s8oh/BG_01-main.ai?dl=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know how to fix these imperfections? (Link to download the work file in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 00:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u're one of the lucky bastards with a SCAM spinner, someday... someday...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there an economically sound equivalent to "Hydro Flask" (like how "Ozark Trail" is to "YETI"/"RTIC"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 08:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an RTIC tumbler for a while and recently ran into the walmart clone Ozark Trail that is nearly identical to the RTIC and YETI. Tumblers are great but it would awesome if there was a Hydro Flask clone that has the same build quality for half the price (or in terms of the YETI, a quarter of the price).

Edit: I recently discovered that MonoPrice has bottles that look identical - anyone have any experience with them? If they're exactly the same, I'd love to be able to buy a Hydroflask spout cap and pair it with the MonoPrice equivalent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 07:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is exactly why i went through a dozen EDC pens and finally landed on the [BOKER PLUS](https://amzn.com/B007BN9RZI), small sacrifice with the cartridge but the pen's design is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 09:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RTIC is half the price just as good if not, better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 09:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dave, I just ordered a SlimFold Original SS (can't wait to get it in my hands!) - anyhow, I've got some sort of odd things that I currently carry in my wallet and I've been scouring the internet to find plastic sleeves that would fit into the SlimFold's slots. Everything I've found seems to be way too wide for the SlimFold's card slots, would you happen to know of any sleeves that would be a perfect fit for your wallet? I'm looking for [exactly this](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61rOBdAKMyL._SL1000_.jpg) but with a narrow enough footprint to easily slide in and out of the SlimFold's card slots. I would not be using it for cards, more for like a spare key, band aids, thin pocket tools, etc.

On the same note, I would absolutely love some kind similar accessory that is folded or has a tab that can accommodate a photo to slide into a slot or two sort of turning the SlimFold into a faux L-wallet.

Since you're the designer/founder I thought I'd ask you direct - I can't be the only person looking for these types of inserts, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is the GIF limit is only 3MB? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to take anything under 10MB but google search yield says it supposed to be under 3MB??? that's ridiculously small! Anyone confirm this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know if there's a capacity limit on the Mk3? Looking to get a 128GB card or higher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be a bit out of the loop but I remember there's been some issues with high-capacity cards on certain cameras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 20:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the original was on colored paper, i'm sure the original i have is a copy of a copy of a copy lol - at this point i think i'll just rebuild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's another page that's a bit more complex

http://i.imgur.com/d5UKmMP.jpg

I can rebuild all the pages pretty easily in InDesign, it's just tedious is all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 07:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i choose this sample because it had the most defined artifacts, i've got 4 other pages that are much more complex than just a simple spreadsheet with the artifacting all over them. i think the source was printed on color paper or something but i'm not sure, it was a request from a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 07:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unfortunately this is just a sample, i've got about 4 pages to do - the sample posted is the simplest one. I chose that one because it had the most definition to the artifacts, the other pages are much more complex than just a spreadsheet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of an automated way to get rid of tiny little artifacts from a document that's been scanned way too many times? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 00:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/diRwqh9.jpg

Aside from making the image again from scratch or manually clearing with the marquee tool is there anything else I can do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info - looks like I'll have to wait until I build my own NAS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I've got a LaCie 5big Pro with simplyRAID and it's getting full - does anyone if I can just hot swap bigger drives without needed to format? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if ahead of time if I've asked this in the wrong sub. 

I'd like to slowly start swapping out my 4TB drives for 6 or 8TB drives. Eventually I want to just build my own NAS but budget's not having that for a while.

http://i.imgur.com/gQroLNy.png

There's nothing in the UI that I can find for a drive replacement, I know it's possible if a disk starts failing but I have no idea how I'd go about this with healthy disks.

Thanks for any info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20oz french pressed coffee

2 tbsp organic valley unsalted

1/2 tsp cayenne pepper

blend for 35sec (preset) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My official Burger King Kid's Club card  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The blue stacked letters](http://www.ideahunt.io/ideas/c29d4a82-4137-4109-a792-85d3aa35210b)

[The abstract logo](http://www.ideahunt.io/ideas/9f32d093-d39b-46ce-99b6-dca72718e8d7)

[The stylized "B" in the form of their watch](http://www.ideahunt.io/ideas/682f6a0d-0d36-41ab-9396-2e8c485c200f)

thew together some other versions their respective pages along with some mockup applications. 

Looking forward to any feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My three submissions to the BLOCKS modular smartwatch competition (direct links in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is that? i've never eaten there (but they're everywhere here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite keto meals from chain restaurants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's a nearly 10min documentary on this lol https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AVXY8OEZAEQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to set a character style based off of type condition? I would like to be able to change the font of words that are in ALL CAPS automatically. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm using data merge to automate some labels. I've got a column for descriptions and a column for directions: I was hoping there was a way to automatically set any words that are in all caps to a different font. I cannot just highlight and change as these are data merge elements. Thanks ahead for any input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a benchmade 940 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to replace all instances of an action? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a very long action that I built a long time ago on a previous version of PS, I'm not sure what adobe has changed but  now the actions "select", "delete", "Merge Layers" are no longer valid operations. Thanks ahead! anything helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About to make my first order, total is well over $75, any coupon codes available? (signed up but didn't get any code e-mailed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 22:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 09:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The skin i'm using is the titan skin.

I ended up going into the application support folder and deleting all of my addons and it seemed to have fixed it. had to re-add custom repositories but everything's running smoothly again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP! I've looked up and down InDesign and cannot for the life of me figure out how to get rid of these little lines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie [RUBBER](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1612774/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking out of a straw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S6E2] Rhaegal and Viserion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not compatible with MM (i think). FC when launched, i'm running dirty unicorns 10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real life inspiration for the movie [RUBBER](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1612774/?ref_=nv_sr_1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FireTV USB path substitution. What else can I move besides thumbnails? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering what else I can move anything else from my FireTV - currently it takes a whopping 5GB internally. My advancedsettings.xml is as follows:

    advancedsettings
    pathsubstitution
      substitute
        from/storage/emulated/0/Android/data/org.xbmc.xbmc/files/.xbmc/userdata/Thumbnails//from
        to/storage/sdcard1/external_sdcard//to
      /substitute
     /pathsubstitution
    /advancedsettings
     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know the most economical way to get rid of a bunch of slash/tree trimmings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just trimmed down a large tree in the Lakewood area, we've got about a full pickup-truck's bed worth of branches. Was hoping to find a cheap and easy solution to get rid of the slash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 18:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on OSX, installed normally - have been running KODI for years on the same machine forever. Suddenly noticed that now I cannot contact any repos whatsoever, it's really strange: I can scrape, I can stream, I've got weather, I can use youtube and other apps but repositories all give me the error: cannot contact repo.

http://i.imgur.com/kgtriDp.png
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I managed to install everything via zip - it seems installed but if i open up channel config it hangs at 80% =T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accidentally cleared my Kodi data and had to start over, pseudoTV stalls at 2% when downloading and crashes Kodi - am I missing something here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 20:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the amazon FireTV 4K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Denver. Other than the more than occasional smell of weed, the population has exploded which makes traffic sucks balls and it feels like housing has skyrocketed (although that's probably everywhere).

On the plus side, because of the population growth we're seeing some really cool restaurants and other non-weed business being established/opened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else unable to connect to repositories? I can scrape and stream just fine but all my repositories are empty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 20:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> might try that - my UPS has never failed me before, i think this was just a faulty router. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 19:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info!

I've been trying to contact the seller on ebay, completely unresponsive. Very interesting to hear that the warranty should be tied to the device though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will continue to scour the internet for some sort of fix I guess. 

I've contacted the seller multiple times, he's completely unresponsive =(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two aggregate ports is what sold me on this router, dual gigabit coming from a NAS is awesome. Most of my stuff is wired, the wireless isn't that important to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My nighthawk x8 ac5300 crapped out on me, netgear won't RMA because it's registered to someone else (because I bought it on ebay) - what are my options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had the router for about two months and it has been flawless. There was a power outage recently and even though the router was plugged into a UPS it somehow bricked the router. Solid amber power LED; hard reset does nothing, doesn't even flash the LEDs no matter how long I hold it.

I took a risk and got the router on ebay which turned out ok until the brick, I called netgear but the seller had already registered it under his name and is now unresponsive. Netgear won't RMA it because it's registered to someone else and I have no receipt for proof of purchase so now I'm out nearly $300 and no network!

What are my options now outside of dropping $350 on a replacement router?

Thanks in advance for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I plugged my Sony DSC-RX100M3 used to mount as a camera with neat little dated folders when I was on windows8 but with windows10 the camera it does like a system mount as two separate drives with arbitrary folders, how do I fix this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 07:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that anything is missing but it's a pain to have to seek out my images and video in different places; it's simply a pain to navigate. Any help would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 23:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been waiting on steve for my coin forever, can't wait to get mine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Made two tasks:

**Task: Flash LED**

* Torch:on
* wait: 200ms
* Torch: off
* wait:200ms
* Go to 1

**Task: LED stop**

* Stop: Flash LED
* Torch: off

**Profile 1**: Alarm ClockFlash LED

**Profile 2**: Alarm DoneLED stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I set a profile that flashes my torch when an alarm goes off and continues to do so until I turn off the alarm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess this would be a loop question. I can get the torch to go on/off with a task that flashes it but I'd like it to loop that task until the alarm is turned off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 16:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was the first camera i tried using but sadly it FC on launch for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Her FB page](https://www.facebook.com/TashaCosplay/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasha and her dead-on Tracer Cosplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ROMs aren't coming with the stock camera, what's the best 3rd party camera? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 22:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running Dirty Unicorns 10.0 which I absolutely love but the camera is garbage - what's your go to 3rd party camera app?

I'm looking for an app that shoots in RAW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balzs Bnk ported Flappy Bird over onto a eVic-VTC Mini </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Bowie knife will stand in Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 22:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you Shogun but you gotta rep your hood set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 16:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 22:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i found the source, it's on a behance profile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tracked it down to a digital rendering: https://www.behance.net/gallery/33765682/Superman-logo-shelf-interrior-design-bookshelf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does this exist or was this a digital mockup, can't find it anywhere - superman shelf. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 06:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 09:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been having the same issue, not sure why it's not working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manually making a family tree (work in progress) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Information is so difficult to track down especially when my grandfather had six wives, no pizzazz or shine to the tree yet but here it is: http://imgur.com/wIq23wY critiques welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 21:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/QA2wXqB.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The total blender presets are 65s, 35s, 180s, 23s, 65s, 60s - these do not match the manual at all: does anyone have the updated chart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 22:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: If you're having notification issues remember to manually give your apps the correct permissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 18:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heavily rely on custom notification sounds so as I know when I really need to look at my phone, for months I thought I was having syncing issues with gmail and hangouts. Gmail would do like this batch notify and it'll try and play like 4 notification sounds at once and it wasn't like instant push. Then hangouts would only use stock notification sounds.

I don't know why I didn't think of it before but I eventually I figured out giving hangouts and gmail the right permissions all my notifications started working normally again. This may be due to the ROM I'm running defaults the least amount of permissions possible on stock apps but I'm just glad the issue is finally solved, just thought I'd post this in case anyone else has been having custom notification sound issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] How come my iG videos don't load anymore? There's just a turning arrow on all videos (my feed and even my own posts). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 21:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> browsing /r/all with your pick of exclusions is actually pretty awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 18:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm running AOKP, camera is junk - do you know if it's possible to download the stock camera?

tried [this method](http://techxat.com/how-to-download-install-lg-g4-camera-apk/) but the app won't launch, looks like because this method only works on 5x and not 6x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this. is. awesome! had no idea this was a thing, no more three-finger-clicking for me =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what happened to the three-finger-middle-click? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 08:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, just came back to ubuntu from about two years on mint and i'm feeling a bit lost. When I tap my trackpad with three fingers all it does is bring up application switcher (alt+tab). I can't seem to find any three-finger tapping options in settings, what am I missing here? I'm on 15.10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Updating multiple files with linked placed files all at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 22:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I work for a company that creates custom labels for many chemical products. In order to streamline various sizes that are requested I create what I call a "master label", with those master labels I then place those files in another document, scale for the appropiate dimentions, doubled up (sometimes tripled up) along with volume text (net weight/volume).

This file is then used by another computer to print via Acrobat.

Theoretically if I update the master file, the changes should ripple across any file that uses that link - which it does if you open the file in Illustrator on the computer it was originally created on. But if it's opened on a different computer using Acrobat it will display and print what the file looked like when it was last saved (not showing the changes that made in the master file).

My workaround for this is to open up all the files that uses the linked master file, select something, nudge it and nudge it back and then save. This then changes the 'last saved' and the file is now updated.

It has been an absolute chore to do this, each brand I work with has at a minimum of 40 different files that uses linked placement and if there's a small change like say a new phone number I have to change it on all the master files then open up all the files that references the linked files, nudge, nudge back, and save.

I work with over 2000 different brands so when there's a change, the simple task becomes a daunting nightmare.

So my initial question is: is there a way to update a bunch of files all at once ensuring that the linked files are refreshed and is displaying the latest save of the master file?

Also, have I approached this situation correctly in using the "placed linked" file or is there a much better, more efficient way of handling this?

EDIT: so I've come up with sort of a workaround. I ran into this script called [WR-SAVEcloseALL](http://illustrator.hilfdirselbst.ch/dokuwiki/en/skripte/javascript/wr-saveandcloseall) - I open up every document that think has been affected by changes and run the script, it saves the illustrator document and moves onto the next one until all open documents have been saved. It's not what I want to do ideally but it sure as hell beats opening up the doc, nudging an object and nudging it back and saving. Hope this helps someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> added a screen shot. it's definitely the right folder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yessir i am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could not find waze folder in com.waze http://i.imgur.com/bRRfTf8.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 22:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry that completely spaced my mind, i will be sure to do so from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 23:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.baddaddysburgerbar.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 23:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we only have one here that i know of but the seem to be around

http://www.baddaddysburgerbar.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still getting an error in sideload.zip - man, i'm getting ready to give up on this venture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my system recovery has changed from lrx21t.g870aUCU1boc5 to KOT49H.g870aucu1ane4

looks like recovery went from lollipop back to kitkat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not sure how i would do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found myself an G870A debrick image, got back download mode, at least i have that again lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it won't let me flash either...

something has happened and now i don't have download mode, it only lets me go into recovery =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm using three different versions of odin and flashing various combinations of kernels, modems, cache, what-have-you. at one point i lost recovery ability but i've got that back now.

do you know if there is there anyway i can flash a custom recovery through odin? i'm thinking if i can get a custom recovery i can just flash an unsigned rom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I tried but it won't let me enter any characters into the box - it's really weird, no numbers, no letters, no nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after multiple tries I managed to pull the zip file smartswitch creates in the temp folder but odin will not flash the tar.md5s, I get the stupid SW REV CHECK FAIL error =[

i'm looking at the files smartswitch downloaded, they're dated last modified May 29, 2014! what the hell - smartswitch pulling legacy files?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> amazing! will come back with my findings tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i see the file downloading, i will probably have to wait until tomorrow to try and do this though as i'm at work and it's about time to end the day. thank you so much for your help!

you wouldn't happen to know of the tools i need to convert them over to odin flashable containers would u? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
