<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8335</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 12:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that's an interesting and very good point!  From another perspective, though,  when we move toward making citizens legally accountable for abiding by newer social rules, many people tend to make that same type of argument - that authoritarianism is spreading. 

So if you look at with things like laws against workplace discrimination on the basis of race/gender/age, or  how so many American pharmacists run into legal problems in refusing to prescribe medications that run against their religious ideologies, as a more specific example, people who are being held accountable to these relatively new standards tend to argue the same thing and feel very strongly *their* freedom is being infringed upon, that totalitarianism is at work, when in fact these laws aim to protect the freedom of all, freedom *from* discrimination. I can't see anything really coming of these types of pronoun cases, but we are definitely, in Canada, moving toward making everyone accountable for accepting, at least in the public sphere, more modern, progressive views on gender identity.  I think that's a net positive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 09:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like "how deep this hole goes" is actually not nearly so deep as  what you read and hear on the internet would suggest, especially on echo-chambery-websites like this can be. In the real world you will plausibly never meet anyone who thinks or feels like this. Anyway, people who get riled up over non-binary gender ideas, slippery-slope-argument-style, are highly reminiscent of people in the not-so-distant-past (and present even) who believe things like "Well if we let gays marry then next they'll want to marry animals!" or "if a man's attracted to another man, then he's just as likely a pedophile too!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 08:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely people do that! I'm a teacher and many Ms's correct people or tell people who call them Mrs or Miss to call them Ms. Some older women I know if called "Ms" or "Miss" will correct them to call them "Mrs." Maybe it's more common in a setting like a school where people get called "M-- Whatever" all day long. But yes, many people don't care either.

"Ms" is not the same as "Miss"; "Miss" denotes unmarried female, and "Ms" is a marriage-status-neutral title, like "Mr". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 07:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? A person is given a name at birth. They may prefer to go by a nickname their parents did not choose. A person whose preferred title is "Ms" may correct someone who calls her "Miss" or "Mrs". They may change their first name into something very different. They may change their last name either for marriage or another reason. We still deserve to have that change respected, as a gender change or correction should be similarly respected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 14:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the most recent polls have him polling, for a 4-way race, at 39-44%, which still leaves a "majority" not voting for him - those polls also doesn't include the people who presumably fear him yet plan on not voting anyway or spoiling their ballot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from *The Girl with the Lower Back Tattoo* by Amy Schumer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 07:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 05:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe check out [this wikipedia article on human height averages](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_average_human_height_worldwide). For males, the average in Germany is 175, Russia 177, Italy 176.5, and UK 175-178. 

Best,

North America / East Asia / Northern Africa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 08:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you funny! You seem mad bro. You really never got the memo on eating vegetables being, uh, extremely relevant to your health? I'm sorry to hear about that. TL;DR: eat lots of veggies son :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 06:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the past year in the China, I've had 0 colds or flus. Anything more than 1 every few months seems a lot. Are you eating enough vegetables? Exercising? Washing your hands regularly? Getting enough sleep?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 06:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manlet? Kit Harington is 5'8", which is about 1 inch shorter than the average white male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say that at all. In terms of prep and performance in court, which was far and away most important to his case, she was powerful, astute, and convincing if not flawless in that courtroom - up until the choice to put him on the stand. Her personal choices re: Naz were ridiculous, but she learned a valuable lesson and, for someone who likely graduatead law school 5 years ago, I think this completely fictional character has incredible potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love it. It's tense and smart and gripping in ways I can't really even describe. I guess I'd say it's like *The Wire* had a 10-episode love child with a well-written *Law and Order.* It's accessible, but very smart. Some people (e.g., other commenters above) feel it's lost a bit of momentum but I love the direction things went. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anecdotally, when I started practising vipassana (as taught by SN Goenka) I found myself much more prone to bursts of creative insight, like my mind was massively more clear and free. The removal of mental blocks/obstacles you mention can be pretty amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, absolutely don't be held back by this.
I'm a bit like you - I went into my training with a very strong meditation practise and was one of the least physically flexible people in my YTT class. In fact, it was yogic philosophy that really drew me, not the physical aspects of yoga. In my teacher training, we had SO MANY assorted strengths and weaknesses. Some people's main struggle was the pranayama. A few people were reeeeally inflexible. Many struggled, instead, with the theory. Others could hardly sit through our daily meditation sittings at first. Others had trouble with the timetable. Etc. Etc. 

Yoga is about SO MUCH MORE than having perfect-form asana, and we should not worry about being judged by others in our practise, nor should we judge others - especially in a YTT setting! Further, your YTT will enable you to grow immensely in your practise in exactly the ways you need, which may or may not end up having anything to do with those tight hamstrings of yours :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Not to concern-troll, but the comments thus far are a bit confusing at best. I feel inspired by this man. I understand the desire to be a householder (as I am) instead of a monk, but if the general r/yoga consensus on a brahmacharya who eats a simple diet is "welp, that sounds like a shit life" that's just... weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 11:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am extremely confused - why is Charles being brought BACK to his house on a stretcher? Is he coming home to die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 04:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a Gr 9 textbook at the end of the school year I found something interesting : "Ms subject8335 is a" followed by a short word that had been scratched out basically completely. At first it SORT OF looked like "cunt" but I could have been projecting. It really was impossible to tell. But the mystery killed me. Was I a cunt? Did I stop being a cunt at some point? Or had I been something else all along (a sweetie, a weirdo, a bitch, a beaut)? Had the same person judged me and then reevaluated? Or had someone else tried to correct him? I still wonder to this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was taught that showering after yoga actually will drain your prana, or vital energy, that you rejuvenated during your practise. Unless it's a hot yoga class, I never shower after my practise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think certainly a day-to-day mix could be beneficial, particularly when you're still discerning what works best for you.  For example, personally, traditional hatha is my core practise, but I do vinyasa a couple of times a week, yin 1-2 times a week, and less regularly kundalini and ashtanga; I get different and valuable benefit from each.

If you really want to "feel like [you]'ve gotten a workout in", then you're probably best, well, working out! You mention you have bad joints but even if you're not referring to your knees, you can still work out in ways that are low impact (swimming, using cross trainers, vigorous walking). I'm a bit against the grain here because I was trained in a highly classical style of yoga (Sivananda) and studied under teachers in a tradition that has remained largely unchanged in many decades, if not centuries; more modern approaches to yoga don't always resonate with me, so I'm maybe not the best to advise on your question. 

About the $, yeah, it can be a bit much! Many studios have intro packs, sometimes unadvertised, where you get unlimited monthly classes for a big discount for those new to the studio. But even 1-2 drop in classes a week will make a big difference in your exposure and practise. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power Yoga tends to move very quickly, and most classes I've attended follow a similar structure to Ashtanga, whereas "Vinyasa" classes are sometimes similar to Ashtanga classes, but can vary immensely. Power yoga will feel more like a "workout". 

Personally, power yoga classes are so quick I feel like I'm hardly practising yoga, but then I'm a bit of a traditionalist I guess and have different goals in my practise than the ones you mention. 
I'd recommend going to classes over watching yoga videos while you're fairly new in establishing your own practice. Try a variety and see what works best for you. There's no saying you can't do both, either - or even try other styles too. You may be surprised with what resonates most with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://dailyhealthpost.com/4-hidden-ways-drinking-ice-cold-water-is-bad-for-you/) is an article with references to findings based on a few different select studies.

Anecdotally, my digestion definitely improved when I stopped drinking water colder than room temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 03:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8th year teacher now. Right now I'm teaching overseas, living on a school campus so my situation is pretty incomparable, but before I moved I found a pretty good routine. I would always work hard throughout the day and finish my work by 4 or 4:30 then go home. For each meal I would make, I would make sure to have 4 meal-sized servings out of it, so I'd only be cooking supper once throughout the week (at least once during the work week I would do take out). 

Lunches were very simple snack-kind of things (simple salads that took 1 minute to assemble, fruit, cheese, bread/crackers, nuts) or more leftovers. This freed up a LOT of time in the evenings and I would usually either run/workout or do yoga every night, and both saturdays and sundays, so I had 4 workouts, 4 long yoga sessions, and a good amount of free time afterward to chill, see friends, watch tv, whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comments were really interesting and sad and thought-provoking to read. I'm definitely not from a place as rough as detroit, but have taught at some pretty rough schools, including several now-gang members and have seen sometimes sweet kids, with massive potential, slip into lives or violence and crime and misery. To take u/GeneralMalaiseRB's idea a step further: many of these gang members, like the one who survived his accident, more often than not come from terrible family situations, whose lives and choices (rightly or wrongly) seem mapped out from them from the beginning, at least in hindsight. It seems quite likely, ironically enough, that this drunk-riding, reckless, plausible gang member actually had a pivot point in his own life similarly tragic to the sympathy you felt for those mother-less kids. That gang member may actually BE, in a metaphorical sense, one of those children you felt such sympathy for.

And from another angle, often people, when given a new lease on life, especially one that seems unlikely or even miraculous, also take their lives in markedly new directions. Hopefully he was able to use this as a huge wake-up call. Hopefully the mother's children will be OK. There's a lot of apathy in the universe, but there's also an infinity of possibilities too. 

How do we respond to the apathy we encounter? You mentioned feeling crushed by it - which is valid. I'm sorry you felt like that. I like to think of it as an impetus to push me to do more good in the world, to ease more suffering, to remain hopeful and compassionate. The universe may be apathetic - which is the best reason for us NOT to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking semi-human animals? No problem. Fully functioning underwater society? Sure. Portraying December 31 in Labrador as mild without a spec of snow in sight? Completely unconscionable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was beautiful watching that in real time. For those few episodes before we learned who he was, I had such compassion for him and frustration for how he was being mistreated. And then he flipped the whole show on its head. He was one of the great characters in TV history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would reapply - in fact, I was in this exact situation several years ago and DID reapply, then sent an e-mail to the principal thanking again for her consideration for the first position, and said that if they decided to choose another candidate for that position, I would be happy to be considered for the newly posted one as well. It may also help to add a couple of things not mentioned in the interview that may make you a good candidate for the first grade position as well. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 07:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am queasy just reading the vast majority of these suggestions. Is this just a giant troll thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 05:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/index.asp) is some information from the government of Canada website on immigration. Most people your age interested in immigrating come to Canada for university - after 4 years living in Canada as a permanent resident (or for 4 full years out of 6, rather) you can apply for citizenship, so in theory you could probably become a citizen in 6-7 years. 

Even if you come to study and change your mind, Ontario has many great universities in either a metropolis like Toronto, very rural areas, and everything in between -- as long as you can afford it, that is -- which can give you plenty of time to decide if Canadaland is right for you while getting a good education.

Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I would just up- or downvote the comments i most agreed with, but just in case y'all are doing an informal poll with the feedback here: I'm hard-passing on the mobile site for almost every single reason listed above. I was disproportionately irritated with virtually everything about the mobile site til i was able to opt out. Reminds me of finding that damn U2 album in my itunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 17:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually if I can hear things like birds or voices outside, I will put in earplugs. Not because I "need" silence to meditate, but it helps my practise for sure to be in as quiet/dark a space as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 10:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. A period is probably best, or possibly a semi-colon if you elaborate in the rest of the paragraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 15:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on how long we've been seeing each other. If it's only been a month or two, I wouldn't sweat it. I want to get married, but sometimes men really aren't interested in marriage until they fall in love or meet the right woman. If it's been a few months or longer, though, and they expressed that adamantly, I'd let him know my own need to be with someone who is open to marriage, and that if he was sure on his position I'd have to honour our differences and end the relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 13:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to INFJHealing's advice, I'd recommend you begin a meditation practise as soon as possible. This is BY FAR the best single practise you can do if you're looking to deal with anxiety. Cardio will help, but it, in my experience, can't hold a candle. r/meditation is a good place to check out if you're a complete beginner.

My other recommendation is to start an asana (yoga posture) practise asap. Pranayama and asanas go hand in hand, and if you go to a good yoga class, you will leave feeling rejuvenated and noticeably less anxious. Pranayama on its own will only take you so far. Meditation combined with a regular yoga and pranayama practise can take you anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 10:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to do this pretty compulsively, and then HAD to figure out the exact midway point between random Point As and Bs. Still do, just not nearly as much, and it's less obsessive and just, uh, intense interest... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 10:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, neither? I would say that Emile Hirsch's performance is good, and that he brings a unexpected, unique charm to McCandless that I never imagined when reading the book. As far as Penn's directing, I would say it was brilliant.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha!! Thanks for reminding me of this!! I've always been a voracious reader but I had no idea that that would be something that would get me so terribly. Remember the unique joy when a new sign/notice was put up? It was like Christmas! That instructions pamphlet I remember devouring countless times too - it was pretty satisfying for a while, in its own way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best advice is to scale back the impulse to find out everything you can about the experiences of others - sign up, try to increase your sitting time between now and then, and let go of your expectations as much as possible. You will not have the same experience as the other people who have gone before you, and it will likely NOT be what you expect in most ways. And don't be afraid of the 10-hour-thing.. you'll figure it out when you're there.

Assuming you go: have a happy course :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 08:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first heard that song outside the context of The Wonder Years my 7 or 8 year old mind was kinda blown. My music teacher was playing it in class or something and I was like "Whaaaat? Why are you playing The Wonder Years Song?" and she explained it was a "real" song by the Beatles and I just... didn't understand what was happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Philippines elects its first transgender politician </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 10:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 12:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oprah Winfrey. Not that she'd necessarily be the BEST candidate possible out of the millions of non-politicians, but as a person, she is immensely inspiring and would give such a dynamic, unprecedentedly fresh spin on the whole business. She'd be like the anti-Trump of 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love triangles very seldom end well.

Bee doesn't invite me to the Saturday festivities because he doesn't want Dee hearing about them showing up to any of them. This pains me

Have you spoken to Bee about this, telling him how you feel? You are not your brother. You can and should have a social life that does not always involve your brother. If Bee thinks you are a package deal, you should make it clear that his friendship is important to you.

I want everyone to get along, but this situation is impossible to deal with. I hate this drama. 

You want everyone to get along - this is why you're miserable. A situation like this will naturally cause friction and drama. You have not caused the drama, and cannot fix it, nor is it your place to do so. The best you can do is accept it, and that the friend circle you were a part of is, at least temporarily, not going to be the same. You can mourn the loss of it, but ultimately you should accept it. Be a good brother to Dee, and be a good friend to Bee, and it wouldn't hurt to expand your social circle, forming and developing new friendships.

 I have an irking suspicion that the girl is simply milking sympathy out of the two, which has led me to silently resent her. 

I hope this isn't the case, but I suppose that's possible - we don't know her here, after all. Either way, don't resent her. What use is that resentment serving you? Resentment is toxic, for you more than anyone else. Let it go. You don't need to be friends with her, and if she is being manipulative that will come out sooner rather than later. If someone asks your opinion, be careful in offering it, but you're best off letting this whole thing play out and letting go of your anger and resentment.

As a bit of a PS, the language you use in these statements is a little troubling, though maybe you were just being hyperbolic with the metaphor (emphasis mine): 

Here came my brother, Dee, coming to **steal the girl**. For months, they said their relationship was unofficial. Of course, **he succeeded at winning her over, but victory was not without cost.**

Girls and women are not objects or prizes to be won. As a side piece of advice, you may want to ask yourself if this is actually how you see girls, or women. If you do, even partially, this will not bode well for you in your relationship future. This statement too, is troubling: "Dee thinks Bee is being a pansy, because Bee is so upset that "**he couldn't get [the girl] into a relationship with him."** For Dee to think that if you can't "get" a girl into a relationship with someone that makes that person a "pansy", or less of a "man"... well, that's a really unhealthy type of approach too. Again, girls are not manipulable objects. Maybe be mindful of when these kinds of statements or ideas are being thrown around, and if you're being influenced by that type of ideology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 07:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest that your "only issue" is not that your parents aren't religious -- though absolutely you should discuss your inclinations and beliefs open and honestly with them. I'm more concerned by this:

I don't know for sure, but I can't imagine myself getting married and having children. 

If you don't know for sure, you're not ready. You are extremely young (I'm guessing 17)? And someone who was not raised in the Church, and therefore of maybe a few years' full exposure to Catholicism and the Catholic faith? Just as someone your age is in all probability far too young to marry another person, making the choice to become a nun (which is considered metaphorically marrying Christ) is a MASSIVE permanent decision, one that the vast majority of young women, however strong their faith, are simply too young and inexperienced to make.

What's the rush? You will have your entire lifetime to devote to sisterhood if/when the time is right. There are so many other ways you can live your life over the next several years: maybe enrol in a Catholic post-secondary institution. Study theology. Be active in the Church. Do mission work. Just continue to grow and know yourself and your relationship with God before making this commitment. 

Similarly, your relationship experience when you're a teenager is not a good indicator for your suitability for marriage as woman 10+ years older--you need to thoroughly discern that that is NOT the life you want. 

You can live a life of chastity, poverty, and service in the years while you develop as a young woman, to truly discern what you want. Again, there really is no rush, and if you feel there *is* a rush, that's probably a warning sign that something may be amiss in your spiritual or personal life.

Good luck :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 07:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not worth it. You will both be representing the past with one another when you both should be moving forward. If you're breaking up with them, then they will probably still be emotionally "holding out" for you, which is a misdirection of their mental/emotional energy, and unhealthy in general. You will need to let both of each other go to make space for the people who are right for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 07:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if this man isn't seeing other women, if you and he haven't had the exclusivity talk, then he's not your boyfriend, you're not his girlfriend, and therefore you didn't cheat on him and have no reason to "confess." 

Are you being honest with yourself about your residual feelings for her? In other words, are you more attracted to this woman than the man you're seeing? That might be a bigger part of the emotional cheating that's causing your guilt feelings. But if you are serious about moving on from her, you need to really cut her out of your life. No more drunken texting, no hanging out when you move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, friend :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you did a 10-day course but decided not to continue vipassana, but mindfulness instead? Why did you make that choice? (I'm not criticising at all, just genuinely curious.) 

To answer your questions: would mindfulness conflict with kundalini? No, I don't suppose so, if only because mindfulness is a bit more of a general and spiritually neutral practise.

would kundalini yoga potentially open up my chakras allowing me to reach the same experience through the breathing exercise that I do?

The breathing exercise you're referring to, I assume, is a a form of pranayama. Pranayama, like the practise of kundalini yoga, will be largely useless and even potentially harmful if you are not on a yogic path already, which encompasses more than just doing pranayama and meditation, especially if these practises are done casually or without a pure intention. 

Re: opening your chakras: your chakras should be "cleared" or "cleaned" before you worry too much about opening them. (Warning: lame analogy ahead, sorry) Think of your chakras like a train station, a station of energy. If the train station is in a huge mess, untidied, hasn't been swept or mopped, trash cans overflowing, it's really not suited to be "open" to the public. It won't be efficient as a station, and will likely end in an even bigger mess. First you need to clean it, purify, then you can think about opening them up. Again, casual meditation and pranayama will not make a lot of progress here -- it requires purifying the mind as well, regular practise of asanas if possible, a sattvic diet, and maybe a change in lifestyle. But what exactly do you want to accomplish? Do you want the rush that comes from unleashed spiritual energy? Do you want tangible evidence of your progress? Or do you want actual spiritual progress?

If you feel comfortable PMing me your city, I'd be happy to help you find a studio/yoga centre that may be near you that could be really helpful with appropriately trained teachers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 15:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree. (though anyone who criticises *Girls* for being hard to watch because of wildly self-absorbed, socially/personally self-destructive characters will be completely unable to handle even a minute of Mickey!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 15:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude! Ilana totes came first. *Broad City* the webseries began filming in '09, about three years before *Girls*. And Ilana's character is meant to be a fictionalised version of herself, so arguably Ilana could have come at any point between 1987-2009. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 15:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the extremely limited information given in your post, I would ballpark your likelihood of enjoying this show at, uh, at least 40-42%.

I wouldn't say it's "extremely" funny, though there are absolutely hilarious moments. It is certainly a "good comedy," though, albeit rather more relatable if you're a young woman. Definitely check out the first few episodes and see if it's your cup of tea. What's an hour or two? And let us know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 15:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are without a doubt meant to be immature and grotesquely self-absorbed, including Hannah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 13:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a few (probably 50+%) of the vipassana assistant teachers I've met are *extremely* cautious of yoga in general, in how it can "manipulate" energy. Some centres will even bar students from sitting 2nd or later courses if they've indicated they are yoga instructors as well.

The statement you gave about the desire for Kundalini coming from the ego? I tend to agree with that, actually, from a limited sample of people I've met (including some people on r/yoga and maybe even this sub). A lot of people truly do seem to want a dramatic, immediate spiritual experience and power and transformation without putting in the "work." I think that's often a combination of ego and/or spiritual laziness (weird term, sorry) and impatience.

In my understanding, the type of Kundalini practises we see now are modern in the way your teacher alluded to. Classical hatha yoga (i.e., lonnnnng way back), it was believed, did very subtly balance and calibrate one's prana, or vital energy/life force, and in this process, it was believed, kundalini could in an advanced practitioner be awakened. The former happening was a slow but unavoidable effect of the practise of yoga, whereas the latter was very rare. This is what my teachers have taught me, anyway.

Personally, I am a classical hatha yoga teacher and a vipassana meditator, but I am very cautious about kundalini practises and would never recommend to a student who is not very solidly on the spiritual and yogic path already, leading a very sattvic lifestyle, with a noticeably growing taming of the mind. 

PS - I chuckle whenever I hear the "two horse" or "two holes" analogy; it's like a broken record at vipassana centres! But, well, mostly true I think..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 11:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great question! I've thought about this quite a bit. First, I think there is certainly a way to be mindful when we engage in sexual activity, whether it's alone or with an SO, a mindfulness not unlike mindfulness in other fairly ordinary but pleasurable activities. One important thing a vipassana meditator will do, however, is be careful that all things are in moderation. For a kind of lame analogy, as a lover of chocolate, it's OK to eat it once in a while, of course. But if I need to have a piece every hour, it's already become personally and spiritually problematic. 

Secondly, in saying this:
I m wondering if there is times where masturbating....is bad in terms of used as an escapism of an emotion, stress, boredom

you're kind of answering your own question: If you are aware that when you get stressed/bored you feel the need to masturbate, then you're using it as escapism. Go sit instead.

It may be helpful to ask the following kinds of questions too:

* Am I doing this because I feel a desperate need for it? 

* Is it interfering with my mindfulness -- i.e., I can't focus on X and Y while doing X and Y because my thoughts can't help but gravitate toward sex/the desire to masturbate?

* Am I attached to the practise? If I go without it, will I become frustrated, angry, or irritated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Handmaid's Tale coming to Hulu; Elisabeth Moss to play Offred </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 05:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in a position where you are rebuffed and decide to re-initiate or "try harder" as you say, I would say that's in the "desperate" category. Personally, I don't initiate with men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried sitting on a chair, with or without cushions? It is best to keep the spine as straight as possible, but there's no reason you can't make yourself more "comfortable." 
I hope your pain isn't so bad that that won't work for you...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 16:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol

First, my friends would be shocked because I don't "hook up" with randos. But once they got over that shock, they wouldn't think much of it because they know I'm a fan of the south asian men.

Anyway, don't worry too much about your ethnicity. Plenty of girls are into Indian dudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 16:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several good warning signs listed here already. The only one I would add would be if the conversation's tone is, by his doing, really heavily flirtatious from the get-go and almost never deviates from that. Learned that warning sign first hand a few months ago.

If you really want to make sure you're avoiding being pumped and dumped, I would recommend waiting until you and he have a) been dating for at least a month b) have gone out with him several times and c) are in an exclusive relationship before sleeping together. 

Most women (and men) really hate doing that for various reasons, but that's truly the best way imo. A man interested in only sex will be VERY UNLIKELY to wait around that long, and will also not lie to you about exclusively dating you unless he's a scumbag which, in my experience, is very rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't put a whole lot of stock in those types of reports and studies, but I visited Melb in December, and damn, I 3 3 3 it and would move there in a heartbeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's a dry heat, right? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 04:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.first30days.com/breaking-up/articles/breaking-up-is-hard-to-do/1.html) is a good article giving some more spiritual but practical advice on dealing with breakups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't want to hear that what they're currently chewing is cancer causing. There's a time and place to bring those things up, and in the middle of a meal is really not the time, unless they've begun the conversation themselves.

A lot of people truly aren't interested in the cause, or care. You can express your ideas but like you said, you ARE losing mental energy, and you are likely better off accepting that some of your friends will not be moved by your arguments. If you can't accept that, your friendship will turn to shit.

The "leverage" you seek will probably best come from you living your life as you see fit, expressing your ideas calmly and rationally from time to time, and supporting causes you identify with. Getting all angry and emotional over it just alienates people who may actually be receptive in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of actual LSD on the tab can vary quite a bit, so you're always taking a risk of getting a higher dose, unless you know your dealer/supplier really well. 

Second, your environment and who you're with and what state of mind you're in when taking it also affect your trip quite a bit, and if you're not able to control or manage those things, it could be a very unpleasant experience. 

That said, about 15 years ago, I did LSD twice, and both times were amazing, eye-opening, and uniquely spiritual experiences. Two of the best and most memorable experiences of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 15:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will either either jokingly or seriously (depending on the person who makes such a statement) somehow convey that I work more than enough to make up for it the other 10 months of the year. 50+ hour work weeks are absolutely the norm, for example, which more than compensates for 2 months vacation. Furthermore, most teachers TRULY need that vacation, and will burn out fast without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 08:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you e-mail the center they may tell you how likely it is. I remember one time I was waitlisted they were very helpful; another time they were ultra-vague and I didn't get in.  9 people ahead of you isn't much for a big course with a lot of likely cancellations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 14:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Hannah was a forever-unpaid intern @ the law firm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 05:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just called them. They have 5 copies. I like you very much. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! but I'm looking for a paper copy.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have it at the store on Fuzhou :/ And the amazon price was something like 250RMB and would've taken a while to get to me. It's my plan B though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like being laid off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 12:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interesting article - thanks for posting! It's difficult to make  definite conclusions after only a few days' experience with a technique. 
Personally, my spiritual and religious teachers have always warned me vehemently against mixing techniques in this kind of way, and would be disturbed by an experiment such as this. For those two reasons I'm a little dubious about the conclusions..but great read though.
Might want to x-post this on r/meditation - some of the readers there would really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 03:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. I must have an Ultra Secure Laowai Special Wechat then because what you're describing has not been the case when I've blocked people. I've blocked a couple of gentlemen callers and they couldn't find me again. And a couple of months ago right before a friend was about to leave China forever and wasn't going to use wechat, I blocked her for science to see what would happen. She tried to find me again with my ID. I didn't come up in any searches and our chat history immediately disappeared from her phone and my phone too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 03:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is something so poignant and sweet about that first image.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 14:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You blocked him (not just deleted him)? Blocking him is 100% supposed to remove you from his contact list, erase your chat history with him, and make it impossible for him to even find you again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Block him. It'll be like you completely disappeared from wechat as far as he can tell.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 05:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mathematically, that is absolutely not necessary at all. In theory you could have 1000 "one night stand"s with one female and 1000 different males. I'd wager that it's more likely that for every 8 straight males having a one night stand, there are maybe 2 straight females sleeping with multiple males.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
