<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1055</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favourite Churchill quote; applicable to anyone, regardless of your situation and goals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 03:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 03:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked all of that, but it still felt like the "aftermath", if that makes sense - like, to use a weird example, if it were a comic book, I feel like that all of that wouldn't be in the main run, and it'd be like an extra spin off thing. I guess I just wanted more Daredevil/Punisher interaction and action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 21:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I didn't care at all for the whole Elektra/return of Stick/The Hand element of Season 2. It was just boring to me, and I didn't feel interested at any point, really. It was so detached from the Punisher plotline, which is what I expected to be front and centre the entire season. I was really disappointed that the last few episodes focused far more on the Hand stuff than the Punisher stuff. To me it felt like The Punisher was only really the complete focus in episodes 1-4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 05:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know what the "Did you read it?", "I did, Ben didn't care and I don't either" was about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 02:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just crazy how much younger it makes him look, granted this picture is probably from years ago but during the flashback parts of the show he looks genuinely 19! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 22:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has he done to earn that reputation? Not defending him, I'm just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Beck wrote and composed the music played by the fictional band Sex Bob-omb in the movie "Scott Pilgrim vs. The World" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 02:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 02:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your approach to writing lyrics very different and separate to your approach to writing music? Do you start with an idea that pops into your head, and build on it gradually until you have a full set of lyrics, or sit down with a concept in mind and try to write a song and full lyric around it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halsey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 01:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 23:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually something I hadn't realised at all, like literally nothing of consequence, to Iron Man alone or to the Avengers, happened in that movie at all. The biggest thing, Tony "quitting" being Iron Man, was just sweeped under the rug by the start of Age of Ultron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually feel like, if he were to only be in one of the two parts, it's a lot more likely he'll be in Part 2. Have the shadow of his death hang over the first one, and then a big reveal at the end, or a dramatic revival of some sort. I'd like to see that play out a lot more, anyway, it'd be disappointing to have Cap bow out a whole movie before Iron Man and Thor and the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so disappointed when she (Iron Man 3 Spoilers) [turned out not to have died in Iron Man 3. It was really powerful and a great way to humanize Tony and show him in a vulnerable way, in a lot of emotional pain, and then she's revealed to be alive in a really underwhelming way.](#spoiler)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, I hope not. (I say, after spending 5+ hours on Reddit today while two college assignments are sitting on my desk waiting to be done) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic - Ahto City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 15:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jenna just posted this on her Instagram, these mini reunions always warm my heart 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 05:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SLAP ATH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 20:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, come to think of it, I remember barely anything about the final fight... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually really liked The Wolverine. I thought Origins was ok except for the last third or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following the success of R-Rated Deadpool, Wolverine 3 is Targeting R Rating for 2017 release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about it, dude; a lot of people are just being assholes in this thread and it's completely tasteless and uncalled for. You did a good thing posting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really tasteless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 04:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah hey don't worry about it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 02:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah, I wouldn't be asking if I'd found it there, it was the first place I checked. I just can't find it anywhere to stream or buy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where I can hear the The Wonder Years and Motion City Soundtrack 7" split record online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 00:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did a really cool thing where the frontman of each band wrote lyrics and sang over an instrumental track of a new song by the other band, but I can't find it anywhere online because I think they only did a very limited 7" record run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hands Like Houses - Colourblind (Official Music Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 22:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hozier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Frames - Revelate [Irish Rock/grunge] [1996] Glen Hansard's band before he went mostly acoustic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 15:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sorry if it may be a very obvious thing to ask - but is the way to find a part time job as a student, besides seeing if anyone in your family has something guaranteed, just handing out a CV to every shop you see? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 03:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this a couple of summers ago as I thought it'd be good to have the money, but it didn't really work out (not complaining, I know it's extremely difficult for anyone to get a part time job). But now, I really actually need the money to buy things I need for my college course. I have lots of CVs printed but thought I would just post here to see if there's some way I've missed or some better thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favourite episodes of other podcasts on the Nerdist network? (podcasts beside Chris's main one) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 23:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been getting really into some of the other podcasts on the network lately, especially You Made It Weird and Terrified. Pro You is good too. 

My favourite episodes have been the Glen Hansard and Noel Gallgher episodes of You Made It Weird. I was listening to both in bed but I had to get up and grab a pen and paper because there were so many amazing things said about creativity and life and so much more, I had to write some of it down. Seriously, if you're a creative person and haven't listened to these episodes, I'd highly recommend them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think Chandler may have written the subtitles for the Janice scenes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 22:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's an egg yolk. (not that that makes is any less confusing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever stray from the given description of a character, and form your own image of them? I feel weirdly bad for doing this as it goes against the author's vision, but I tend to do it a lot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most recent case was Darth Plagueis by James Luceno. [The way Plagueis is described](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/13/138522/3770452-4977199912-640px.jpg), just... I don't know, I really didn't like it, and considering that most of the novel featured him I didn't want to be picturing a character who looked silly in my head. So I just imagined him differently. Is this common?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 06:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well, it'll grow back. Just wanted a change for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panic! at the Cena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 02:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I don't know how Silverlight works, I'd assumed that it just buffers the best it can do at the moment, not preemptively buffer HD content for later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stefie Drew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 00:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense actually, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, that seems to have come up - is there a specific thing I should choose that might fix it? (Sorry, I don't really understand how to navigate it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 23:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's already on high, so I really don't know why it still starts so low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there some way to get Netflix to start a movie/episode of a show in full HD, rather than in lowest quality and wait a couple of minutes to get up to full HD? I can load 1080p YouTube videos no problem, no sure why it's like this. [UK] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 22:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there some way to get Netflix to start a movie/episode of a show in full HD, rather than in lowest quality and wait a couple of minutes to get up to full HD? I can load 1080p YouTube videos no problem, no sure why it's like this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 22:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 03:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really like to, but I'm not sure if it'd just end up looking really bad for my head shape - might try it someday though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 22:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it's Keith Richards, he could very likely have been off his head on more than a few different drugs when he thought of it. Even if he wasn't, even simple things can go out of your head fairly easily, especially if you went to sleep straight after thinking of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the guitar riff for '(I Can't Get No) Satisfaction' popped into Keith Richards' head as he was going to sleep in a hotel one night. He quickly recorded it and went to sleep. When he woke up, he heard the soon to be iconic riff and "then me snoring for the next 40 minutes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 21:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 21:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually looked away for a few seconds before reading the rest of the title out of fear of just that. Relieved to say the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd actually gotten that a few times, that or an awful early 90s teen soap. Have to see I kind of agree in retrospect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decided to get rid of the ol' middle part, feels good! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why James Bond Beats Batman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 21:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Bowie performs Jacques Brel's 'My Death' in his final performance as Ziggy Stardust in 1973 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 05:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 07:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guardians of the Galaxy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Krasinski and Steve Carell reunited at the Golden Globes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 07:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conan Remembers David Bowie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 06:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video of the moment Samuel L. Jackson persuades George Lucas to give him his own purple lightsaber - heard about this tonnes but never seen footage before now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 01:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Force Awakens and Star Wars Formula - Fascinating commentary on the most common criticism of The Force Awakens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 19:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 18:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think any actor could have made some of that dialogue sound very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 06:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the ending in that it was gripping and I couldn't put the book down, but I felt that the tone of the book shifted too drastically, and it became far too action oriented. Only thought that in retrospect though, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 22:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't all porn eye porn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PVRIS - Let Them In </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 21:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black and Blue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 11:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 08:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably. You're missing out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pixie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 00:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 00:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really enjoying it, the flashback/forward aspect makes it really fresh and interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 1] The tension and problems between Cohle and Hart make their "bro" moments so amazing and rewarding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 22:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching from the start (I'm very late to the party), and just finished Episode 3, The Locked Room, and that part where Hart learns of a key connection that might be a huge breakthrough on the Lange case, and the two are in the car and Hart's like "I gotta say, you were spot on on this one", and Cohle is like "Fuck yeah, Martin.", I honestly squealed with joy. And it's mostly because of all the tension and mistrust between them thus far, they hadn't had much of that. 

I don't know, just a random thought I thought I'd share because I usually never feel super pumped when two characters have sort of "bro-ish" moments because it might be in their nature anyway, but with these two you know they must be seriously happy with each other in this moment due to the previous tensions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 19:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think that's still a pretty big resemblance to Di Caprio now(besides the hair and facial hair, obviously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 16:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll wait until the season comes out to form an opinion on MCU Punisher, but he doesn't look great to me here - he really looks like he could be any random henchmen, honestly. I hope he'll at least have the signature skull somewhere on him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 14:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really annoyed I only found out about it now, I'd say if I knew back then I would've travelled to see it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 12:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Disrespectful to the creators"? Seriously? I'm sure they won't mind. Not sure where you're coming from though. Not liking a particular album of a band I love overall isn't disrespectful to the band. Didn't mean to offend anyone with my question, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the two actors known for playing modern interpretations of Sherlock Holmes on TV, Benedict Cumberbatch and Jonny Lee Miller, both played Victor Frankenstein and The Creature in Danny Boyle's 2011 adaptation of Frankenstein, alternating the two roles each night the play ran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 11:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, turn on the subtitles and get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 23:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you *are* saying he needs to dumb it down. You sound entitled and aren't really making sense. He chose authenticity over simplification. Buy the movie and turn on subtitles if you want to understand it, it isn't hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're being authentic to the accents of the people being portrayed. If you can't understand it it's not the fault of the filmmaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how the title is misleading, the information is sourced in an article I linked in another comment. They lived together for a week and did this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not speaking in Scottish accents. They're speaking in Northern Irish accents, don't think there's video with subtitles online though, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching for signs of over rehearsing but I didn't see any, it felt fairly natural for me given the urgency of the subject matter and the context of the conversation they were having. I think both characters were very on edge but not wanting to show it straight away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was McQueen's first film as a director, he was a visual artist previously. I think it's really interesting to see the quality in his work improve so drastically between his three films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, so glad to see Hunger getting a lot of love :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 Years A Slave, though Fassbender wasn't the lead in that one - he was still great in it though (but a complete bastard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get your point totally and there are tonnes of these sort of "technically impressive" scenes that I'd say that about, but honestly I feel that it adds to the quality of the film in this case, especially in the context of the rest of the film. There was very minimal dialogue previously, and nearly everything was told through angles, imagery, actions etc. Then we have this very long, dialogue heavy scene, and while the element that was previously basically absent (dialogue) comes in full force, the elements that were previously completely amped up come down to the bare minimum; a completely bare room, very basic wardrobe, and **one angle and take**. On top of that I sort of feel like it adds to the intensity of the scene, I think it'd feel weirdly 'safer' if there were traditional cuts as the scene went along. The single take keeps it on edge always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably the 10th comment like this, but again, it's just because this is rarely done in films in such a raw way. It's impressive. The fact that there's a more impressive version of it in a different medium doesn't discount the power of this scene or the merit of it and the work the actors put in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 14:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could've just fixed the typo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 13:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta be honest, this one is probably more depressing than Shame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love scenes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 13:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU. Honestly it kinda shocks me that people don't realise the point you've just made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 12:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't something you'd see in a film often so I feel that it's good content for the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
