<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4019</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I do my best," she winked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What are you so happy about?" she teased Edmund.

"Lady Druscilla, thank you for throwing this feast. I'll be sure to have my father pay you back," she said to her mother in law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ser Gerold Redhand,

 That is perfectly fine, my grandson is quite the stubborn one, gets that from his father. I wish you two the best of luck on your adventures.

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood

[M] one little canonical error I found was the sad goodbye with his father. Selwyn doesn't like his dad xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Lore] Just another witty lore title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **2nd month, 315**

It would be an understatement to say that Selwyn didn't want to leave Spottswood, after all, he didn't even want to become a warrior, it was his grandfather and father who made him go. _Seven hells, I told father I didn't want to become a knight but as usual he didn't listen. I'm surprised mother didn't say anything about me leaving for a whole year, but she probably wants me to leave too! Ughh, the whole lot of them, all they care about is fighting, it's a fucking disease with them._

"Selwyn, be safe," his mother Rhaenys said, rocking his little sister Jeyne back and forth in her arms.

_Fuck you._

"Son, don't fuck too many whores, you're bound to get one pregnant," his father said, taking another swig of wine from the glass bottle.

_Typical, Ser Lorence Santagar, he couldn't even tell his own son goodbye because he's that emotionally unavailable, fuck you too dad._

Last but not least was his grandfather. He was close to him, closer to him than his actual parents. He wanted to say "fuck you" to his grandfather too for doing this to him, for sending him with some false knight out into the desert but every time he did he couldn't help but think of all the good memories he and his grandfather shared. The countless hours reading together in his study, all of the chess games they had played, even the losses made him nostalgic. He couldn't bring himself to say that to a person he actually loved.

"Well Selwyn, I'll see you in a years time," Ser Aron said, a bit teary eyed, but holding it together well.

"As will I, grandfather. Hopefully when I return, I'll be a man," he said, thinking about how hot the Dornish desert was.

"Aye, and maybe you'll learn to be a knight too," Ser Lorence stammered. 

"Lorence!" Rhaenys shouted in shock.

"What, the boy is already fifteen. I lost mine when I was fourteen to a whore in Sunspear," he smiled, his teeth stained purple from the wine.

"Well, I guess it's goodbye, Ser Gerold is outside now waiting for me. Hopefully I'll see you all in a years time," he waved as he walked out of the dining hall.

While walking out of the dining hall, Selwyn felt a little guilty for saying that to his parents. Sure, one was a brazen drunkard and the other a pushover when it came to her husband, but strangely, he would miss them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them are missing at least in the US :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rheagar Santagar

Ser Lorence Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daemon Santagar

Rhaegar Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaehaerys Santgar

Rhaego Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's our way of life down there too," she said. "Although we hide it well with our love of fucking and relaxing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh I know I will, we Dornishwomen are quite strong" she said smiling, trying to reassure him. "I guess this means he'll be a fighter." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once Damian touched her belly, William immediately kicked her. "This little bear is going to be the death of me, I guess he's more of a northerner," she winced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It is, is it?" She teased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A wise move, my lady," Ser Aron smiled. "We should all be following suit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 09:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad to see you go :( I hope you come back soon! (Whether it be Dorne or not.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good to hear," she said, her face as red as a beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Aye, and more playful," she winked. "True, you did once ride a leopard."

[m] the sexual tension is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well since it appears that they are staying on Bloodstone, I would recommend that we keep our men, and possibly send some more, to make sure nothing unfavorable happens on Bloodstone. I would also recommend that we have some spies there," he said, thinking about what else they could do to make sure the Iron Islanders don't do anything stupid. "If I may ask my lady, what have you thought regarding this matter?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lady Visenya with a dragon, that sounds familiar," she chuckled, thinking about Aegon and his sisters. 

"A bear riding a dragon, I'd pay to see it," she grinned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Maybe we'll even win favor with the king," she chuckled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In truth, I have no excuse. I'm not going to lie to you, Lady Nymella because I respect you too much to do so. I did not talk during the meeting and that is a mistake that I shall never make again, I will rectify this mistake anyway I can, my lady," he said, his voice shaking a bit.

In truth, he was quite intimidated by Lady Nymella, and for good reason, she's quite a powerful woman. He knew he made a mistake of not thinking of an excuse, but he respected the lady too much, he just hoped she didn't admonish him too much.

[m] real reason is because I was busy, but can't say that IC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Maybe we'll even get to meet the king!' she said, thinking about what King Vaemar is like in person. "I don't reckon you know him?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I wonder what it'll be like," she said, imagining the Red Keep in her mind. "Have you been to King's Landing?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, what would you like to know?" He asked, breaking a rib in half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm glade to hear it," he smiled. "So, what would you like to talk about, my lady?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "True but he must be a very busy boy and everyone must be wanting to stay at the Red Keep," she said, thinking about how wonderful it would be to stay there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We shall," he said, holding out his arm.

They arrived at the dining hall and on the table was an array of different foods. Fresh bread, sasauges, roasted onions dripping gravy, crab, ribs roasted in a crust of garlic and herbs, pigeon pie, blueberry and apple tarts, and sweet pumpkin soup. To wash it down, they had Dornish summerwine.

"I didn't know what you liked except for apple tarts, my lady. I hope there's something here you like. If there isn't, please let me know and I'll tell the kitchen to cooks something up for you immediately." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 01:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Only if," she grinned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 01:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We're going to King's Landing?" she asked, thinking about what they could do there. "Hmmm... I'm not sure myself." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 00:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And healthy," she smiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes, my position on Bloodstone," he said, now thinking about the island. "On one hand it'd be great for the Iron Islanders, but on the other it could potentially be bad for us."

He a second to think about it, really think about it, and told the woman "I don't agree with it."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A bit disappointing, but I guess being just William is fine," she chuckled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "William the Conqueror, King of the North," she said thinking about the baby growing inside her. "It has a nice ring to it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "William Ursus? That's a nice name," she smiled. "I bet he'll be a soldier like his father and grandfather." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So, my lady, what did you mean to talk to me about Bloodstone?" He asked, opening the door of his office.

The once infamous messy room was now spotless, as he was expecting a guest. He pulled out a chair for her and took a seat opposite her. 

"Forgive me, my lady, it's not the most extravagant office," he chuckled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, what do you think of the name Wilem after your father?" She asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How do you know it's a boy?" She asked."What if it's a girl?"

[M] I'm not entirely sure if I said it was a boy, let me check the letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You're already my husband," she said, kissing him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A huge party in a couple of years will do, the smaller the better," she grinned, looking down at her swallon belly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A small wedding sounds wonderful," she smiled, thinking about their child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes?" She asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think of it Damian, soon it'll be us," she smiled and kissed him on the cheek.

/u/cknight15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [M] perfect title (insert thumbs up emoji)

"My lady, come in, we've much to discuss," Ser Aron said, once he saw Nymella Toland. "Would you like something to drink, my lady?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping reach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping vale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping stormlands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping crownlands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping riverlands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping dorne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping west </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping north </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Archery Sign Up** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Joust Sign Up** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Melee Sign Up** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Letter] I'm sorry it's so early </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To the Lords and Ladies of Westeros, and to His Grace King Vaemar Targaryen,

 We cordially invite you all to next year's New Years Festival at Spottswood. The festivities will begin on the 1st month of 316. There will be a joust, a melee, and an archery competition. Only knights or people of noble birth are aloud to enter the joust this year, and there will be forfeiture as usual.

 Hope to see you all there,

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If I may say, Lady Nymeria, you look lovely tonight," he smiled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 5:55 Rhaego left his chambers to escort Lady Nymeria Artis to dinner, just like he said he would, and he knocked on her door promptly at 6. 

/u/Doctor-Clockwork </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Of course I will," she smiled and kissed him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 01:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Haha indeed, let's hope not," he chuckled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 01:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't know Gerold, I think the lady might be developing feelings for Ser Gerold, the Smiling Knight," he grinned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 01:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Jonos.... that sounds really nice!" She said, smiling harder than she ever had."Winters in Dorne and the rest in San Freysisco, owning a business, the kids, everything." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [m] I was just going to make a separate comment since it's the same day, but that sounds good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Of course, my lady," he bowed and left to mingle.

[M] do we just skip to 6? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That is quite strong indeed," Ser Aron said thinking about all the adventures Selwyn will have. "I don't mean to be blunt Ser Gerold, but has anything happened between you and Egwene Jordayne? Will there be another wedding soon?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In truth, there wasn't much battling in the world when I was squring,"  Ser Aron said, lowering his voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh all sorts of things, though I was much scrawnier than Selwyn. I remember once I had to work on a farm with a Reachman to build strength, sailed around the world for a couple of years too, learning and practicing, it was quite unorthodox. I also remember camping out in the desert, boy was it hot!" He said, thinking about his squiring days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daemon Santagar

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ser Lorence Santagar

Daemon Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaehaerys Santagar

Rhaego Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How long will you all be out west?" Ser Aron asked, hoping that he wasn't being annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "With all the recent parties, I'd say it's good indeed," Aron chuckled, trying to lighten the mood. "Where will you two be going first?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Apple Tarts it is, my lady," Rhaego smiled. "I'll be here promptly at six to escort you to the dining hall."

Rhaego could see that she wasn't very comfortable going on a date for political gain, which was understandable. In the back of his mind though, he hoped the marriage would escalate from political gain to actual feelings, but whatever happened was fine by him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can't even imagine what he'll be like the next time we meet," Ser Aron said, wondering if Selwyn would be a complete stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That sounds wonderful, Lady Nymeria. Before you go, what is your favorite dessert?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Try not to kill the boy, Gerold," Ser Aron chuckled taking a sip of wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "San Freysisco sounds nice, what's it like?" She said, dreaming of the apartment and the pitter patter of their children's feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's all we can do after all. Can't make the boy gifted in something he's not," he teased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ""Dinner with Lady Nymeria Artis, the man who almost took down Rand Jordayne? It sounds splendid!" He smiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ashara imagined shelves of books, sky high in a room twice the size of the Spottswood dining hall.

"I can't wait to go," she smiled. "Reading, being with you, it sounds perfect," she smiled, laying her head on her shoulder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I guess I'll have plenty of time to read it when i move to Wyl," she smiled. "How many books do you have?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oooh, I haven't read that one, what's it about?" she asked, intrigued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What have you recently read?" she asked, thinking about what she should read next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ah," she nodded. "So what do you enjoy doing, Lord Edmund?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nor I, but it is quite interesting," she said. "Are you more of a melee man, Edmund?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Thank gosh Lady Nymeria didn't die and match between Ser Gerold and Rand Jordayne was quite entertaining, they seem evenly matched," Ashara said, rewatching the match in her head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She could tell that he was lying and forcing the smile, but she didn't dare say anything, frankly, she was too embarrassed to because of bringing up what seemed to be a touchy subject. She wanted to tell him sorry for bringing his father up, but she thought it'd make it worse, so she tried her best to change the subject.

"What did you think of the joust?" She said quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhaella couldn't help but blush when he said that, after all, what lady wouldn't when told that by a man she has affections for?

"It's not much, but it's home," she smiled, looking up at the keep. "I know your father would never let you back into The Twins, would you like to live here?" 

She knew it was a touchy and quite possibly risky question but she had to ask it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She smiled. She couldn't believe how everyone could think he's a cold or tough person. 

"What would your father think of me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, let's hope she likes me," Ashara said, a bit self conscious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I hope I do too," she said, with a hint of doubt in her voice. "Have you told your mother about me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I wouldn't tell a soul," she said, kissing his cheek. "I cannot believe it Edmund, three months from now, and we'll both be at Wyl." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Edmund Wyl, are you secretly sweet?" she teased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nonetheless, it sounds as if our wedding will be a joyous event," she said, wondering if any Santagars would enter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Only if it would hurry," she smiled. "Will there any events at our wedding?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My uncle told me it is the fourth month, correct?" She asked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ashara forced her way through the crowd, not even worrying saying excuse me, when she finally got to Edmund, she said:

"You look quite handsome yourself," she smiled, moving her hair behind her ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Edmund!" Ashara called out when she saw him in the crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's fourteen now, he'll be 15 in a couple of months," Aron said, taking a sip of wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This sounds like an excellent opportunity for Selwyn and I'm sure you'll make a great teacher Gerold," Ser Aron said, thinking about all of the adventures Selwyn would go on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm well, how are you, ladies?" Daemon asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's not great with it, but he knows what to do," Ser Aron said, taking a sip of wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhaella and Jonos sat at a table all by themselves talking when Rhaella asked "What do you think of Spottswood, Jonos?" 

/u/TheMallozzinator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The pleasure is mine, my lady," he smiled, moving his hair out of the way. "I saw you in the joust today and you fought well, I'm sorry you got injured." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Selwyn knows how to ride a horse and is only a beginner with a sword," Ser Aron said, somewhat disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Announcing the marriage sounds good," Ser Aron smiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 05:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good evening ladies," Daemon bowed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hmmm... I think there was one opening up down the street," Ser Aron said, finally remembering it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I believe there's a painter in Sunspear," Ser Aron said, thinking about if he's sure or not. "Yes, it was Sunspear." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Not offended at all, you are absolutely right. It's a harsh word out there," Ser Aron said, thinking of past tourneys he won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Of course he does, taught him myself," the knight said proudly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's a Dornishman, Ser Gerold, he's great with a horse," Ser Aron teased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Of course it's not too much my lady! Please excuse me for just a moment," he said, putting his goblet on the nearby table.

A moment later, he whispered into the ear of a passing maid and then she scurried off. A few minutes later Rhaego arrived. He had long half black, half Valyrian blonde hair, deep purple eyes with blue flecks in them, and freckled pale skin.

"Rhaego, this is Lady Nymeria Artis of High Hermitage," Ser Aron said.

"My lady," Rhaego bowed.

In truth, Rhaego thought Lady Nymeria was absolutely beautiful, but of course, he didn't want to show all of his cards, at least not yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ser Gerold,will you be leaving with Selwyn tomorrow or would you like a position here?" Aron asked, sipping his wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " Let's" Ser Aron smiled, noticing the lady looking down at her arm.
"What would you like to know about him?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gerold, my boy! How does knighthood feel?" Ser Aron smiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ser Aron looked at Lady Nymeria and saw that she had a cast on her arm and was scrapped up a bit, a small part of him couldn't help but to feel sorry for her, the injuries must hurt, but another part of him didn't feel sorry at all, instead, proud. Rand Jordayne was a big man and she went head to head with him for multiple rounds, he'd never met a stronger woman in his life and he would be proud to call her a daughter in law.

"My lady, you fought excellently today against Rand Jordayne," he smiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping dorne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Event] The Feast at Spottswood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **1st Month, 315**

After a long day of watching the joust, there was nothing Ser Aron wanted more than food, and boy was the joust close. Rand Jordayne and Gerold the Bastard, or *Ser* Gerold went head to head to the last round, neither once giving an inch and Lady Nymeria Artis of High Hermitage almost died. To say it was an eventful joust was a gross understatement. Thankfully, no one lost their lives today. Aron knew that he was expected to give a toast and maybe a little speech, but he was exhausted, he just wanted eat. So, he knighted the boy, Gerold, said the words, and let the Septon pour the oil over him, nothing fancy.

"Thank you all for coming. Now, let's eat!" he yelled, holding up his goblet of Dornish summerwine.

[m] go crazy guys, not going to organize the feast at all.

In case you missed it:

Joust winner: Ser Gerold the Bastard

Melee winner: Ellion Blackmont

Archery winner: Ser Gerold the Bastard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **WINNERS**

Joust: Gerold the Bastard

Archery: Gerold the Bastard

Melee: Ellion Blackmont </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GEROLD WON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard-1]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Rand Jordayne-1]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Rand Jordayne-2]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard-2]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JOUSTS FINALS

[[1d20 Rand Jordayne]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Arrtis]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Artis]] vs [[1d20 Rand Jordayne-1]]

/u/rollme

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Artis-1]] vs [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Artis]] vs [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Artis]] vs [[1d20 Rand Jordayne-1]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Artis-3]] vs [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]]

/u/rollme

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GEROLD WON! Sorry mersillion :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Ellion Blackmont]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Ellion Blackmont]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Ellion Blackmont]] vs [[1d20 Gerold the Bastard]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[1d20 Nymeria Artis]] vs [[1d20 Rand Jordayne]]

/u/rollme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Event] The Joust, Melee, and Archery Tourney Rolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be the  post with all the rolls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh no, that's my nephew Daemon," Ser Aron chuckled nervously. "He's been talking about lady Valery quite a bit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Please, come in, Lord Guilian," Ser Aron said, coming out of the keep.

A moment later, they all went back into the keep, and Lord Guilian and Ser Aron went into his office.

"What would you like to talk about, my lord?" he asked, sitting down in the leather chair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not sure yet, I guess we'll have to set a date and find a septoin," Aron said, continuing to write in the old book.

A knock on the door sounded and Lysandra entered, this time without Jacaerys. She was with a boy, he had dark olive skin, jet black hair, and green eyes with yellow flecks in them.

"Here's Selwyn," Lysandra said, opening the door.

"Selwyn, come in. I've someone I'd like you to meet." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My nephew Selwyn. He's more of a scholar but my father insists on him learning how to fight too," Aron said, putting his pen down and looking up at Gerold. 

Aron walked out of the room for a minute to talk to Lysandra. After a minute he kissed baby Jacaerys on the forehead, and Lysandra went away.

"She's going to get Selwyn now. As for tonight, you can stay here," he said, sitting back down in the wooden chair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No, you'd be right," Aron said, looking up at Gerold again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 07:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'd like my nephew, Selwyn, to be your squire until his sixteenth name day," Aron said, not even looking up from the dusty book. "In return, my father, Ser Aron, is prepared to knight you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 07:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Very well then," Aron said getting up out of his seat. "Here is 800 stage, if you go to the armory, Martyn should be able to help you find a lance, you can use some of my younger brothers. How died this sound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, If you'd like to joust, I could give you some money for armor and a lance, how much will it cost?" He said, looking up from the book briefly. "No, there will be no forfeiture this time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Dorne's New Year's Festival is hosted at Spottswood

* Got three betrozals

* My gay heir's wife gave birth to twins

Overall, a great week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's a pleasure to meet you Gerold," the woman smiled. "Come, I'll take you to my husband's office." 

After a few minutes, they stopped at an old wooden door, the paint was slowly chipping off but you could see that it once was Santagar blue. 

"He should be in here, Gerold, I told him you were coming," she said opening the old door while making sure the baby was secure. 

  When the door opened, the room smelled of old paper but for some reason it was cool in the room, it had to be one of the coolest rooms in the keep. In the room sat a man at a messy desk reading. He was quite handsome for an older man as he was around 40. He had olive skin, black hair, and deep eyes.

"You must be Gerold, I heard you'd like to sign up for the tourney next month, I assume you'd like to joust?" He asked, writing down something in the old book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 02:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lady Nymella Toland,

 The second month is fine my lady, we've much to talk about Bloodstone. I apologize for not talking during the council. Hopefully this meeting will be able to rectify that mistake.

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood

[m] a bit short, but I didn't know what else to say other than "that sounds good." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 02:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guards could smell his breathe a mile away, and it smelled like booze. The tall guard, Petyr, was deciding if he should let this Gerold fellow in. After all, he did come for the tourney.

"Come with me." Petyr said, as he opened the gate. "Stay out here Garrin."

   The short one, Garrin, nodded and put his visor back down.

"Before you meet with Ser Aron, we need to sober you up a bit more," Petry said, going towards the fountain.

   A moment later, Petry dunked Gerold's head in the cold fountain, his huge hand grabbed the nape of Gerold's neck and pulled him back up thirty seconds later. By that time, Gerold was soaking wet and gasping for air, all the while shivering.

"Someone get the boy a towel!" Petry yelled, his voice booming across the keep.

  A moment later, a woman came running down the hall with a baby and a towel in hand. She had wavy silver blonde hair, beautiful purple eyes, and skin as soft and white as Northern snow.

"Petyr stop yelling, you're going to wake the children! You already woke Nymeria, don't wake Jacaerys," she said, looking down at the baby in her arms.

"Apologies, Lady Lysandra," Petry whispered. "This man named Gerold has come to see Ser Aron."

  She turned to the boy and gave him the soft towel.

"Ser Aron is getting ready for the festival next month, but my husband Aron is here, come, he'll see to whatever you nee," Lysandra smiled.

  "So, what business do you have with Ser Aron?" she asked, walking down the hall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 01:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two guards saw that the man at the gate was inebriated and said "get out of here, you damn drunkard!"

It had been quite regular for drunks to come up to the guards so the two thought nothing of it, they'd seen a million drunkards come up to the gates of Spottswood and they were bound to see a million more.

"Unless you have an appointment with the knight of Spottswood, you best move along," the short one said, raising his visor to show his penetrating black eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [m] didn't want to tag you guys because it gets old after awhile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Letter] For Dornish Eyes Only </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To the Lords and Ladies of Dorne,

 My third son, Jaehaerys is in need of a wife as he's 24. He's a good man, a strong man, and if I may be say, a good jouster. I believe this marriage will do great things for our houses as it will strengthen the bonds and if no bonds exist between our houses, it will create new bonds.

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 02:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't put it down but it wasn't your fault either, it was the company's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers AGOT) Does this mean... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 01:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Mirri Maz Durr was talking with Dany and basically telling her that Drogo was always going to be a vegetable, she said "When your womb quickens again" on page 759 (paperback) does this mean that Dany is now barren? A stupid question, I know but is GRRM telling us that Dany is never going to have another child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaehaerys Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ser Lorence Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 04:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not our fault, that's the company's fault for not paying you a living wage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 02:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edmund Wyl,

 That date is perfectly fine, I will tell her the news at once. I will see you at the festival!

 Ser Aron Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 01:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Gerold,

 It is an open tourney, however if you or your gang cause any trouble, we're going to have to kick you out. I'm not saying you will, but I've heard stories.

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 01:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lord Edmund Wyl,

 I believe this is a splendid idea and believe that this union will be great for both our houses. When shall the wedding be?

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I guess we'll just have to wait and see," she smirked.

Ashara considered marrying Edmund. After all, she was looking for a husband and Edmund seemed to be a good man. Charming, funny and smart also it didn't hurt that he was quite attractive, at least she thought he was, she wasn't going to tell him that though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fair enough. It could even be me," she chuckled.

She couldn't help to think about a life at Wyl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What do you think of this mystery woman?" Ashara asked, smiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 09:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sure you'll find Lady Wyl eventually, my lord," she smiled, tucking her hair behind her ear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 08:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It sounds absolutely wonderful," she said, thinking of living there, right in the middle of The Red Mountains. "You're lucky that you're the lord of it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 08:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can't say I have. What is Wyl like?" She asked, thinking about what Wyl looked like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 06:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That is quite a big family!" He said thinking about his own family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 05:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lord Matthias Hellfyre

 That sounds like an absolutely splendid idea, I cannot wait to tell everyone about the union of our houses.

 Ser Aron Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 02:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lady Nymeria Artis,

 That sounds absolutely wonderful, I look forward to meeting you and will make the guards keep an eye out for you.

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 02:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Damian,

 I found out about a week ago, I was as surprised as you and also a bit scared and nervous, but I'm sure that's natural. I pray it doesn't come to a siege, and if it does, make sure to be as safe as you can, you have a family now. I haven't told either but I will write to them right after this letter, you're the first person I've told so far. I long to see you too, sweet Damian. I'll be keeping an eye out for you. I even told the guards do to the same and if they see you to come get me immediately, no matter what time it is. Please be safe.

 Love,

 Visenya


P.S. I've been thinking of some names. If it's a boy I'd like to name him Oberyn or Willem, I hope that sounds good to you, Damian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 02:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I know exactly what you mean, my lord. There's been so many weddings and tourneys as of late," she said, thinking of her sister's wedding in Oldtown a year ago. "Not much, I usually just ride my horse or sail." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh, you're thinking of Aron, my lord. My uncle Lorence has been married for about fifteen years now," she smiled. "Don't feel bad, my lord, I don't pay much attention to politics either." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lorence's little indiscretion? What has my uncle done now?" She asked.

"Only if you knew earlier," she chuckled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lady Nymeria Artis,

 This sounds like a splendid idea! I will surely pay you a visit at High Hermitage, my lady. However it cannot be until the new year as we have a festival to set up.

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What do you think of us, Lord Edmund?" She asked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 22:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes, yes you do. At least for now," she teased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Maybe it's working a little too good," she chuckled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's the way I like them," she chuckled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Please do," she said, sipping wine. "So, Lord Edmund do you think I'm intimidating?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She noticed how he was looking at her body, but she didn't say anything.

"The pleasure is mine, my lord," she smiled. "I have no idea, I guess most men find me intimidating." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automod ping dorne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Letter] Be Our Guest, Be Our Guest! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To the Lords and Ladies of Dorne,

 The Santagars will be hosting a New Years' festival this year at Spottswood. There will be a joust, a melee, and even an archery competition. This festival will begin on the first day of the first month. If anyone from your house is competing, please list who in your letter.

 Sincerely,

 Ser Aron Santagar, Knight of Spottswood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well Lady Lucillia, it is an honor to meet you," Daemon bowed. "Didn't know you had a sister Valery, how many siblings do you have?" 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 20:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am Lady Ashara Santagar," she smiled.

If she had been talking to anyone else, she wouldn't have called herself a lady, but she was trying to make a good impression, so she sucked it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 20:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Is he looking at me?* Ashara thought, playing with her curly brown hair.

She looked nothing like her mother, a Lysene, but like her father, a Santagar which made her jealous of her siblings. They had the light skin, purple eyes, and pale blonde hair of Old Valyria while she was more Rhoynish. She wore a simple blue dress and a necklace as she didn't care much for fashion, though she did make sure she looked nice for potential suitors though there were unlikely to be any tonight, just like every night. Her father told her "Lords and sers don't like tomboys, they want a proper lady." She didn't care. 

After a couple minutes passed she realized this mystery man was looking at her again, which made her quite embarrassed. In truth, she thought he was quite handsome and prayed to the seven he'd walk up to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will miss you trekkie! RIP Stout-Santagar marriage :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 16:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, I cannot say for sure, we only met just now," Daemon chuckled. "Who might you be?"

Remembering that he was originally talking to Valery, he turned his head back to her.

"Why yes my lady, the average Dornishman is much bolder than the rest," he smiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 05:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Santagar, my lady," Ser Aron smiled.

A moment later, Daemon, Ser Aron's nephew, came up to him drinking wine.

"Uncle, have you seen any beautiful ladies yet? Oh, well it looks like we've found one uncle," Daemon bowed.

"Please excuse my nephew Daemon, he's a bit...aggressive when it comes to flirting," Ser Aron said, scratching his bald head.

"I am Daemon Santagar, and you are?" Daemon smiled ignoring his uncle and moving his silver blonde hair out of his face.

"It appears I'm overstaying my welcome," Ser Aron chuckled. "You kids have fun." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 04:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [m] oh, sorry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 04:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [m] wrong post? xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/cknight15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Letter] Congratulations! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Damian, 

 I hope this letter finds you well, Damian because I have big news for you, you're going to be a father, the maesters said so. I hope this news does not come at a bad time, I know you're quite busy out in the field. How is it going out there? I miss you dearly Damian and I pray to the old gods and the new that you come back to us safely. I hope this letter doesn't make you come back home. Truly Damian, the men need you more than I right now. 

 Love,

 Visenya

After Visenya finished writing the letter, she paced back in forth in her room, wondering about the future of Damian and her, wondering if he'll make it back to Bear Island alive, and wondering what their child with accomplish in its lifetime. Eventually, she began to feel tired and laid down in her bed. Moments later, she was fast asleep dreaming about Damian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
