<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 15:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoney, Bill, and Sarah: Worst morning show in the city. Good for Tate for getting the point across that they are garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detroit: Thomas McGees in Eastern Market. Should be a couple hundred supporters strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mechanical engineering, more specifically automotive product development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. I tweak my LinkedIn every so often in a similar manner and watch the views/calls jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the better pieces of advice I received, especially working at a larger corporation was, "If you want a pay raise here, the only real effective way to do it is to leave and come back". It doesn't hurt to make a move this way; I plan on going back to my last job at some point myself (and have been asked to interview for positions there multiple times, but I'm not ready yet).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about your situation, but I've been asked about this before in interviews. I have straight up told them "I have student loans, rent, etc. and my current salary isn't going to get me to where I can live comfortably financially, and that's why I'm looking for a new job".

I've told this to both the companies I have left and the ones I was joining. Both sides were incredibly understanding and I could get a job back at any of my previous employers with one phone call. The sentiment stands though: Don't ever burn bridges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously I'd take my desire to leave the current industry into account before making a demand like that, but I don't see why not otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan. There is a solid demand for engineers here which may help my case, though I've had opportunities offered all over the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I live pretty comfortably. I've been making around that wage for two years now living in Michigan where the cost of living is pretty manageable, so I have no complaints. Can't forget bonuses, car allowance, paid phone, etc. as well. It all adds up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BSME working in the automotive field. Started at 45k/year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell them you're not actively looking but would be interested if the salary range is at least X-dollars. Don't give your current wage, because they don't need to know. They just need to know what it's going to take to make you interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, within the same industry with all of my changes. I changed from my entry level job after 6 months. Diverse experience would end up being to your benefit in opening new avenues down the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 15:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gave the answer in your question. You are changing jobs. You have experience and you are obviously valuable enough that you aren't unemployed while looking for a new opportunity. Once you get that first job, the rest is easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly tripled my salary from 23 to 28 by changing jobs a few times. I get calls daily by recruiters just by keeping my LinkedIn updated. 

I never say "no" to an opportunity, I just make a demand of no less than a 25% increase over my current wage up front to avoid wasting any time. It's worked very well for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had this issue. Turn off the "noise reduction" option under Settings Language and Input Other Sounds Noise Reduction. Worked for me.

Another thing I did was use a pin to clean out the microphone hole on the bottom. No problems since.

EDIT: "On", not "I". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought my girlfriend a gift and paid extra for a hand written card. Not quite the romantic card I was expecting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the pedometer question would be the question of the day, but this one takes the cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volleyball at Z's Villa via ComePlayDetroit. I've been in their league for two years now, and its a blast. Not very competitive, just show up, eat/drink (and drink some more), and play a few games. Runs about $60 for a whole season/playoffs.

Going to a DCFC game is a great time as well. Pre-game at Harry's, march, and watch some great soccer for $10/game. Season ticket holder for two years now, it's a great time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Stevie G mid-air celebration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...You're dating [Blake Anderson](http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/04/17/Blake-Anderson.jpg?itok=sKsVrjmG)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 22:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In college, there were very few slots for classes and registration was online. I figured out that the servers that opened the registration window were set to open within 3 seconds of when my cell phone's time changed.

Knowing this, along with knowing the pattern of the registration form, I created a single keystroke macro that would fill in all of my class numbers and submit it by pushing one button. I never missed out on getting the classes I wanted again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tron: Legacy. Daft Punk FTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 16:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children. Never thought I'd love one, but her daughter is my world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charles Rodgers. Just couldn't stay away from the booze and ganja. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh no! Don't poison our world with that...steam... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 19:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost.

Such a cool introduction and a new concept for network TV at the time. It was so expensive for the time that it got the network president fired for greenlighting it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 15:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother started in her early 40's and is the top realtor in her office now, less than 6 years later. I think you'll be just fine at 36. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roger from American Dad. I couldn't tolerate the show when I started watching, but now I feel it wouldn't work without him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Buck, Mickey Redmond, Ken Daniels, and Rod Allen are all terrible. Let's not forget the stupid guitar riff they play with that awful "slap shot" sound with every Wings game. The crowd noise audio is awful for football games compared to CBS. Their studio crew is better, though.

To be fair, I love George Blaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this sucks. FSD's sports presentations are atrocious, with FOX a mere step above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor diseased child... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 20:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently you didn't graduate high school  yourself if you don't realize that stooping low is another symptom of Parkinson's, hence the inclusion of that phrase in the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He really stooped low with that one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 19:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 22:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Automotive Engineer here. The reason is because the amount of development needed for both an automatic and manual transmission is extensive; both cost and time consuming. The returns are essentially naught sales-wise. Because automatic transmissions have become so advanced in their reliability and performance, the manual is essentially being phased out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping for a teapot; perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Ronaldo during warm-ups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessir. Originally A but transferred out before first semester. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Flint, the 24 oz 211's were one buck per can. I actually can say that the flavor isn't horrendous, hence why I drank so many of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I can drink Steel Reserve now. I love all beers, though I have moved on to a higher quality of booze. I only drink Steel Reserve now when I see the roommates, for nostalgia sake.

The cans were in garbage bags. I washed them all out when finished as to not make the whole apartment smell like fermented malt liquor.

I functioned fine during those 3 weeks. I was steadily drinking them throughout the day to avoid getting ridiculous for class (weekends not included).

I graduated on time with my intended BSME degree, so no regrets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sort of Facebook Verified](http://i.imgur.com/ulkUMQ9.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 22:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, who were you when you were masturbating in the same bed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried 12 steps, but I drunkenly stumbled on the first couple, busted my shin on step 3 or 4, and decided to let Jesus chill at the top without me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I get for trusting a website's quote. Thanks IMDb.

In fairness, I should have caught that because even though I knew it was "annals" I was still reading it as "(anal-as-in-anus)s".

Oh well, I'm not editing because you're anal about anal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4x11 cans starting from left to end of the table plus 4x20 cans (subtracting the first 4 rows because they were counted in the initial 4x11) plus the one can in the center-back = 125. If I can't math my beer drinking correctly, maybe engineering isn't for me. Thankfully, I think I got this one right. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. I have since moved past this 3 week binge and am functioning like a normal human being again. 

Long term damage to my health? Maybe. Opportunity for internet points? Yes. Prognosis: worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kettering, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 19:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A college budget calls for college booze, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 19:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I'm thankful every day that my parents blessed me with a steel liver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 18:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blacked out at 9 for sure, don't get me wrong. But hey, that's what weekends in college are for, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the anals of history people are going to be talking about three things: the discovery of fire, invention of the submarine, and the Flint, Michigan Mega Bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sir. Flint, Michigan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to ride an all day buzztrain. IIRC I put down 9 in a day, but averaged around 5-6. 

Those hangovers were brutal, but we all know the best cure for a hangover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 125 Steel Reserve's in 3 weeks. They were sold for $3 for 3 cans; perfect for my college budget. This was dubbed the Steel Curtain by the roomates.

1 Steel Reserve = 8.1% ABV @ 24 oz per can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter drinking eh? Here's 3 weeks of my drinking in college. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Score. Bill, take this so I can make it my new Tinder profile pic." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked at CTC for a couple years. About twice a year this exact scenario would happen. It was mind boggling how many people don't understand what happens when they hit "reply all" and that there is no specific distribution list that they are being purposely spammed with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must work at Chrysler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: Find a way to squeeze "golf" onto your resume if you're in engineering/product sales/management. Gotten me many jobs and opened up a ton of casual conversations during interviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 15:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used Holbrook to Woodward a few times; most direct path I'd think. Caniff doesn't make it to Woodward.

From your starting point, take Joseph Campau to Holbrook and hang a right. Next stop, Midtown.

On top of that, keep going to Cass if you want to get downtown. Woodward sucks with the construction.

EDIT: Downtown added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit post-storm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyline view of my town as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You couldn't make the QB selection chart wide enough to fit the second overall players' names in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 18:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, sounds like you're going to need to find a roommate. That's a pretty tight budget to find anything reasonable. After living downtown a couple of years and spending tons of time watching the cost of rent for a single bedroom or studio (I pay too much at $1215 a month with no included utilities and I know it), the "starter" value for a one bedroom/studio in that area is closer to $850/month.

As /u/filipinohitman suggested, finding a spot in Woodbridge would probably be a more realistic bet. Great area and a renter community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a WTF post if I've ever seen one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought I'd share this on a day we will never forget. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 17:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 22:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the material. I have mostly all cotton shirts and button-downs and I can get all the wrinkles out by just misting them using a spray bottle filled with water. 

I haven't folded laundry in 10 years; it just goes from a clean bin to a dirty bin. I am pretty hardcore on my dress code as well (I am a corporate exec, neat dress is important) and swear by this method. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat face, doge face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/uycAUHY.jpg

Picture for context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favorite smoke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing better to me than the Barber Pole 708. 

It has the perfect draw, unmatched flavor, and incredible overall consistency that keeps me coming back. I have smoked a couple boxes of these and have can say confidently that the law of diminishing returns does not apply with these.

What's your favorite smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 16:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice gooch shot ya got there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's played forever and was nothing more than a fringe role player at best at the time he came out anyways. Him coming out as gay had absolutely nothing to do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 20:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, but if they aren't yet I'm going to have to keep an eye out for him plagiarizing this moving forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider not using the browser until they patch it for 5.0. Chrome has been working just fine for me since the upgrade, try using that in the meantime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an error message that pops up with the crashes? Are the same programs crashing it?

More specifically, did you update to Lollipop when this all started happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you just upgraded to Lollipop, do this:

SettingsStorageCached Data - Clear cached data

Did this after the Lollipop update, everything works fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 03:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be incredibly easy to give this the ability to tighten and untighten as well. You just need to create a socket wrench style toggle switch and put pivot pins where the "feet" are. 

From an engineer, cool design and impressive rendering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 04:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is difficult to help with without a budget and whether you are looking to rent or own. Care to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...did no one notice that the ball spins back on the first bounce, thus making the guy that served on the far side the winner of the point regardless of the return shot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 04:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video is brilliant. I didn't know how to explain why I cared about wrestling growing up, but this synopsis summed it up perfectly, especially the TL;DR at 21:30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where my brain immediately went when I saw this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/9nnsYEY.gifv

A Casey Anthony reaction gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couldn't help but to upvote... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 15:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 14:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-potato link of the halftime show. Still the most memorable one to me; it was glorious.

EDIT: Favorite solo starts at 9:45.

http://www.wat.tv/video/prince-superbowl-half-time-4uv1f_2hztv_.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero Red Wings is mind boggling to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 04:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The dress is whblueeeee! ](http://i.imgur.com/nhDyF2R.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends used to search for the best beards they could find. They found this one during the Woodward Dream Cruise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 03:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 280lb Catfish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 19:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
