<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they no longer need to be accessible do they? So you can box them up and put them wherever. Is that so hard to figure out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but if backed up, they don't need to be accessible, so you can box them up in the attic or something. And you can backup the harddrive, keep that in the attic too.   

Edit: its much easier because you can literally take all your films to a TV and choose from any one of them, without having to fuss around with discs, a player, another remote, a bunch of copyright screens, trailers and menus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roth also wrote The Insider I believe, which was a great script.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere there's a school where an english teacher sets homework to write a transformers story, english teacher photocopies the results, faxes to Michael Bay, gets produced into $300m film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever thought of ripping them all to a harddrive? It saves A LOT of space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! I bought the book it was based on for my dad (also a fan) but he said it was nowhere near as good. The film is so quirky and odd, I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive seen The Usual Suspects and do enjoy all of it. The writing, sense of mystery, soundtrack and style all add up well. I'd happily watch it even if I knew the last 10 minutes wasnt there for whatever reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I simply disagree with most of what is being said here. I wish I had more time to read your replies

Do you even notice your own obtuseness?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its funny this sole scene is more atmospheric, better acted and far more memorable than the entire recent Nicolas Cage movie based on the event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMA request - the only person who went to see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a remake of the UK christmas animation where the snowman comes alive, then tries on the kids sisters clothes and reads his dads porno mags?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that a deleted scene from The Room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Quaid was having the Rekall experience. The film is a kind of representation of that experience, with bits added for us, because we're also kind of having our own Rekall experience. Its one of those meta-analyses of film/audience a bit like The Prestige and Inception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This was the bit](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SX9y5JPuRHY t=64) that made everyone laugh/cringe when I saw it (especially Jude Laws face when Hunnan's pulling the sword). After that, all the efforts to try and make it look Ritchie-esque (the cuts, swaggers, soundtrack) just seemed phoney and jarring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, complete idiot or not, anything you laugh at will seem funny *to you*. There could still be a disparity between what a person finds funny, and what the film is *intending* to be funny. If a film shows a section that is supposed to be serious, and people laugh (for example, because they think it looks silly), hopefully you can appreciate that their response might be one of awkwardness, even nervousness, at how misjudged and off-key the film is?   

But more to the point, /u/Psittacula2 was usefully explaining how an audience could be embarrassed or awkward about a trailer, and rather than considering that you just considered your own reactions. Coupled with your other reply, I have to wonder whether you're able to apply theory of mind or empathise with others on any level, and its no wonder that my first comment was the "strangest sentences" you'd read in "some time".    
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do not need to "watch" an audience's reactions to be aware of them. As mentioned, its *audible*, and there are plenty of cues and indications as to how an audience is responding to something. Being sat in a dark room, or making up your own mind vs following a mass has *absolutely nothing* to do with it. There is nothing inherently bad or inappropriate about making inferences based on such cues, its part of social awareness.  

Yes, you could just as easily say what you did, and if you had, it would have been fine. I've had many experiences of audiences being pumped for an awesome trailer, have you not? The cues would be people cheering or gasping in the right places, perhaps hearing whispers about how great it looked.  

You made two question marks after the term "knowing way" so I'll just explain that. It means a film is a little cheesy and *knows* its cheesy - e.g. Independence Day Resurgence. When I said "not in a knowing way" I meant that the film doesn't seem to be aware of its own cheesiness, it seems to take itself more seriously like Game Of Thrones or something. Does that make sense now?  

You seem to have a bizarrely overt and negative sensitivity to the idea of gauging other peoples responses, indeed it even seeming like the strangest thing to you. Do you have Asperger's at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! It feels almost like a Die Hard movie in places, Bond being like a vigilante McClane trolling this drug kingpin. Same soundtrack composer too (and even sounds similar in places, those occasional twangs).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I thought that the Ridley Scott produced miniseries of Coma would put the excellent Crichton directed Coma back on the map, but noone gave a shit and barely anyone knows the miniseries exists. I hope more people do see the film of Wake In Fright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its an inference made from certain audible sounds. Not quite groans or sighs but something more awkward, like nervous laughter and cringing. Does that help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) Here are some [comparison shots](http://imgur.com/a/64kh4) of the locations!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a neat moment, but I think a better example in Aliens is that little late night gathering looking over the blueprint maps, finding the flashing dots beneath the cooling towers. You see all those dots and think "fuck, what must that look like in real life, all the aliens squirming around".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to Vienna last year and ended up staying behind the concert hall where the defection takes place. Turns out it was a short walk to Kara's apartment too. A quick tram to Schonbrunn Palace and the Prater fairground for a ride on the ferris wheel, and my little accidental Living Daylights tour was complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean about those movies that lure you in and take you for a ride. I love those movies too. Its hard to discover them unknowingly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I would hugely recommend, if you have Netflix, is to watch the Black Mirror episode called "Be Right Back". Its a neat little film (about 50 mins) about a relationship with an AI, but gets under your skin in very clever ways. I actually preferred it to Her and found it lingered in the memory for longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wake in Fright! I never see this film mentioned, such a great film. I think Jacob's Ladder would belong nicely on your list also.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? That film was extraordinarily cheesy and lame. It was like a one-note Twilight Zone idea dragged out into one excruciating feature. The CGI butterflies, ugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Hiddleston would be *absolutely shit* as James Bond so I'm happy about that. His performance in The Night Manager as a sort of rogue vigilante-come-spy was terrible, so wooden and self-conscious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timothy Dalton was brilliant. I still love his two movies and could watch them any time as standalone thrillers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this trailer at the cinema recently and the whole audience seemed a little embarrassed by it. It was cheesy as fuck, and not even in a knowing way. It looked like an ad for some TV easter special or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw the penultimate episode, and Todds offing of Andrea was horrible. This is my first rewatch and Id completely forgotten about that. It affected more than anything in the show up to that point. Jesses reaction too... Just brutal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but it can be a red flag too. Sometimes contempt or resentment develops and you don't notice it until a moment like this, where your internal unconscious and automatic reaction is just not where it should be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shamefully I still haven't seen Brazil, but maybe now I should prioritise it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they stole the idea from Superman 3, by taking the fractions left after the decimal point that would have normally been erased? I love the film but not sure it really has that "oh fuck! what's this anomaly!" moment of sinister foreboding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah! I watched that recently and wow, it has dated so much. Its hard to believe it was actually a normal release film, the production quality and direction were terrible. The scene on the boat, good grief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some cool moments in films where a small, almost overlooked "glitch" on a computer screen ends up being something bad ass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It usually has accompanying bits of dialogue like "that can't be right!" "Maybe you're not reading it right!" or maybe characters just believing it must be a glitch. But then it turns into something awful that throws the rest of the film into anarchy. 

Examples - the planes changing course on the screens in United 93, the spreadsheet in Margin Call, the cyclone in Day After Tomorrow, the anomalous signal in Contact.    

I know there are some really cool ones, I love those scenes and the atmosphere where some crazy event starts with an innocuous blip on a screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a videogame poster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the dolly up to Marcy just before she winks in the apartment, its like the camera is in on all the mysteries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When one of you resents the other being happy about something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodness, that would take all day. Technically its brilliant, the acting, writing, production design, editing, music (both score and songs) and cinematography are all top notch. There are so many nice touches, like when he runs up the stairs, the keys falling from the window, the taxi ride, the sweeping camera movements in the office, along the road by the diner, and in the apartment, the rapid-fire editing of the burns book. So many details. The characters are ALL really credible, nuanced, interesting and quirky. The mysteries that start to unfurl and stack on each other, like the history of Marcy, her weird rape story, the crossed out names, the newspaper cutting on the sculpture, the woman who randomly shoots the guy in another apartment. The characters are so credible that even their own back-stories are curious, like why catherine o-hara is so fucking weird and enjoys trying to disrupt him when he's remembering the phone number. What does John Heard see in Marcy? Whats the history between Marcy and the other cafe owner? What's the deal with Kiki and her S M boyfriend? Normally when films try to be quirky its self-conscious, gimmicky and annoying, but in After Hours it feels so real and deserved. Even the first cafe scene where Marcy rushes over to talk to Paul, but then rather than listening to what he's saying she rudely watches over his shoulder at the till guy practicising dance moves. He's irritated by her, but overlooks it through his desperation to get laid. The atmosphere of the whole night with all the weird quirky details feels EXACTLY like my summer as a late teenager in New York, where everything you try to do just spirals out into weird unpredictability, mainly because of the people and their stories. On another level, I hugely relate to his character trying to reach out and connect to someone, hitting that point where he thinks "fuck, is this still worth it?" decides to invest more time because "what the hell" but then it just gets worse. How completely other worldly people seem, and locked in the bubbles of their own story. Like no one ever asks about him or gets to know him, he's just unbelonging to this weird world that's "after hours" and wishes he'd just stayed at home and jacked off. Its also just so funny, especially the end where he says "I just want to live", gets into that nice slow dance with a woman he's absolutely not attracted to, listens to the relevant "Is That All There Is?" by Peggy Lee, finds himself finally connecting to someone, and then just as the song is about to reveal the singers thoughts about death, all hell breaks loose when the vigilante mob breaks in. I've seen it so many times and love it just as much each time. It has a life of its own, like a good Coen bros movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have great taste! Its such a deeply enriched and atmospheric film. The characters are SO well drawn and believable, the little strange details, the amount of things which get started but not finished (eg his story about having his eyes bandaged, even the sculptures). Normally with a quirky film like this it would dated and tacky by now, but Scorsese's direction and the camera work really lift it into brilliance. It really hasn't dated at all, it barely even looks 80s (maybe just the computers in the opening/closing scenes).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you guess the twist about the timelines or was it a surprise?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he later gets himself into a 12 Monkeys type deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're confusing "Recently Added" with "New Releases". "Recently Added" is simply listing recent additions to Netflix, which could be from decades ago, there is no presumption for being recently produced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its got such an eerie quality to it, the ticking and that little sinister keyboard melody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its explained in Insidious XII, the Final Chapter, Finally, For Real, Ultimate Edition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these points are so funny (in that I agree with them). Being briefed two years after hibernation, and the ship finding the settlement instantly after descending through the clouds are inexcusable. But still, you will get fans saying "duh, you just didn't watch it properly and think things through! Stick to Transformers!" etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my favorite film! I love it so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nice try" has no relevance here, trying to be an asshole still prevents discussion doesnt it? And learn to spell "your" ffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kind of prevalent attitude makes having a discussion on this sub practically impossible. It all gets reduced to black and white thinking, reductionist bites for impulsive upvotes and the fickle hive mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not so sure the mind is as black and white as that. I absolutely think that people can be led to believe something, to imagine something, only later to realise it was a consequence of suggestion rather than something more considered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From IMDB: "Jamie Foxx is an American actor, singer, and comedian".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. Jamie Foxx, Whoopi Goldberg, Kristin Wiig, Walter Mattau, Charlie Chaplin, Jack Lemmon, Harold Lloyd and Stan Laurel never won an Oscar.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the hell not? Its a Danny Boyle film, its brilliant, and its very inventively shot with an awesome soundtrack. It was my favourite cinema experience so far this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know lol lol I never said anyone did lol :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also recruits an impressionable young girl into his criminal enterprises, brainwashes her with bullshit and almost fucks her up for good.  He also makes no effort to get back his original architect (Lukas Haas) from Saito. Doesn't even mention him. *Cunt*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with you lol lol lol :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the one where the disillusioned guy trapped in his own psyche goes on a wild spiritual trip leading to his eventual liberation? 'Cause yeah, that's definitely so psychological whilst Inception isn't psychological at all because Inception is like *any other movie*. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, which then? Lol lol :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For having an interpretation and liking a film? Yes, as pretentious as you are a moronic and judgmental dork.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes LOL :D so funny hehe ;D no movie is psychological is it! LOL :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I found with older films the boards were almost entirely legitimate discussions. Your stalker sounds like an exceptional bonkers situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fucking pedantic can you get? It was psychological in that it dealt with guilt, aspects of the subconscious and paternal influence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not at all. Everything is bullshit when viewed from a certain perspective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop being a dick. It was a highly original script, was daring enough to cross a heist film with psychology, a great soundtrack, fun performances, and very meticulous direction. Its also intriguing from a layers point of view. Didn't you stop to consider that the whole film is metaphorical therapy session revolving around letting go of guilt, and adrianne is the therapist? Watched like this it works like a companion piece to Shutter Island.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Temple of Doom is such a non-stop atmospheric and adventurous thrill  ride. When I was a kid, there was no better film to be excited about being on TV. It was impossible to start and not want to keep watching to the end. So many set pieces and cool moments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a few excellent, lesser known single season shows. One is Rubicon, a corporate conspiracy thriller, thsts shot and directed like a David Fincher film. Its brilliant. Also, Day Break, which is like 24 crossed with Groundhog Day. Guy keeps waking up on the same day, and uses the clues he can find by trying new things to clear his name of murder and find the real culprit. Its great fun and really well written in terms of structure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like it if in a few years, after you have a moment of clarity about your core strengths and passions, you turn this all around and write a great autobiography. Sounds like you've been dealt some tough cards, but now its how you play them. You can push through and make something of this, its your divine right.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll go HBC - fight club - brad pitt - inglourious basterds - SLJ (kinda, he did a voiceover).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I'd have gone argo - ben affleck - changing lanes - Sam Jackson - Jackie Brown - De Niro - Cape Fear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, if you go for the actor's bigger casted films, it gets a lot easier. Walken - Pulp Fiction, Jonah Hill - Wolf on Wall St. Then you're just looking to connect DiCaprio with someone from Pulp Fiction. Django Unchained should do it, with Sam L Jackson.  

Edit: actually fuck, Jonah Hill was *in* Django, so that's even easier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I play this with family all the time. OK - Scoot McNairy and Robert Mitchum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing more than what it was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I rarely cared for discussions of unreleased or recent blockbusters anyhow, but even so they were often fine (eg Arrival board was quite intelligent). But the older and more obscure stuff was brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK there seems to be a problem with the ambiguity of your term *everyone*. You meant company responsible to a client, rather than person responsible for the mistake, which wasn't clear from your post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fargo is probably my all time favourite of theirs. Its such a rich, detailed and thoughtful film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One I don't like is the one in Fight Club. I rented Flight of the Navigator from there and it was all fuzzy, couldn't even make out the dogs catching frisbees at the start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree about Clooney. He has "look how self-consciously suave and charming I am" mode (gravity, oceans etc) and then "look, I can be so wacky! Aren't I a good sport?" mode. I appreciate Barton Fink more than actually enjoy it, but I still have a hard time with Raising Arizona. I appreciate its style and individual scenes, but it doesn't hang together as a coherent story that I want to watch all in one go. I also need to rewatch A Serious Man, its one I didn't enjoy first time but I have a feeling it will grow on me like the others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would disagree on that one, the show was actually pretty entertaining and off-beat, whilst the film was massively stupid and shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember going to see this at the cinema when I was about 14, and absolutely loving it. Its still such a perfectly suspenseful and endlessly rewatchable family thriller, and refreshing in its reliance on tight situations rather than overt violence or headshots. The characters are so well drawn and acted, especially Tommy Lee Jones and his team. Fuck, now I need to watch it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Mann's Miami Vice movie has grown on me with time, I really enjoy its feel and aesthetics. The TV show was pretty awesome mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy Wiseau, also playing Trump, would be my choice.   

"I did not hit her I did not hit her I did naaahht. Oh Hai Putin"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weirdly I often have a hard time with Coen brothers movies on first watch. Millers Crossing, Big Lebowski, Burn After Reading, O Brother and No Country For Old Men I really didn't enjoy on first watch. But now I absolutely love them, and have watched them so many times. I think they sometimes just take a little time to adapt to their world, lingo, atmosphere and ideas. I haven't rewatched the lamer comedies though, like Intolerable Cruelty, Ladykillers and Hail Caesar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at that subtle off-blue coloring. The tasteful thickness of it. Oh my God, it even has a watermark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet if you read more about Vertigo, then watched it slightly drunk one night you'd absolutely love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it wasn't so much shocking, but I was kinda surprised when the Red Panda lady flipped all those bowls into that bowl that she had on her head, whilst riding on a unicycle. I mean it was just so unlikely and ridiculous, and I have no idea how even practicing for years allows a person to be able to do that in front of a massive crowd. Like I said, it isn't really shocking in its nature, so I hope I haven't done anything wrong here in mentioning it, but I really did think "did that just happen?" and even let the gif recycle a few times to see it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...so you mean "not allowed to exhibit the Bluray publicly without a license" which means a slightly different thing as I'm sure national cinema chain would have a license.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a common misconception, schizophrenia has nothing to do with dissociative personality disorder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a terrific thread for procrastinating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL my local community center is pulling a fast one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK, you can show a film to non-friends and family (i.e. at a community centre) as long as its not advertised or charged for. I'm sure the same would apply to a bar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with my parents. I think it keeps everyone suitably engaged without having to think too much. Last night I took Deepwater Horizon over and they loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you seem to be ignoring the concept of magnitude entirely by leveling all errors as equal. Surely, they are not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this in my mind as a kind of trilogy with The Matrix and Truman Show with the theme of recognising the captivity you're in before being able to escape it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Peter Jacksons Braindead (Dead Alive in US). Its a gloriously fun, inventive and stupidly gory comedy horror from New Zealand in the early nineties. Also, Jacobs Ladder. A very different kind of horror but amazing film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the David Julyan score to this film as well. He also did Memento and Insomnia, really cool music that gets under the skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty big error though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mention of Dear Zachary, what the hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should have been, and would normally be, bulletproof. I noticed some similar things in Bugsy Malone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds so cool, I would love to go somewhere like that as a social thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did go see it actually, but again was a blu projection and eventually just felt like watching it on TV. The contrast wasn't great. Weirdly I missed the scratches and cigarette burns of a classic print movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly off topic, but I always wonder why cinemas don't show older films for cheaper on quieter days (normally mon/tues). An arthouse cinema near me sometimes shows older films like Goodfellas, Batman etc but tickets are always 11 and the screenings are always practically empty. Its no surprise really when you can buy the bluray for half the price. I went to see Quadrophenia and was dismayed to actually have to see someone navigating a bluray menu screen. Projecting blurays is hardly as expensive as the old days of renting actual cinema reels. I used to enjoy seeing classics at the cinema, but these days I'd much prefer to see them at home where its free, and the screen size is just the same (in terms of perspective). However, if the tickets were something like 3-4, it would be worth going to just for the shared atmosphere and meeting other like minded people etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious what makes you say this is his best film, over say, Lost Highway, which is just as intriguing as a puzzle but also loads more going for it (darker neo-noir vibes, *awesome* soundtrack, interesting undercurrent themes). Lost Highway to me feels like a more complete film, not only due to its mobius strip structure but also it was written as a film, not a scrapped tv series condensed into a film.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? If you've had someone close to you die as a result of wreckless driving, then watch a scene like that written for laughs, you wouldn't think so. But nevermind, sorry for replying to your post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't sure of that at first but see what you mean - [The Abyss](http://www.iceposter.com/thumbs/MOV_8c661eef_b.jpg), [The Thing](http://img.moviepostershop.com/the-thing-movie-poster-1982-1010467005.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SL2: Judgement at Nuremberg Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the time you were only half watching whilst pairing some socks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a great Liam Neeson film. He basically has to look after these jews in his factory, and then when the nazis come, he gets loads of guns and has a massive shootout. There's a scene where he jumps over a barbed wire fence that uses about 200 different shots which is a little annoying. But the scene where he fist-fights hitler with glass taped round his fists is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Individual interpretations and all that. I guess people differ on what love is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We want you back! Next time, how about you er, throw some *different colored bowls* into that bowl, eh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
