<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couldn't sleep, so I spent 3 hours writing a Bohemia AAR. Let me know if it's worth continuing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might not be as strange as it is something I just don't understand. I was playing Austria and annexed a Romagna and Ancona from the Papal State. This generated some Urbino Separatist rebels. I didn't secure military access over to stop them from rising up, so they occupied both provinces and then crossed the sea and took Istria from me, too. I decided to just accept their demands, which were "All provinces owned becomes Urbino," or something like that. When I accepted, the separatists seemingly become my troops, and the occupied statuses all disappeared. I figure maybe it had something to do with Urbino still having been a vassal under the Papal State, but I have no clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my Luck of the Irish run with Thomond, and found it slightly easier than Desmond. While morale and manpower theoretically can help against someone like England, but early on it won't make much difference. You need good allies and numbers to push back England. Thomond's money making ideas gives you the funds to actually create the army that Desmond dreams of early on--when you'll need it. If you have late game ambitions, certainly Desmond will have the edge, so I can see the allure. You can argue that they have objectively the better ideas, as they align more with how most people play this game (expand and expand and be the best army you can be). However, you can also argue that Thomond has ideas better suited for more comfortable gameplay, emphasizing a stronger economy and colonizing. I'd say choose which style you want to play, then choose accordingly.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that on NPR's book concierge last year and was interested. I checked it out at my library, but had a stockpile of end of the year best of books that I never got around to reading it. Good to hear more praise about it to keep it on my radar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R5: Just an album of images relating to my Lucky Lucca run. Was kind of surprised to see this listed as a "Very Hard" achievement on the wiki, as it seemed to me to be more about patience rather than anything else. As long as you can set up an early hold in Northern Italy, it's primarily just colonizing and chilling with strong allies for the rest of the game. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucky Lucca pre 1700 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, first it was Savoy. Then I was able to secure France. Then France got angry at me for something and I jumped into the soft arms and heroic chins of Austria. I believe early game, though, Lucca usually is friendly toward the Papal State, whereas Florence is pretty much hard-coded as a rival to them always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! With a little patience in conquering provinces and securing friends in high places, you too can achieve mediocre success as little Lucca!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl, don't you worry about Lucca. http://imgur.com/a/L2XHo
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I guess that has to be it. I guess it's just the combination of Austria having weak heirs/negative prestige all early game long while Hesse (a two province nation in the middle of a volatile HRE) survived aggression and still maintained enough clout for 100 years to dominate the votes every election. Brandenburg and Bohemia were doing quite well this run, and usually I see them vote for themselves at some point. The amount of Protestant electors that continued voting for Hesse after 1500 (Again, Brandenburg and Bohemia converted, yet still overwhelmingly voted Hesse). 

I just found it peculiar how Hesse continually defied the odds, and maintained such a strong hold on the throne. Thanks for the enlightenment, I didn't know about the IA stored influence thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to preserve this name placement forever. You can put a straight line under that tag and it would STILL be perfect. They're  straight shooters, those Palatines. Angles and curves be damned, we're GOING STRAIGHT THROUGH NUREMBURG'S BORDERS. 

T H E  P A L A T I N A T E 

**T H E  P A L A T I N A T E** 
######T H E  P A L A T I N A T E  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T H E P A L A T I N A T E (Tag Porn) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R5: I'm also kind of posing a question to everyone here. I didn't think it was super strange that Austria didn't get votes in the first election, but then Hesse won again. And again. And Again. I have no idea how, but for a solid century, every elector was locked into voting for Hesse. Here's the screenshot I took marking the first time Austria took back emperorship. (And still...most electors switched back to voting exclusively for the Hessians)

http://imgur.com/a/Ostvf

You can also barely see that Hesse's IA was at 71 in the title picture, and managed to keep boosting it up for their century of power. But no one would vote for any reforms, so the HRE remained impotent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alternate Fact: Von Habsburgs lost. I'll tell you this, they lost, alright? Hesse has the best emperors. The people agree. Trust me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, I suppose it's just a passive kind of game. Honestly, if Austria doesn't inherit the Lowlands, I rarely see them expanding much into the HRE on their own. More often I see Brandenburg or Bohemia get strong on the east side, Cologne or Munster or some random, unstable duchy that had no right being big miraculously accumulate a chunk of land in the west, and Austria in the south. Usually the religious war sparks some excitement in relationships throughout, but I guess you didn't get lucky there. 

The one time I played through Poland to the end I did feel a little bit unstoppable. Once Russia is out of the picture, and if the Ottomans stagnate, you can just go wherever you want making the right alliances. Maybe try colonizing Canada and begin a colonial war to spice things up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're saying that Russia, nor the Ottomans, nor France, nor Spain, nor Great Britain, nor Austria, nor any alliance between any of these typical great powers is going to be your enemy? Usually alliance blocks form between rivals around this time, so I would expect you to find some opposition team-up on you. Otherwise you could be doing well enough on your own, Poland can get pretty strong. 

I'm not sure what your plan on playing is, but games can be fairly boring if you're not pushing AE to its bounds, backstabbing allies, and remain complacent in your position. Not saying any of this is what you're doing, it's just I'm not really sure what the state of your game really is, or what you expect it should be. If you don't interact with France or the HRE, not a whole lot is guaranteed to change.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give up on Bohemia. They've got quite a few obstacles to overcome in the beginning stages, what with the Hussite rebellion. Just take Jiri Z Podebrad and become emperor and then have your way with the world. Annexing Silesia on its own won't break you, but taking too much land too fast will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it is my hope that no one puts stock in the aggregated rating of a book on Goodreads, I know that people still do. So many of my favorite books are under 3.5 stars, because people use the rating system on their for personal use. Just recently, one of my friends rated Lincoln in the Bardo 2 stars because she was bothered by David Sedaris' voice in the audiobook. I get vehemently upset when people do this--and maybe I shouldn't--but I feel like if you're going to rate a book, you have to do so objectively. Goodreads simply isn't the place to look for impartial or informed ratings. 

However, as a librarian, it is an immensely useful metric to use for recommendations, or finding popular books. Certainly, then, you'd want to follow reviews that have more reviews, but 1,000 ratings might be a little steep. Something with 3 reviews that all laud a book as the next To Kill a Mockingbird should be taken with a grain of salt, but a few hundred ratings that fluctuate between 1-5 stars is good enough for me. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
