<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 18:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's currently at $168,000  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd you eat that leaf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I knew a guy who was unbelievably far up his own ass. I hung out with him for a bit and literally everything we did had to revolve around him. He also would only message me if he wanted something and wouldnt respond to my messages unless he felt he could get something out of it.

Stopped talking to him pretty quickly, so did my other friends (we knew him from HS). Kid couldn't understand why people weren't bending over backwards to talk to him. Narcissist men usually end up lonely in my experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 23:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up Unit 731. It was a Japanese biochemical weapons research facility in China. The stuff they did there easily rivals the Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS itself throws gay men off tall buildings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 17:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair a modern cruise ship can hold 7k comfortably, with their own rooms and space to eat and play and such. If we stacked em end on end like animals, i'm sure we could fit much more people in there. That doesn't make Noah's ark any more plausible of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty cool with returning to my base atoms when i die, I find it beautiful in a way. However, I was absolutely terrified of the concept when i first thought about it. Don't know if it was the religious upbringing or not but the thought of just not existing anymore took me a little while to get over. It is a real fear for some people, whether there is something to actually fear or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 18:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called the "Sunk Cost Fallacy" I think. He's trying to justify wasted resources.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sunk_costs#Loss_aversion_and_the_sunk_cost_fallacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 16:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounded steep to me too but apparently 20 years is the standard sentence if it's his third strike for Marijuana possession. Louisiana has some of the strictest possession laws in the US. 

 http://statelaws.findlaw.com/louisiana-law/louisiana-marijuana-laws.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting that you admit to only knowing the female side yet still feel qualified to assert the frequency of men's issues while also asserting the frequency of women's issues as being higher. You yourself listed a reason you are biased. How do you know men's issues aren't as prevalent when you have only experienced the female side? Wouldn't it be a no-brainer that female issues seem more prevalent or worrying considering that they're issues that effect you personally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened in Canada as well. My grandpa was 17 and got his mom to sign a paper saying he was 18 so he could join the Canadian Navy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 23:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it works out for him too, he's a good guy. Also, glad to hear that you landed on your feet man. It can't be easy to bounce back from that, prepared or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what he said, I thought It sounded steep. 

Also didn't mean to imply that traveling is inherently a waste of money. That's just how he described it to me. That he wasted the money traveling because he thought it would never end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point but he himself said he wasted it traveling. He didn't think the money would end so he just spent it on expensive trips. 

Didn't mean to come off as judgemental man, travel is enriching and spending your money traveling is a completely valid way to live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very fair point. He moved back to Ontario and i dont think he ever bought property in his time in Alberta. He was just very surprised that it didn't last forever which I thought was relevant. 

But you're right the people who owned houses and have other debts are the ones really hurting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 16:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was working a temp job recently with a guy who got laid off from the oil fields. He was making $85/hr as a general laborer. He blew it all on expensive trips abroad. So when the price of oil dipped, he got laid off and had nothing to show for it. 

Now hes working minimum wage jobs with me and complaining about not having any money. Nice guy in all fairness, and a good worker, but I can't understand how he thought that the oil market would always stay as high as it did. 

Edit: Wasn't trying to imply that travel is an inherent waste of money. The guy described it to me as him wasting his money traveling because he thought he'd always be working at the oil field. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IAKg6kbXIJM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 05:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if they don't share that respect for common humanity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 17:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my understanding a lot of US military equipment nowadays is made regardless of need. There are tanks sitting in depots somewhere in the US that will never see action but were still built because they need to justify the budget. I wonder how much that plays into the more recent militarization of the police. It seemed to get more prominent after the US began to pull out of the middle east as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 00:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same thoughts about Flowers for Algernon while reading this. Highly recommend it, it's a short but really touching book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 08:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some say that one of the most powerful and influential people in the entire country is a black man. But I'm not entirely convinced yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 08:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but then you'd be on a list.

Only if you're slower than the cops (   )

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 07:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Though perhaps her matching Kylo is still problematic. He was already injured when she dueled him, and it could be argued that his mental instability detracts from his mental force capability, but it's still questionable, I'll admit.

Remember how they showed off Chewbacca's bowcaster? They had multiple small moments of Han using the bowcaster to blast away stormtroopers. One shot was him killing 3-4 with one bolt. I think they did that because they were trying to establish how much damage it can do to the average person. So that later on when Chewbacca uses it to injure Kylo, we know that it's a fatal wound to anyone else. 

IMO that injury was probably meant to be way more damaging than it looked. I don't think they executed it properly though, because it did seem weird that she had that level of ability against him even with the injury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if i elect someone to represent my opinion on each individual matter, that isn't me having my say in each individual matter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 15:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell is voting for then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this proposed law would protect you from those rotten ones, no? There would be no benefit to them lying about being on the pill (or convincing you not to wear a condom) and possibly getting pregnant if you have to actually consent to parenthood. 

Also where's women's role in this? With this proposed law in place can they not demand men wear condoms, and then not have Sex with them if they don't wear one? Is it only men that would have to play an active role in preventing these things like stds?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't people continue wearing condoms for the STD protection? Like who doesn't care about getting an STD? And people who don't care about STD's probably aren't protecting themselves to being with*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 05:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya Canadian politeness only goes so far, there's a reason fighting is an actual part of Hockey. 

Honestly though the Dutch sound a lot like Canadians. We also swear a lot (depending on the company) and try not to bullshit, its too fuckin cold for that really.

Or to put it into Canadian: "Ya just gotta tell er how it is bud." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a famous "casting couch" for porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 02:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VDFnrNtqAjo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 00:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it isn't MGM then what is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't she claim to have a consistent record though? It would be one thing if she was saying that she was wrong and changed her mind. But isn't she presenting it as if she never held the position against gay rights?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somalia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or has a degree in "Communication" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're so enlightened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my understanding it's his fashion company that's eight digits in the red not him. Corporate bankruptcy is not the same as personal bankruptcy. He's still personally wealthy. 

(D. Trump has had ~4 corporate bankruptcies over his career, he's still worth billions) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THESE WOUNDS THEY WILL NOT HEAL

Also this:https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l9dEZ0hRlF4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS is selling slaves right now. But only white people have ever oppressed anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 00:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Go buy yourself a used car from 1993" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 16:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it isn't stress related? Like the meds you used to take caused side effects which cause stress and that can exacerbate almost any condition you have. Now that you stopped taking them the homeopathy could be doing nothing but the lack of stress from side effects of the other meds could be helping to clear up your other conditions.

Just an idea, you'd probably know better than I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 16:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed isn't homeopathic if that's what your getting at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 16:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Career path

Is that sleeping with superiors for advancement or is that selling your body on the street? I might switch fucking industries if either pays well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 16:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my understanding that was a piece about why men might have evolved a sense of humor as a form of attracting mates. The title was deliberately inflammatory, but AFAIK the actual article isn't saying women are incapable of being funny. Just why a sense humor might no be as prevalent or developed in women on average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely, I was just explaining what the word Nippon is. Wasn't arguing your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 22:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For further clarification Nippon (Land of the Rising Sun) is a Japanese term for Japan.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 22:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In certain feminist circles treating one gender better is considered sexism. It's called benevolent sexism. 

source: http://www.understandingprejudice.org/asi/faq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I guess I was the one who missed it then lol.

Have you ever heard of Numberphile? Pretty good if you like interesting math.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairly certain the comment above you is sarcasm. Either way, thanks for showing me SmarterEveryday. I just subscribed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 04:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/BGRAonpLeQg?t=37s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 14:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this to be the absolute saddest and most infuriating consequence of the SJ movement.* They've cheapened the terms for racism and sexism. Being called a "racist" doesn't mean shit when it can literally mean anything from "beaten and murdered for having a different skin color" to "this made a rich black person uncomfortable". 

Imagine if "murderer" could also mean "someone looking at me angrily on the subway". How much weight would that term now carry? How useful from a legal or language perspective would this term be? How insane is that SJW's are actively doing this with terms like: "rape", "harassment", "sexist", "oppression", "misogyny", and many others? 

They're actually throwing useful terms under the bus and it's so rage-inducing. 

*Edit: Upon further thought, this is second to false rape claims, as those have more direct and immediate consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 14:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if the men aren't white. It's not PC to bash a Muslim or a black man (even if they're doing something horrible *cough* Cologne *cough*). So they are sometimes offended by male-bashing. It's funny that they can't even keep their hatred of men consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 14:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fanboy feminism works as well IMO. A lot of them defend feminism like someone defending their favorite show, or series, not as activists defending a movement. Feminism is the new TV for a lot of them it seems like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 14:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, came here for the jerking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Quality of life expectancy" would probably make the most sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know that Bush was behind 9/11! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does EI and welfare force able-bodied men into the military? Genuinely curious because the military is selling your body in a way, and if your reasoning is sound here there should be nothing stopping them from doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to ask if that was sarcasm but holy shit it's actually real. This just blew my mind, the lengths some people go to.  

https://www.yahoo.com/health/blowtox-injections-keep-hair-looking-good-during-128033223152.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 22:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, our population is also far more centralized than the US. The majority of Canadians live in Ontario and Quebec (about 60% combined). For perspective the two most populated states (California and Texas) account for only about 18% of the total population of the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it funny how they decry stereotypes while a lot of them use stereotypes to navigate the world. Like you're from a "POC" place, therefore you are a "POC" religion. Regardless of whether it's something statistically unlikely like Judaism (0.2% of the world population) you just couldn't be a "white" religion. 

To be fair though, I actually assumed Lebanon would be demographically closer to other middle eastern countries like Iran  (98.4% Muslim). I was surprised to find that there's like 18 different major religious groups there, with ~40% of them being Christian. Oh yah but i forgot, I'm white, so I can't understand this fact.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 19:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "don't stick your dick in crazy" Isn't that just practical advice? I don't understand how that's somehow denigrating the victim. It's essentially saying to stay from abusive women. Why's that bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 03:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya some of them are just garbage. The problem with YouTubes system though is the automation itself. If you get a video flagged for copyright u basically have to wait for the claim to lapse (90 days of unmonetization) or get the other party to give up on it. YouTube won't step in unless you make a big enough shitstorm on 
twitter (look up the youtuber "I hate everything" and his situation). An MCN will give you a direct line to YouTube to deal with this stuff quickly, saving the content creator money and time. They aren't really a bad idea in theory honestly, they just tend to be run more like a scam than anything else unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 03:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main thing that MCN's do AFAIK is provide a middleman between a content creator and YouTube itself. This allows for quicker resolutions to disputes regarding copyright, flagging, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little did we know that the "trip" was a drug trip and "find and heal myself" meant get high af. She wasn't lying she was just keeping it low key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 20:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the ban was on any device capable of accessing the Internet, not just a computer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 03:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone who doesn't want to do this anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 17:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you EA, you can't tell me what to do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here in Canada I believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Bill hit that too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They call the parents "crisis actors", it's messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And only when the definition benefits them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 04:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really dislike Paul's approach tonight, it seems like he's constantly trying to 1up Milo instead of provide a counter-argument. It's annoying because I think he's capable of so much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 19:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A miserable little pile of secrets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 20:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that it's like approaching the speed of light in concept. The closer they get towards the heart of masculinity, the less and less it can be influenced sociologically. You can't argue oppression with a y-chromosome, it isn't listening. So they will experience diminishing returns for increased effort the farther along they go down this rabbit hole IMO. 

It should also be noted that repression generally leads to rebellion and i feel that all this push to end masculinity will end in a push in the opposite direction. I don't think the anti-masculinity crowd has any control beyond social shame and if you push men out of society then you lose that control. Basically i'm not worried because in my eye's they are digging their own grave as we speak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 19:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who called them in though? Cops usually aren't just sitting around at churches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 16:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So either I could write a fake letter and smuggle it out of prison in the hopes that it would reach outsiders eyes who would then report it to the jail/media, thus getting the other prisoner a beating and/or solitary. 


Or I could just put drugs in his cell. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 15:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, is a learned pattern of behavior the same as believing in the concept that a certain race or races is inferior? I just don't think a dog abused to the point of attacking certain races is really thinking that he is a superior race and they therefore deserve to be attacked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan underwent a military coup in the 1930's which eventually led to their involvement in WW2. So being a right wing militarist is like being a Nazi to them AFAIK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 17:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The argument makes a smidgen more sense since it happened in France. The french language is gendered, and in physics most of the forces are masculine words and most of the things that are acted upon are feminine IIRC. So i think it was more of a semantic argument against the use of gendered words, and not an argument against objective reality. 

However, the things they argue about never ceases to amaze me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 14:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male privilege is dying and not being around to make women comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 16:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disrupting the class was the final straw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 15:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom had the second of our cats declawed when we spayed her (3-4 months old? Not sure, she was a stray, but she was under a year). We got lucky and she still loves us but my mom regrets it and won't do it to any other of our cats. She's a very sweet cat and we spoil the shit out of her. Though, I do feel bad every time i think about what we did to her.

Through a remarriage my family now has 5 cats (used to be 6 :C), and the declawed one isn't even on the bottom wrung of the totem pole. She can't fight back as well but if she's attacked she'll make the most godawful noises, so the others tend to leave her alone.

I guess what i'm getting at is that even if you're lucky and it works out like my cat, it's still a horrible thing to do and if you empathize with your pets at all, you should avoid it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 16:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweak x Craig </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 05:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't ask permission for his Billy Joel parody IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aneurysm* But I only know that because my grandfather has one in his Aorta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TAKE A RIDE ON THE QUADROCAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're hate full slurs are through! WEUWEU!


I call weuweu on you! WEUWEU!



We'll fight until you're pc black and blue! weuweu!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, If you could hook us up to the heating system too we'd really appreciate it, eh. Watching the game in a parka can get tedious. Especially when you're trying to keg stand on a moose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 01:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The patriarchy is really a cosmic force of sorts. It's not really perpetrated by anyone, it just kind of is. Sorry, I'm not a theoretical feminist so i can't explain any deeper than that. All i know for sure, is that it's men's fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 20:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world has much better access if you can afford it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "pics or it didn't happen" applies here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
