<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, the *only* smoking gun that could take Trump down would be direct payments from Russia to Trump *provably* made to curry favor or get sanctions removed. I have no doubt members of his team will get nabbed along the way but I'm not positive there will ever be enough to take him down too. 2020 is really important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but they're going to do whatever they can to make "leaks" the "real story" to keep Russia news out of the spotlight in whatever way they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not willing to make any bets on that account. Benghazi stuck around for like several years more than I would have thought they'd be able to keep it around, so who knows with this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point it seems to me they've successfully overtaken the narrative and now the Susan Rice "scandal" is all we're going to hear about. Fucking incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want that - I thought it hit the perfect balance. Too much to do and you get quest fatigue or just plain old annoyance like in Far Cry 4, where there is so much bullshit constantly happening that it's not longer enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We agreed to forget about that one, remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   silly hop that didn't contribute to the mechanics of the game

 There was a lot of that in Skyward Sword. Lot's of silliness that didn't contribute much, from mechanics to design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BotW is largely a derivative blend of many recent trends in games. It's Ubisoft+Tomb Raider+crafting+Shadow of the Colossus+Zelda. That's not a bad thing because they took the essential elements that make each of those things great and stripped out the bad things. They perfected the formula of each element. It's not, however, an original formula by any means. It's just a really well-done blend of many things that came before it (like everything else is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot that I own Link Between Worlds - that thing needs a replay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a way I agree - but the dungeons were great in most of the older games because they often felt unique and distinct, using different mechanics and challenges in each dungeon, and their length made them memorable. The only issue I have with BotW is that the shrines and beasts are not all that distinct from one another (visually or in content), and they're short. So I totally agree that the world is amazing in BotW and I'd much rather have that than the silly portal-linking overworld of Skyward Sword - but distinct, unique, lengthy dungeons would push this game to a new level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, interesting point - I haven't faced ganon yet, but the game definitely does seem to get easier as you go. I still wouldn't say it's trivial - I have a tough time with Lynels and if I'm not careful, I sometimes die while exploring and getting caught by a pack of monsters I didn't see. But it definitely gets easier - a fucking weak enemy could wipe you with a single hit early on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blights were really repetitive, I agree. And I think I did the beasts in the "wrong" order, maybe. I did the elephant, the lizard, the camel, then the bird. I think the ideal order would have been bird, lizard, elephant, camel, based on ease of beast and benefit of power you get for doing them. But regardless, the beasts got repetitive in both style and action, so I would love for them to return to traditional dungeons in future games rather than beasts and shrines. Most everything else is perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is totally valid reasoning. That was the excuse Republicans used. Throw it back in their faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved both of Dave's new specials. Thought they were fucking hilarious. That said, there were a couple of times where you could definitely tell he'd been sort of "out of the loop" for awhile. Once or twice it felt more like I was watching an 80s Eddie Murphy show than a modern comedian. Did it disrupt my enjoyment of the show? No. Did it occasionally feel a little weird and out of place for 2017. Yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To what end? What good is served to the people by preventing that regulation going into place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one really satisfying thing about this whole ordeal is going to be watching the next president undo all of Trump's executive orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are convinced the have 6 million subscribers when their posts regularly have like 180 comments on them. 500 is a high comment count for a typical thread there. Subtract the bots posting about bricks and the wall and you've lost some of the paltry contributions - much of the rest is low-effort memeing. There are typically just a handful of actual posts in the comments. It really is a ghost town. /r/politics has a bit over 3 million subscribers and vastly more participation and activity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have more than likely already moved on and forgotten about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One person posted about how they saw those tweets months ago, but since no one else in the herd was making a big deal out of them, they just went along with it.

 I actually saw all those tweets the day she wore that dress since I went through her twitter. I assumed she became Trump supporter recently and since no one else mentioned those tweets I thought it wasn't a big deal. Turns out no one fucking knew until recently. Fuck me. I could've made a thread about it long time ago.

Pack mentality. Little room for independent thought. 

It's also funny how many comments there are about how terrible her music is. Suddenly, now that she's not on their side, the truth comes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...as if /r/the_donald isn't frequently jam packed with low-effort shit posts and memes about whiny liberals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, everyone needs a break. There's also (in my view anyways) a big difference between playing golf sometimes, on the courses near DC, and flying, several weekends a month, to YOUR privately owned course at major taxpayer expense. Golf is one thing - this is something else though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *bows as m'lady m'lania passeth by* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you keep the context of this donation (which was provided in the very comment you replied to) in mind, he's essentially flushing this money down a black hole for good publicity. The budget cuts he proposed, if any of them pass, would do massive damage to the national parks. This is a photo op for Trump, nothing more. That, plus the fact that he is directly profiting from his weekend trips to Mar a Lago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that the sources aren't nameless *to the journalists*, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though I wasn't a huge fan of the film, I thought the acting was great - very naturalistic. There were a couple of points where Robert Redford seemed to actually goof up his lines (not sure if it was an actual goof but it really felt authentic) and they intentionally kept those moments in there. It made it feel very real. One example is early on when he asks the newsroom if anyone speaks Spanish - he accidentally says "does anyone speak English" before correcting himself and it seemed like he genuinely made a mistake, but it added to the film because the rest of it is so solidly acted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pieces are starting to fit together. These meetings that were conveniently undisclosed, more of which come to light every week. The connection between Devos and Prince (who set up this particular undisclosed meeting). The server on Trump property that was almost entirely used by a Russian bank and Betsy's husband's company. All of the pieces are starting to click. Individually each story adds to the intrigue, and if they all come together the way it's looking like they're coming together, each story will have been integral to the whole. Something fucking weird is going on, and as more pieces come to light, we're finding out exactly what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it *does* make a difference (I asked why the person I replied to thinks it makes a difference - I didn't assert that I don't think it doesn't make a difference). It opens up new ways of looking at the character through different opportunities for backstories, reinterpretations of the relationships they have with other characters, and creates different angles for character development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the book? I watched the film and came away disappointed. It might just be that I'm used to more modern filmmaking, but the movie is like 2.5 hours long and everything that actually *happens* in the movie is typed out by a typewriter in the last 30 seconds instead of actually happening. I imagine in book form a lot of this investigation would be really interesting though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is way too much to keep straight with this story. No wonder Trump and his team aren't able to keep their bullshit under wraps. I'm flummoxed and I'm not even involved in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The layout on the site is awesome - in the print book I read it in it was lots of arrows and boxes. The little expanding tabs feature is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically more than just a character's appearance changes when you change their race/gender - that's what can make it interesting. It opens avenues for exploration of very different kinds of backstories and interactions with other characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are interested in a peek into the world of conservative talk radio, check out an essay called "The Host" by David Foster Wallace. It was written like 15 years ago but it's still totally relevant today. Really interesting stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you're coming from but disagree that it's disrespectful to the new character, or that it's automatically shoehorning. The fact is, long-standing characters have name recognition and value to the brand that new characters just don't. Most new characters, regardless of race, will always lurk in the background of the classics. Allowing types of people that you don't typically see in the "prime-time" slot to embody those classic characters is very respectful if you ask me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not safe to assume they all were. Unless the people I worked with (real flesh and blood people) were bots as well. There were a few Bernie or bust people who didn't vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's about to win a double-whammy. Gorsuch will be on the Supreme Court by week's end AND the filibuster option will be gone on Supreme Court nominees. That means, god forbid, if Trump has the opportunity to nominate another SC judge, it can be as loony-ass right wing a nominee as he wants. And there's nothing democrats could do about it if it happens before the election in 2018 (and possibly not then afterward if things don't go well). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have liked to like JJ. But it was just... really boring. An 8 episode run would have been great, I think. 13 was just too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But again, what difference would you say it makes what race they are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle called Trump an idiot, unqualified, terrible candidate... the works. During the primaries. Then Trump became the R candidate for the GE and my uncle was standing outside the polls holding a Trump sign for hours. He completely flipped. Bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that "silent majority" idea. Such a humble brag. Plus Trump barely won by scraping by an EC win in a few states, and he lost the popular vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it's been that way since political cartooning of this variety came into existence. It's not a very common format these days, so younger people probably haven't been exposed to it much. But it is by no means an original stylistic choice by this cartoonist - it's been around for several hundred years at this point. Not that these are great examples of it, but that's how political cartoons work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else occasionally find themselves drinking in dreams, and then feeling guilty about it for the rest of the dream? It's only happened a few times (I've been sober for roughly 2 years now) but it's a strange thing to go through. It feels great waking up and realizing it was just a dream though, I will say that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats and keep it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it's likely OP posted it on an alt account. Look at the timestamp. He posted it, screenshotted it, posted it here. Other clues: use of underscores in both usernames, extremely generic Donald Trump username. So that's my theory. Cut the bullshit people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Hardly anything will come of this. The writer might get fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Rather than talking out of your ass, you could review their standing in comparison to other charities on the internet](https://www.charitynavigator.org/index.cfm?bay=search.summary orgid=3247) (hopefully, said internet will still exist once Trump and co. are done with it). The ACLU has an overall rating of 94%, with a 93% in financials and a 96% in transparency. Administrative expenses make up only 5.6% of its budget. And it has been there for some huge, historic victories for civil liberties. It's a great organization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mormons largely voted for Evan McMullin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't wind up reading it, not yet anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does The Easter Parade stack up to Revolutionary Road? I really liked Rev. Road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what turned me off about The Girl with the Dragan tattoo, too - why the hell do I need to know the make, model, and processing power of every computer the characters use? Why do I need to know what socks they're wearing? I felt bogged down by details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This week, I finished **Consider the Lobster** by David Foster Wallace. I really enjoyed most of these essays, especially his review of a usage dictionary (never really thought I'd say I enjoyed a dictionary review), John McCain's 2000 campaign, and the one about conservative talk radio. The essays about Updike and Dostoyevsky were less interesting to me, but for fans of those authors, I imagine they are worth a read. What I noticed most about his non-fiction writing (this was the first non-fiction I've read by him) is that he is great at making the essay about so much more than the subject he's writing about, and at making topics you would typically see as boring (such as "American Usage" or, literally, the boredom of riding a bus and doing a tedious job for weeks on end) incredibly interesting. He's very perceptive and observant as well - there are always multiple layers to everything he writes about, and he sees it from many sides. The interweaving of his personal experience into the subject he's writing about is done very artfully. I give this a 4/5 and I'm looking forward to reading A Supposedly Fun Thing later this year.

For my book this week, I'm reading **Hard-Boiled Wonderland and the End of the World** by Haruki Murakami. I read Norwegian Wood earlier this year and really enjoyed it, though I'd heard it was his most "normal" book. I'm now on chapter 3 of HBW and that seems to be an accurate assessment. I liked a short story called Ice Man that I read by Murakami, which is what initially got me interested. I have a feeling I'm going to enjoy this book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sick post bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More often they call it "a one-trillion dollar infrastructure package." Turns out that's a valuation though, not a price tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have faith that democrats won't get on board (in large enough numbers to pass anything) that is such a blatant corporate handout. Considering Trump's dismal approval rating in the democratic base, they have no real incentive to as long as they clearly present their case. They can make it pretty clear, pretty easily, that this isn't real infrastructure investment, and people will get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority of other posters on this subreddit are not selling anything either, or telling other people they need to read 200 books. And people who are posting here who read tons of books aren't "demanding anyone keep up" either. Anyways, that's not what you take issue with in the post I responded to, either - no mention of monetization or sale. Your issue was that you felt like people were making it a contest or comparing the number of books they've read or using it as a measure of their intelligence, dedication, or worldliness. My point is that, in the very act of publicly reporting how many books you've read (12/52), you are essentially participating in the same thing. And my larger point is there's nothing wrong with that, particularly in a subreddit specifically created for people to post about their reading goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot of irony in this post, with its 12/52 flair. Keep in mind that many people could say the exact same things you're saying about the idea of trying to read 52 books in a year. I'm not sure why people are being so judgemental about this. No way am I reading 200 books this year but I don't hold anything against people who do. Sheesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, it sort of seems like these posts are meant to provoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's pretty sick. I had not heard some of those. All this reminiscing about "the good old days" where you could beat the shit out of people. How bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awhile back I was thinking about that video. A watermelon is the perfect object for that situation. The explosion makes it look like a headshot in a movie.

I was also thinking about what it must have been like to be the person who assembled those catapult things. On the one hand you'd probably feel bad that it malfunctioned and literally blew up in someone's face. On the other hand, you would know, even the first time you watched the video, that you had helped create a piece of video that would survive the test of time and go down as a classic fucking hilarious clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where this differs from what you describe is that Pence's is tied specifically to his wife being there. That creates the weird implication that I cited above. It's not "oh, I might get drunk and do something stupid like get in a fight or go streaking". It's not even "I limit my drinking because I don't want to do something stupid". It's, very specifically, I might get drunk and cheat on my wife if she's not there to keep an eye on me. It implies a weakness of character and it's also... well, weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the reason it comes across as odd is the implied lack of self-control. Refusing to attend events where alcohol is served if not with his wife implies that the second he gets some booze in him, he'll be off the races chasing down hussies. An actual sense of personal responsibility and self-control allow a person to drink casually without having to worry about cheating on their spouse, in my view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do find it, link it - I haven't seen it before, but if he does do it frequently I'd like to know so that I don't make a bad argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to say. I agree with you that our current landscape is being reshaped by what he's doing. The historical impact of it is TBD. I'd like to think this will be an aberrant event and that people will gradually reawaken to reality as the incompetence and unproductivity continue. If that's the case, we'll go back to a reasonable world once he's out of office, and he'll be viewed, in the grand scheme of things, as an ineffective president that doesn't get much coverage in history classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...you're in a prison of your own sins... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People try to pretend that Trump wasn't mocking the disability of the reporter. Has anyone ever seen him do that little hand-wavy gesture in another context? He uses his hands all the time - but never like that. It's always thumbs up - OK symbols - conductor's baton type shit. Never the little curled-in flailing. It's pretty clear what he was doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even so, eventually he'll fade into history just like most other presidents unless something truly earth shattering takes place during his time in office. So far it seems like the biggest takeaway will be incompetence and unproductivity. People forget those things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you claiming that people don't read newspapers anymore without having done any research to validate that point? That's sure what it looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WSJ is a good option for that as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good bit of the stories on NYT and Washington Post (the straight news that is, rather than columns or editorials) come from wire services like AP and Reuters. They do their own investigative journalism, for sure, but most of their international stories are from a wire service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am torn on ACA repeal being dead. They claim it's still on the table, but personally, I feel that may just be a tactic to placate voters. They don't want to look like they lost. They want ACA repeal to appear to still be on the table whether it actually is or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't I ever get to see this shit when I'm out in public? I'm jealous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being convinced one way or the other is a bad idea right now. There's an ongoing investigation that will hopefully yield results. If there's an investigation, there's enough to go on to make it worth looking into. At the moment we know there was Russian meddling via the targeted disbursement of fake news in swing states. This was confirmed in the open hearing Monday. We know there were several aides and members of the Trump campaign who had meetings with representatives from Russia that they did not previously disclose or that they lied about (Flynn). We know Trump's campaign manager (for five months of the campaign) was under contract with a Russian oligarch several years ago specifically to influence politics to benefit Putin. That's some of what we know, and the intelligence communities say they know more. What does all this mean and how do all the pieces fit together? That's what the investigation is supposed to turn up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want some insight into how those conservative talk radio stations actually work, check out an essay called The Host by David Foster Wallace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I just kiss. I don't wait. And when you're a star they let you do it. You can do anything. Grab em by the pussy. You can do anything."

Can and could have different meanings. Can do means you are able to. Could do means you theoretically could. How would he know he can if he hasn't tried? He says that he walks up and kisses people without even asking. Why would it be surprising that he grabbed a pussy too?

Look again at how the sentences interact. Just after "they let you do it" comes "you can do anything." Taken together, that essentially says "they let you do anything" - the "can" functions as an indication of assumed permission, not as "could". "Grab them by the pussy" is just an example of the "anything" that you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I also poke my head in to see the shit show once or twice a day. If they really think there are 6 million people subscribed, why do threads only tend to get 100-450 comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, well you shouldn't have put "could" in quotation marks then. And the "you can do anything" comes directly after Trump lists things he *does* do. "I just kiss. I don't wait. And when you're a star they let you do it. You can do anything. Grab em by the pussy. You can do anything." That does not read as theoretical by any stretch. It is tied directly back to his statement about things he claims to do, which he concludes by saying "you can do anything". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I consider all leaks to be a net benefit if they reveal corruption on either side. I was glad to have access to the fact that the DNC was rigging the primaries and I'm glad to hear about the corruption and incompetence of the current occupants of the Whitehouse. So we definitely see things differently on that front, and to be frank, I don't believe you when you say you think all leaks are bad for America considering the clear insinuation in your post when you talk about Clinton. Maybe you're being honest, but I am very skeptical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nope.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FnMAo1T3OzA) No could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to any other crime, does "they let me do it" (from the mouth of the person who committed the crime, mind you), count for jack shit?

"Hey, did you just steal that guy's wallet?"

"They let me do it."

"Oh, carry on then." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the content of the leaks matter? Or is it just leaks = bad? Just want to see where the narrative's sitting right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good news - there are still many, many people alive today who would have died if not for the ACA. So there's that, even if there is an eventual repeal and literally everything is undone. I'm sure it's still frustrating as hell, but a lot of those policies did a lot of good while they were in place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so much more humanizing and less embarrassing to just admit you goofed and go back to sign the things. Sheesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the inherent flaw in the idea of unmoderated free speech is that at a certain point, without moderation, one group or another will dominate the conversation and drown out dissenting voices (much like the paradox of limitless liberty and tolerance, where to meet that definition, you have to give liberty to those who would take yours or tolerate intolerance). Conversely, with too much moderation, you get /r/the_donald, where dissenting views are disallowed entirely. There is a balance that should be sought, where speech can be free within a set of reasonable guidelines. Different platforms can define what reasonable means, whether it's a company or a team of moderators. The community either tacitly agrees to that set of guidelines through continued participation, or they move on to one that better meets their definition. There are plenty of bastions of truly "free speech" on the internet, but they don't tend to be highly trafficked because they devolve into one-sided echo chamber shit holes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Not even close. You can say whatever you want. Whether or not a particular company wants to carry what you say is totally up to them. Freedom of speech has been around as a guiding principle of our republic for far longer than social media has been around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, I go for a daily 5-minute dose of wtf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a general sense, sure, absolutely. On reddit specifically? Not necessarily. They can choose to (or not to) harbor whatever types of discussion they want. Just because free speech should exist doesn't mean it has to or even should exist unfettered on all platforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next generation... but not the next generation of Clintons, for the love of god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once the election was over, I completely stopped caring about anything Clinton had to say. Would I prefer her over Trump? Of course. Beyond that, I have zero interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the steel beams - the entire building was essentially a giant furnace once the fire of the explosion took hold. Think about what a furnace is used for.

 So both of the twin towers were hit by airplanes, and they both collapsed. The thing is, they collapsed almost exactly in the foot print of their building. When you think about a building that large coming down, and the fact that the buildings surrounding it were largely unharmed, it seems unlikely. I am not a PE (yet!), so I can't really explain this.

Hopefully, once you're a PE, whatever that is, you'll figure this one out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After watching hundreds of horror movies, yes, I've definitely adjusted my standards. I think of "good movies" and "good horror movies" as two separate things with separate goals now. Sometimes, though rarely, there's overlap between the two. Thrillers tend to have a higher crossover with "good movies" - but more conventional horror has lots of movies that are great at being scary (and/or fun-scary) while pretty pitiful at everything else that makes a non-horror movie good.

Thinking more deeply about it, the Catholic bent of The Conjuring might have had something to do with its popularity, too. The film exists within a framework where god and demons, etc, are accepted as being real, in a way that many other horror films are not - there isn't a layer of skepticism about the existence of god and demons in the Conjuring like there is in a lot of movies, or at the very least, the question is firmly answered in the film. I haven't seen it in some time, but I remember walking away from it almost feeling like it was a "Catholic film", kind of like when you hear Christian rock and know it's Christian rock even if they *don't* say Jesus all the time. It felt "safe" for Christians/Catholics et. al. to watch, if that makes any sense at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just reminded me of how fucking obnoxious tomorrow's going to be. It's not cute, people. It's fucking annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the reason it gets a lot of love is that it's a horror movie *and* a halfway decent movie. Much of the time, horror movies are horrible movies even if they're effective at being scary. I love horror, but I can recognize that, aside from the horror elements, many of my favorite horror movies are otherwise not very solid films. The Conjuring is a watchable film even for people who aren't horror fans. It's not a top-tier horror movie, but it's coherent and functional as a film *outside* the horror elements, so I think it has broader appeal than most conventional horror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last 20ish minutes of insidious are so fucking funny. Once he goes into the "other world" or whatever it's called, it's like he walked into a small-town haunted house at the high school. If I remember correctly he's like punching ghouls in the face and shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Eileens, a whole group of em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it was created by wedding dress companies, but I also doubt they're opposed to it continuing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a principle. I am opposed to the death penalty, period, because if it's misapplied in *even one case* it's wholly unethical. Particularly now, since we have the ability to clear people post-mortem through DNA evidence, and because we have executed people that we now know are innocent, it should absolutely be done away with.

Once there are exceptions to the principle, there is room for error. Even if someone "really deserves it", there is no place for it in modern society, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. It disturbs me that people are gleefully calling for the death penalty for these people. Maybe that's just because the death penalty disturbs me in general. Jail them if they're guilty, no qualms with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People keep insisting that there must not have been any skeletons in the RNC's closet or else they would have released it. I guess these people haven't heard of a little thing called blackmail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading *Consider the Lobster* right now and there are two essays in it that are very interesting to compare to the modern political environment. 

One follows McCain's 2000 campaign during the primaries. He was, in a much more dignified and respectable manner, the Trump of that election cycle - outspoken, an "outsider"/maverick, and someone that people felt was being genuine when he spoke to them (whether or not he actually was). And yet the big "scandal" in that campaign was that Bush and McCain had a handshake agreement not to campaign negatively against each other, an agreement that was broken with comparatively mild rebukes. The stuff Trump pulled in the race (and is continuing to pull) would have been in a whole different stratosphere.

The other essay is about conservative talk radio. The themes of hyper-partisanship and echo chambers is still very relevant today. Worth a read, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fake News, I'm 29 and they are still freaky as shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider the Lobster is similar in many ways, especially the writing style, but since it's non-fiction it's different as well. Infinite Jest was the first book of his that I read, and I think these essays would have been an easier introduction to his writing. But I loved Infinite Jest either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
