<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Diner Scene in **Mulholland Drive** is tense as hell. So eerie and weird. Very unusual kind of tension. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UozhOo0Dt4o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love most of their albums! Especially The Powers That B and Bottomless Pit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you're smart, doesn't mean you're empathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underrated achievement, this is actually amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% Achievements on Hotline Miami 2, beaten Super Hexagon and just now beaten this bad boy (Fairly hard rythm game): https://youtu.be/LhiBng4WbOk 


Edit: Oh and 100%ing "I Wanna Stop the MELTDOWN" which is a free hardcore platformer. God damn was I not ready for the bosses, the fourth one took me over 20 hours, never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 1 8 4 -  (Birth of a New Day) Very atmospheric, rainy, cyberpunky feel. One of the only Vaporwavey records I like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanikani is an online learning Spaced repetition system. It is paid though, nonetheless you can easily find the 50% off code. It teaches Kanji and Vocab through Mnemonics which are sometimes good and sometimes "meh". It also teaches radicals, kun, on, irregular pronunciations and has natives pronouncing the vocab. I like it so far though you really have to do it daily or the reviews stack up and also it is veeeeeery slow in the beginning and you can't adjust your learning speed. Maybe KLC is worth getting as a quick memory-refresher it isn't _that_ expensive after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there is the integral of e^(-(x^2)^) and the Fourier Series definition below it so it isn't all that trivial, the quadratic equation however is of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 13:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you recommend getting it, even though I use WaniKani already? Or should I only buy it if I want to know the stroke orders? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 06:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friends quote this masterpiece all the time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Northernlion Live Supershow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People make fun of Vaporwave but there is some good original stuff out there. 2 8 1 4 and Blank Banshee are my favourites too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Isaac
2. Spelunky
3. The Stanley Parable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Cytus, I love that it can be challenging as opposed to Deemo, which is a great game but there are too few songs and the difficult ones are too easy. Cytus is great though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 00:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Careful with this one, if you really want to know what this is about, watch Mathologers video on this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 12:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hotline Miami made me discover Carpenter Brut and Perturbator, I'm pretty into Synthwave now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the WaniKani trial and I'm sure it is worth the money but it's still a rather expensive subscribtion service. Are there cheaper versions that are also good, or should Anki be enough in that case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 20:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much, would you personally recommend starting off with the Core Anki decks already or is it not that necessary as of now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short question about how to proceed after getting started with Genki 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have decided to start to learn Japanese and I've now worked through the first three chapters of Genki 1. After reading a lot about Anki Core decks and the Kodansha Kanji Learner's Course, I don't know whether it makes sense to already start memorizing the Core vocab in Anki. I suppose that it will mostly be unrelated to the Genki vocab and I won't understand many example sentences anyway. Also, should I buy KLC already? Genki 1 + Workbook was pretty expensive for me and I don't know whether I really need it right now. Thanks for your answers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks, I'm going to look for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the Schinizer charts? The problem is that many of his sdxv II charts are desynced unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 01:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you also have the mega link for similarly organized sdvx I and II charts? Would be great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 09:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would probably work until you hit the 13s/14s. Which is when you wouldn't manage to hit both knobs that fast and to switch to buttons. Example: you need to use the left knob and press the 1st and 3rd or the 2nd and 4th button simultaneously, it would get tricky. My main advice would be, wait for more answers. I am semi-experienced in K-Shoot but I always played with a keyboard myself. I'm sure there are people who use a controller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 09:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll need to do a lot of finger gymnasitcs and keep your middle finger on the triggers at all times. I would also recommend putting something on L1/R1, like a shortcut for the 1st and 2nd/3rd and 4th note. If you run into problems you can use them to reallocate some other shortcuts that help you out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 09:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dann wr Caravan Palace auch was fr dich  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 09:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aphex Twin ist super, ich freu mich ja schon auf das kommende Album  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 00:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danke, Herr Skelett </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 23:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alles von Death Grips und Swans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 13:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that you can use AdBlock if you REALLY don't want to support them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> source: https://i.redd.it/q19c98vrc85x.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself CUCK. I have two degrees and a 142 IQ. Is also knock your fucking head off if you spoke to me like that. The only "dumb as dog shit" person here is you... You fucking CUCK. I'd suggest watching Trumps speech about Hillary from The other day. We both know you won't, and I'd be a large portion of my salary that you've never watched one of his speeches. You get all your news from what? CNN? MSNBC? Tyt? Huff post? Tumblr? You're a little shit, with a shit brain and zero clue what's going on. Get fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speak for yourself CUCK. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself CUCK. I have two degrees and a 142 IQ. Is also knock your fucking head off if you spoke to me like that. The only "dumb as dog shit" person here is you... You fucking CUCK. I'd suggest watching Trumps speech about Hillary from The other day. We both know you won't, and I'd be a large portion of my salary that you've never watched one of his speeches. You get all your news from what? CNN? MSNBC? Tyt? Huff post? Tumblr? You're a little shit, with a shit brain and zero clue what's going on. Get fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 07:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this really belongs here, although I'm a big fan of Richards work. This one sounds very similar to what he did on Syro, not sure how I feel about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 20:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also an acquired taste. The first time I tried Club Mate I really hated it, now I'm actually obsessed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 19:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or quantum physics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like Dennis' "Implication" from Always Sunny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 20:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making fun of the video mostly implies making fun of the advertisers and funders of such garbage and not of the kids, who aren't really the problem here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 00:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the reason I'm using that particular keyboard is that it's a mechanical gaming keyboard which doesn't ghost for at least 5-6 buttons. I've found a semi-solution by now, unplugging the mouse and playing with 45 fps, still a lot better than 30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 10:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 09:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now it's difficult. I watched it in a small theatre in Hamburg, it just came out. If you're not in Germany you'll probably have to wait :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just seen the film and I think it was pretty good, definetly requires some thought. It really subverts your expectations and challenges your perception of what is going on in each moment. Kind of light on the horror, would still recommend the experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Der Nachtmahr (2016) Recent German horror film, what do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very misleading.

Edit: I suggest watching this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jcKRGpMiVTw if you want to know what -1/12 really means in this context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that can be described by comparing it to Foodfight in any way is a not good idea.

Edit: Wording </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so tired of reading this, just because their party has "socialists" in their name doesn't mean they were far left. You can actually read up about their policies (using an unbiased source by actual historians) and judge for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another one was: "Mehr Geld fr die Oma statt fr Sinti und Roma" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er fokussiert sich hauptschlich auf indie games und ich hr ihm einfach gerne zu :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bei mir war es genau andersrum, bin jetzt auch oft bei Rockleesmile unterwegs. Hab durch Northernlions und Arumbas EU4 videos das Spiel lieben gelernt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 23:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unterbewertet, aber er und seine Crew sind echt coole Leute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 08:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right, damn. For now I gotta play with 30 fps because ghosting is just much worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game runs badly because of my USB-Keyboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always been playing on 30 fps, even though my machine is pretty good actually and now I've finally found the reason: The game runs horribly on my notebook when my USB-Keyboard is connected(110 fps difference), can't use inbuilt keyboard because of ghosting. Do you have any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 11:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reaper, Lucio and Roadhog. Super fun characters! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 23:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) there are sane parts of the community and b) that doesn't influence the value of the game either way in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, it was pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is actually very helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 17 too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a ranking of lvl 14/15 maps based on their difficulty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 14:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have beaten almost every lvl 13 map but Party Stream. I also managed to clear about a fifth of all 14 maps but I've noticed that the difficulty varies A LOT. Some 14 maps are pretty easy while others seem impossible to me. Now my question is, is there a ranking of higher lvl maps and if there isn't, which ones would you recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja so ziemlich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 16:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schau doch mal, wer den Kommentar verfasst hat... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 16:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meiner Aussagen? Lies nochmal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 15:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ist das deine beste Antwort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll also recommend "Things to Make and Do in the Fourth Dimension" by Matt Parker. Really entertaining and witty journey across all of mathematics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 09:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, it is fun but it really lacks diversity when the host chugs 14 times and I'm not complaining about trying to win when your world is invaded but it is just not fun fighting against 3 players with a sum of 30 estus at least. Even the fact that Invaders have some Estus just make all fights boring and slow because half of the time a player is running away to heal. Also it is impossible to punish properly. My hope is that From intoduces a PvP arena like in DS2's arena, which was pretty great after a few patches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 07:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only moment I was genuinely upset is when this guy invaded me, holding two torchers, wearing kirk's armor and that ring that makes you dodge everything with everlasting i-frames. I genuinely couldn't hit him. He just rolled around and wasted 15 minutes of my time, while
 throwing consumables and rolling around my feet. It was hell. Then he decided to jump off a cliff and free me from this prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hits too close to home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 07:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an awesome Spanish movie called "Timecrimes", you really should check it out, it's great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 19:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, however after starting up HM1 again, I've noticed how much more fluid the mechanics work in the sequel, even though gunplay is borderline unavoidable in HM2. There are definitely things that the original does better but for me, the gameplay improved on some of the rough edges of the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 11:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hotline Miami 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 11:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it is an unpopular opinion but I actually liked Hotline Miami 2 better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 16:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I love this tool. With just this and a little Photoshop I was able to make this: http://imgur.com/Ddpo64D

Really hyped for Dark Souls III </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keyboard players who can beat lvl 14-15 maps, what are your preferred controls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 00:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just asking out of curiosity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 10:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much, this is really useful, I've cleared almost all of the 13s except for Party Stream, which is insane to me and now it's getting really hard to progress because some of the 14s are ridiculously easy while some are also not even remotely possible for me at the time. There are also comparatively easy 15s like Brain Power so this list helps keeping track of it, thanks! One question: What does the different coloring on the tracks mean when you click on them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 01:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that! Thanks for correcting me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 01:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to print a Roleaux Tetrahedron! ...or 3! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really neat but isn't (0.5)=(-.5)! because (n+1)=n! ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 22:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate!

Edit: very dank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 22:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can enjoy some of the music and the aesthetic but for me personally the memes are also part of the genre. Some people take Vaporwave really seriously, some not at all and some lie somewhere in the middle. Also it can be hard to find good, or original Vaporwave because people who actually want to create that sort of music are just as accessible as low-effort or meme-producers. Though records like "Vaporwave is dead" are kind of ambiguous if they want to be taken seriously or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternativlos, Methodisch Inkorrekt, Hoaxilla, Psychotalk, Der Weisheit, Insert Moin, Wrint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 12:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have this problem. The first session it ran well but then I suddenly only have about 30 fps and my graphics driver doesn't recognise the game. I tried reassigning the .exe to the Nvidia Card instead of the on-board Intel Chip but it didn't work. Now I'm stuck at 30 fps :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 21:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/ifLgVPVjmgI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 07:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could just google it, for the third one, search for Trump wanting to kill the families of terrorists because it hits them harder. Just an example.

Edit: And also search for "Trump Waterboarding", might also get you results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The SJWs are going to hate this one xD" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 11:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A common notation for derivatives is f(x)' or y'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 19:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, there is a sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 08:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've already 100% the game and I can tell you: Hard Mode is way more difficult than getting an A+ or an S in Normal Mode, so congratz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 14:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed it, even though hard mode was borderline impossible on some levels. I think the controls in the sequel are also much more precise and satisfying after having played the original again recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found his work from the video game Hotline Miami 2 and it really blew me away, perfectly fits the hyperviolent but modernised 80s style of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 07:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schroedinger's Race </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 08:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 14:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god thank you so much! You may have saved my paper! Now that I know that it's just a single note and it might not even have vibrato! This really helps out a ton, also I probably don't even have to explain DFT in my paper anyway so that's going to make it a lot easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 23:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my second attempt at writing this up again as I accidentally deleted the first one before I could send it... First of all excuse mathematical inaccuracies or bad English. I'm from Germany and English is not my primary language.

So the term paper is supposed to be about synthesizers and the fourier transform. It doesn't have to be very detailed or math heavy (15-18 pages only). My task is now to analyze the frequency distribution of a recorder and to try to "mimic" the sound by using an additive VST-Synthesizer. Now I have this sample (I will post it below) which is a continuous chord with some vibrato, which will be easy to realize by using LFOs.

My main problems are that I a) have never used Scilab and it seems really inaccessible to me because I don't any of the commands and b), thata I don't really have an idea of how to interpret the frequency plot where dB is plotted against Hz. Especially when window functions are involved which they are. The only thing I understood about window functions is that only the peaks are important. I know what dB and Hz are but I don't understand how to read the proportions of the harmonics from the graph. I'm assuming I can't just linearly compare the dB values, right? Do I even have to find out the proportions in order to synthesize the signal or do I maybe just need the dB values anyway?

Next up, in order to make the process simpler, I have copied and pasted one oscillation from somewhere in the signal over and over again so I have a continuous tone which doesn't change over time. This would also mean that the intensity wouldn't change either, which is good. It *does* sound less like the sample but it would be distorted when synthesized anyway. I don't think it will have a significant negative impact.

My main concerns are now:

* How do I interpret the FFT plot, especially with respect to the window functions?
* What about the Fourier Transform do I need in order to explain what I'm doing?
* Is it advantageous to use the copied and pasted signal for the sake of simplicity?
* Could spectrograms be of any use?

Anyway thank you very much for dealing with this, I really appreciate it.


Here is the recorder sample I'm going to use for now:

https://www.dropbox.com/s/oj1y6nkoc7e7i3m/recorder.wav?dl=0

And here are some screenshots of the original signal, the copied and pasted one and the frequency plot of the latter:

http://imgur.com/a/R2nMI

I hope this clears it up a bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 11:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much for the detailed answer, i'll look into finding an optimised recorder sample but the one I have right now is indeed only a single chord all the way through. There is also a demo version of MatLab I could try to use. It is entirely possible that my given fundamental frequency is not correct because of the window function approximation I used but I also generated a sine wave with the same frequency but it did sound the same so it might be the actual one. Thanks anyway I'll look into it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help for my 11th grade term paper about Fourier Transforms and spectral analysis of an instrument. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 09:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly I know it is a difficult subject but I can already mostly understand Fourier Series or Harmonic Fourier Analysis, though I don't think I'll fully understand the Transform for non-periodic functions as it is too complicated. Now my task is to analyze a Recorder(instrument) sample with the help of Audacity f.ex.. So my question now is: Can I handle the Recorder signal like a periodic signal by only looking at one period of it and then assuming that it sounds that way all the way through? Or do I need to research about the Fourier Transform and FFT? Another one: If I use the spectral analysis feature audacity offers, I know it is performing an FFT and giving me the result through a window funcion of my choice. Is there a way to only get Fourier Coefficients for the fundamental frequency and its harmonics? (The recorder sample is at a constant 391 hz)
Thank you in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 15:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's incredible and supenseful. Honestly one of the best soundtracks of all time for me personally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 13:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Adam would really appreciate the British Tv-Show "Utopia" but sadly it is not very well known and it has been cancelled after two amazing seasons nobody watched. The art style and the directing, aswell as the story telling are absolutely amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 00:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean xboning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And funny and original "triggered xD" jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 00:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NATURE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
