<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7030</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was a Lee Harvey Oswald quote. Learn something new everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing the same shirt as zoo keepers...yeah not going to work on most animals. Animals at a zoo know their familiars or zookeepers by proximity, size, scent and location rather than color. Zookeepers are generally the only ones to enter the pens. They tend to also mainly be adults. Besides Giraffes, there aren't any large mammals that can distinguish colors very well. African apes and monkeys can see as well as humans. South American monkeys are near dichromatic (red color difficulty). Elephants, Hippos, Lions, Tigers, Wolves, (weak dichromats) most rodents are dichromatic and so are fish. Interestingly Rats are Blue, Green and Ultraviolet sensitive. Reptiles are all over the place with some snakes that can see both dichromatic colors and infrared. Frogs are weak dichromats. Birds have the most enhanced color vision at 5-7 colors of common Zoo animals.  Mantis shrimp is the crustacean exception with 16 color receptor cones. Most other crustaceans have Blue/Red cones. Cephalopods see blue only...crazy to think that an almost color blind animal can imitate all colors so well. This one blows my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK don't listen to people who say bring dinos AND rpgs...your just going to end up killing your own dinos. Here is how my tribe is doing all the way up to hard mode. We bring 18 rexes and 2 Theraz (we have a Therizin breeder so normally I would not recommend but his a god like now). Rex Stats: 40-80K Health (recommend 60K for almost guaranteed survival), 800 Mele Min., 1K recommended. Therizin are 60K Health 1300 mele. High Quality Saddles on all dinos. We use Master Craft Saddles on all Rex's seems to work just fine. Set all fight dinos to "Attack my Target" We bring 3-4 people, gear doesn't matter dress for the environment. Teleport into arena, "J" call the cluster fuck of dinos into a good position (in the bottom pit for Broodmother, Back of tele area for Ape (kite ape down with a rifle then move command dinos and players back away let tank rex's corner him), up the dumb ramp and into the open for Dragon). THEN get on your command dinos. Whistle game from here on it. Each person have pre-assigned Rex's to their dino group. So J calls, Passive, AMT whistles only affect their group. If you get the positioning right (AKA trap boss in a ball of rexes) it's a cake walk. We have only lost 2 rexes with this strat on Dragon due to a positioning F-up; Rex's getting stuck on rocks etc when coming back from air to ground phase. Manticore is another story altogether...14 or so high level Lightning Wyverns, Heavy armor gear, High quality armor piercing weapons for players. Wyverns FF the Manticore, players just play bodyguard for wyverns that pass out. Killing Death Worms and Elementals from the starting platform, and kiting them away from passed out wyverns. Bring lots of food, blood bags, soups and stimulant etc. As of right now you can avoid Manticore (get tek grams from other bosses) I would recommend that. Deadliest part of this strat is a Lightening wyverns coming into range of players. They will TK you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HaHAHA that is soooo amazing and high effort! Well done good sir. Do you have an MLG ID? I'd love to add you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Map/Mission Idea (a sort of wall motive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm sorry I didn't mention EVERY news site. CBS, NBC, FOX, MSNBC, Washington Post, they are all shit. That was my point. And yes the far right news outlets are decidedly worse on bias. But the far left news outlets have far more reach. Equally bad IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "According to my research, a donut is the size of a hockey puck." Please provide donut size reference to sporting equipment research proofs for peer review. I would love to see how this was outlined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Stole Bernie's Election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (((Swarm88))) -- keep an eye on him. Reddit needs digital arm bands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn right. I want my fucking lebensraum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo! Was looking for this. Perfect example of fake news. Insinuating that "in 30 days" means his first 30 days. Then turning the story around about how be breaks campaign promises.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What press? CNN? Who constantly lies through omission? Trump is an idiot, but he is almost right in regards to the press. It's a complete and utter farce from all sides. Right, left, middle. I honestly feel like I have to double check everything I hear these days. The biased is unbelievable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think one of the underlying issues is that app developers can change major privacy and even ad settings AFTER purchasing an app. I purchased an app a year ago (I was glad to help support the devs) and a few updates later there are now ads on the pause screen...for a paid app. And privacy changes. Google needs to address these issues. Hard lock privacy and ad settings for app purchases based on initial release.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good defense. We can learn something from nature here. Pretty sure if you walked up to a guy with a gun and started undressing, looked him right in the eyes and said "I'm now going to mate with you." The guy with the gun would probably GTFO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. My dad died at 54. He had Non Hodgkin's lymphoma, Castleman's Disease. 2 Bone marrow transplants, 5 other treatments. My entire childhood up until he died from 39 to 54 years old he was always getting some type of chemo. He refused the last time...15 years was enough for him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They called him monkey and taunted him with bananas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick hummingbirds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The WSJ should be happy he isn't suing their lying asses." hmm PewDiePie is probably better off financially than the WSJ...he probably should sue them just for shits and giggles. Would be hilarious if PewDiePie ended up owning them like the Hulk Hogan ownes Gawker now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ascendant pick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Organic Polymer...oh yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anklyo sucks. Get an ascendant pick. Sooo much faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bump, I'd like some details as well. We're doing our first runs under the new tiered system this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4: epoch date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Honor Open Beta vintage 1969. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even cannon in the Harry Potter universe. I did some digging and the wiki says "J. K. Rowling's Official Site (Mentioned only)" No other source of a mention. I did a insite search of her website and could not find it...so someone could have just made that up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ask logical questions of a game where you milk flying lizards? I could not find a single instance in D D and fantasy history where anyone ever milked a dragon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you all for this important research. Especially the hard working scientists and most likely interns whose job it was to jerk off monkeys.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw dawg that's what we call a hood grill. Toss some stakes on the manhole cover, let the kids spit roast some hotdogs. Hmm mmm good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pro abortion...but 1st trimester ONLY. If you can't decide in 14 weeks that you don't want to keep a rape baby...I think there are more issues at stake. The child is a victim in this case as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah damn memory leak and that weird thing in the corner all stretched out is a tribe mate....GTX980 I turned the settings way down due to the latest patch giving me issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All refugees welcome on our server! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I went to the website and did the little challenge. 

I found a few hidden elements. One is the quote "BETWEEN SUBTLE SHADING AND THE ABSENCE OF LIGHT LIES THE NUANCE OF IQLUSION" which is a reference to the solution of Kryptos Stage 1 (that art/statue at CIA HQ). 

Stage one was a Vigenre cipher...so that may be a hint to something. It may just have been obvious and point out the hidden banana on the page...and the banana phone song. Not sure. 

Third was the hidden FSociety mask behind the server panel.  

http://imgur.com/gallery/S7dRW. 

As others have figured that out the "XITXITXITXITXITXITXIT" if the Kryptos is any clue, it may actually be " IT IT IT IT IT IT IT" as the artist that made it used the letter "X" in the decoded cipher of Stage 2 for "esthetic reasons" which also was a Vigenre cipher. Big stretch here...

Besides that, the background of the image has their logo in the center (G or TG for The Gathering) which is surrounded by what appears to a decoder wheel. Bottom right hand corner has a box I can't make anything else out besides a few random letters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The markings in the center is the logo of gathering.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sick Whale "euthanized" due to ingesting plastic trash. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red army time to flex, sportin hulk hogan style pecks, ready to bring wreaks

of a bygone era reborn for the modern world, let our children live it too,fist ready to hurl

down destruction at a nuclear pace, rearm this nuclear race

like a sprint to the river styx, no coin in hand for the man turning da tricks

it's like we all forget, Charon's in charge, the baron von swear in

the new president, relations on the rocks, soldiers in camo cleaning out glocks

seems like war these days is the only answer, there's no cure in sight for this political cancer

cut it out like a tumor again and again, we resort to baser instincts of lesser men

we allow to leads us, to a flaming wall mislead us

if destruction of our world is the goal why wait? open the flood gate, 

we need no Arks for this ride of apocalypse, the sands of time run low in drips

maybe our time is done, no hope in the setting sun, for in a war that cannot be won

listen to Joshua, 

The only winning move is not to play. If you want to live past this d-day

so lets stop making all these arms, putting out children in harms

way to the future, stich this dark suture of destruction, life hostage holding abduction

Set the pace China build new peace for the human race

don't give in to the hate, walk the path of Siddhartha be great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Tests Missile With 10 Warheads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I remember the days so clearly**

When Martin and Malcolm walked

The streets flooded dark in color from city block to block

Unified voices shouting the same message

Speaking truth that rings so clear like bullet presage

Like Sisko back in Twenty Twenty-four 

I feel like I have awaken in past tense horror

Looking for hope on the horizon of the future scope

Graspin at memories past looking for hope

Hope of freedom, equality, digging my mind to understand this political causality

Everything we fought, bleed and placed chains on to bind us

Lady liberty stood tall to blind us

Emancipation proclamations words ring so hollow

truth and reality getting harder swallow, Looking for a moon shot of hope ride the wings of Apollo

Into the future that Sisko lived, all men equal no color of skin

Where the Merritt and actions of man are the fireing pin, and you'll know when

The cartridge in the gun of revolution triggered by the pen

will write the words in the social consciousness

where the word equality won't be played like chess

Where truth trumps ignorance, no more moron hinderance,

In the way for Trek like world where all wings can unfurl and all men are best

this I pray for, cast prejudice aside for, hug my brothers of all colors for the glimpse of the hope killing Klingon's with no scopes
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Two steppin boots of Mother Russia**

make ya blush a like the cold winds of winter,  knife in yo back like a spliter

fuck Eddard Stark doesn't know what's commin artillery strike make the Ukraine ears hummin

unprovoked war for a naval base let face it, you can go back and trace it

strategic location for the soviet fleet, nukes on preheat, looking for a place to make Blyat!

Ukraine government on downfall, time to move in on the throne like after Thrall

Adidas tracksuits on check, poopin squats in the snow with my comrades on fleck

We called separatists, better drop that shit in parenthesis

we not Russian army regulars, Putin's not flipping this bill like a creditor

Bum rush the artillery like a predator, AK locked and loaded ready like a whity redditor

Stale mate the EU writtin nasty letters to Putin, you know them bitches aint gonna put a boot in

Ukraine gonna have to step up, give mother Russia a quick check up

Soviet era is gone, we aint no pushover, we'll stand in defense of our lands till its all over

Lower your arms Putin, we aint gonna stop shootin

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deaths Mount Daily as Renewed Fighting Hits Eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I remember the days so clearly**

When Martin and Malcolm walked

The streets flooded dark in color from city block to block

Unified voices shouting the same message

Speaking truth that rings so clear like bullet presage

Like Sisko back in Twenty Twenty-four 

I feel like I have awaken in past tense horror

Looking for hope on the horizon of the future scope

Graspin at memories past looking for hope

Hope of freedom, equality, digging my mind to understand this political causality

Everything we fought, bleed and placed chains on to bind us

Lady liberty stood tall to blind us

Emancipation proclamations words ring so hollow

truth and reality getting harder swallow, Looking for a moon shot of hope ride the wings of Apollo

Into the future that Sisko lived, all men equal no color of skin

Where the Merritt and actions of man are the fireing pin, and you'll know when

The cartridge in the gun of revolution triggered by the pen

will write the words in the social consciousness

where the word equality won't be played like chess

Where truth trumps ignorance, no more moron hinderance,

In the way for Trek like world where all wings can unfurl and all men are best

this I pray for, cast prejudice aside for, hug my brothers of all colors for the glimpse of the hope killing Klingon's with no scopes

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco sues Trump over executive order targeting sanctuary cities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the official response from No 10, Prime Minister May had the following to rap:

Drop me a sick beat MC Captain Peacock

Yeah yeah

Oh dear jolly old chap are you free?

For Im da P to the R to the I to the M to the E

The main ill-ist the for-realist Tay Tay May

Not looking to drop bombs on yo ass today

I got a steel tube full seamen ready to lay shots

Curzin down the Keys at 55 knots, hollaren at Joe Biden Testing out some trident

When a couple of guidance systems who were up to no good

Started making trouble in your neighborhood

Dat Trident veered off course dick hangin left like a draft horse

Headed for Miami ready to impact the ground like whammy

No hot tip on this heat seeker rocket, we blew that mother focker up before it had a chance to cock it.

So chill yo mange, this aint no revenge for that time yall set our tea out to quench

But let dis be a reminder, should yall ever shit step our Queen well put your ass in a grinder

I got Red coats on reserve, unencumbered and unnerved begging to ask the question

Are you being served?

Tay Tay May out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain's May faces pressure after reports of Trident test malfunction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the official response from No 10, Prime Minister May had the following to rap:

Drop me a sick beat MC Captain Peacock

Yeah yeah

Oh dear jolly old chap are you free?

For Im da P to the R to the I to the M to the E

The main ill-ist the for-realist Tay Tay May

Not looking to drop bombs on yo ass today

I got a steel tube full seamen ready to lay shots

Curzin down the Keys at 55 knots, hollaren at Joe Biden Testing out some trident

When a couple of guidance systems who were up to no good

Started making trouble in your neighborhood

Dat Trident veered off course dick hangin left like a draft horse

Headed for Miami ready to impact the ground like whammy

No hot tip on this heat seeker rocket, we blew that mother focker up before it had a chance to cock it.

So chill yo mange, this aint no revenge for that time yall set our tea out to quench

But let dis be a reminder, should yall ever shit step our Queen well put your ass in a grinder

I got Red coats on reserve, unencumbered and unnerved begging to ask the question

Are you being served?

Tay Tay May out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god been there. This was in 2005 or so I had a shitty Alienware. I was converting all my mother's VHS family videos to DVD for christmas when the fan failed...while compiling video. The shitty laptop ran so hot I ended up sitting outside in December in the freezing cold to finish the project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This will probably make you mad, but this was a Gen 1 mutation. Crazy luck!](http://i.imgur.com/DQnaE4x.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raptor Neon Green Mutation!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was half expecting it to be the singer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
