<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9815</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is at an awkward time. It'll pick up later probably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article makes me wonder why he didn't just do a 1 year deal and then cash out the next year. I guess that would be a gamble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> had to check my carpet to make sure it wasn't the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hit 29. I'm behind. I put 100 as my goal but I'm thinking about changing my goal to page count. Favorite so far has been Team of Rivals by Doris Goodwin. (Non-fiction) Favorite fiction was maybe Lincoln in the Bardo? I haven't done enough fiction reading this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Kluber because I had the same thought as you but I think Kluber's command has been iffy this year. So I like our chances a little better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Probable Pitchers](http://houston.astros.mlb.com/news/probable_pitchers/index.jsp?c_id=hou) has Kluber on Thursday though. Did the Indians switch up too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of just froze. I'll try that next time. I just don't want to be attacked by a wild turkey to be honest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also any advice for dealing with wild Turkeys? Two runs straight where they've intersected my path. One just ran away from me, the other ruffled up his feathers and started coming towards me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was an alley that had a chain across the front but space on the sides that  I ran by yesterday. I assumed it was fine to run down and did, but I'd like to be able to know my shit if anyone ever harangues me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a breakdown on where I can and can't run? Private roads seem to be fine. But what about roads for emergency vehicles only? What about along side rivers that go through people's backyards/properties?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody added Brad Peacock in my fantasy league!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yuli's hair was on point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Maria Semple's "Today Will Be Different" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my fiction buffer. I've read *Where'd You Go Bernadette?* as well, so I was familiar with Semple's style. 

*Today Will Be Different* is a one day sampling of the life of a former cartoon animator as she struggles to deal with her missing husband, her Seattle suburban/white bread life, and her strained relationship with her sister. 

On the level of language, even the choice of the slightly disturbing-sounding steakfish creates a sense of uneasiness and absurdity.

From [NY Times Review](https://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/09/books/review/maria-semple-today-will-be-different.html)

I felt the beginning was too quirky and too manic. Which I know was the point, but reading Semple is like a rom-com about a manic pixie dream girl but from the MPDG's perspective. It's refreshing while at the same time there are moments of absurdity where I had to stop myself and really think it was over the top or not. (I mean she hires an adjunct professor to be her existential guide nee poet.) 

The book was exactly what I needed though after slogging through some heavy non fiction. It's light, funny, and has the occasional deep moment of bitter self loathing. The self loathing and pity of course always wrapped up in some caustic humor. 

Did anyone find the book too unbearably quirky to continue? There were so many details I could see it as extraneous and off-putting. 

The ending too was both neat and dangling. One relationship arc gets resolved (which in hindsight I like because marriages should be more about compromise and continued work rather than drama and blow up) and another just gets a one line put off. 

What did others think of the book?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was reading Seattle native Maria Semples new book. When she was describing some scenario involving her husband she included, "It's October so the Mariners are playing playoff baseball." It totally took me out of the story and made it unbelievable to me. Only then in the next paragraph she pointed out her made up scenario and concluded "the Mariners would never be in the playoffs."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished Worst. President. Ever. And I think DJT will challenge him for worst. I'm curious if we'll get a Lincoln, FDR, and a little bit LBJ to pull us out of the shit though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has absolutely not happened just this one time. Arguably this was why Buchanan won in 1856. Republicans were a relatively new party and split the vote with Know-Nothings. It seems like a lot of those early 1800s presidency's got thrown to the house to make the decision as well. Quincy Adams over Jackson was another one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My internet sleuthing says Quiz Bowl Nationals were in IL? I did Science Bowl in HS, should've made the transition to Quiz Bowl in college. It looks fun. Did you guys win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only been to the Barclays Brooklyn Shake Shack. The Downtown Brooklyn one always looks super busy. Madison Sq is tops in my book since I dormed near there, but it's also nice waiting in a park for your food. (when it's not cold.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clap back is pretty great but I don't know if that's just because I despise Jeff Sessions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's absolutely pushing for a run and is even courting progressive Dems with current legislation. There is a lot of talk of him living in his father's legacy, and struggling to overcome it. Mario absolutely should have run for President but didn't, Andrew probably shouldn't but will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Trump Avoid A Government Shutdown On His 100th Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any specific examples? I actually really liked their Le Pen article from today, and it makes more sense. I give credit to Nate for mostly focusing on the statistical aspect of things. I'm not pro-Trump though so I can see how that can be frustrating because they're definitely more on the negative side, but I think just journalistically there is a lot to cover negatively about Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bearded bookends. 

Neat collection!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing you didn't respond with anything weird to his question! "These two? Uh yeah... of course they're my kids. No self respecting kidnapper would take two kids to a hockey game. Right?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even our *bad* players are having a good year so far. Sipp and Peacock have been better than expected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aren't their seasons significantly shorter though? I feel like ties would become a scenario nightmare after 162 games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, Im not necessarily advocating for MLB to bring back tied games. But I am saying it would be in line with history.

Just in case anyone didn't want to read the whole thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pea coats are all the rage here in NYC. I've gone my 9 years here without buying one though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Great. 
* Greater. Took the dog and kid for a hike. They both loved it. (Probably). It was beautiful NY weather. 
* Probably a book or something. Though I just bought a foam roller and it has changed how I think about leg pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see baseball in Midtown Manhattan. It would be such a mess transit wise, but such a great in ballpark experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also contains this terribly written sentence 
His fly ball rate is actually a little higher than last year, he's not just hitting the ball with any authority, with an average exit velocity just below the MLB average.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something is up with [Brad Peacock](http://www.fangraphs.com/statss.aspx?playerid=5401 position=P) SSS obvi, but through 9.2 IP he has 13.9 K/9 and is stranding all runners. Questioned him getting a spot after ST over Hoyt, but he's definitely earned it so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Flashback] Night of the Goose Eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angels and Mariners just can't quit each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interested if your take on Chambers holds up. I loved her first book, but have had zero interest in the sequel because of the change of characters. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished **Worst. President. Ever. by Robert Strauss** I was seeking out a Buchanan biography, which this isn't really, and it's short. I'm glad I read it, and maybe even a little glad I didn't have a Lincoln-esque biography to slog through. 

**The Path to Power by Robert Caro** LBJ gets shit done. Possibly super corrupt? Find out in the next 20 hours. I'm finally half way through. 

Year of long books.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a decent amount of "Private Roads" in my current town. (Not to mention those stupid historical markers for every little thing on the East Coast, "George Washington once popped a squat in this location. Wow!") I still run down them but I aggressively look over my shoulder and I'm pretty sure I sweat more heavily because I'm paranoid someone is going to call the cops on me or question my intent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Luhnow likes his pitchers' but id like to see another position player on the roster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After like 4 or 5 games too? Surprised he wasn't razzing you about having faith in Altuve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve and Correa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MadBum doing mad aerials on his bike. Injured and now out 6-8 weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHY ARE THE ASTROS IN THE AL WEST? NOBODY WANTS TO START WATCHING BASEBALL AND THEN FALL ASLEEP MID WAY THROUGH BECAUSE THEY LIVE ON THE EAST COAST AND IT'S LATE AND A WEEKDAY.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's why I think their [BP hat](http://riverbandits.milbstore.com/store_contents.cfm?store_id=28 dept_id=158 product_id=91670) is the best. Raccoon Bandito + Menacingly Wielding a bat? Check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO HRS FOR CARTER? YOU GUYS BROKE CHRIS CARTER!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you suggesting that a ridiculously hot April by Marisnick portends a playoff appearance? If so, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if dabbing was his idea also, but it looks like that's gone this year and I'm glad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but you get to play the Blue Jays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is Astros, Red Sox, and the Tigers for the AL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any opinion on the new Quad City [logo](http://riverbandits.milbstore.com/store_contents.cfm?store_id=28 dept_id=-1 product_id=92248) 

It looks like a baseball wearing underwear to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SSS Alert]

He is hitting .313 with a .450 on-base percentage in 20 plate appearances this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jake Marisnick finding success at the plate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Isnt A Do-Nothing President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you know the Rangers *fixed* him. It was all Dave Hudgens fault. The Astros were too young. Gomez was going to revert to the near MVP levels he put up twice in Milwaukee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The SI Yankees have a [Cannoli](http://siyanks.milbstore.com/store_contents.cfm?store_id=94 dept_id=-1 product_id=82566) variant but I can only find the cap and not info about it on their site.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason Castro upset about a strikeout? Color me surprised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it 1-16 versus McCullers and hitting like .220 at MMP? Definitely not MVP numbers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not sure I can leave work until this game ends. It's going to be a close one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ay caramba! Futurama en espaol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collin McHugh in common too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dallas Keuchel Garden Gnome was the biggie I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait a second, radio guys are saying Strom's wife is Mrs. America (1979)! Someone on this sub was saying it was false the other day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude went from a stadium where there are Taco Trucks right outside to Whataburger Field, I think he's doing a food tour to cultivate mass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so is Altuve no longer doping since all that power is gone? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah sure I agree with that. After the first week he was the Astros fWar leader as well (SSS obvi). I'm just saying if one person goes down to bring up another IF, it's gotta be Marwin. Or Marisnick, but I'm not sure you send down an OF for Reed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Singleton get further demoted to CC? Plus he's no longer on the 40-man, would be a waste to put him on for probable non production.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve also always hits better on the road than he does at MMP, so I guess it shouldn't be that surprising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it hasn't happened yet, but Marwin has options right? Otherwise I'd say probably just drop a bullpen arm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta figure it's just stretching Yuli out. He's never played 162 games in a season and he's a little on the older side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angels having some OF problems this series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aggressive use of Beltran there. Also surprised Yuli is getting the day off because Marwin has been pretty bad lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any perks to the 230 over the 620? I have the 620 now and would like to upgrade to something I can more wear all the time, but the 230 seems like it's a bit of a downgrade in terms of data capture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one team with a winning record in the ALW and that's because the Astros have only played teams in the ALW. the one out of division series they lost to the Royals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get including Clemens, but including Morgan and Caminiti seems a little weird since they didn't spend any of their peak with the Astros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retired Miners Lament Trump's Silence on Imperiled Health Plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the NuVision 8" Tablet for iPad like situations. It runs full windows, is approx 8 inches, and comes in under $100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astros are continuing their Wednesday dominance from last year. 3-0 on Wednesdays. No other day is undefeated except Sunday (but they got rained out for the last one)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Singleton? Actually busted and suspended for marijuana use. Was playing for the Fresno Tacos. Got super fat from eating munchies lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't notice too much story overlap I guess. I enjoyed it, but it did become a bit of a slog towards the end. Stick with it for sure if you need to know what happened specifically with Mutt and Jeff. Charlotte is a great character throughout the story and gets more fleshed out as the story goes on. I thought it was worth finishing, but I can see why others might set it aside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she feels like she was brainwashed to a certain extent by her family and surroundings, and doesn't necessarily see herself being able to vote for a member of the GOP. There's talks of her home town being redistricted and creating more Town Councilman, I jokingly said she should run. (She had an MPH and would like to work in government healthcare) But most of the women candidate backing programs are specifically looking for Pro-Choice Democrats. So I think that'll be her next big challenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic Altuve TOOTBLAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Trout their only good OF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altubae gotta bring him in now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woot Reddick triple. Goood stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't need to add up. It's just saying X ump was on Y percent of the ballots but not the remaining Z.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's giving Chaffetz a lot of credit that I'm not sure he's earned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CB Bucknor Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not unexpected given the climate

isn't that reading into it? How does the climate effect this one election but somehow won't others?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still a loss for now. But ignoring the trend is being unable to see the forest for the trees. Clinton outperformed Obama. Ossoff outperformed Clinton. There's obviously a Trump effect that's going to impact other less safe Republican seats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this election supports your second half of the argument. Republicans aren't de facto Trump supporters, especially if his poll numbers stay low or plummet further. The pro-Trump Republican finished a distant third in this runoff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These 'Hot Dogs' Are Breakfast Sandwiches In Disguise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [538](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/5-takeaways-from-the-georgia-6-special-election-results/) sums it up really nicely. I think the biggest takeaway is the nationwide pro-Democrat environment. Ossoff wasn't necessarily supposed to win, that would have been the icing on the cake, he was supposed to outperform, which he did. 

From here it's going to be about controlling the narrative, don't let it become subverted to Democrat loss after loss and instead talk about gains versus traditionally deep Republican seats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These 'Hot Dogs' Are Breakfast Sandwiches In Disguise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hinch played with the rotation after the rained out game. I guess he slid people up one. Or just is skipping Fiers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Keuchel Is Going Full Ziegler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually its by a judge order given extenuating circumstances. And no. They wouldn't reduce hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A PR probably would've scored there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been watching so much as listening, but he looks a little thinner? He's channeling his inner Devo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bud Norris sighting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super dumb question, I have a relatively long torso and shorter legs. Any benefits to this? Or ways I can take advantage of that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you recommend a particular book of his to move to next? This was my first by him because I'm a sucker for books about New York and dystopias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reluctant Trump Voters Swung The Election. Heres How They Think Hes Doing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Demands a Ride in the Queen of Englands Golden Carriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Demands a Ride in the Queen of Englands Golden Carriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cubs Bullpen Will Be Fine, Probably </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Psycho. 

Just for the cultural significance. And I'd suggest that anyone not into gore just feel free to skim to get the gist. I think I even skipped a couple of the music review chapters after I got the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hola Ispeople, soy dad!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I especially liked the part where there was a dog on the cover for no reason.

I mean how could you pass that up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planned Trump Order Will Discourage Hiring of Low-Wage Foreign Workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything You Need To Know About The Georgia 6 Special Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Stanley Robinson's - 2140 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked this up because the concept of a submerged NYC fascinated me, and as a NYC resident I felt an even deeper need to read it. 

I appreciate that Robinson is able to do what John Dos Passos accomplished with his Manhattan Trilogy, making NYC into a fully developed character in the story. In some ways 2140 is a love letter to the city, digging up old history, famous residents, changing neighborhoods, community resilience, all while discussing rising tides and water levels. 

The book is basically about climate change and the way it will redesign or coastlines, and possibly our living habits, but towards the end (and with a tease in the beginning) Robinson injects political intrigue around financial speculation and bailouts. 

The book felt a little long, a little thin in places, but overall it was a great read. What did others think? Was anyone put off by the conclusion and the political leaning? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Springer has been pretty bad the last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve just needs a little more speed on those underhanded tosses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's why I was wondering. It was a point of optimism for his otherwise bad catching  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's Gattis doing throwing out runners? My eye test says bad this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do my run home basically over the same route. But I have 3 I mix up. A 3,4, and 5 miler. Then on weekends I try to always do different long runs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in my fourth year running. My only concern is im having trouble explaining it and it seems more subjective. It just feels like knots or stiffness. But yeah im trying to find a doctor that works with my work sched. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been having a weird pain in legs. I assumed it was from being cramped during my commute. It's more a tightness than pain. Feels a little like plantar fasciitis. It spread to my calve a little more intensively this week, but I relieved it with some self massage and stretching. Can anyone recommend a good low cost all body foam roller? I think that might go away towards helping me out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was at my kids bday party all day. When I checked it was 5-2 and we were getting no hit. I think ill have to watch this one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vaguely remember Marwin hitting a 2 R homerun. But its Marwin so that sounds wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made r/all though. Power to the aquarium  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I didn't say that I was a little shocked to see Castro is doing really well for the Twins so far. Has like .5 fWar already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
