<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're awesome. THANKS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shocker. Developer pitching "SnapChat, only for businessmen!", backed by Billy Bush and GOP Establishment types, boasting "military-grade encryption" but offering no further details AND being Closed Source turns out to be Silicon Snake Oil.

Oh, and illegal if used by government officials on official business, even if it did works as advertised.

Fie on Encrypted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Encrypted App Used By White House Staffers Suffered From Serious Security Flaws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Encrypted App Used By White House Staffers Suffered From Serious Security Flaws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We prefer not to use PDFs. Can you find a source that uses HTML? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A question concerning implications arising from code names.

If this cache is called Vault 7, does that mean there are Vaults 16? 810? 15?

Since Vault 7 is millions of lines of code   tens of thousands of pages of text, does that imply there are multiples more of these sorts of operations and attacks?

Or, do agencies retire failed off-shoots, keeping the survivor one, so there aren't active programs 16? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to check out the [mobile section of PrivacyTools.io](https://www.privacytools.io/#mobile_os). There are actually 3 others they recommend, but CopperheadOS gets a mention below that, with a link to their site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is worth repeating, so I'll keep it here, but locked. Thanks SO much, /u/ourari! 

We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're awesome. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, feel free to Reply then add to the list. Also, if any of these articles has a good quote or raises an issue, paste it into a *new* comment (not this one) so we all can enjoy and discuss it.

**Groups**

[Electronic Frontier Foundation  *Hey CIA, You Held On To Security Flaw InformationBut Now It's Out. That's Not How It Should Work*](https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2017/03/hey-cia-you-held-security-flaw-information-now-its-out-thats-not-how-it-should)

[Privacy International  *Reaction to Vault 7 Leaks*](https://medium.com/@privacyint/press-statement-privacy-international-reaction-to-vault-7-leaks-3cb6e6c4b295#.dv29v956p)

[Open Whisper Systems Tweetstorm](https://twitter.com/whispersystems/status/839204754718932992)

*The CIA/Wikileaks story today is about getting malware onto phones, none of the exploits are in Signal or break Signal Protocol encryption The story isn't about Signal or WhatsApp, but to the extent that it is, we see it as confirmation that what we're doing is working Ubiquitous e2e encryption is pushing intelligence agencies from undetectable mass surveillance to expensive, high-risk, targeted attacks.* 

The same can be said of other OTR   secure computing systems.

**Media  Day One**

[The Guardian  WikiLeaks publishes 'biggest ever leak of secret CIA documents';
The 8,761 documents published by WikiLeaks focus mainly on techniques for hacking and surveillance](https://www.theguardian.com/media/2017/mar/07/wikileaks-publishes-biggest-ever-leak-of-secret-cia-documents-hacking-surveillance)

[The Guardian  To security establishment, WikiLeaks' CIA dump is part of US-Russia battle; WikiLeaks says documents about CIAs computer hacking tools came from US, but many perceive group as pro-Russia following role in 2016 election](https://www.theguardian.com/media/2017/mar/07/wikileaks-cia-documents-us-russia-conflict)

[The Guardian  Smartphones, PCs and TVs: the everyday devices targeted by the CIA; Documents published by WikiLeaks reveal extent of intelligence agencys capability for targeting the public](https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/07/cia-targeting-devices-smartphones-pc-tv-wikileaks)

[The Intercept  The CIA Didn't Break Signal or WhatsApp  Or Bypass Encryption  Despite What You've Heard](https://theintercept.com/2017/03/07/the-cia-didnt-break-signal-or-whatsapp-despite-what-youve-heard/)

[The Intercept  CIA has an "impressive list" of ways to hack into your SmartPhone, WikiLeaks files indicate](https://theintercept.com/2017/03/07/cia-has-an-impressive-list-of-ways-to-hack-into-your-smartphone-wikileaks-files-indicate/)

[The Intercept  WikiLeaks Dump Shows CIA Could Turn Smart TVs Into Listening Devices](https://theintercept.com/2017/03/07/wikileaks-dump-shows-cia-could-turn-smart-tvs-into-listening-devices/)

[Wired  WikiLeaks Just Dumped a Mega-Trove of CIA Hacking Secrets](https://www.wired.com/2017/03/wikileaks-cia-hacks-dump/)

[Ars Technica  WikiLeaks publishes docs from what it says is trove of CIA hacking tools; Docs claim CIA can defeat WhatsApp, Signal, Telegram encryption, among other apps.](https://arstechnica.com/security/2017/03/wikileaks-publishes-what-it-says-is-trove-of-cia-hacking-tools/)

[Motherboard  The CIA Spied on People Through Their Smart TVs, Leaked Documents Reveal](https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/the-cia-spied-on-people-through-their-smart-tvs-leaked-documents-reveal)

[Motherboard  The CIA Allegedly 'Borrows' Code From Public Malware Samples](https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/the-cia-allegedly-borrows-code-from-public-malware-samples)

[Motherboard  The CIAs Stash of the Dankest Emoticons](https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/the-cias-stash-of-the-dankest-emoticons)

[Slashdot  WikiLeaks Reveals CIA's Secret Hacking Tools and Spy Operations](https://yro.slashdot.org/story/17/03/07/1440252/wikileaks-reveals-cias-secret-hacking-tools-and-spy-operations)

[TechDirt  CIA Leak Shows Mobile Phones Vulnerable, Not Encryption](https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20170307/10360836862/cia-leak-shows-mobile-phones-vulnerable-not-encryption.shtml)

[Reason  4 Takeaways from the Wikileaks 'Vault 7' CIA Leak; From using smart TVs for spying to hoarding IT vulnerabilities](http://reason.com/blog/2017/03/07/4-takeaways-from-the-wikileaks-vault-7-c)

**Media  Day Two**

[The Guardian  Apple to 'rapidly address' any security holes as companies respond to CIA leak; Company says it already fixed many exploits described in Vault 7 documents released by WikiLeaks, as CIA and Trump administration refuse to comment](https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/08/wikileaks-cia-leak-apple-vault-7-documents)

[The Guardian  'Am I at risk of being hacked?' What you need to know about the 'Vault 7' documents; Should you be worried about agency snooping? Is this WikiLeaks release just the tip of the iceberg? And is someone at the CIA watching too much Doctor Who?](https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/08/wikileaks-vault-7-cia-documents-hacked-what-you-need-to-know)

[Cult of Mac  Famous jailbreaker says WikiLeaks CIA dump is overhyped](http://www.cultofmac.com/470951/famous-jailbreaker-says-wikileaks-cia-dump-overhyped/)

[RT.com {yeah, I know, but its claims are sourced by a @Wikileaks Tweet}  WikiLeaks says just 1% of #Vault7 covert documents released so far](https://www.rt.com/news/379856-wikileaks--cia-hacking-vault7/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? *Thanks!*

Would you mind reposting your *excellent* post over there, as a comment? That way, everyone can participate and it won't get lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this isn't technically a Vault 7 post, would you mind reposting this in our megathread there? Thanks!

And readers, please don't comment on V7 here, but over there instead (otherwise we'll have to lock it)

We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? *Thanks!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? *Thanks!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? *Thanks!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? *Thanks!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're trying to make a MegaThread out of the Vault 7 Wikileaks story. Would you mind reposting your question (and comments, other subscribers) [over here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5y0kcf/vault_7_cia_hacking_tools_revealed/)? *Thanks!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind posting on our Vault 7 Mega-Thread? We're trying to funnel them all into one, since this will be a tsunami. THANKS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Ericthor was kind enough to post important clarifications. Pending their reposting (so they can earn all that sweet, *sweet* karma), I'm borrowing it so we can sticky it so it's at the top of page.

If your phone is compromised doesn't matter which app you use. **The issue isn't with apps, but 0-days on iOS and Android.**

I'm out of my depth on this, but looking at the [article here](https://wikileaks.org/ciav7p1/) they link to this page of [iOS exploits going up to 9.2.](https://wikileaks.org/ciav7p1/cms/page_13205587.html) I'm guessing it be fair to assume that this doc is a little out of date and they have exploits for the most recent iOS and Android OS now.

Then /u/AnonymousAurele was kind enough to follow up with:

Good link. A few others [here](https://wikileaks.org/ciav7p1/cms/page_13205587.html), [here](https://wikileaks.org/ciav7p1/cms/page_10453042.html), [here](https://wikileaks.org/ciav7p1/cms/page_33685523.html), and [here](https://wikileaks.org/ciav7p1/cms/page_33685523.html).

Note these are all links to Wikileaks.org.

Also note the Vault 7 leak includes hacks for consumer devices (Smart TVs, IoT devices) so it's not *just* mobile phones (at least Android and older iPhones), but many "smart" devices.

If readers want to follow up with other interesting, cited documents (with context), that'd be appreciated.

**Good Coverage So Far:**

Saint Bruce hit the ground running with, [Schneier On Security Blog  WikiLeaks Releases CIA Hacking Tools](https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/wikileaks_relea.html)

Probably the most brilliant Tweet on the topic, by @Snowden: [In 2014, the government sought to create the world's most dangerous key, claiming it would never be leaked](https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/839203485941923840) Followed by FBI Director Comey's WaPo Editorial, *Compromise needed on smartphone encryption: Apple's and Google's approach to encryption is too extreme*. The Snark. IT BURNS!!

See below for more. Also feel free to add your favorite news articles. You may have to uncollapse replies to this Sticky Post. :)

**Wednesday Edit:** Note  Day Two News Stories Have Been Added to the Replies On This Post. Click to expand comments to enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be a top-level comment so I can sticky it, and /u/AnonymousAurele's. Can you do this? I'll wait 30m but if you're away, do you mind if I do this myself (or AA, you can), with a credit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some comparisons to the Snowden Leaks being made here, so I'll get this out:

Obligatory to emphasize, Snowden didn't release **any** docs to public. Rather, he gave them to reputable journalists since he knew he lacked expertise to properly vet.

Unlike a certain raging narcisict with a specific, partisan agenda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might also trying to contact Signal, or if they have a Sub here, them. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend towards your view on a very ugly situation. 

The Czars? Jerks terrorizing their people and those standing in the way of their creating an empire like their cousins.

Politburo? Same, though arguably less energetic than a US delivering the Washington Consensus with the twin barrels of the IMF, World Bank, the CIA and the Seventh Fleet. With, I stress, some significant benefits, even if most went to whichever leader the Dulles brothers felt were better stewards of the Seven Sisters or United Fruit Company's progress.

But less Imperialistic. Horrible to be behind the Iron Curtain, but as you point out, Vietnam had worse times under French   American colonial rule than when the USSR was a factor. Less of a regional threat than China.

I'm not a citizen of a state bordering Russia and, while sympathetic to Ukrainians, Russia is less a global Imperialist threat to the world. Horrible regional threat. Personally, a rat bastard who's stolen $40 *Billion* from his perch running Russia. That makes Donald, Ivanka and Jered look like rank amateurs. Get your act together, America!

So, yeah. Complicated, as you say. But for a lot of the world, better than Imperial Japan, Nazi Germany or perhaps the world order dreamed by the Dulles brothers. IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to point out Russia's contributions to world peace.

The current regime is, for sure, problematic. As were their former ones.

But let's give the ~~Russians~~ Soviets, including the Russians (thanks, /u/MemeMeUpFamilia!) credit for the huge sacrifices they endured to free the world from tyranny and Fascism. If you watch too much American film or TV, you'd have the false impression it was almost all the US. It *was* the US (and allies). But quite a bit of it  and certainly the sacrifice side of it  was Russia.

Repulsively ironic that those working with "Uncle Joe" under US Gov't auspices and urging were then later targeted by McCarthy and other Red-Baiting Conservative pols in the United States. Were it not for them, we'd all have quite a bit more goose in our step. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefox  Tor Browser  Tor team reviews 2016 successes, outlines greater integration w/ Firefox team leading to more privacy-improving enhancements (Tor Blog) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefox  Tor Browser  Tor team reviews 2016 successes, outlines greater integration w/ Firefox team leading to more privacy-improving enhancements (Tor Blog) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling safer online with Firefox  their engineering manager explains the latest privacy   security improvements in Firefox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling safer online with Firefox  their engineering manager explains the latest privacy   security improvements in Firefox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Incomplete is veering dangerously close to a Does Not Pass. Please marshall whatever meager forces you possess to overcome your deficits and answer the question in the allotted time remaining.

Again, no double-space, you're responsible for your work and *Chicago Style* isn't a fashion choice, it's the law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd add to your thoughtful post, even if Nazi-Punching is #5 on one's Daily List Of Things To Do, don't do it when the other side is *obviously* trying to provoke you into a specific time, place and set-up when to punch them.

Common sense, people. :) We're supposed to be the smarter half of the divide, remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, it sends fake cloned messages, then? Because if it didn't pass them along, wouldn't it make the phones (etc) not work?

I'm not trying to be argumentative or a troll. I'm trying to wrap my head around how it works conceptually so perhaps we can figure out counter-measures while being more competent for ARP Spoofing threats. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Ibid*, [above](https://www.reddit.com/r/berkeley/comments/5xkflt/elderly_protrump_supporter_peppersprayed_at_march/dek02wx/)

Note: the word is not an invitation to participate in an auction. It's Latin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's not how it works. Recall "Free speech doesn't allow you to shout "fire" in a crowded theater? Yeah, that. Same principle.

 Bonus points  who wrote it, where and why? I'm sure a reasonable precocious middle-schooler would be able to answer this, without any problem  or even an Internet!

Then, please explain how this context, with the quote, relates to your four-word, nonsense post. But because you're posting in a UC-related Sub, you will get an Incomplete rather than a Fail.

It's suggested your response fills at least two Blue Book pages (no double-space: we're not Stanford, heathens). As always, spelling and punctuation is your responsibility, so respond accordingly. You have five minutes after reading this before you must close your Blue Book.

Welcome to /r/Berkeley! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are a couple more:

[Earlier woman with #BlackLivesMatter button bleeding after a Trump supporter attacked her with a Trump flag](https://twitter.com/tigerbeat/status/838178923095584768)

[Trump supporters with mace, helmets, head   body armor, **two** knives and what looks like a "flag pole" that's actually a club](https://twitter.com/ChrisGEdwards/status/838158322846978048) And that's just two of them.

[Trump woman that maced us](https://twitter.com/ChrisGEdwards/status/838192949942878209)

[Nazi with knife arrested](https://twitter.com/ChrisGEdwards/status/838193824643993601)

Yeah. "We're just visiting Berkeley to advocate for Free Speech."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems that just "mixed-race" would be enough to send his ticker over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any way to create a bot that sees if anyone who posts on T_D who then posts here? That'd be fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he's one of those who caravanned from Orange County. ~~Daily Cal (their liveblog, or perhaps their political reporter's Twitter feed, I can't recall: sorry!)~~ Berkeleyside had an article where they found out that was apparently A Thing. Granted a Tweet has a name and mentions San Francisco, but he doesn't have an SF vibe about him. At all. 

*Edit: misrecollected, sorry. It was [Berkeleyside's coverage of this](http://www.berkeleyside.com/2017/03/04/live-tensions-run-high-among-pro-trump-anti-trump-protesters-berkeley/). Although Daily Cal's main political reporter had an excellent Tweetstream on this, and I've already posted Daily Cal's article [here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/berkeley/comments/5xlryo/hundreds_gather_for_protrump_rally_that_results/).*

It's not as though journalists in that environment can take a DNA swab or [verify via a Voight-Kampff machine](http://www.allthetests.com/quiz30/quiz/1386100782/Voight-Kampff-test-questions). They have to take at face value whatever someone says about where they're from.

Folks still use Voight-Kampff machines, right? Especially on queries about one's mother? Because, let me tell you about my mother  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'd be shamelessly remiss if we didn't note our top sticky post, by /r/thatoneprivacyguy, [*That One Privacy Guy's Guide to Choosing the Best VPN (for you)*](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacytoolsIO/comments/4ihtdj/that_one_privacy_guys_guide_to_choosing_the_best/).

But Torrent Freak's article is comprehensive and they're reputable.
 
Let us know of issues and we'll review this post, but since TF is aces by me, my default is, "Sure, why not". 

**Please do not mention/hype any VSPs not on either two lists.** They'll be removed since /r/VPN exists for that purpose. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some ways, folks' desire to transcend censorship (even well-meaning, appropriate and parental kinds) is self-policing. That's why I used "teens". 

I think if you raise kids right, explaining *why* you're putting limits, and what for, building up their empathy muscles, by the time they're independent enough to want to explore on their own, they'll also be mature enough to handle the material.

At the same time, we don't want to make the Internet safe for second or third graders, since that would mean curtailing expression and exploration that adults need and deserve.

Another option is see if the YouTube app allows parental controls, and if so, go that route (in addition to /u/SillyBlack's excellent suggestions). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, but specifically, which techniques would they use? If not among those I listed then others? Generally. Or, am I imagining the basic processes wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technical question. Since this MITM device has to respond faster than the WiFi modem its trying to clone, how does it do that? Does its hardware have faster response time? Does it use optimized routines so its software implementation polls faster than the real modem? Is its signal louder? Something else? If none of the above, does it just hope that a 50% success rate meets its goals? 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ironic that once teens are old enough and independent, they can visit the page, then the Wikipedia entry, then see the multiple ways to defeat ARP Spoofing listed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better, it took three tries. Trump had to delete the prior two because the first one had a misspelling a second-grader would have caught. The second misspells it *again* but in a new way. Then finally the survivor. Which asks, Why shouldn't he set the entire Federal criminal justice system against (two!) current political opponents who question him, based on a false-equivalent, public photo taken a decade ago.

 #NotFascist #NoReallyNotOneBit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you use a drawing based on a face photo, it confuses the face recognition schemes mightily. But it still meets the needs of your class.

I posted on for one of my other social presences then did a reverse picture search. The closest matches it found were similar sketches, who turned out to be some really amazing entertainers and athletes. So according to algo-matches, I've won many Oscars, have sold out many concert arenas and have many Olympic gold medals.

I can live with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Field Guide on How To Snoop-Proof Any Phone or Tablet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be remiss if I didn't point out that /u/PrivacyIntl, who has partnered with EFF on this, is hosting an IAMA *this very moment* [on this topic](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/). Feel free to join in and ask them questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filthy casual.

*True* connoisseurs of dessert horror know it's *custard* that is the **true** menace! Or should I say, The Meringue Menace!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sure. Totally cool question. I just wanted to add a note for general readers. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more a tech support issue, honestly. You might want to try one of the Windows or WinTel Subs (which I'm unfamiliar with so I'm unsure which, sorry) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note it's not advised that anyone to get too specific on their OpSec. Some generalities are okay, but if you're concerned about spies, why make their job easier for them in your public activity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I was *nice* to him when he was a jack-ass before, thinking, "Maybe he'll learn" Perma-ban, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazed and pleased at the new editors of Teen Vogue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Free".

Pay up from a reputable VPN or figure PII leakage is part of the business model. Or malware infested ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's a good thing all our infrastructure is tended to and secure.

Hey, I've got an idea. Let's piss away $40 billion of US taxpayer cash on a wall separating us from Canada No, wait, I like maple syrup. How about Mexico? I *hate* Err, Ford?

Sure. Indulge my inner seven-year-old. I HATE FORD!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eww. *Eww!*


Good call. Just from your description, I want to take a shower.

FWIW, Snowden seems to like SpiderOak. and /r/PrivacyToolsIO has suggestions, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The post is fine, it's just the title needs to have something like "14 years in prison for doing journalism?! - Sign the petition (UK citizens)"

The idea being, Open Rights Group doesn't want 1,000 sign-ups if they're American. We shouldn't create extra, wasted work for them. But they seem to be an okay non-profit, so we approve of it. If anything, we want to protect them further.

So, you can go ahead and repost with the clarification, is what I'm saying. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you repost this with a title that emphasizes this is a UK group? I'd hate for the NGO to be swarmed with petition signers from the US. It's extra work for them with no payoff.

If you delete it yourself, then repost, then Reddit won't flag it as a dup. So it's better than if I remove it (which I will after a couple hours sorry!)

Thanks!

Trai_Dep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm removing this since VPNs are such a complicated topic and this service isn't one of the ones that /u/thatoneprivacyguy has reviewed. Perhaps try /r/VPN? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For our newer readers, here are some resources to become more acquainted with digital security and privacy:

* Besides subscribing to /r/Privacy (!) we have [a FAQ here, ](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/wiki/index).

* /r/PrivacyToolsIO also has [a Wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacytoolsIO/wiki/index). And, visit www.privacytools.io!

Outside of Reddit, there's the [EFF Surveillance Self-Defense page](https://ssd.eff.org/en). [The Intercept](https://theintercept.com), in addition to publishing great investigative journalism, also has wonderful privacy guides and covers digital rights generally. Search for Micah Lee's articles, especially.

*Ars Technica*   *Motherboard* also cover tech   digital security   privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes folks 2nd or 3rd level responses are for you guys. So when you return, can you check those out, too?

Like, I had one [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/dedss6f/), which I'm okay if you feel it's been answered, but other readers might be expecting a response for their queries that aren't first-level questions.

Besides that, you folks are doing GREAT! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've confirmed they'll be back.

It's actually better here since PI will monitor this post, but not the cross-posts. I keep a loose eye on those, but here is the best place to ask them Qs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very general question. But we've all been there. :)

You might want to check out [The  Wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacytoolsIO/wiki/index) that /r/PrivacyToolsIO has. And, of course, visit www.privacytools.io!

You can visit /r/Privacy (there's [a FAQ there, as well](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/wiki/index)).

Outside of Reddit, there's the [EFF Surveillance Self-Defence page](https://ssd.eff.org/en) and [The Intercept](https://theintercept.com), in addition to publishing great investigative journalism, also writes great privacy guides and covers digital rights generally. Search for Micah Lee's articles, especially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the fact that someone of his stature *and running hotels himself* could imagine ordering "off menu" in Moscow wouldn't have any complications.

Kind of, sort of, exactly like stumbling around through multiple high security zones per day with a consumer Android phone, and allowing his top aides to do the same, won't either.

His recklessness is going to get someone killed.

Oops, too late. Already has! x20! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to try /r/VPN. They're more up to date on this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I won't distinguish this, or make this a warning.

But I will ask, for now, that you use a different tone here. We're not like some other Subs where "edginess" is seen as virtuous. The opposite. It'll get you banned.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While waiting for the sun to rise over Greenwich, folks might enjoy [this Motherboard article](https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/smart-meter-data-is-intimate-and-deserves-privacy-activists-argue).

Joseph Cox wrote, *Smart Meter Data Is 'Intimate' and Deserves Privacy, Activists Argue.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating veal? Why, that's *reprehensible!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Bill Would Force NYPD to Disclose Its Surveillance Tech Playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Bill Would Force NYPD to Disclose Its Surveillance Tech Playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks **so** much, /r/Crypto Mods. We really appreciate your allowing us to cross-post here! 

3! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org) is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/).

Like /r/Crypto, /r/Privacy transcends political boundaries. This non-profit is UK-based with deep roots in the Continent. As such, if you've ever wondered how crypto development and deployment, IP   digital rights are implemented or any privacy-related issues are handled in a global setting, please ask them. PI has committed to having their staff available during this rolling 3+ day IAMA, so if they can't answer your question immediately, they'll reach out to someone who can!

We are Privacy International  we fight for the right to privacy globally in courts and on the street. Our work includes: reverse engineering smart car parts to understand what data is being collected by car companies, taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking of thousands of innocent people's devices. With our partners in the PI Network we research privacy globally, sending FOI requests to various police agencies in the US   UK to find out if they use predictive policing or social media surveillance. And more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter 

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are Privacy International  Ask Us Anything! [ r/privacy crosspost] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wasn't Snooper's Charter crushed?

Such a simple question; apologies for what I'm sure is a very complicated answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it better to have codified protections like the Constitution/Bill of Rights or the EU Charter, or what seems to be a very vague and ill-defined set of limits on government power like the United Kingdom seems to have?

Granted, abuses exist for those that live under both systems, but it seems very strange for citizens to not demand a set of codified rights and restrictions. 

I mean, it's been *800 years* since the Magna Carta. Why havent havent the good British people said, Cor. Right then. Time enough to make a second go at things.

Related: If Hard Brexit, then will UK citizens be stripped of the EU Charter protections? Is your organization and the British public concerned at this prospect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The United Kingdom group [Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org) is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/).

We try *really* hard to make /r/Privacy a global Sub focusing on working towards global solutions since our threats are global. We are very happy to host Privacy International as part of this effort. We would *very* much appreciate those from outside the US to join in!

We are Privacy International  we fight for the right to privacy globally in courts and on the street. Our work includes: reverse engineering smart car parts to understand what data is being collected by car companies, taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking of thousands of innocent people's devices. With our partners in the PI Network we research privacy globally, sending FOI requests to various police agencies in the US   UK to find out if they use predictive policing or social media surveillance. And more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter 

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are UKs Privacy International - Ask Us Anything! [ r/privacy crosspost] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very general question. You might want to check out [The PTIO Wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacytoolsIO/wiki/index) ,

as well as visit /r/Privacy (there's [a FAQ there, as well](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/wiki/index)).

And, of course, visit www.privacytools.io! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IoT seems to be implemented Poorly.

There are no controls, little regulation and no incentives to provide secure devices, let alone privacy-respecting ones. Parallels with smart metering exist: lofty goals, poor execution that increases our risk.

IoT botnets taking down many sites through DDOS attacks gets all of the press, but lax security rules seems to ensure that users' privacy will be the next casualty.

1) Are Smart Meters as likely to be vulnerable as IoT, or does part of their mandate include that they be secure? How do we know they're secure? Are they even required to, say, use TLS/HTTPS, let alone more sophisticated protections? 3rd-party audits?

2) Governments don't seem to be taking advantage of these IoT/Smart Meter information leaks. Do you think that it is likely that governments might start using these vulnerabilities?

3) In the US, police served a warrant on Amazon to access their always-on, always-listening Alexa device. Amazon is currently fighting them in US courts on Constitutional grounds. In the UK, and in the EU, how would this play out (both regards warrants, legal defenses and through protections like the EU Charter or with more nebulous UK ones)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The British NGO, [Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org), from Great Britain, is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/). 

Did you know that they're English? And British? And of the Commonwealth? (Yes, I'm a sodding Yank and some of the finer geographic distinctions confuse me, so I'll aim to hit all the Cricket  rarely Quidditch, *never* baseball  bases)

We try *really* hard to make /r/Privacy a global Sub focusing on working towards global solutions since our threats are global. We are very happy to host Privacy International as part of this effort. We would *very* much appreciate those from outside the US to join in!

We are Privacy International  we fight for the right to privacy globally in courts and on the street. Our work includes: reverse engineering smart car parts to understand what data is being collected by car companies, taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking of thousands of innocent people's devices. With our partners in the PI Network we research privacy globally, sending FOI requests to various police agencies in the US   UK to find out if they use predictive policing or social media surveillance. And more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter 

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are the British group, Privacy International  Ask Us Anything! ( r/privacy crosspost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAmA  Privacy International is doing a rolling, 3-day AMA  Ask Us Anything over at /r/Privacy! [Crosspost] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org) is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/).

Our work includes: taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking, and intelligence sharing, investigating a number of 'smart' technologies including cities, cars, and home automation, and looking at how these technologies impact privacy, working with partners globally to map trends in surveillance, filing FOI requests on police and intelligence agencies, and more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are **so** awesome!

I was about to ask if we could post something here, but since you've already done one (a-w-e-s-o-m-e!), here's an intro to their IAMA.

[Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org) is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/).

We are Privacy International  we fight for the right to privacy globally in courts and on the street. Our work includes: reverse engineering smart car parts to understand what data is being collected by car companies, taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking of thousands of innocent people's devices. With our partners in the PI Network we research privacy globally, sending FOI requests to various police agencies in the US   UK to find out if they use predictive policing or social media surveillance. And more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter 

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org) is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/).

We are Privacy International  we fight for the right to privacy globally in courts and on the street. Our work includes: reverse engineering smart car parts to understand what data is being collected by car companies, taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking of thousands of innocent people's devices. With our partners in the PI Network we research privacy globally, sending FOI requests to various police agencies in the US   UK to find out if they use predictive policing or social media surveillance. And more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter 

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are Privacy International - Ask Us Anything!  r/privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Privacy International](https://www.privacyinternational.org) is having a rolling, 3Day IAMA over at /r/Privacy, and [the link is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5wpnqx/we_are_privacy_international_ask_us_anything/).

We are Privacy International  we fight for the right to privacy globally in courts and on the street. Our work includes: reverse engineering smart car parts to understand what data is being collected by car companies, taking governments to court to fight mass surveillance, government hacking of thousands of innocent people's devices. With our partners in the PI Network we research privacy globally, sending FOI requests to various police agencies in the US   UK to find out if they use predictive policing or social media surveillance. And more: AI, machine learning, international landscape of privacy, Snoopers' Charter 

We recently joined forces with the EFF in the USA to question the legality of requiring people to install smart meters. Smart meters can ping usage data back to electricity companies in frequent intervals such as every 15 minutes, which can reveal a lot about a person or family. We think current global legal frameworks are insufficient to properly keep peoples data secure, and we are working to test and strengthen laws and policies.

Ask us anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are Privacy International  Ask Us Anything!  r/privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We Mods are kind of hoping our UK   European (or really, everyone outside the US) will take advantage of this British group being here to ask questions. We try really hard to make our fight global so any questions concerning non-US issues are especially encouraged!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tibetan women's soccer players denied US visas for Texas tournament. US embassy officials in Delhi told 15 players they dont have strong reasons to go to Dallas, raising questions about Trumps policy toward the contested region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, I checked out my HD (also checking w/ the Finder's Find function), and there were several, but the four were all tiny. Like, 100 kilobytes tiny.

I wonder if Mac housekeeping is better, or if I'm just among those that have small log file leftovers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A repost of one here several months past, but the discussion is interesting, and an example of sometimes how good notions don't meet the demands its creators intended.

And, thanks to those behind Canary Watch, as EFF closes their article with:

Finally we would like to give a huge thank you to our coalition partners on this project for the last year: The Calyx Institute, Freedom of the Press Foundation, The Berkman Center, and the NYU School of Law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canary Watch  One Year Later (Why EFF   partners are degrading Canary Watch Program after experiments success and failures) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canary Watch  One Year Later (Why EFF   partners are degrading Canary Watch Program after experiments success and failures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note when Republicans claim every American will have access to affordable health care, they mean it in the same way they have access to winning the lottery. Every week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The resistance v Trump: here are this week's victories and losses; the resistance fought back, and had some satisfying wins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blatant Rule #4 violation. Removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook is The Devil.

If you do t know why, scope out /r/Privacy for a bit ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me ping our Mods again. I agree, we should decide one way or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhat related, Micah Lee's excellent [How To Run A Rogue Gov't Twitter Account](https://theintercept.com/2017/02/20/how-to-run-a-rogue-government-twitter-account-with-an-anonymous-email-address-and-a-burner-phone/) that also covers how to covertly buy a burner phone.

What threat profile are you trying to address? Phones are very leaky so things that might work against some foes won't work against others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The story of the week is Trump, Russia and the FBI. The rest is a distraction. The White House reportedly tried to influence an active counter-intelligence investigation. All else, press ban included, is designed to deflect attention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, it's an example of well-meaning people letting through a bug existing for years, until it's found. Until there are security audits (which are expensive and have a limited shelf life), FLOSS isn't a iron-clad guarantee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize it's an easy claim to make, but we need to differentiate between companies that strive towards privacy but are (for a time) compromised by the three-letter agencies and those that see themselves as partners from the start.

Also, the only claim for this is that NSA slide, with no details. And note that Apple is a *very* late entrant to their timeline, versus all the telecom companies, and Microsoft, are pioneers in helping the government in their mass surveillance efforts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What You Need to Do About the Massive Cloudflare Data Leak. Millions of websites may have been affected by Cloudbleed. Heres what you should do to keep your accounts safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Thursday, Google's Project Zero disclosed a serious security issue, now known as Cloudbleed, with popular internet infrastructure service Cloudflare. In short, Cloudflare-protected websites and servicesincluding Uber, dating site OkCupid, and Fitbithave inadvertently been leaking sensitive user data, potentially including passwords and private messages.

This isn't the fault of the sites themselves, but the way Cloudflare parsed HTML pages. The leaked data was then archived by search engines, as web pages and data are. Google and Cloudflare have worked to remove much of the exposed data, but some examples may remain.

So what do you actually need to do in light of this?

Why, click thru to read the article, of course! 

It's Joseph Cox, who's good. So it'll be a pleasure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What You Need to Do About the Massive Cloudflare Data Leak. Millions of websites may have been affected by Cloudbleed. Heres what you should do to keep your accounts safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What You Need to Do About the Massive Cloudflare Data Leak. Millions of websites may have been affected by Cloudbleed. Heres what you should do to keep your accounts safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not smog. It's Axe spray.

And wafting cocaine dust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gas station signs were 3,000 feet tall? Why, were they that high so dinosaurs could read them?

It's not gasoline, it's *dinosaurs* lizard-people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your computer has binary blobs (hint: if it's new than a decade, it does) then it is theoretically suspect. Non-free ROMs? Same thing. And simply because something is FLOSS doesn't mean it's safe (witness Heartbleed).

Let alone, it's what you do with your computer that counts more than if you're running MacOS vs a 'Nux. Signing on to your Facebook account? On a browser w/o any privacy plug-ins? Visiting other sites and using the FB plug-in to share it? Your privacy is hosed.

That said, you can dual boot. Probably /r/Apple could help with the particulars. 

Keep in mind that, unlike Windows, MacOS is Linux based, proper with permissions. And it's not built around monetizing your every online move, as any Google offering or Windows 10 is. [Apple does care about your privacy,](https://www.apple.com/privacy/) and more importantly, their business model ensures that you and their interests are aligned. They've also shown (during the Apple vs FBI fiasco that came out in their favor) that they'll go to the mat to protect their users' privacy.

Unlike Microsoft and Windows (let alone Facebook), where *at best*, you might with a LOT of work, fight the strong anti-privacy currents that these other companies' businesses are founded upon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, honestly, I think I misread your comment. You weren't saying what you felt was a reasonable excuse, you were giving what a Palantir employee might be telling his friends   family (and themselves) to justify their existence. 

Sort of like those IBM employees simply helping '30s Germany with a simple punchcard sorting problem to get their ethnicity background project running ship-shape. "Nothing to see here, I'm simply a process engineer!"

(Yeah, I went there, but I also have Muslim and Dream Kids for friends: they're freaking out)

Apologies. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 10:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siloing is keeping your separate social identities separate. Bonus points if you have different emails for them, too.

If you lose one, then only that one is affected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of them as being good for advice in this case. Agree 100% that taking a homeless cat to a new neighborhood with no other plans is not good. Or sheltering one when better alternatives exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy cow, so many double negative questions designed to force the preferred response.

And, The Daily Show counts as TV News, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police may be given power to arrest anyone involved in a peaceful demonstration that is merely suspected of turning violent.

You now have a situation where you have full-time, *almost professional* agent-provocateurs that attempt to create public disorder.

By "almost professional", they mean, "not professional, not full-time, not paid. AKA, Registered voters in their districts voicing disapproval at town hall meetings given by these same GOP politicians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AZ Republicans vote to give police powers to arrest people planning peaceful protests. Backing Republican concern-trolls, I have been heartsick with whats been going on in our country, what young people are being encouraged to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

And for you (and everyone!) feel free to contribute to this or any conversation. I've PMed the Mods letting them know of this thread so over the next few hours/days, we should get some good discussion going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the interests of transparency fellow Mods, we may as well have the discussion here.

I'm favorably disposed. /u/bvbn8c4fg raises good arguments and counter-arguments. The security review goes far. And Wire, through /u/cityroler, making themselves available for our questions and concerns is welcome and moves the proposal far in my book.

For our technical Mods, what do you think? Issues/Concerns? Let's figure it out here. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge: No, feds cant nab all Apple devices and try everyones fingerprints. Such Fourth Amendment intrusions are [not] justified based on the facts articulated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge: No, feds cant nab all Apple devices and try everyones fingerprints. Such Fourth Amendment intrusions are [not] justified based on the facts articulated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge: No, feds cant nab all Apple devices and try everyones fingerprints. Such Fourth Amendment intrusions are [not] justified based on the facts articulated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for Joseph Cox. After an excellent article proving how vulnerable Android phones (and some jailbroken iPhones) are (if someone has physical access to your phone), he wrote up this follow-up, answering, Now What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Protect Yourself from Creepy, Phone Snooping Spyware. Off-the-shelf spyware is often marketed towards jealous lovers to spy on their spouse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll make this the official "SHA-1 Is Busted Wide Open" post. :D

Here's Dan Goodin's take on it, via Ars Technica. [At deaths door for years, widely used SHA1 function is now dead. Algorithm underpinning Internet security falls to first-known collision attack.](https://arstechnica.com/security/2017/02/at-deaths-door-for-years-widely-used-sha1-function-is-now-dead/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burn in Hell, spyware vendors:

An NPR investigation in 2014 found that 75 percent of 70 surveyed domestic violence shelters encountered victims whose abusers had eavesdropped on conversations using hidden apps. 

And,

Consumer spyware is not marketed to governments. Instead, many of the companies explicitly gear products toward jealous loversespecially menwho want to monitor their spouses.

"Many spouses cheat. They all use cell phones. Their cell phone will tell you what they won't," reads the website of FlexiSpy, another company selling spyware.

Cindy Southworth, executive vice president of the National Network to End Domestic Violence, pointed to several examples, including one from a website called HelloSpy.

"It showed a woman thrown off a bed as part of their advertising for their spouse-tracking," Southworth told Motherboard in a phone call. Another image on the HelloSpy website, online at the time of writing, includes a woman, with her face cut and bruised.

"It's repulsive, it's misogynistic, it's gross," Southworth added  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth noting the article notes that these require physical access to the victim's Android phone while the owner is absent. And, while physical access to a *jailbroken* iPhone is possible, none of these commercial spyware packages work on a regular, updated one. This suggests that, for newer iPhones properly configured (i.e., using the defaults), you're talking one of those million-dollar hacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The artwork and marketing used to sell these hacks is repulsive. One literally has a picture showing a man grabbing his battered spouse by the arm  I mean, her face is *hamburger*  with blaring ad copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth noting the article notes that, while physical access to a *jailbroken* iPhone is possible, none of these commercial spyware packages work on a regular, updated one. This suggests that, for newer iPhones properly configured (i.e., using the defaults), you're talking one of those million-dollar hacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [East Bay SPCA](http://eastbayspca.org) is the *cough* cat's meow for all good furry things. Check 'em out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Tracked Myself With $170 Android Smartphone Spyware that Anyone Can Buy. For a relatively small fee, you can snoop on someones messages, call logs, photos, and location from across the planet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Tracked Myself With $170 Android Smartphone Spyware that Anyone Can Buy. For a relatively small fee, you can snoop on someones messages, call logs, photos, and location from across the planet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quietly amused that there are more than eight leaked, secret documents, a 10pp+ expose of a billion-dollar program of questionable utility that is hazardous to everyone's privacy and an excerpt of a Podcast by a Pulitzer-prize winning journalist, and you're focusing on to what extent you can fit this into a partisan lens that neither *The Intercept* nor I here have engaged in. 

Think bigger. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, this just gets better and better:

In the demo, Palantir identified Wikipedia users who belonged to a fictional radical religious sect and graph their social relationships The unmentioned and obvious subtext of the experiment was the fact that such techniques could be applied to de-anonymize and track members of any political or ideological group. 

Won't *someone* rid us the the scourge of out-of-control and *evil* Wikipedia editors?! How about if we throw $1.2 Billion taxpayer dollars at it. Now, will someone?

Among a litany of other conclusions, Palantir determined the group was prone to violence because its Manifestos intellectual influences include Pancho Villa, Che Guevara, Leon Trotsky, [and] Cuban revolutionary Jose Mart, a list of military commanders and revolutionaries with a history of violent actions.

Yeah, that, or they finally nabbed that nefarious cabal of college juniors working on their mid-term paper for Latin American Studies.

*One point two BILLION dollars* for this crap. No accountability. No 3rd party review. No audit. And sure the Hell, no cancelling the contract or clawing back our wasted money.

What a Libertarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think that *The Intercept* has been pro-Obama, or even pro-Clinton, you've **clearly** read very few of their articles, if any.

Check 'em out.

There's no need to bring your (R) or (D) knife to all our privacy gun fight, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **blush** |blSH|

*verb [ no obj. ]*

Develop a pink tinge in the face from embarrassment or shame: she **blushed** at the unexpected compliment | [ with complement ] : Wednesday felt herself **blushing** scarlet when her aunt said, "You look like warmed-over death!"

 feel embarrassed or ashamed: [ with infinitive ] : Milo **blushed** to think of how he'd paraded himself as edgy when, after all, he was simply a nattering attention whore.

 (often as adj. blushing) (of a flower or other thing) be or become pink or pale red: the trees are loaded with **blushing** blossoms conspiring to devour your little dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of off topic from the article, don't you think? A distraction, even?

We should try to avoid that. This isn't /r/writingcraft or /r/wordsmithing or even /r/MFAEnglishLit. We're about *privacy* :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANKS SO MUCH, u/eleitl!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palantir has never masked its ambitions, in particular the desire to sell its services to the U.S. government  the CIA itself was an early investor in the startup through In-Q-Tel, the agencys venture capital branch. But Palantir refuses to discuss or even name its government clientele, despite landing at least $1.2 billion in federal contracts since 2009, according to an August 2016 report in Politico. The company was last valued at $20 billion and is expected to pursue an IPO in the near future. In a 2012 interview with TechCrunch, while boasting of ties to the intelligence community, Karp said nondisclosure contracts prevent him from speaking about Palantirs government work.

I have the suspicion that Thiel and his team decided, 

"We'd **love** to get billions of those sweet, no-bid, Black Budget tax dollars. No accountability and dense idiots who still have AOL email accounts in charge of signing those checks."

"So how can we spin enough technobabble and hire enough lobbyists to make it happen?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Intercept* staff has collectively won multiple journalistic awards, including Pens, Pulitzers, Oscars and more. If you can't read their articles, try reading slower? It's good stuff  you just need to give it the attention it deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad guys like those millions of people participating in the Woman's March on Jan 21? Black Lives Matter? The Muslim Ban? Anyone part of any government database (and many private ones)? Anyone posting on a political topic using social media?

Because all of these - and more - have been surveilled by local and Federal authorities. Palantir ties together **all** of these then sends them to whoever in whichever government is willing to sign a check.

If that doesn't alarm you  assuming you're not trolling  then you need to reflect a bit more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted entire thread just because of this one brilliant response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soda companies, supermarkets report 30-50% sales drop from soda tax. (Philadelphias passed Soda Tax augers well for Oaklands passed tax) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Peter Thiels Palantir Helped the NSA Spy on the Whole World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Thiel reminds me of what our world would be like if Mr. Potter from *It's A Wonderful Life* won, and was in the tech sector. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Peter Thiels Palantir Helped the NSA Spy on the Whole World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope quickly, before the corpse becomes too squishy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose it's to be expected, when the (im)mortal remains of grandson of a god is lolling about, excited to *finally* be able to use the express Handicapped lines at EuroDisneyWorld.

Well, as excited as a corpse can get, at any rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Jong-nam's body targeted in morgue break-in, say police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related article has a video, [Last Stand at Standing Rock as Police Prepare to Evict Pipeline Opponents](https://theintercept.com/2017/02/21/video-last-stand-at-standing-rock-as-police-prepare-to-evict-pipeline-opponents/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half the equation for "I need to protect my identity" is, "[Now that I have done so,](https://theintercept.com/2016/11/12/surveillance-self-defense-against-the-trump-administration/) how do I share important information?"

This article, featuring BitTorrent, Tor hidden services, OnionShare and more, help answer this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half the equation for "I need to protect my identity" is, "[Now that I have done so,](https://theintercept.com/2016/11/12/surveillance-self-defense-against-the-trump-administration/) how do I share important information?"

This article, featuring BitTorrent, Tor hidden services, OnionShare and more, help answer this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Scientists Can Protect Their Data From the Trump Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Scientists  Or Anyone  Can Protect Their Data From the Trump Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Run a Rogue Government Twitter Account With an Anonymous Email Address and a Burner Phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An update: [Milo was forced to jump off his Breitbart perch before he was pushed](https://www.reddit.com/r/progressive/comments/5vegsm/milo_yiannopoulos_resigns_from_breitbart_news/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo Yiannopoulos enablers deserve contempt  and must be confronted. The poster boy of the alt-right has lost his book deal after speaking in defence of suggested sexual relationships between older men and younger boys, but his lucrative bigotry was left unchecked for far too long. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note that there are [multiple reports of Breitbart workers threatening to quit if Milo wasn't fired](http://www.dailykos.com/story/2017/2/20/1636022/-Breitbart-employees-are-threatening-to-resign-if-Milo-Yiannopoulos-isn-t-fired), making it more likely Milo jumped before he was pushed.

See also Owen Jones' *Guardian* article, [Milo Yiannopouloss enablers deserve contempt  and must be confronted
](https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/feb/21/milo-yiannopoulos-enablers-contempt-alt-right-bigotry) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo Yiannopoulos Resigns From Breitbart News Following Cancelled Book Deal and CPAC Speaker Ban. Thats 3 for 3 in only two short days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to illustrate how messed up that line of "argument" is, I hit puberty around sixteen. Which means, I looked around 12. Yeah, with my mouth, high school was FUN! 

Which means if some Conservative, Neo-Nazi in his 20s-30s stalked me "for my own good as a "guiding coming out experience," they would have done so when I was still 3+ years from my voice dropping.

Yeah. That would have been *great* for me. Really great.

I had enough skeevy adult guys trying to hit up on me as it was. To have a Neo-Nazi jerk trying to normalize it? On national media on on one of the two major party conferences? No. But thanks for thinking of me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww. Looks like his [book deal just got cancelled, too.](https://www.reddit.com/r/progressive/comments/5v85uj/simon_schuster_cancels_milo_yiannopoulos_book/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simon   Schuster Cancels Milo Yiannopoulos Book Following CPAC Withdrawing His Speaking Engagement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo Yiannopoulos disinvited from CPAC after suggesting sex between younger boys and older men could be a coming-of-age relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until there are responses to this question, here are the ones I got when I asked the /r/AskHistorians, [Did Men REALLY dress as well as portrayed in European and US cinema, '40-'60s? If so, how did this work, what coping mechanisms did they use and how different were mens' clothing budgets/usage compared to today's?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1k7vs9/did_men_really_dress_as_well_as_portrayed_in/)

Thanks again, amazing contributors to AskHistorians!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, just a quick scan on his post history includes gems like this, 

Police: NYC Muslim woman's bias report is false 

by /u/sanfrustration in /r/news

Yeah, just take a quick read through the comment history of this assclown /u/(another redditor here) and you'll find nothing but hate, spite and racist generalizations against whites and his obsession with a perceived 'caste system' in the U.S.

This guy would have been banned weeks ago for these racist rants if they targeted any other race, but he has become emboldened and more angry at the lack of any repercussions... now imagine how many more like him are out there?

At some point, policing forums for concern trolling and "POC whining about racism in the US are the **real** racists!!!" gets fatiguing. 

Mods are volunteers and each Subreddit has its own look and feel. If he feels "battle lines are drawn" and "trenches must be dug", perhaps this brave  *so* brave  armchair warrior can find another front upon which to plant his various flags.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, after reading these posts, I don't see anything besides smoke and a bit of conspiracy hysteria. They even have the founder show up an comment and no one makes any objective critiques that can be countered. Then there's a technical follow-up that's beyond my comprehension levels supporting DDG, but looks decent to this non-programmer and (again) none of the techies on Stack Exchange critique with specificity enough for the poster to counter.

It's fine for folks to have preferences, and they always will. Let a 1,000 flowers bloom. But if that's the worst  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe have it as a FAQ entry? I have concerns about having the site becoming too cluttered  scare away the Newbies. Perhaps with a sentence at the bottom of the site that has a link that takes readers to that section of the FAQ?

I'd also like to see YMMV disclaimer text. For some, the rejects are okay given their profile. It also conveys an important point: you don't need to completely commit to an always Tor, Linux, no-mobile existence to reclaim a lot of your privacy. That's *Scary!* ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I ran Clinton's campaign, and I fear Russia is meddling with more than elections. Putin wants to extend his influence beyond the ballot box and into the very fabric of our public life. We must take action before its too late. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opponents of more rational health care cherry pick cases that require immediate care with ones that don't. Critical cases - of which Canada has fewer due to catching things early - are quickly seen to while optional cases are not.

The strongest argument for Single Payer is structural: how can a system with a middleman - a billion dollar sector with insane profits - be cheaper and more efficient than one without? It's irrational to think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The White House is literally writing away any incidences of Right Wing terrorist attacks from being tallied by Federal reporting, so probably by next month, it wouldn't have counted. Even if it was a churchful of elderly Black people. Or a mosque. Unless, I suppose, they defended themselves from a Roof-type attacker.

But remember, "Alt-Right" is **not** "Neo-Nazi". FAKE NEWS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already covered by [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5uhohp/some_thoughts_on_confide_secrecy_in_the_white/), so removed. Thanks, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And [more](http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2017/02/17/oakland-police-shot-man-after-armed-standoff/):

 Police have identified the man who triggered a tense standoff with police after firing a high-powered rifle at officers and residents near Bishop ODowd High School Friday morning as Oakland resident Jesse *Enjaian* (thx, /u/fooz_the_face!)

He is a 2008 alum of UCLA and a 2013 alum of University of Michigan Law School.

Enjaian is the co-founder and computer engineer at the computer company Oakland Microsystems.

Police sources confirmed to KPIX 5 that officers had responded to Enjaians house earlier this week regarding either threats or a report of a gun.

Oakland Microsystems doesn't exist so far as DDG or Google are concerned.

I'll try to be neutral here, but does the portrayal seem similar to those when people of color engage in shooting rampages? It seems *different* to me somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, less LOLs-tastic. 

From the CBS story linked below:

The gunman was clearly seen in helicopter video shooting out a window of a home on Las Vegas Avenue located near the high school which was on lock down.

The gunman then exited the home, spray painted eyes on a neighbors garage and also spray painted a white car on the street.

He then walked into the backyard, fired shots toward a fence and then the helicopter.

The man had been shooting at residents and parked cars and fired on Oakland police officers as they arrived.

No injuries were reported but officers are still canvassing the neighborhood.

The high school across the street was locked down, as were neighboring businesses. It looks like the home he vandalized was ~~his own~~ a neighbors (worst neighbor ever!)

But given he painted a pair of eyes on it, it looks like he didn't take full advantage of the larger canvas and extra composing time that he had. Amateur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tee hee hee. Ha ha ha.

Of course not. He's ~~White~~ a lone wolf, a misunderstood person, quite the anomaly. Unrepresentative and unfair to compare him in any way to whichever ethnic group he belongs. In fact, why are we wasting precious media attention on this at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a shooter, [he's an artist!](https://twitter.com/TheNothingarian/status/832648154122067969)

OK. A really *crappy* artist. Geezus, emojis have been around for what, 10 years now? Just how hard can it be to draw the Poop emoji? Let alone the eyes-closed-I'm-LOLing-so-hard one. 

He also "personalized" the garage door of a home there, too. Waiting for updates for that  hopefully he did better. Second attempt, larger canvas. One can hope!

If the initial description over the scanner is correct, the first white victim of an OPD officer-involved shooting since Matt Cicelski in 2011 [another Twitter link](https://twitter.com/awinston/status/832665038154403842) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. We can't approve this since Rule #4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JZdziarski has a similarly-preliminary, YMMV, [quick look at Confide](https://www.zdziarski.com/blog/?p=6945)

But the spoiler is, it breaks too many rules for good Crypto. It seems more Silicon Snake Oil pitched at businessmen too embarrassed to use SnapChat for work (which, is *also* crap but) but have finally caught on to the fact that naked SMS is no longer safe. Next on their list, change their AOL email password.

Or the, "Based on the existence of a really cool webpage and a shiny icon, let's have our most confidential discussions on someone else's cloud that the company that runs it doesn't even own". What could possibly go wrong?

Oh, and there's the whole, Let's Break Federal Law By Refusing To Conduct Business On Gov't Systems So Mandated Record-Keeping Requirements Are Evaded aspect.

I believe emails, and even email servers, were *briefly* mentioned by the Trump Administration, largely for this and for security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JZdziarski has a similarly-preliminary, YMMV, [quick look at Confide](https://www.zdziarski.com/blog/?p=6945)

But the spoiler is, it breaks too many rules for good Crypto. It seems more Silicon Snake Oil pitched at businessmen too embarrassed to use SnapChat for work (which, is *also* crap but) but have finally caught on to the fact that naked SMS is no longer safe. Next on their list, change their AOL email password.

Or the, "Based on the existence of a really cool webpage and a shiny icon, let's have our most confidential discussions on someone else's cloud that the company that runs it doesn't even own". What could possibly go wrong?

Oh, and there's the whole, Let's Break Federal Law By Refusing To Conduct Business On Gov't Systems So Mandated Record-Keeping Requirements Are Evaded aspect.

I believe emails, and even email servers, were *briefly* mentioned by the Trump Administration, largely for this and for security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some thoughts on Confide. Secrecy in the White House has always been a hot topic. What do we know about the App that WH staffers are using? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some thoughts on Confide. Secrecy in the White House has always been a hot topic. What do we know about the App that WH staffers are using? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, talk about things I never expected I'd be typing.

Breitbart isn't normally a site we prefer when others exist. The level of journalism they have simply isn't up to par. But in this case, with this article, they **do** have an exclusive with William Binney. He's kind of A Big Deal.

Maybe Binney is hinting if we want to increase privacy and prune the Deep State, we need to a) look at all media sources and independently verify them, and b) build coalitions. 

Anyway, I'd hate to have gods knows what is on their ad serving side of things, so I'll post most of it here. 

Appreciate the reports, and we *get* it. This is a special case.

William Binney, a former highly placed NSA official turned whistleblower, contended in an exclusive interview today that the National Security Agency (NSA) is absolutely monitoring the phone calls of President Donald Trump.


Binney was an architect of the NSAs surveillance program. He became a famed whistleblower when he resigned on October 31, 2001 after spending more than 30 years with the agency.

Asked whether he believes the NSA is tapping Trump, Binney replied: Absolutely. How did they get the phone call between the president and the president of Australia? Or the one that he made with Mexico? Those are not targeted foreigners.

Binney further [contended](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/13/us/politics/donald-trump-national-security-adviser-michael-flynn.html) the NSA may have been behind a data leak that might have revealed that Michael Flynn, Trumps national security adviser, allegedly misled Vice President Mike Pence and other Trump administration officials about the contents of his phone calls with Russias ambassador to Washington.

Regarding Flynns case, Binney stated of the NSA:

If they werent behind it, they certainly had the data. Now the difference here is that FBI and CIA have direct access inside the NSA databases. So, they may be able to go directly in there and see that material there. And NSA doesnt monitor that. They dont even monitor their own people going into databases.

So, they dont monitor what CIA and FBI do. And theres no oversight or attempted oversight by any of the committees or even the FISA court. So, any way you look at it, ultimately the NSA is responsible because they are doing the collection on everybody inside the United States. Phone calls. Emails. All of that stuff.

He was speaking on the podcast edition of this reporters talk radio program, Aaron Klein Investigative Radio, broadcast on New Yorks AM 970 The Answer and Philadelphias NewsTalk 990 AM.

During the interview, Binney referred to a 2008 report referencing two NSA whistleblowers who said they worked at the agencys station in Fort Gordon, Georgia and were asked to not only monitor phone calls of U.S. citizens but transcribe them.

Utilizing data provided by whistleblower Edward Snowden, the Guardian and Washington Post in June 2013 released a series of articles reporting that the NSA was collecting the telephone records of millions of Americans.

Prior to those reports, National Intelligence Director James Clapper claimed on March 12, 2013 during an open session of the Senate Intelligence Committee that the NSA was not wittingly collecting data on Americans.

Not wittingly, Clapper said when asked whether the NSA was spying on U.S. citizens. There are cases where they could inadvertently, perhaps, collect, but not wittingly.

During the interview, Binney charged that the NSA was over-funded and out of control.

He offered recommendations for how he says Trump can reign in the agency:

He can order that they put a filter on the front end of all their collection that eliminates any U.S. citizens anywhere in the world unless they have a warrant for it. If they dont, then he has to put people in jail if they violated.

So, I mean, thats the way to do it. The other way is to cut their budget. I mean they are given too much money anyway. When they are given too much money, they get to do wild and crazy things. And this is wild and crazy. Violations of the Constitutions 4th, 5th, and 6th amendments.

On Wednesday, Trump singled out the NSA and FBI in a series of tweets about Flynns case as well as reports in the New York Times and Washington Post claiming further contacts between Trump advisors and Russia.

The real scandal here is that classified information is illegally given out by "intelligence" like candy. Very un-American!

 Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) February 15, 2017

Thank you to Eli Lake of The Bloomberg View  "The NSA   FBIshould not interfere in our politicsand is" Very serious situation for USA

 Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) February 15, 2017

Information is being illegally given to the failing @nytimes   @washingtonpost by the intelligence community (NSA and FBI?).Just like Russia

 Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) February 15, 2017

The Times on Tuesday seemed to be quoting from intercepted phone calls to report on alleged contacts between Trump campaign aides and Russian intelligence agents.

The Times [reported](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/14/us/politics/russia-intelligence-communications-trump.html):

Phone records and intercepted calls show that members of Donald J. Trumps 2016 presidential campaign and other Trump associates had repeated contacts with senior Russian intelligence officials in the year before the election, according to four current and former American officials.

American law enforcement and intelligence agencies intercepted the communications around the same time they were discovering evidence that Russia was trying to disrupt the presidential election by hacking into the Democratic National Committee, three of the officials said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to work out well. One of the top level comments refers to the TC one, yet convos for both end up here.

It's the comments that are the main thing I'm trying to protect. :)

If enough folks say the TC article or any other, we'd be fine with posting it. But it has to add something new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. Approved!

Sorry about that, but it looked like plug-ins, but wanted to make sure.

Believe it or not *sigh* sometimes people shill for their site, buried under a bunch of other ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks of looking. Lemme confer since we like the post, just the format's a problem. Grr. Thanks for your patience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. We'll make this the main article. I removed the duplicate you mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed in favor of original sourced article [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5u868y/ghostery_is_acquired_by_cliqz/). Thanks, tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out [Anatomy of a Deep State](http://billmoyers.com/2014/02/21/anatomy-of-the-deep-state/). Required reading.

Note it was written during Obama Presidency, although could have been written any time after Truman's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arguably, national security. Really, embarrassing the military/intelligence folks, exposing their lies, ineffectiveness and corruption that they'd prefer be kept hidden in the Black Budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're buying into a narrative foisted by companies that profit off of their lil' niche thinking all the other niches are evil, uncompromising, unrealistic and an existential threat. You   yours are rational and sacred, the Other is a feared beast.

It's not true. We know this. The Greeks knew this. Remember, United we stand, divided we fall? The father, with those sticks, that he bundled?

Don't be conned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I approve this, I want to check its purpose. It was flagged since so many URLs were included.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a paragraph in Greenwald's article addressing this:

The motives of leakers are irrelevant. Its very possible  indeed, likely  that the leakers here were not acting with benevolent motives. Nobody with a straight face can claim that lying to the public is regarded in official Washington as some sort of mortal sin; if anything, the contrary is true: Its seen as a job requirement.

It's also the difference in someone leaking to journalists, who then apply their training, versus a data-dump like Wikileaks did. Having someone else base a story on it helps insulate whatever biases the leaker has (which, I agree, in this case are suspect). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mere fact that an act is illegal does not mean it is unjust or even deserving of punishment. Oftentimes, the most just acts are precisely the ones that the law prohibits.

Thats particularly true of whistleblowers  i.e., those who reveal information the law makes it a crime to reveal, when doing so is the only way to demonstrate to the public that powerful officials are acting wrongfully or deceitfully. In those cases, we should cheer those who do it even though they are undertaking exactly those actions that the criminal law prohibits.

This Flynn episode underscores another critical point: The motives of leakers are irrelevant. Its very possible  indeed, likely  that the leakers here were not acting with benevolent motives. Nobody with a straight face can claim that lying to the public is regarded in official Washington as some sort of mortal sin; if anything, the contrary is true: Its seen as a job requirement.

Click thru for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, *some* of the Left. You're painting with too broad a brush. Many in the left were and are concerned. You've heard of the term, Deep State?

More importantly, it's a good thing that there's this switch. If half the folks whose partisan fears were ignited by Obama join half that are now ignited by Trump, then those, plus those who were concerned with *any* administration having these vast powers, then that's a positive trend.

So, rather than cramming this news into yet another partisan filter, how about focusing on shared concerns over policy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, so horrorshow UK Snooper's Charter (hate "Snoopers" btw but I guess we're stuck with it) sez all traffic sources need to be catalogued, to the site level but not more granular than that. Correct me if I'm wrong.

Then if OP gets a UK VPN, their government would *also* be able to get those records, correct? Thus the only viable VPN use would be for a VPN that is outside the UK, or Five Eyes generally? 

And, same with any other components the OP is contemplating?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity and for those readers less sophisticated than OP, why not just pump all the data, including Steam   other streaming traffic, through the VPN? Is it because of bandwidth limits   pricing tiers? I'll bet it's b/c of bandwidth limits   pricing tiers. :)

Any other reasons why you'd want to split traffic like this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dup of https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5t5yfr/sony_patents_contact_lens_that_records_what_you/?ref=search_posts but thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So *So there's HOPE!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it okay to use Hey, baby, *three* of my posts made it all the way to /r/Popular as a pick-up line?

Asking for a friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
