<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 11:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what actually makes you special? What can you do that normal people can't? Why were you chosen to be a balancer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 11:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, my eyesight is really bad anyway.. So I probably wouldn't really notice the difference haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially when your only real reference point is horror movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she didn't steal the child, but it's not yet old enough to become a werewolf like her other children. They might live in the second house. Maybe the strange man is the drunk husband and that's why she didn't want to talk to him, but he was still allowed to see the baby. Who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with you! Chances are that op took something that didn't agree with him, for whatever reason. Thus leading to all this :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 10:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ewww, it was licking feet. That's sick, even for a monster!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't lack of emotion in child something that doctors / health visitors look out for? Did you never raise this with anyone? I feel like even prior to the bird eating, he obviously needed some kind of intervention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet heart you need to see someone and get help, but I guess now that you've had an unsuccessful suicide attempt you'll have doctors there to help. What you're feeling isn't normal, it's depression most likely or something related. Falling in love, and being so encompassed by the feeling, to the point of obsession isn't normal either and is probably related. I strongly suggest seeing a doctor, getting medication and / or therapy. It can really help.
You're not a failure, you are just in a bad place at the moment. But all storms pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been the first child most likely, the one she aborted five years prior. That one wasn't Terry's child either. So it would be weird that both terry and the child had the same red eye thing going on in the sunlight, if the child was supposedly not completely natural. 

That's why I'm thinking that it was just a trick of the light, and she got swapped. With alternate dimensions, there must be easier ways to get unborn children's souls.

And, he took the unborn child didn't he? I wouldn't have thought that he would then give it back. But who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two goes for the price of one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, that's really weird. Maybe try telling a stranger about the dream to see if that makes any difference to their actions. Or invite a work colleague over for a beer to see what happens. If they notice the weird behaviour, it'll mean that you're not mad or having another person their might 'break the spell'. Who knows. 

I've never heard anything like this before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope nope nope. Pretending I didn't read this comment!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to get rid of the dream catcher. Gift it away to someone else, I'd guess that instead of catching nightmares, it's giving them. How did your cat actually die? 

The same thing probably happened to the cat, as cats sleep a whole lot. Maybe the pain is real enough to drive you insane... But with an animal it works a lot faster.

Good luck op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to tell specifically from the story, but just in case haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I thought too, but I would expect the grim reaper to know where his intended appointments are going to be lol. But maybe that's why shut ins always seem to be ancient haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the guy smelled like death? After a few days, a body can start to smell fairly bad depending on the conditions. You should tell the police, it's their job to investigate. If they find nothing, it's not going to look bad on you and I really don't think that they would have any reason to look into your medical history based on you seeing a visitor. Like you say, these kind of people hanging around aren't uncommon. 

Giving directions isn't you helping a murdered either, it's not like you could guess that Jerry was going to die or be killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that? Is ops shadow gone for good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 02:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy hell op. Did you get swapped with Terry's other woman? You hadn't seen him in five years, but you woke up with a five year old son! That would also explain where his money was going, why he hid the mail... Although the the woman on the magazine could just be coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 02:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be scared of Vincent, you and him, you can do it. You're young, go to social services again. They can help you now that your parents are gone or in too much trouble to get you back. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAVE THE CAT OP. And be careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 02:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's all it takes, your poor dead gf never had a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 02:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped reading your replies because it seems like you broke character. Which is a rule breaker and a turn off for me when I'm here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 00:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's going to try something, possibly to get rianne back... Or maybe just finish what she started? 

Or perhaps, he's just rebounding after his loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 00:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 'Matthew is dead' was reversed correctly. 
But the second part was not reversed, it was just jumbled. Or the spelling was wrong? Was it intentionally that way? 
The ending was kinda off as well, who was the girl? What was the relevance of your brother, did he kill himself too? I feel like you need to tell us more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The relationship in this story is really unhealthy. And the views expressed about Thailand are really generalised, it took me out of the story and kind of spoiled what you were trying to tell me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful writing, wonderful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killed by the actions of her greedy, crooked father more like :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I hope that you get out :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why would I not read this? 

Also, that's not afterbirth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's why all the bark was missing in the lower half of the tree. 

Could the farmer just not build a huge fence around the tree, to block most of it from view?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 12:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when these beings make deals, but then make up bs terms to go with them. A deal doesn't really transfer onto someone who wasn't involved, that's not how it works man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why is the whistle pigs thing so bad for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 22:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, why not sooner then? The story gives the impression that you weren't all that bothered right up until the actual pregnancy was mid way imo. I don't know, it feels a bit like something is missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 22:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everything is a skinwalker. Why has that become the default?
This sounds more like a lost dog who has followed you home. Bad news for your probably.
I'd start by asking your near Vegas family for any information, and then closing that doggy door up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 04:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the vibe that I got too... Like, definitely not a handy helper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 04:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really understand. Did you know this would happen if you had a child? Or did the priest tell you more than you told us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 04:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What on earth could your father have wanted so badly that he'd sacrifice his whole family?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 03:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woop girl, no one should ever be treated that way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 03:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op is kill :( 
sorry that pj was an ass monster, I was suspicious as soon as the two tie thing came up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, your new purpose in life is to assume a new tourist identity and hunt down this crazy woman. Think of all the other poor guys and girls being kidney robbed! 

I hope that you're still around op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? You saw her just like that, and fell so deeply in love immediately that her being a murderer is fine? This is so weird.

And what's the significance of the font changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 00:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, call up that psychic and ask her what she has done. Also, try some parenting tips. If this is really coming to life his behaviour will not change once he is animate. So maybe try some gentle discipline, and talking, he might be able to understand.

Otherwise, hot foot it out of there... Dropping the doll off with the psychic on the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 00:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what do you do? What is the benefit to the suit I wonder?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never heard of this game. But oh man, I want to play it now haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 01:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potentially you did just have a nightmare, sometimes when I wake up I can still 'hear' the sounds from my dreams and maybe your brother just heard your dream talking. I've also scratched myself while half asleep, because I don't realise that I'm using too much pressure.
You would have probably had another incident by now, so I'm not sure it's ghostly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 01:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yeah spooky. 

He was your best friend, and he gave you both the strength that you needed to be free. He helped you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, I thought I had misread it at first as well. :) it makes sense for the police to talk to him like you said, so op could mean that anyway though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He literally says 'I'm still under investigation' right at the beginning of the story though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 15:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ps, call police and run!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 15:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smell of three different bodies rotting in the air vents would have been atrocious. You didn't smell them in there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 14:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, it's been either your guardian or just a being wanting a home. Either way, I guess that you have no reason to be scared of it. 

Newly defined pupils though, as in they changed after the killing? Probably best not to 'feed' it again, just in case lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you always hear that children are far more susceptible to these kids of things, and as she grows up I'm sure that she will come to understand how wonderful your grandma was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it follow you then? Must be more reason to it than just wanting to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't see why haha.
All you need to do now is set up a business with added options for bi / gay cheats and you are literally rolling in cash. And making the world a better place while you're at it. 
I'd use your services, although I probably wouldn't keep the fella afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 19:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I would just pour a tonne of concrete into the well, and move 1000 miles away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She says on another comment that her brother handles those cases :) so it's all equal game I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed? Who removes an iia story? :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you do that to a fish, it's so mean :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm gonna pause and say well done for being a bit nasty. You shouldn't steal anything from someone, and it's not very nice to try to get to know someone by reading their personal things. You are meant to introduce yourself, talk etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she died in a car crash, why would you be under investigation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this story actually about. What's even with the stag?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dear, if it's in bed whispering to you, I don't think it's really just after food. You should probably call in some one to check the vents, claim that you can hear rats or something.
Ask your neighbours if they are having any issues. Also, confide in your partner... See if they have noticed anything or suffered at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! That's awful, just insane. Please update us op :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 14:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be really careful. Also, take a quick break and look up the previous home owners... Just to see if they had any experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 13:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mesmerising, totally stunning. Your writing was just brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't really negate my comment though, if you really think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His wife had depression.. She didn't 'abandon' him by choice. I'm sure that she wanted someone to be close to her, not leave her alone even more to meet other women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 20:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like duh, but it's not like he didn't end up in that situation by chance. Maybe meeting strangers for casual flings isn't the best idea. When you know nothing about them, where they live, who they might live with, whether they are crazy or not or have a knife fetish. 
None of his actions are exactly stellar either.. Maybe calling the cops was a redeeming actions, but that's about it lol. 

Honestly, I don't feel sorry for him at all. I hope everyone involved is happy and feeling better... And knife girl is seeing someone to control her fetish better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
