<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4538</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 08:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burn Gorman. That man is hella pretty and no one can convince me otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 16:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! I'm really happy for you man :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg that's so cute!! I've always wanted to try decoden but I worry I might mess it up :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 20:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing! I'll pm you as soon as I get home :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are so beautiful! I'd love to have the cream-colored sala necklace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 00:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, me too! :'D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 22:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He makes a lot of valid points. I like him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite colors are green and blue. I love colored pencils. Prismacolor is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For pants? Usually I'm a size 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha actually I always wash my hands after using the bathroom. Sorry :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 07:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, yeah, some. Largely because 1) she's a woman, and 2) she's a democrat. Beyond that, she's just as crooked as any other big name politician. Personally, I'd much rather have Bernie Sanders in office, but the likeliness of him winning against "the first female president" is slim, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, are you me? Those three things are terrible to feel, especially the second one. When you open up to someone about how you feel and they go "I mean, everyone gets sad some days, subject4538. It's not a big deal." Or "Don't be selfish, jeez, people go through way worse and they don't cry about it - they move on. Why can't you be like them?"  It just completely invalidates your feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Comfy but not sloppy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't do it any more, but when I was a kid I used to cut off the little ends of sausages and throw them away cuz I thought they looked like assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old people complaining about how today's music is all "autotuned garbage".Yes, autotune and other effects are often used in songs to some degree, but honestly, there's tons of excellent music being released every week - even among the often looked down on top 40. It's impossible to hate all of it, you emotionally constipated walnuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smartasses. People who try to add in their own witty comment to put down someone's opinion or belief. People who never fully express satisfaction if they're happy with something - like they'll say "eh. It's decent" for literally everything, and they're very quick to point out its flaws. Like damn can you at least pretend to be positive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents, mostly. They'd feel horrible if I died. That's usually enough to keep me going most days. Other days, when I think they'd be better off without me, I try to think of stuff I want to do in my life. Get a good job with a stable income. Travel. Get a pet. It's simple stuff, but it keeps me going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god bless you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. That's right sweet of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel dumb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep crying. I can hear my dad yelling at me in my head. I feel so dumb. I don't even know where this came from. I just feel so childish. Even now, I can't take his criticism well. I just want a hug.

I want to talk about it and be asked if I'm okay and I want to feel safe, but I'm alone here. The friends that I know in real life - I can't bother them with kind of thing. It's depressing to have to hear about how your friend just wants to die. I've been on the giving and the receiving end of that, and I know how hard it is so I'm not going to bring it up with them. I don't know. I just want a hug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Bee Bro 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's...it's *beautiful.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I hope it gets picked up soon! I was so surprised nbc dropped it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I never realized that before - that's exactly what he looks like! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears the titties have left the physical realm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 21:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did! But what did the word puzzle thing at the end say? I couldn't figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 06:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember waking up early on saturday mornings and watching this. Best show ever for 8 year old me :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 14:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I heard this song in a store a couple weeks ago, but I couldn't find it either! :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Books about a mentor and student slowly falling in love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 05:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to find a book with this, just cuz I like the concept :p. I loved the Beekeeper's Apprentice series and Pagan's Crusade series (even if Pagan's Crusade wasn't exactly that, the mentor/student relationship between Roland and Pagan was close). Bonus points if there's some kind of fantastical or historical setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 18:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played it about a week ago - loved it, one of my new favorite games :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I was expecting dwayne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 03:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have my hair down to my shoulders a few years ago, but it looked awful. Then again, I was about 14 at the time and had braces and glasses, so that probably didn't help...
Either way, I'm wary of growing my hair long, but l'll see how it looks when it gets maybe an inch or so past my chin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ. This shit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 00:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pelon pelo rico - tamarind favor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I played this on my android a while back! Excellent job man :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww shoot this is probably one of the sweetest comments I've ever gotten :) Thank you. I'll definitely try to smile more and keep my head high 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 02:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bob's kinda like [this](http://www.prettydesigns.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/2014-Fashionable-Short-Wavy-Hair-Bob-Haircuts.jpg) or [this](http://www.short-hairstyles.co/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Short-bob-hairstyles-side-view.jpg) But if it looks good at that length I'll probably keep growing it out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man, it's the best :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am glad u have never been replaced by a crab person my friend, u have a good soul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What hair color would you recommend? I've thought about dying it before but could never decide what would look right. There's like 15 different shades of brown in the hair section at walgreens :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably grow my hair out into a bob over the next couple months, based on all the comments about it :p

Could you give me an example pic of someone wearing eyeliner not in the inner corners? I've tried it before but both of my parents said it made my eyes look strange, but maybe I was doing it wrong.

About the username, Hannibal's such a good show 3. And the new season's coming soon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get him to make you food :D. A nice plate of fried chicken and waffles with a side of maple syrup is fairly easy to make in under 30 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying. I might grow it out into a bob or something of decent length, but I remember noticing that after a certain length (something like a couple inches past my chin) it starts making my face look super elongated so I gotta be careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have it down to my shoulders but tbh it looked awful on me at the time - I managed to look like a seventies surfer dude somehow. I've been thinking about growing it out into a bob maybe as a kind of a middle ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) I've never really noticed my nose before. Also fair point there about my chin. I've considered maybe getting surgery for it when I get older but Idk if it would really change much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man :) I'll try my best to smile more. I used to have super- messed up teeth so I'm trying to slowly grow out of my past insecurity about them - its reassuring to get told my smile is nice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww thank you, thats really sweet of you 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [18F] Do I look alright? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/FpM2v

http://imgur.com/a/T1RWa

Hey guys. I've always been pretty insecure about my face, especially my chin, and I was wondering if I could get some honest opinions on how I look. The first album is basically me on "good hair days" and the second albums highlights my weird chin/jaw and a bad hair day.
I'd sincerely appreciate any feedback or constructive criticism!

Edit: Thank you for all the sweet compliments and constructive feedback everyone 3 Based on what you guys have said (along with irl friends too), I think I'll grow my hair out into a bob and look into eye makeup/etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not too sure how to style my hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 01:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/VaydP 

I've had my hair short like this for about a year now, but it never seems to look right. I usually put it so that it looks like the first picture. It's also pretty thick, grows relatively fast, and is naturally curly. Prior to cutting it, my hair was to my shoulders and looked awful tbh - I basically looked like a surfer dude despite being a girl.

Any tips or recommendations on styling it or getting a new hairstyle would be appreciated! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, sounds good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha good point man :p Maybe that's what I'm missing in my diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feeling like I'm losing my ability to feel full, and I'm getting kinda worried. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some background info: I'm female, 18 years old, 5'4, and weigh 110 lbs. I used to be super underweight when I was a kid but I got to a normal weight and appetite by the time I was 13 or so. 

Now, here's the problem. In the past year, my appetite's gotten a lot larger. I can eat less if I make myself, but I can easily eat large portions without feeling sick. Yesterday, I ended up outeating my dad at dinner - we had giant plates of noodles and vegetables and he couldn't finish his but I could and felt fine. Today at lunch, I ate two big bowls of rice and had to pull myself away from the kitchen because I still feel like I wasn't satisfied. My dad's started warning me I'm gonna get fat if I keep eating like this, and I'm getting worried too. Anyone else ever dealt with this situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwww :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 22:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HELL YEA :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found some info [here](http://makanidotdot.tumblr.com/post/116706090741/oooooh-makani-im-sorry-for-being-another-person#notes)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl who was kinda my friend for a couple years started getting a crush on me about a year ago. In the months since, she's slapped my butt, awkwardly given me a massage outta nowhere (worst massage ever btw), talks to me by leaning reaaaally close to my face, and called out in the hall, "Hey subject4538! I like that skirt! *and what's under it.*" 

I literally don't want to be in the same room as her now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 04:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosemary. And if it's too long, people can call her Rose or Rosie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A healthy relationship needs equality, and what y'all have going on doesn't sound like that. Sit her down and say how you want her to start pulling her weight. Give her a couple weeks, remind her of it frequently, and if she still doesn't change this means she's not willing to put in the extra effort for you that you already give for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved them. Played them with my dad as a kid (well, mostly sat in his lap and told him to click on stuff) but appreciated them even more as I got older. Beautiful game series with an amazing storyline. The graphics aren't great now but they were the future to me when I was little. The amount of work put in to all the little details and dialogues, every automaton and edifice - everything is unique. I loved them and hope the third game comes out soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A movie reviewer! I'd love to watch movies and get paid to write essays about them. To be fair, I guess I could do it as a job, but it'd be awfully hard to get a livable wage off of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a small nose stud would look lovely on you. Like the other commenter said, you really do have delicate lips - I think a lip piercing would detract from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you're welcome man :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best I could do fam

http://imgur.com/EsbHvIH

Edit: shit, pretend her big toe is her pinky toe

Nvm I redid it. More realistic now.

http://imgur.com/n4c2N9P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, looks sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good lord, she took off like 7 layers of skirts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **RISE** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god this is like my new favorite thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yep I do :p love your blog btw! I'm sweetgardenpath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I think I follow you on tumblr. I saw this on my dash earlier today :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bless these lads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 17:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through Heaven's Eyes is my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 17:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 23:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a senior in high school and to be honest I've never felt that learning games or projects were effective in teaching us. Time spent cutting and pasting and googling could be better spent just copying down notes so I've actually got something to study with when the unit test comes around. I think I learn best by writing and visualization, so powerpoints honestly work pretty well for me, and I'm sure for some of your kids as well. Just wanted to give a different perspective :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 18:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so hyped!!! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 14:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I'm a fish now :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Femalefashionadvice seems like it's geared more towards 30-somethings that work in an office environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 04:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 14:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! :) I'd love to have those samples, or just the primer if possible :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I wanna have skin like that when I grow up! How long have you been taking care of your skin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 19:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why are you treating her like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Syberia. Absolutely beautiful game.   Made me appreciate mammoths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woahh that sounds amazing. Anybody know if it's available somewhere in the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're getting some silly comments, but damn this is sweet. I love you too! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it! My friend's made 50 dollars in the past couple weeks so that convinced me pretty quick to sign up :p. If anyone else wants to try, [this](http://instagc.com/656512) is my referral link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn :T

I guess most likely I'll have to move out of state. I'm a bit confused though. Dental hygiene as a field has been recommended to me by my counselor, a teacher, and what feels like a billion of those "best jobs with associates/bachelors degrees" lists. Yet anytime I read about it online in forums, I see tons of people bashing it.

Is it simply a bad job? Are there any states that pay them decently and don't deny benefits? Or should I just look for a different job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best laptop you can buy for your money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 14:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ds lite for sale, $40 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 13:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, me again :p I've also got a ds lite for sale for $40. I've had it for about 4 years, it works perfectly. Minor scratches on the top outside face, but otherwise clean and well-maintained. Silver gray color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
