<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1409</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL when a 16th century cathedral in Salamanca, Spain was renovated in the early 1990s, ornate stone carvings of an astronaut and a gargoyle eating ice cream were added near the entrance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Warren: Dismantling health law 'irresponsible and cruel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original study](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/355/6321/159) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artist Suzanne Moxhay produces photomontage scenes which seem to effortlessly combine elements from both her own photography practice and her large archive of collected images. To compose her taken and collected photographs, Moxhay relies on a film technique dating back to the early 20th century called matte painting, a process where backdrops are illustrated on glass panels and integrated into live-action sets. Using this method she creates the illusion that all of her disparate pictures are one cohesive image, first arranging the fragments on glass, then re-photographing the new configuration, and finally touching up the compositions digitally.

[more](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2017/01/photomontages-suzanne-moxhay/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forest in abandoned building, photomontage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater sculpture by Jason deCaires Taylor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Former MI-6 Spy Is Reportedly the Author of the Reports on Donald Trump and Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monastic activity on the island:

The monastery's exact date of foundation is not known. The first definite reference to monastic activity on the island is a record of the death of "Suibhini of Skelig" dating from the 8th century; however, Saint Fionn is claimed to have founded the monastery in the 6th century.

The monastic site on the island is on a terraced shelf 600 feet (180 metres) above sea level, and developed between the sixth and eighth centuries. It contains six beehive cells, two oratories as well as a number of stone crosses and slabs. It also contains a later medieval church. The cells and oratories are all of dry-built corbel construction. A carefully designed system for collecting and purifying water in cisterns was developed. It has been estimated that no more than twelve monks and an abbot lived here at any one time. A hermitage is on the south peak.

The diet of monks living on the North Atlantic islands was somewhat different from that of those who lived on the mainland. With less arable land available to grow grain, vegetable gardens became an important part of monastic life. Of necessity, fish and the meat and eggs of birds nesting on the islands became staples.

The "Annals of Inisfallen" record a Viking attack in 823. The site had been dedicated to Saint Michael by at least 1044 (when the death of "Aedh of Scelic-Mhich" is recorded). However, this dedication may have occurred as early as 950, around which time a new church was added to the monastery (typically done to celebrate a consecration) which was called Saint Michael's Church.

The monastery remained continuously occupied until the 12th or 13th century. During this time, the climate around Skellig Michael became colder and more prone to storms, and this, along with changes to the structure of the Irish Church, prompted the community to abandon the island and move to the abbey in Ballinskelligs.

[source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Skellig_Michael) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skellig Michael is 7 miles west of Ireland and is home to a monastery which was in use from the 7th to 12th centuries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas farewell message on democracy: Show up. Dive in. Stay at it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 12:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be offended by your racism, but your spelling points to a lack of basic education.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blooms are 3-D printed sculptures designed to animate when spun under a strobe light. Unlike a 3D zoetrope, which animates a sequence of small changes to objects, a bloom animates as a single self-contained sculpture. The blooms animation effect is achieved by progressive rotations of the golden ratio, phi (), the same ratio that nature employs to generate the spiral patterns we see in pinecones and sunflowers. The rotational speed and strobe rate of the bloom are synchronized so that one flash occurs every time the bloom turns 137.5 (the angular version of phi).

[much more](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2017/01/blooms-2-strobe-animated-sculptures-by-john-edmark/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mesmerizing strobe animated sculpture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are, of course, free to spend your fortune however you choose, but making large political contributions to buy influence does not qualify you to help set policy for the education of Americas school children. To the contrary, your history of support for policies that would drain valuable taxpayer resources from our public schools and funnel those funds to unaccountable private and for-profit education operators may well disqualify you from such a central role in public education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Elizabeth Warren Denounces Trumps Horrifying Education Pick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In their defense, I'd be cutting some noxious farts too if I knew it would get me a free trip to Bali. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a plane en route from Australia to Malaysia with a cargo of 2186 sheep had to make an emergency landing in Bali when excess gas from the animals set off smoke indicators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While renovating the Government Center subway station in Boston, construction workers came across a hollow section of concrete... Inside, there was a red-and-blue ball of dirty cloth. Unfurled, the ball turned into an even creepier find: two cloaks, dotted with stars, with ghoulish masks stitched into them.

Its not clear where these trash wizards came from, but the Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority (MBTA) does know that this section of concrete was poured 60 years ago, which means that these cloaks have been there for decades. 

[backstory](http://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/found-extremely-creepy-masks-hidden-for-decades)

[closeup](http://imgur.com/yLuY49b) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious masks and cloaks found hidden in a Boston subway station after more than 60 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Postal worker stuffs mailboxes like a well oiled machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dude knows how to catch watermelons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traffic cone fits perfectly into space between sidewalk stones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 394-page manual was said to have been handed to new couples in the city of Kutahya, and a similar version given out in Pamukkale.

Just wondering, what department would be responsible for producing such a document? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish marriage guide advises wives to wear sexy outfits after being beaten to 'please' their husbands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original study](http://psycnet.apa.org/? fa=main.doiLanding doi=10.1037/pspi0000080) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study shows that the satisfaction of causing harm to those who have made them suffer enhances the mood of those who have experienced social rejection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Las Lajas Sanctuary crosses a forested gorge on the border between Colombia and Ecuador </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Far-right blogger Chuck C. Johnson is reportedly helping vet Trump administration candidates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The President's views appeared in a policy forum article in the highly regarded research journal, Science.

The editors believe it is the first time that a sitting President has written such a feature.

You can find a link to the full text of Obama's article [here](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2017/01/06/science.aam6284.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama says shift to green energy is 'irreversible' despite Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a baby koala in a fleece blanket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five of Trump's choices who will face Senate committees  secretary of State pick Rex Tillerson, Education secretary choice Betsy DeVos, Labor secretary pick Andy Puzder, Commerce secretary pick Wilbur Ross and Transportation secretary pick Elaine Chao  have contributed $449,559 combined to current senators' campaigns or outside groups supporting them, according to the Center for Responsive Politics. All but Chao, who is married to Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, contributed to at least one senator elected in 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Trump Cabinet picks have given big bucks to senators voting on their confirmations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original research](http://www.aanda.org/articles/aa/abs/2016/11/aa29835-16/aa29835-16.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this slow motion water droplet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California's famous 'Tunnel Tree' is toppled by storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop Saying Trumps Win Had Nothing To Do With Economics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 11:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Shkreli kicked off Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> abandoned Beelitz Sanatorium in Germany--treated a wounded soldier named Adolf Hitler in 1916 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alec Baldwin trolls Trump with Russian "Make America Great Again" cap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prediction: In 2022, two stars will collide into one another. That collision will unleash a massive amount of energy. So massive, the two stars  which are now invisible to the naked eye  will increase in brightness by a factor of 10,000.

And not only will we be able to see this explosion, in real time, with unaided eyes, it will become one of the brightest objects in the entire sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stars may collide in a stunning red nova in 2022 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a non profit group called Nurtured by Nature in California provides the opportunity for children with terminal illnesses to swim and play with otters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Only 'stupid' people think warm ties with Russia are a bad thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wedge-tailed eagle with a mouth full of rat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out my thumpers, y'all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Francesco Albanos human body sculptures drip, melt, hang, and often appear to be boneless  even the work primarily featuring bones is distorted and lumpy. Working with wax, polyester, latex, iron, and other materials, Albano sculpts shapes and contortions that render the erect and boundaried body flaccid and grotesque.
Albano is interested in and influenced by a wide range of subjects from philosophical, mystical and spiritual arguments to scientific theories, from psychological studies to real life stories. Albano uses skin and bone as a critical and personal tool of expression to focus on the effect of societal pressures and psychological violence on the human body and collective conscience. More than an inner envelope the artist defines the human skin as a limit and an identity, that interacts with outer world.

[source](http://beautifuldecay.com/2013/11/21/francesco-albanos-body-sculptures/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Empty skin bag slides out of bathtub: by Francesco Albano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Turning American Companies Into Reality-Show Contestants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More info](http://www.atlasobscura.com/places/victoria-s-way-indian-sculpture-park):

Covering 22 acres, the park includes a series of dancing figures of Ganesh, Shiva, and other Hindu deities. It also includes more bizarre sculptures of a skeletal Buddha-like figure, an enormous disembodied finger, and a sculpture called The Split Man which shows a figure ripping itself in two, representing the mental state of the dysfunctional human.

Intended to represent the spiritual progression to enlightenment, this collection of 14 statues took 20 years to complete. A plaque dedicates the park to mathematician Alan Turing.

The park was known as Victorias Way until 2015, when it was closed by the owner, who stated, Too may day-trippers came turned it into a fun park for parents with children. It was designed as a contemplative garden for over 28s. It was reopened in 2016 as Victors Way (reverting to its original name) with new age restrictions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferryman's End piece at Victor's Way sculpture garden, Wicklow, Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is the assumption that by bullying corporations, such as Ford, and stepping into aid other corporations, such as Google, the Trump administration can achieve various objectives that will widely boost output and employment. But this is an expansion of corporatist policy of a kind not previously seen since the German and Italian economies of the 1930s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel Prize winner likens Trump bullying of companies to fascist Italy, Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By Adam Hillman.  Tons of cool posts on his Instagram feed @witenry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Reindeer herders in Finland are painting their reindeer's antlers with reflective paint to cut down on deer-car collisions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starry Night on a paintbrush </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M M Watercolor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow up, Donald. Grow up. Time to be an adult, he said. Youre president. Youve got to do something. Show us what you have. Youre going to propose legislation. Were going to get to debate it. Let the public decide. Let them vote in Congress. Lets see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Biden to Trump: Grow Up, Donald </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has repeatedly threatened to slap American manufacturers with a border tax if they move jobs and production out of the country and then sell goods back to the United States. But this appears to be the first time that Trump has warned that a foreign company could face similar repercussions, and his tax proposal does not lay out a framework for how a border tax might be implemented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump just threatened Toyota  but it looks like he got the facts wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mortsafes were contraptions designed to protect graves from disturbance. Resurrectionists had supplied the schools of anatomy in Scotland since the early 18th century. This was due to the necessity for medical students to learn anatomy by attending dissections of human subjects, which was frustrated by the very limited allowance of dead bodies - for example the corpses of executed criminals - granted by the government, which controlled the supply

[more](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mortsafe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mortsafes, placed over graves to deter grave robbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump may not fully understand North Koreas nuclear program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original study](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep36652) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have found a way to make memory chips perform computing tasks, which is traditionally done by computer processors. This means data could be processed in the same spot where it is stored, leading to much faster and thinner computers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A surprising factor in the extinction of the dinosaurs may have been how long their eggs took to hatch--sometimes nearly six months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As self-evident as it may be, Trump operates in a world in which someones worth (whether it is Schumer or Ryan or Russian President Vladimir Putin) is a direct reflection of whether he is saying nice things about Trump. This may be one reason he relies so heavily on his children; they know better than to insult him or to challenge him in ways that prompt him to lash out. (They are, in a word, enablers.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps inability to tolerate critics may be his biggest problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's some type of [chimaera](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chimaera) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep sea horror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guinea pigs jumping over lava </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for clearing that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the feces of Donald Trump reveal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romesh Ram Gour, from Srimongol in the countys north-east Sylhet region, has become a local legend as the inventor of a multi-layer tea.

For him, its not about the combination of different temperatures, but different colours and flavours. He manages to get seven of them (sometimes even 10) in one glass (around 1), all lining up like a dusky rainbow. Each sip delivers a different taste, from syrupy sweet to spicy cloves.

[source](https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/aug/28/sylhet-bangladesh-seven-layer-tea-nikantha-tea-cabins) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 layer tea in Bangladesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Books organized according to the color spectrum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL modern sports betting originated in 19th century competitive walking, called pedestrianism. Pedestrianism started when English aristocracy would match their servants against each other in walking contests and bet heavily on the outcome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original research](http://www.yossiyovel.com/images/PDF-Files/Prat%20Taub%20Yovel%202016.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have learned that a lot of bat squeaks are actually them bickering with each other over things like food, sleep, and mating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy to seek to track down and deport migrants with no right to stay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tweets to 'Enemies' as World Leaders Share New Year's Messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the bling, anonymous gilder!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China has promised to close down its domestic ivory trade completely by the end of 2017, a decision that offers real hope to curb a poaching crisis that is wiping out tens of thousands of elephants across Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omo isn't albino; she has a genetic condition called leucism... Her skin cells dont produce pigmentation, but soft tissues, such as her dark eyes, do.

[more](http://news.nationalgeographic.com/2016/01/160126-giraffes-white-tanzania-animals-science/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pine marten surveys the world from the safety of his tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare white giraffe in Tanzania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haserot Angel, Lakeview Cemetery, Cleveland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, that's classified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rock balance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mnuchin led a consortium of investors that purchased the troubled bank IndyMac from the federal government in 2009, acquiring a $13.9 billion portfolio of some of the nations shoddiest loans for about $1.6 billion. Tara Bradshaw, a spokeswoman for Mnuchin, said about 178,000 loans were already in the foreclosure process when he took over the bank and renamed it OneWest. Bradshaw said he oversaw 101,000 mortgage modification offers, some of which forgave part of borrowers' principal balance. Mnuchin sold OneWest to CIT Group in 2015 for more than double what he paid for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats are already building a case against Trumps pick to lead Treasury Department </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lightning strikes over North Africa and Turkey shot from the International Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lightning strikes over North Africa and Turkey shot from the International Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroin surpasses painkillers as the leading cause of overdose deaths </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber driver saves 16-year-old girl from sex trafficking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber driver saves 16-year-old girl from sex trafficking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After noticing the birds in Michigan were far different than those in her native Germany, Lisa M. Ca., an amateur photographer, began photographing them with her DSLR. In an attempt to find more creative ways to capture the variety of species that flew through her backyard, Lisa purchased the Bird Photo Booth 2.0. The device uses a motion detector to snap its shutter, capturing birds with a macro lens at ten images per second.

[more](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2016/12/close-up-portraits-of-birds/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue jay trips camera's motion detector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point taken and upvoted accordingly. But   *Lion's* in your comment should also not have an external ear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write yourself a sticky note to tell me later and I'll remind you to pm that guy with a link next month when the gold runs out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, has that username worked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice cave near Mutnovsky Volcano, Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A seal eating an octopus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morbid creation, Sarah Sitkin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vK2t27FNJmU feature=youtu.be) her appearance on Stephen Colbert's show last January.  

Colbert referred to her as a "space archaeologist wizard genius."

She also won the 2016 TED Prize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that, by examining high-resolution satellite imagery with algorithms developed via trial-and-error, Sarah Parcak and her team have discovered 17 pyramids, 1,000 tombs, and over 3,100 settlements in Egypt alone. She now wants to crowdsource "space archaeology" to prevent looting of ancient sites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 12:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The voters have spoken on marijuana. Trump ought to listen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [link](http://www.nature.com/nmeth/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nmeth.4121.html) to original research </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have found a way to track the types of RNA that control embryonic development in living animals, which might lead to a greater understanding of the whole process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skull of a person afflicted with yaws, a chronic disfiguring infectious childhood disease affecting skin, bone, and cartilage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's Everything the President-Elect Threw a Twitter Tantrum About Over Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing with his food--orca hurls sea turtle into the air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 16:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> photo by the incomparable [Clark Little](http://www.npr.org/sections/13.7/2014/07/17/332211283/ocean-waves-as-you-have-never-seen-them-before) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaiian wave at sunset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst person ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Sarah Bishop was attacked by British soldiers during the Revolutionary War and fled to a cave in the NY woods. She lived isolated in the cave until 1809 when, during the winter, she was discovered standing upright and dead, feet frozen into the boggy ground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Nobel Laureate Explains How Trump Could Nuke the Economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Narwhal coming atcha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science professor is obsessed with Lord of the Rings and is also kind of a dick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice I avoided using the word "perfectly" 

Edit: apparently I should have also avoided the word "round" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This extremely round rock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [link](http://www.nature.com/neuro/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nn.4468.html) to original research </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have found that emotional hangovers, physiological and internal brain states that persist for long periods of time after the emotional events have ended, can influence how we attend to and remember future experiences. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creepy marble death statue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump repeating some behaviors he criticized in Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newborn pygmy hippo chomps some veg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 00:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> orange peeler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police union demands Amazon to remove 'Bulletproof Black Lives Matter' shirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's cabinet reminds me of that [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S6V0S1m5a7U) of the redneck who blew his leg off by shooting at a lawn mower packed with explosives.  It makes for a great, destructive show, but in the end all it does is fuck you up for years to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps wrecking crew: A cabinet of zealots who yearn to destroy their own agencies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's Hot-and-Cold Bromance With Vladimir Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby anteater </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA satellite photo of first snow in the Sahara in 40 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarah Sitkin sculpture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Line of ballerinas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Lottery Security Chief Charged With Rigging Wisconsin Jackpot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China has tried to stay positive with Trump. But it calls his trade chief pick no laughing matter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL by eating herbivores with seeds in their stomachs and then leaving scat across a large range, cougars are able to plant around 94,000 plants a year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pangolin curled up into a ball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J.K. Rowling Reveals She Has New Books on the Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers set new record for heat-resistant materials. Hafnium carbide can withstand temperatures of nearly 4000C and could pave the way for both materials to be used in ever more extreme environments, such as in heat resistant shielding for the next generation of hypersonic space vehicles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graffiti art in Greece by Achilles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faucet releases water in a swirling pattern, reduces usage by 15% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golden eagle attempts to carry away deer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How conservatives will be forced to fall in line behind Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evenly spaced pine trees in Tuscany, Italy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> photo credit [to Mike Eisenberg](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2016/07/a-double-rainbow-over-chicago/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Double rainbow over Chicago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Russian fisherman has been posting pictures of all the terrifying stuff he hauls up in nets from the depths below.  You can check out some of his other finds [here](http://www.sciencealert.com/this-deep-sea-fisherman-has-been-posting-his-finds-on-twitter-and-it-s-legit-terrifying) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemur is very excited about a pear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 15:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frilled shark from the Arctic deep sea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 15:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsweek reporter asks Twitter for ID of Trump supporter he says caused seizure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original research](http://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-98221631286-6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demand for cellphones and computers threatens ghostly octopod known as Casper as deep sea mining for manganese removes sponges to which they attach their eggs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel just announced it will take in wounded civilians from Aleppo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who fear Trump arent weak. Theyre being reasonable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
