<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Kaspersky [may well be Russian goverment spywire.](https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2015-03-19/cybersecurity-kaspersky-has-close-ties-to-russian-spies)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a judge. He's a giant ass hole wearing robes

Give it a rest. He's conservative and that seat should by rights be Garlands, but [he absolutely is a judge, and a pretty good one at that.](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/31/opinion/why-liberals-should-back-neil-gorsuch.html)

Pretending nobody more conservative than Kennedy can be "a judge" just makes you look foolish and snobby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to turn on subtitles for Spanish dialogue to be subbed into English (and for that matter, there is no option to sub only English dialogue into Spanish either.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not an actual competition. Wrestling is scripted. Obviously.

Yes, people are playing roles, and the champion is the top star who is trusted to close the show and represent the brand. Sure, in principle that role could be given to anybody, in the same way that the role of Hamlet or Sweeney Todd could be given to any actor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Actually they do. They hand them out to whomever the boardroom says "this is who gets it." 

Whoever "the boardroom" thinks can carry the brand and put on main event matches. Not "anybody."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yes and no. It's a prop, but its also symbolizes excellence in pro wrestling performance. They don't just hand them out to anybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what? Why would people need to be stupid as hell to think a wrestling championship is prestigious and that its holder ought to treat it respectfully?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ok then maybe act like it, do your job and take responsibility for it?

Has he not been doing his job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, a lot of people are stupid as hell, since it's not a real competition. 

Why? Game of Thrones isn't real either, but I think people would be a little upset if Peter Dinklage busted a nut all over his Emmy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bah, surely it's the height of respect to spread your seed across the symbol of the honour bestowed unto you.

I suppose, but it was Paige's championship, not Maddox's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Shane hasn't had a good match since he came back. 

He totally brought it in the Survivor Series match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna come clean and clarify that I have not played Gone Home. I accidentally got spoiler-ed while reading Gamespot's games-of-the-year coverage. I did, however, play and love Dear Esther.

I think Dear Esther did push the envelope significantly. While you are right - environmental storytelling certainly isn't new and might have peaked with Half-Life 2, Metroid Prime, and Shadow of the Colossus in the Gamecube/PS2 era - motivating exploration with subtle storytelling rather than mechanical rewards was a bold decision in 2012.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  OK, 'at all' is a bit harsh; but definitely I think that the likes of Gone Home are pretty superficial as games, **they don't engage much with the potential of games as a medium** or with the cultural mainstream of game mechanics. It seemed like they got the attention and the credence as 'art games' they did mainly because they dealt with "artsy" themes; I think Yoko Taro (or Papers Please) are more genuine in that respect.

I don't really understand this type of thinking at all. I don't think there's any reason to cling to the mainstream of game mechanics when there's no need to. 

Obviously, work like Dear Esther, Gone Home, Everyone's Gone to the Rapture, etc, do something - a lot of people like them, quite a lot, and they wouldn't work as movies, novels, or paintings. Why do they have to justify themselves with more gameplay? 

If anything, I think Gone Home or Dear Esther utilize  the medium better than a number of cinematic shooter or action/adventure wannabe movies with some superficial gameplay tacked on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm OK with it as long as they aren't shoehorned into wrestler's promos. Announcers and corporate people being corporate just helps kayfabe in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... defeats the strongest booked guy today after just getting off a couch...

Just getting off a couch in better shape than most of the roster?

 ...and then gets a world title shot for no real reason...

Because he just squashed the strongest-booked guy today?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Weary Defenders Face Fresh Worries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A (possibly worked) knee injury isn't as lifestyle-threatening as multiple concussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has been accused by many people of assaulting and pimping out wrestlers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alt-right jersey, if you will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch her Takeover matches with Sasha and you will understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $95,000 in *spending* per employee, not salary, correct?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Perkins is just jobbing now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, can Brooklyn please get over itself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rolling Stones   Muddy Waters - Mannish Boy (Live) [Blues] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least we don't have to wear high heels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Madoff was sentenced to one hundred and fifty years in prison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> F.B.I. Is Investigating Trump's Russia Ties, Comey Confirms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> vs Punk and vs Reigns + Rollins were great, but those are all that come to mind for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The languages and names are similar, and they've also been driven out of their ancestral homeland.](http://www.timesofisrael.com/are-tolkiens-dwarves-an-allegory-for-the-jews/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well i like being weird :p if i was normal i would be boring

I fucking hate this condescending attitude. I mean yeah, be yourself, but don't rag on others for being "too normal." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony's "Playstation" is a pun on "Workstation" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not being a precious unique snowflake doesn't mean you're automatically a horrible person.

I suppose not. But [engaging in ethnic clensing](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trail_of_Tears#Landmarks_and_references) does.

 Obama killed more people than Jackson yet I'm sure you view him as the next Dalai Lama

If you are referring to the drone program:

a) Probably not - drone strikes are estimated to have killed [about 2,000 millitants and up to several hundred civilians,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Civilian_casualties_from_U.S._drone_strikes) while it is generally accepted that around [four thousand Cherokee](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trail_of_Tears#Cherokee_forced_relocation) alone died in the forced relocations.

b) There is a huge fucking difference between extrajudicial attacks on militants and fucking ethnic cleansing.

c) No, I don't view him as the Dali Lama. I view him as a generally good president, unlike Cheeto Benito.

d) I thought you denizens of the Drumpfster Fire didn't care about Muslims anyways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all well and good, but we were talking about Andrew Jackson. It's probably worth clarifying that he was a horrible person.

Nobody was shitting on the US or anything - theFX was just clarifying that Jackson was a bully and a racist (even for the times.)  I think that it is important to remember this and to not glamorize him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Seeks Proposals for "Physically Imposing" Wall With Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There were plenty of legitimate reasons to dislike her.

True, but she lost because she was a woman and Trump was a man. A man with her credentials would have won, and a woman with Trump's rap sheet would have lost. Period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seth **Freakin'** Rollins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just has PTSD from when he shook Trudeau's hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a crummy old laptop, a Steam controller, and hook the laptop up to your TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. "The Devastation Continues" looks awesome though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why you think she's joking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slouches bigly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mandatory: you really should get a subscription. It's cheap, especially if you have Amazon Prime and we need all the good journalism we can get. That being said... 

**Perspective | The center cannot hold in the Trump White House**

By Daniel W. Drezner

(Daniel W. Drezner is a professor of international politics at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University and a regular contributor to PostEverything)

The hard-working staff here at Spoiler Alerts was working hard in the federal government during the changeover between the Clinton and Bush 43 administrations. Observing that transition was a fascinating anthropological moment.

It would be safe to say that most of the Bush appointees came in thinking that the Clinton administration had screwed up 90 percent of policy and that the permanent bureaucracy was allied against them. Eventually, however, most of them learned two basic facts. First, on 90 percent of policy, the status quo was the status quo for a very good political or strategic reason. Second, the permanent bureaucracy was staffed with very smart people who would improve the implementation of any sensible policy shift if they were properly consulted. Different appointees took different lengths of time to reach these conclusions, but they usually got there.

And now we come to the mind-set of Trump administration appointees. Earlier this week we had Kellyanne Conway suggest that the Obama administration could have been monitoring Trump Tower via the microwave oven. Conway isnt alone in this kind of conspiracy theorizing among Trump administration appointees. If this Politico story by Alex Isenstadt and Kenneth Vogel is any guide, theyve actually become more, not less paranoid during their short time in power:

A culture of paranoia is consuming the Trump administration, with staffers increasingly preoccupied with perceived enemies  inside their own government.

In interviews, nearly a dozen White House aides and federal agency staffers described a litany of suspicions: that rival factions in the administration are trying to embarrass them, that civil servants opposed to President Donald Trump are trying to undermine him, and even that a deep state of career military and intelligence officials is out to destroy them 

Its an environment of fear that has hamstrung the routine functioning of the executive branch. Senior advisers are spending much of their time trying to protect turf, key positions have remained vacant due to a reluctance to hire people deemed insufficiently loyal, and Trumps ambitious agenda has been eclipsed by headlines surrounding his unproven claim that former President Barack Obama tapped his phone lines at Trump Tower during the 2016 campaign.

One senior administration aide, who like most others interviewed for this story spoke on the condition of anonymity, said the degree of suspicion had created a toxicity that is unsustainable.

That last word is the key one. The effect of this degree of paranoia among political staffers is debilitating to any kind of successful policy implementation. To put it bluntly, they cant rely on experts to check their work. The first attempt at an immigration ban highlighted the effects of such a narrow policy shop: badly drafted executive orders, confusing implementation, and eventually, rejection by the judicial branch. The Justice Department had to rely on a single lawyer to make the case for the revised immigration ban in court cases in Maryland and Hawaii.

The Trump White House could respond to this in one of a few ways. First, they could persist in their paranoia. This would lead to a narrow coterie of officials trying to run the government amid massive leaking and bureaucratic resistance. If this is their standard operating procedure, theyre going to screw up repeatedly. This will lead to more bad press, which will lad to more leaks trying to shift the blame to others, which will only increase the paranoia further. As feedback loops go, its a really bad one.Eventually, however, through attrition, learning, and staffing up, they will approach basic competency.

Second, they could try to outsource any significant policy plans to Congress and let them draft the legislation. Of course, if the American Health Care Act is any guide, it wont be terribly popular either.

Third, they can learn that the bureaucracy isnt necessarily their enemy and stop acting all paranoid. The dirty truth, however, is that power is so balkanized in the Trump administration that even the Trump appointees dont trust each other. Given the personnel machinations going on right now, many Trump staffers have good reasons to be fearful.

My money is on paranoia winning the day. Which means we are in for at least a year of crazy policymaking, following by one of two things: mass resignations, or a truly America First bureaucracy.

Buckle up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capitol Hill Republicans not on board with Trump budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The center cannot hold in the Trump White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way is she more over than Dean or Becky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Every single women on the roster is more talented than her. Her promos are cringey and unnatural and she can barely wrestle.

I absolutely do not like her but if you think she "can barely wrestle" you haven't been watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great... for communist sympathizers like you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  . In my opinon, the radical left is in some serious need of good PR people. I feel the same way about terms like 'Micro-aggression' and 'safe space'. 

When the left or center comes up with catchy terms it just gets coopted by right-wing types. (See: Fake News, SJW, Identity Politics...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are hella sensationalist titles for six hours of gameplay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's just the way it goes - companies that actively participate in being part of the hype machine for something generally feel like they're too invested to not enjoy it.

It think it's less that and more reviewers trying to be "objective" and rate games based on production values rather than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Woah now, I know it sounds childish as hell but if true that kinda makes me think everything this guy says is irrelevant.


But... but... I didn't really like TW3 and I thought ME3's ending was OK. 

:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear I heard both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also cheered Shane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from shitting all over AA vs the Usos that AJ/Shane segment was sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corbin needs a win nearly as bad as Wyatt does though (although him getting one over Ambrose three weeks straight now suggests he will probably lose.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That man knows how to take a bump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not a shock to me... 

Well, if it isn't shocking to you, why do you need to be so damn rude about it? 

 ...but this is a majority english subreddit with majority english speakers.

Yes. A majority of native **E**nglish speakers. Not **only** native **E**nglish speakers. Their comment was absolutely legible, and they made a mistake that is very common with users who are either on mobile or non-native **E**nglish speakers - neither of which are something to be ashamed about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People will inevitably downvote because anything that's positive about Alexa and how talented she is always gets shit on thanks to the anti-Bliss circlejerk on this sub but as a fan of silent movies, I really fucking appreciate how truly great she is at putting across her inner thoughts without having to say a word.

What "anti-Bliss circlejerk?" The entire sub agrees with you about her acting - she just also got a bit overexposed and was pretty green in-ring at the beginning of her push.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Government can make laws to force Pharma to lower prices. Insurance can't. The problem is Gov has no incentive to do that, but if Gov is footing the bill they are suddenly incentivized to provide cheaper drugs. Gov can threaten to import drugs from Canada/India as well.

You seem to be assuming that the government has no incentive to reduce the burden on citizens (though deductibles or higher cost to insurence companies and therefore higher premiums,) which is strange. The government isn't some racket that only cares about its bottom line. 

Furthermore, legislating price limits on drugs may well dis-incentivize new drug research, which is very expensive. Material costs of drugs are a very small fraction of pharmaceutical companies' expenses - the overwhelming majority is research, marketing, and education. 

A progressive tax would be much cheaper than insurance on almost every person aside from the uber rich. The main reasons is that every person would be signed automatically, and you'd cut out the middle man of insurance.

Assuming this tax can be effectively administered, this is only more efficient if the government can do a good job of administering health care. It works (reasonably) well in Canada, which has a long tradition of public health care. The (well-regulated) private sector works reasonably well in Switzerland. The middleman isn't just twiddling his thumbs here. 

 Again this is just another product of the US system. Because the Canadian government foots the bill for health care, we are incentivized to attack health care drains like obesity and smoking, as it is in the government's best interest. The US on the other hand has no such incentive and would rather pander to the McDonalds, and Coca Colas, and Marlboro's.

Again, if you assume the government doesn't care about its citizens well-being (or if you must be extremely cynical, the loss of tax base and GDP to preventable illness.) Under a private insurance system the citizens are incentivized directly to take good care of the health.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Trips couldn't get heel heat against Roman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  chattle

"Chattel" means property, especially slaves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the champ coming out first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Like come on now and I spouse to really look at big show like he's strong when he's been a jobber for 4 years now

... well he is literally much stronger now. That's got to help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ares is fucking great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hell is Roid Body Mahal having a competitive match with Roman Reigns?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could not care any less about the New Day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A moldy ham sandwich would be better than Gary Bettman. 

Bernie Madoff would be better than Gary Bettman. 

Donald Trump would... actually be worse than Gary Bettman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gave it up voluntarily to face Y2J at Mania.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if racist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Correlation does not imply causation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Islam isn't a race, ding dong, it's a religion. A violent, subhuman, disgusting religion. But a religion.](https://www.reddit.com/r/thewalkingdead/comments/5z2hi5/the_walking_dead_s07e13_bury_me_here_post_episode/dev3ewy/)

0_0

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Representation" calls for changing the story and characters based on things that do not matter to the plot. This is ALWAYS a bad thing.

Somebody should show this guy the Expanse. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong about climbing being a full-body workout (especially good for core and forearms) but it's not a replacement for rows or pulls. That's like saying running or basketball is a replacement for squats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(

I was hoping for an Orton-Lesnar champion-vs-champion rematch at Summerslam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesnar doesn't cheat either and he has heel heat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deadlifts once or twice a week, chin-ups and/or pull-ups 3-4 times a week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sasha then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He said he's doing rock climbing. Plenty of vertical pull and a lot of horizontal work

Rock climbing with correct form actually doesn't involve that much vertical pulling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair that spot was super challenging and a bit dangerous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice bait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah, I think AJ is a dead cert to go to RAW because they'll need top heels post-Mania (especially now that Jericho's face again) and he's basically one of the top 3 full-time guys in the company right now.

It makes sense to split up AJ and Dean, but RAW still has KO and Joe. Smackdown's tag team  division needs serious help and the both women's divisions need a shakeup. Maybe something like Roman, Cesaro   Sheamus, and Charlotte for AJ, Heath Slater   Rhyno, and Mickie James? I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the AV Club giving Megadeth's latest a D for being mindbogglingly Islamophobic. That was a shitshow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More upper back arch, more mental focus on "straight up" than "no flared elbows," and one set of behind-head shoulder press, plus lots of chest and shoulder stretches afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing in the article suggests they were prostitutes or anybody fought back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  30 is pretty bad, 23-26 is likely to be the upper limits of what they'll consider a passing running time. 

Thirty is bad for a runner, but reasonably healthy. I agree that ~24 is probably a passing time - that would put you on pace to pass the US Army Ranger 2 and 5 mile runs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1.5 million people in the US just in 2015 lost their freedom

1.5 million **were arrested.** As of 2016, only [about 40,000](http://www.rollingstone.com/culture/lists/top-10-marijuana-myths-and-facts-20120822/myth-prisons-are-full-of-people-in-for-marijuana-possession-19691231) people in the US were serving time for marijuana-related charges, mostly for distribution. About half of which were serving time for non-drug offences as well.

  Is it?

Yes, it is. Comparing overzealous and misguided drug law enforcement to **the attempted extermination of an entire ethnic group** is tasteless and offensive. Comparing the illegal distribution of nearly-harmless but banned substances for personal profit to rescuing members of a persecuted minority from extermination is tasteless and offensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They robbed two groups of people, both of which included a trans individual.

Since only about .3% of the US population is openly trans, and they were charged with a hate crime, I'm going to assume these were targeted until there's more information.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a big fucking difference between Schindler risking his life to save a persecuted minority and illegally distributing a controlled substance for profit.

Also, comparing the drug war to the Holocaust is beyond disingenuous.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally fixed my overhead press form and it changed everything. My shoulders and back feel so much better and the gains are coming everywhere! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are seriously comparing helping people get high to fucking Oscar Schindler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think Comey just knows if he tries shit on Clinton, he's gonna "mysteriously commit suicide".

Oh, so *that's* why he didn't tell Congress he found a bunch more dirt on Clinton right before the election! It makes sense now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They robbed multiple trans people the same night. It sounds like these were targeted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dean Ambrose's jacket](http://www.goliath.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sd1121dig1.jpg)

[Demon Finn Balor](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CqbbvjlVUAA_iKg.jpg), especially as [Jack the Ripper](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/m_lo808Ruoc/maxresdefault.jpg)

[Red AJ](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/6f/36/ca/6f36ca0e925ec5ddbbace9d9b27f5805.jpg)

[Becky Lynch with a coat](https://wrestlingrumors.net/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Becky-LYnch.jpg)

Any of [Charlotte's](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CrmOd9QUMAAwCbw.jpg) [robes](https://static.sportskeeda.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/charlottewrestlemania32-1460051464-800.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kidding. He looked like the world's stinkiest neckbeard for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't think of a kayfabe reason for them not to do a triple threat match. Outside of kayfabe, it's because they must be really into the idea of AJ vs Shane. I cannot for the life of me imagine why.

Presumably the kayfabe reason is because it's unfair to Bray - he gets his house burned down, and then has to face two people instead of just one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brock Lesnar vs Kurt Angle, WWE Championship (WM19)

Hollywood Hogan vs the Rock (WM18)

Shawn Michaels vs Rick Flair (WM24)

John Cena vs the Big Show,  US Championship (WM20)

CM Punk vs the Undertaker (WM29)

Charlotte Flair vs. Sasha Banks vs. Becky Lynch - WWE Women's Championship (WM32)

Jeff   Matt Hardy vs Edge and Christian vs The Dudley Boyz, Tag Tag Team Championship (WM17)

Randy Savage vs Ricky Steamboat- Intercontinental Championship (WM3)

Triple H vs Danial Bryan (WM30) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah how dare he be comfortable with his body?

Upvote...

 Do the gene pool a favor and walk into traffic.

... downvote :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your numbers for **"Death penalty for leaving Islam?"** are false - you neglected to include that these were not the percentages of all Muslims, only those who believed in applying Sharia law. This was a bald-faced lie. You also neglected to mention that a significant fraction of those surveyed who believed in Sharia law only believed in imposing it on Muslims. The survey also made no general claims about what "a majority" of Muslims believed - you are inferring from what a majority of in those surveyed did. You are extrapolating broad conclusions from a few regional data points to fit your agenda.

Also, focusing your most incorrect or misleading numbers in your argument is **not** cherry-picking. Contrary to your apparent belief, I was not arguing that no Muslims hold extreme or problematic views, I was simply noting that you were being highly misleading.

Also, noting that you are a liar is not fallacious ad hominum, since that was the premise of my argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nearly 20% of US women have been sexually assaulted,](http://www.nytimes.com/2011/12/15/health/nearly-1-in-5-women-in-us-survey-report-sexual-assault.html) and apparently [most rapists are serial offenders](http://www.slate.com/blogs/xx_factor/2014/05/01/campus_sexual_assault_statistics_so_many_victims_but_not_as_many_predators.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch him demand his title rematch and get squashed by Goldberg in thirty seconds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta lot of nerve calling me deceptive when you have been straight-up lying, buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I think OP was pretty clear. Not an assumption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did I get wrong exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communist Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are badly misrepresenting your source.

[Percentage of Muslims who believe Sharia should be the 'law of the land'](http://assets.pewresearch.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2013/04/gsi2-chp1-3.png)

[Percentage **of the above** Muslims who support the death penalty for apostasy**](http://assets.pewresearch.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2013/04/gsi2-chp1-9.png)

(That's 46% of 29% = 13% for Lebanon, for example.)

And just for some more context, [Percentage of Muslims who believe Sharia should be the 'law of the land' Muslims who believe Sharia should apply **to both Muslims and non-Muslims**](http://assets.pewresearch.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2013/04/gsi2-chp1-5.png)

(Again, that's 50% of 72% = 36% for Indonesia.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why are batteries in such high demand? Are the resources to make them in low supply?

While manufacturing does contribute significant overhead, the bulk of the cost [is raw materials.](https://qnovo.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Batterycost.png) Cobalt, in particular, is expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I bet $250 she would win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is probably for the better. Who are most likely to gain or lose sales based on Steam review score? Indie games. And these games are more susceptible to 

a) Inflated scores around release due to sketchy gifted "review copies"

b) Getting poor reviews from outside their target demographic via inclusion in bundles, and

c) Getting review-bombed during free weekends due to GG/SJWism/whatever controversy of the week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree in principle, but (on Steam) a totally non-functional game is getting refunded so I don't think this case is important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... and suddenly I feel much less stupid for putting $250 on Hillary Clinton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea why the WWE let him keep it. It requires a ton of set-up, is legitimately dangerous, and is obviously just forcing his opponent to do a spread-eagle belly flop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roman's Spear is great, he just needs to lose the Superman Punch and get a power move as a super finisher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If he called the cops, he'd be the one getting arrested lol [+422] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy must be trolling. Noway somebody would sincerely brag about their imaginary Master's degree and cite Chomsky (lol!) in defense of the Alt-Right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radioactive Boars in Fukushima Thwart Residents' Plans to Return Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect Roman could match heel Shawn on the mic if he was allowed to cut loose as a heel too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've never liked the use of the word. Yeah, I think I'm entitled to receive what I want when I pay for it, or refund it. 

I understand this argument to a point when it comes to basic functionality, but I don't think you are entitled to a game you *like.* You don't get to return a movie just because you don't enjoy it. 

There should also be a basic understanding that games developed by small teams are simply going to have issues at launch, games that sell terribly aren't going to receive a lot of ongoing support, and that publishers are allowed to be a bit misleading in their marketing (in a "Cumberbatch Isn't Kahn" sort of way.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil Young - Rockin' in the Free World (Acoustic) [Rock/Protest] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's an article on one outfit](https://www.theguardian.com/world/2015/jun/24/russian-troll-factory-sued-underpayment-labour-violations-vladimir-putin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two decent safety racks and one that's arguably safe enough for overhead press. The floor is uneven and it has very tiny pins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
