<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha the coconut one is obviously not the same as this one! One of my biggest pet peeves! Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to google to get the reference haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it's a pastry board :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly doubt it :(. The almond flour is it a critical component to macarons. There might possibly be a substitute and an online search could answer that. Sorry for not knowing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol so my goal by the time I get my PhD is to be instafamous, so that companies can send me free reagents like matcha haha. But this means I need a consistent posting for followers. I've also decided to just cross post on reddit because affirmation is always nice lol. Plus, baking works even when experiments don't :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just macaron batters.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. No slices. Just macaron batter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no. They go to my labmates haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I've been trying to be consistent for ig, where I cross post lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's for the curd so it thickens up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gel food coloring. Americolor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. So my fruit placement dates back to last October when I started and was trying to figure out how to take pics of some strawberry macarons I made. I put some strawberries on the left and liked how they looked and ever since then, I placed a fruit on the left side or left corner for my fruit macaron pics. It photographs well and gives people a nice reference (which is helpful for things like weird fruits like quince, rambutan, and dalandan) :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind? I also bought some cara cara that I'm wanting to use. I'm excited. haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/republican4,  
Here's the recipe I used for these. Note, I changed the amount of powdered sugar and granulated sugar from my normal protocol, but it still worked out. I also scaled up slightly so that I could have enough batter for different colors (I normally only use 35 g egg white = 1 egg white). This is the French method.   
 nbsp;  
**Macaron Shells**  
For about 10 2 inch macarons:  
68 g almond flour (sift, no big almond pieces)  
62 g powdered sugar  
50 g egg whites (room temp)  
40 g granulated sugar  
 nbsp;  
1. Oven to 300F (or 325F, see below). Measure out and sift your powdered sugar and almond flour. Whisk together and set aside. *Note:* For these, I decided to throw the almond flour and powdered sugar into a food processor to make it extra fine before sifting in hopes it would be easy to manipulate when I piped out different colors.  
2. Make your meringue. Beat/ whisk your egg whites until frothy and start to incorporate the granulated sugar a bit a time. Beat until stiff peaks. Don't add any food coloring yet.       
3*a*. To use different colors and not make more batter, first incorporate the dry ingredients into the meringue so that it is just barely mixed together.   
*b*. Split the batter into roughly 1/3 for orange, 1/3 for white (no food coloring or maybe a smidge of yellow), 2/9 for dark red, and 1/9 for slightly lighter red.   
*c*. Once batter is separated, add food coloring and folded until the right consistency. You should look up macaronage (folding of ingredients) on Youtube if you dont know how already.  
 nbsp;  
In summary: Fold by basically scraping along the edge of the bowl and then pressing down along the center in sort of a J shape. Do this until you have a lava like consistency, where you can pick up your spatula and the batter will drop down in a ribbon. My test is to bang the bowl on the table and see if the ribbon that just fell incorporates back into the main blobif it does, its ready. Otherwise, I do a few more folds.   
 nbsp;  
*d*.  Put into piping bags. Normal macaron tips for the white and orange but use tiny tips for the dark red and red. You'll need to draw out the section shape.   
4. Pipe out your macarons. I use a silpat (would highly recommend).  
*a*. First with the orange batter, hold the tip perpendicularly at about a half inch above the silpat and pipe out an amount slightly bigger than the tip (it should spread horizontally if you don't move your tip).  
*b*. Then using the white batter, place the tip on the center and pipe out an amount to make a size of a normal macaron.  
*c*. Using the dark red batter, pipe out section shapes, but leaving a white center (8 sections ended up being the optimal amount for me).  
*d*. Use the lighter red to add drops along those darker red sections.  
*e*. With a toothpick, adjust the shapes of the sections so that the white batter isn't too thick at any point.  
*f*. Add a drop of white in the center and use a toothpick to move along the white that separates sections.  
5. Rap the baking sheet against the table a few times.  Pop any air bubbles with a toothpick and swirl the toothpick around a bit to have that hole close up.  
6. I hate waiting for the shells to dry, so I cheat and actually put the oven temp at 325. Then I open the oven and hold the tray in the oven, rotating it every 10 seconds or so for about a minute. Then again for another 30 seconds. This quickly dries out the shells and makes a skin :p.  
You want to be able to touch the shell and have it not be sticky. Then I drop down the oven temp back to 300 (its about this low anyways since the door has been open.).  
6. Bake for 15-20 minutes.  
 nbsp;  
**Blood Orange Curd/ Ganache Hybrid**  
1 blood orange, juiced       
5 g corn starch  
50 g granulated sugar  
1 egg yolk  
50 g white chocolate  
40 g heavy cream   
 nbsp;  
1. Juice blood orange and strain. Heat up and reduce so it's not as liquidy.  
2. Beat the egg yolk and add sugar and sifted corn starch, and lemon juice. Whisk well.  
3. While whisking, slowly add the heated up blood orange juice onto the egg/sugar/cornstarch. You're tempering the egg to prevent it from scrambling. Once it's fully incorporated, add the mixture back into the saucepan and stir constantly on medium. Eventually, it'll start to thicken. I usually thicken until it's a nice paste. [I just got a hand blender, so I now turn that on and blend the mixture while it's heating up to make it super smooth. Not required though.]   
4. Take off the heat and transfer to a bowl (I sieved it to get rid of corn starch clumps.)  
5. Add cream to the pot used for the curd and reduce significantly.  
6. Add white chocolate over a double boiler and melt the chocolate until there are only a few chips that are unmelted. Add the cream to make a ganache.  
7.  Stir in the ganache into the curd and chill. I transfer to a piping bag and chill it in the fridge or freezer for a short while to firm up before piping onto my macaron shells.  
8. Pipe the filling onto the shells and assemble macarons.  
9. Let the macarons rest in an airtight container in the fridge overnight for optimal chewiness!    
 nbsp;  
*Additional thoughts:*  
If this is confusing, let me know and I can try to clarify.  
Gluck!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wet on wet batter will fall into itself. If you want to do it directly on top of another, you need to let it dry enough first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used different colored macaron batters. I had previously added different colored dots to the edges and pulled them in with a toothpick to make sort of slice looking things. With that in mind, I knew I could something similar for these for the segments and refine it a little.  
For general composition, about a week ago, I thought about how I could get the edges to be orange. I knew the batter spreads outward when you hold the tip at a fixed height above the silpat, so I figured if you piped one color first, then added another to the center, it would push the first color outward. Yay it worked!  
I went through some trial and error to figure out if I should do orange, white, red and then add stripes of white or do orange, white then trace out segments and refine with a toothpick. The latter worked better. But in the pic you can sort of see some of the trial and error :p. Another challenge was not knowing what proportion of colors to make. I ended up splitting my batter 1/3 orange, 1/3 dark red, 2/9 white, and 1/9 a lighter red. Obviously, if you make more batter, this isn't an issue, but I'm stingy so I didn't want to make more. I had a lot of leftover dark red and didn't have enough orange. But yes, it also took forever. lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll post it a bit later. I made some changes to my normal go to recipe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. Everytime I see a small thumbnail I think they look real too. :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I showed a labmate this pic and she was like, so what did you make with those blood oranges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a lemon macaron pic a while back and a few people thought they looked like segments. Since then, I wanted to play on that idea with another citrus fruit. Saw blood oranges and knew I wanted to try and it worked yayay :D.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Blood Orange Macarons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Do you mind sharing the recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 10:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you clearly haven't seen amazingly beautiful ones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 10:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big fan of fruit flavors :). Raspberry ones are probably my favorite. And if you make a ganache, the raspberry does an amazing job at cutting through the white chocolate sweetness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the quenelle of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *heavy panting* this looks so good omgah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Initially I thought there was a quenelle of something on top :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this looks so freaking delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, so I'm personally really bad at taste and find it difficult to think of bitter tastes. I've asked several people who ate the cake though, and they say they didn't encounter that taste. But maybe the "tartness" I encountered was actually the bitterness? Though, I'm pretty sure I tasted the same thing when eating the kiwifruit on its own before adding to the whipped cream.  
 nbsp;  
I know kiwifruit is often used on top of whipped cream frosted cakes and I don't believe the bitterness is an issue there. I've been trying to read up on it and it says actinidin also liquifies whipped cream. This definitely wasn't the case even at the local points of contact. But I'm sure actinidin exposed on the surface could act on cream (I can't think of why not).  
 nbsp;   
Now I want to understand actinidin's mechanism of action for digestion of dairy proteins. And maybe how it compares to papain (papaya) and bromelain (pineapple). I'll also perform an experiment with different kiwi-whipped cream incubation times and test for this taste. Yay science. Though, I do wish there was a more quantitative bitter test. (Maybe there is, I should also look into that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, I was being a poor grad student and opted for normal kiwifruits because they were cheaper :p. BUT, I've always wanted to try the golden ones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great tip! I did consider dipping them in a simple syrup, but I was too lazy. haha. Story of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no! Yes, stay away from them! (My mom is allergic as well :o). But thanks so much for your kind words :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4 I trick vegetarians into eating meat. "Oh, this tastes interesting." "...That's the uh, kiwi." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, sounds and looks delicious regardless. Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. Wow, it totally does. Where's the dill when I need it? Tea party anyone? :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, here's the recipe. It's pretty simple to execute.  
**1. Sponge** [makes 1 jelly roll sheet]  
112g cake flour  
1 tsp baking powder  
1/4 tsp salt  
5 large eggs, separated  
156 g granulated sugar  
60 g whole milk  
 nbsp;  
1. Oven at 400F. Line baking sheet with parchment paper or silpat.  
2. Whisk together sifted flour, baking powder, and salt.  
3. In a different, large bowl, whisk egg yolks, sugar, and milk until pale.  
4. Separately, whisk egg whites until medium stiff peaks.  
5. Add dry mixture to wet mixture and fold together. Then slowly fold in the medium stiff egg whites. I usually add 1/3 of the meringue first to make the batter light, then fold in the remaining egg whites.    
6. Pour batter onto the baking sheet and then rap the sheet down a few times to release any big air bubbles.  
7. Bake for 10ish minutes (a toothpick should go in and out cleanly).  
8. Using a knife or something thin, move along the edge of the pan and cake. Remove cake from pan and silpat and let cool.   
 nbsp;  
**2. Stabilized Whipped Cream Frosting:**  
470 g heavy whipping cream  
10 g powdered sugar  
10-20 g powdered sugar (depending on your sweetness preferences)  
5 g corn starch  
 nbsp;  
1. Whenever whipping your own cream, make sure the first thing you do is throw your bowl and whisk attachment into the fridge or freezer. Cold is your best friend.  
2. First make your corn starch paste. Add corn starch, 10g of powdered sugar, and about 100 g of cream and stir in a pot.  
3. Heat over medium, stirring constantly. When it just becomes paste-like (you will see a drastic change in the consistency from very liquidy to a little custard like), take the pan off the heat and continue to mix until smooth. You want to make sure the cream doesn't seize, so don't leave it on the stove. Cool to room temperature.    
3. Take out chilled bowl and whisk and add the second powdered sugar and remainder of the cream. Whisk until soft peaks.  
4. Whisking at a fast speed, add in the paste (make sure it's not hot!), a bit at a time.  
5. Whisk until stiff peaks and corn starch paste is well incorporated.  
 nbsp;  
**Assembly:**  
1. Peel kiwis (I used a spoon, pressed up against the skin to scoop them out). Slice several kiwis into thin rectangles (1ish kiwi per layer).  
2. Slice cake into thirds. Remove any obvious crumbs.  
3. Smooth out a layer of whipped cream on the first slice of cake.  
4. Add the kiwi pieces and press in a stripe like pattern down the length of the cake (or however you like).  
5. Add the next slice and repeat.  
6. Once all layers are assembled, finish off by coating the cake. I go slowly to not get crumbs showing. You can add a small amount then throw it in the fridge. Then add the final amount to cover any crumbs. As a final smoothing out process, I like to use a heated up angled spatula and run it across each side.  
7. Add cut up kiwi to decorate the top.  
8. Once finished frosting, chill the cake in the fridge.  
 nbsp;  
*Final Notes*  
1. Most fruits will taste great in this sort of preparation! The freshness is a great juxtaposition to the heavy whipped cream and light sponge.  
2. You don't have to add the cornstarch paste, normal whipped cream with just heavy cream and powdered sugar will do fine. I use the stabilized so that it holds extra well.  
3. I found that the cake was sweet, but there was a tartness about the kiwis. You could possibly try making a simple syrup and dipping the kiwis in before lying them onto the whipped cream for the layers. I highly doubt this will cause the cake to become overtly sweet.  
4. Gluck and enjoy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/axisential, now I can only think of humans every time I use"kiwi" :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww not a fan of kiwis? They taste so yummy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, are you a kiwi? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound dumb. What does lonza mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, yeah maybe it's that I have too high a gelatin concentratation. I'll try that thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
