<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overwatch: Luke Skywalker - Play of the Game (Death Star) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the saddest death in all of Star Wars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a ton and a few standouts, but every one of the deceased is included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pokemon World Exists in Our World? New Sun and Moon Evidence! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 00:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pokemon World Exists in Our World? New Sun and Moon Evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 15:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, fan theorists!

I put together a video detailing why the Pokemon world is a really messed up version of ours using new evidence from Sun and Moon!  I hope you like it!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rFfQ4NiQ3EA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pokemon World Exists in Our World? New Sun and Moon Evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pokemon World Exists in Our World? New Sun and Moon Evidence says so </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 04:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, no problem at all!  I agree with pretty much everything you said - it is somewhat charming for the first few days because of the nice graphics and WoW inspired gear, but after a while it just sort of wears off.

 Maybe my problem is that things seem more dependent on gear than smart tactics

That's perfectly valid and it's exactly what I felt as well.  there isn't anything really engaging about it - you don't have to carefully time things, there isn't even anything remotely close to a story with legitimate content (which is kinda necessary for an RPG of any sort).  At least if this game had a story and nice lore, I would be more engrossed and it would give me an incentive to actually try to equip my character so that he/she could grind out new and better gear.

 this kinda goes too far in that direction like regular auto-clickers

Agreed and I think that there can be that silver lining between regular auto clickers and mobile rpgs.  I just don't know what that can be, but I'm def looking forward to something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a tweet from the Star Wars twitter page btw, but it was taken off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally did a video on this yesterday lol: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WgdQ7hYjpSA feature=youtu.be

If this is real, I really like this title! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars VIII Title Revealed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "this is all speculation and none of it is actually true so no harm gets done in trying to guess the title"

I understand what you're trying to say though and it makes perfect sense :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's My 2 Cents on Every Issue Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha my body is ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's My 2 Cents on Every Matter Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what about them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Potential Titles for Episode VIII </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 10:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 23:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah that's even cooler!  I'm def subbing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 23:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that, my friend, was simply awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Its So Important to See If There is a Tech Bubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 22:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J.J. Abrams: The mystery box | TED Talk - this is really inspiring IMHO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 20:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Its So Important to See If There is a Tech Bubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why It's So Important to See If There is a Tech Bubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though the recent tech boom has been a boon to many savvy entrepreneurs, is the rapid technological growth leading to a more prosperous future in the really long run?  This is a question many historians ask themselves as they take a look back into history to find out what happened in past economic revolutions.

Im going to go ahead and say it  All the people utilizing the tech boom are partying like its the late 1920s.  They are innovating and pushing technology to its limits by creating new consumer products.  Many technology based companies are financially growing at a rapid pace.  For example, just last July, Uber became valued at $50 billion.  The companys idea is very simple in that it took a commodity that almost everyone uses (a car) and added a new realm of income for users of that commodity via easily accessible technology.  Concepts like Uber pop up all the time and success rides this seemingly never ending train of innovation.  However, unlike all other trains, this one in particular doesnt know if and when it will hit a dead end.  If the utilizers of the tech boom are partying like its the 1920s, 1929 is just around the corner.  Analysts and venture capitalists looking to find the next big company to invest in debate have always debated among themselves as to whether or not the tech boom is actually a tech bubble.  However, if history is to be believed, this overflow of technology as consumer products will inevitably cause a collapse of the technology industry.

As more and more investors place their faith in companies that utilize more advanced technology, there is a great shift in dependency for technology based companies to succeed.  However, if these companies dont succeed, millions of people lose their jobs, a huge chunk of the stock market collapses, investors go bankrupt, and banks lose all their because the companies cant pay back the huge loans that they take when they are declining in sales and have a very little margin profit.  Such a collapse would be caused by companies failing potentially due to overcompetition, something that is happening right now in the status quo.  Overcompetition would increase product variation, which would spread consumer money across many companies.  An example of how this spread would happen is when Apple faced a decrease in control in the smartphone industry when Android phones flooded that industry.  A spread in consumer money due to product variation will decrease potential cash flow to all company participants and that decrease will lead to less revenue for all companies.  The decline in revenue would lead to an inevitable decline in profit and in some companies cases, the profit will be negative.  Those companies would need to take loans from banks to bring themselves back up and to appease the investors who are dependent on those companies to succeed so the investors dont back out.  However, the damage has been done and those companies cant recover.  They cannot repay the bank loans and the banks lose money.  The banks cannot function and they close, which hurts people who are both in and out of the technology sphere.  The result would be a more catastrophic event than the infamous 2008 recession as the companies that failed to compete with bigger companies, investors who placed their faith in those companies, banks who placed their faith in both those investors and those companies, and the common people who place their faith in banks would all fail.

This type of collapse would almost be like a bubble bursting.  The industry keeps getting bigger only to pop due to a large size.  Thus, it is extremely important to everyone that we should find out whether or not a tech bubble is happening so that we can take preventive measures to make sure that no one gets hurt.  To explore this possibility, one must look at the current technology market to see if a bubble is in fact forming and growing.

So there it is: This is why we need to figure out right now if there is a tech bubble.  Im going to delve even deeper into this topic sometime soon, but this is a start.

Please feel free to let me know what you think!  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 04:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahaha what a story, Mark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's free to download right now so feel free to give it a listen :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohit Puvvala - Bad Guy Stereotype [soundtrack, dark, free] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Time Playing Soda Dungeon App </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 12:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 12:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's awesome!  A ton of people did like the game, but I just didn't.  Hope it goes well for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 12:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  buying soda unlocks new classes

Well that's good to know!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Time Playing Soda Dungeon!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 05:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review of EZPZ RPG app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 05:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review/Gameplay of Android game EZPZ RPG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 05:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 04:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that the game will usher in a new era of mobile apps.  I don't think any other mobile application has gotten this much hype.  Due to the lack of true concern for the mobile gaming industry, there really hasn't been a mobile game that can stand up to great console games with wonderful gameplay.  I feel like Pokemon GO will be that game that can easily stand alongside the other main Pokemon games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review of EZPZ RPG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] Let's discuss tonight's episode! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed 100% with everything u said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best scene from Donnie Darko - end cracks me up every time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 01:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's surprising (unless ur joking lol) - I'm curious to see why tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which one is better - Godfather Part 1 or 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 01:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal preference is Part 2 because of the beautiful presentation of the parallel lives between father and son, but I'm curious to see what everyone else thinks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EZPZ RPG is a "game" that literally plays itself, which takes the fun out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 01:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing EZPZ RPG by Reality Squared Games on Android </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Time Playing EZPZ RPG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no problem man... no problem :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol "never tell me the odds!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 22:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i'm not too mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 22:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> credit sink :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poster Series II 25 Packs!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 22:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: Card Trader Poster Series II 25 packs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 22:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My guesses for Potential Star Wars Episode VIII Titles :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My guesses for Episode VIII titles :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got some pretty great kills in this vid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 04:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> finally got to the top 5 today for the first time ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 02:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 01:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the writer of Hannibal comes the show based on an older show that has five other shows, three movie series, one reboot that still exists, and generations of fanbases that make the creators milk this franchise to the core.  But who cares?  I'M SOLD THIS IS GONNA BE FANTASTIC :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> chest slots are full :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Short Story Written by Mohit Puvvala (Blugger's Creator) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Rose To Be Fallen - A Science Fiction Short Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 16:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but that's exactly what they were - myths

yup, that was a major point of the article
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 04:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a theory for another day :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
