<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3D modelling and A.I both sound really interesting, but my nearest experience of coding is a bit of HTML I did years ago. I completely agree. I think university is more about the core skills it gives you, rather then just the qualification. University is great because it pushes you to create coherent work by yourself within a deadline, and I've noticed myself improve drastically as person since I started.

Yes, that was my problem with writing. I'd write heaps of notes and ideas, but when it came to actually writing something, it came out as an incoherent mess and I'd get fed up with it. My course forces me to write shorter, planned pieces, so I can really focus on the techniques I'm using. I also got feedback from other students on my writing, which is invaluable.

What is it you're working (or procrastinating) on now? Good luck with the course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck with the essay! Last year I got a nasty bout of flu and it pushed my assignment way back, and I got really stressed about it. Fortunately my tutor was very understanding and gave me an extension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, can you do both at the same time in Austria, then? (Excuse my ignorance) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I like meditation and things like that, so I think it's interesting things like grounding exercises are implemented in the classes. It sounds relaxing at least! What are you majoring in, by the way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, I think IT is a very stable qualification, and it can be used to go into a variety of different fields. How far through it are you? I'm near the end of my second year (it's scary - I still feel like it's only just started!).

I've always wanted to be a writer, so when I saw the course, I knew I had to do it. I know it's not the most secure degree, but I suspect I'll go into something like communications anyway, and English is always useful for that. I've found the creative writing parts I've done so far absolutely brilliant, and I've been more confident in producing my own pieces of writing. If you're interested in writing, definitely keep it up, since it's a nice contrast to maths and IT. 

I enjoy them, although it can get frustrating not being able to do the subject I chose right away. I can understand why the course is structured that way, since it's really about learning essay writing and primary/secondary sources, etc. I think doing subjects out of my comfort zone (I would never have considered studying R.E and classical studies) has pushed me further than ever before, so in that sense it has been very rewarding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maths is probably my worst subject -_-, but I do find IT interesting. Do you like it overall?

My degree is in English Literature and Creative Writing. We have to do two general arts courses before I start on my major, though, so I have to do a bit of stuff like history, philosophy, religious education, as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
