<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a life without cheese is a life not worth living </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes unlike the cucks at the /r/t_d we dont ban people who disagree with us, or even who agree with us but arent devoted enough. We arent a safe space. 

I cant promise you a good reception here but you are welcome to stay as long as you like and say what you want. Or you could stop being a cuck and just join us. Triggering trumpets is fun, if you tried it you might like it, and it isnt that hard. It is like blowing up fish in a barrel with C4. 

You can also join us at 

/r/impeach_trump

/r/esist

/r/enoughtrumpspam

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, yep pointing out how stupid your argument is literally racism. As is disagreeing with you. 

Never mind the actual racism against the brown people, specifically the slaves, in Dubai. Good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, go back to your safe space Trumpet. Nobody will trigger you there like I triggered you here. You can circlejerk each other while you have all collective periods and cry to each other about how insecure you all are, delude yourself into denying the truth about trump. and give each other validation and love you lack in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you lived in either? If not you cant say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. 

And on this point how many people have lived in North Korea. I am  so tired of people judging it based off the media. And nazi germany. Everyone just hates nazi Germany based off what they hear, who has actually lived there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think this photo makes it look dull. Sure the ocean is nice and the skyscrapers are high but it looks too spaced out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right here. It is mostly me triggering you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, you wouldn't be here crying about trump if that were true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't kill yourself because of trump. I never said that. I said you will kill yourself because your life is not worth living. It is clear your support of trump is desperation that he can make you less of a loser. He can't he will only make your life worse. In a way trump is MAGA by wiping out beta cucks like you but I can't support that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you didn't. From our discussion it is clear you are not sharp or have wit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is low test and low iq betas like you who take your own lives. That is why you support trump. Desperation. He won't help you only speed up your demise. I actually want to help you but I can't help out every pathetic case like you some of you are destined to die. You won't be missed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again I don't care who you voted for. The fact remains the only people who will benefit from the tax cuts are the rich, and especially the mega rich.  Most of the rich hare trump too and will hate him after tax cuts. Who the cuts will hurt is his base. Poetic justice i get. 

Trump isn't bringing back jobs. Automation will bring a very few low paying jobs back but robots will get them and the money will go to the programmers and engineers in Silicon Valley who hate trump. This will happen regardless of who won. His base will remain poor and their situation will only get worse but under trump and Republicans they can feel safe knowing there will be no safety net or aid for them. Poetic justice again. I don't need or want trump's aid especially at expense of his base but he is giving me it while ducking over his own supporters. 

Your trailer park will die. Those you hold dear will die of heroin, Alcoholism, obesity, depression, poverty, disease, etc. Trump won't help his base. 

Honestly trump mostly benefits me. I actually make good money so his tax breaks will benefit me and him killing off low iqs  betas like you also benefits me. Still I am not cruel and would never support doing this to pathetic people like yourself. I actually want to help you. You genocide yourself and for that I have contempt for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a sarcastic comment I made above saying I don't care where your trailer is or who you claim to have  voted for cuck.

You are here right now being butthurt over trump's failures. By all means come join us in laughing at him and his retarded cultist followers. If you are going to be triggered by this prepare for butthurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is bitching, crying, and Whining About the 9th Circuit's Overturn Rate, But the Most-Overturned Circuits Are in Trump Country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is bitching, crying, and Whining About the 9th Circuit's Overturn Rate, But the Most-Overturned Circuits Are in Trump Country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is bitching, crying, and Whining About the 9th Circuit's Overturn Rate, But the Most-Overturned Circuits Are in Trump Country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is bitching, crying, and Whining About the 9th Circuit's Overturn Rate, But the Most-Overturned Circuits Are in Trump Country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool story bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump will help himself which he is currently doing. He will also help the very rich has I have already shown. For over 99% of the population he won't help especially your trailer park. 

You got conned cuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The stain of anti-Semitism at the White House isnt going away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The stain of anti-Semitism at the White House isnt going away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The stain of anti-Semitism at the White House isnt going away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The stain of anti-Semitism at the White House isnt going away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video has surfaced of beta cuck/counterterrorism expert Sebastian Gorka getting his balls slapped around by a bunch of students for being a nazi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol here is you 

*I refuse to believe there is proof and if you show proof I will refuse to believe it. But Hillary clibtin*. Look I get trump has no accomplishments so all you can do is constantly talk about old politicians to deflect but the longer trump fails the more pathetic it looks and it already looks pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if I said that but that is certainly true and that is easily proven. Not only do his tax cuts really only aid the rich but rich democrats in nyc, dc, and cali. 

https://www.aol.com/article/finance/2017/03/30/trump-tax-proposal-would-mostly-benefit-new-yorks-wealthy/22019209/

You and your fellow inbreds from the trailer park will get nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it not surprise me you are ignorant of the whole Russian thing. 

Way to live up to sterotype of trump supporters being stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What tax trump smear. I've smeared trump quite a bit but I have no idea what you are talking about. You want a source trump is a failure? That's easy cuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's everything. You asked and got and got an answer and can't dispute it but like all trumpet Cucks still blindly worship your false god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes trumpets are a shirt minded hive mind with no facts. And your support for a traitor is antiamwrican.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, literally everything. Luckily for you like you he has a micropenis so his rape of you wasn't that painfull but 8t must make you feel horrible and humiliated. Normally I'd have sympathy for someone in your situation but you were asking for it cuck. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sex and Hate in the Mountain State: The West Virginia Supreme Court debates whether an anti-gay hate crime is really a hate crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Desperation Is Exposing His Deep Ignorance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Desperation Is Exposing His Deep Ignorance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Desperation Is Exposing His Deep Ignorance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Desperation Is Exposing His Deep Ignorance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol basically Trump wishipered sweet promises in your hear, you bought it up like an idiot, than he bitch smacked you, fucked you in the assignment with no lube, spit on you, and took all your stuff. 

Now you have nothing. Only progress is Trump fucking you over like we said he would. He isn't done yet. So yes snowflake your butthurt  will grow as you get nothing from him, he takes away from you, and we make fun of you more. 

Hell  population you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right and Donald Trump Get a Divorce: Trump was powered to the Oval Office by fascists, but even they are tires of his failures and losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right and Donald Trump Get a Divorce: Trump was powered to the Oval Office by fascists, but even they are tires of his failures and losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right and Donald Trump Get a Divorce: Trump was powered to the Oval Office by fascists, but even they are tires of his failures and losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right and Donald Trump Get a Divorce: Trump was powered to the Oval Office by fascists, but even they are tires of his failures and losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right and Donald Trump Get a Divorce: Trump was powered to the Oval Office by fascists, but even they are tires of his failures and losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is your bitching  won't end your butthurt  it will only grow worse as trump failures grow. Lots of lulz for us to put down cucks like you and trump. 

This is your he'll snowflake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you are projecting per your own logic. It's OK scream and cry the but hurt away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Spat With Canada Is Bad News for Yet Another U.S. Industry That Supported Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump plans to abolish national monuments so private companies can drill and mine on and around them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump plans to abolish national monuments so private companies can drill and mine on and around them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many situations where letting someone who is homeless into the house is problematic due to drugs, alcohol, or mental issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump has a plan to change the tax code to make himself much, much richer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump has a plan to change the tax code to make himself much, much richer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump has a plan to change the tax code to make himself much, much richer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trumps Clothing Line Is Made in a Chinese Factory Where Workers Earn $1 an Hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trumps Clothing Line Is Made in a Chinese Factory Where Workers Earn $1 an Hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trumps Clothing Line Is Made in a Chinese Factory Where Workers Earn $1 an Hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All trumpets have micropenises, that is why they are so angry. Sorry no faggot would ever want you since your penis is too small. Or women, not that you would ever want to be with one. 

Normally I would pity you but Trumpets are beneath contempt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not hard to be appear smart to a triggered trumpet. I wish I could say I could do this to people with average or higher IQs and normal or high test but nope just the substandard ones like you

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the micropenis short trumpet can't play 4d chess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muh trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably turned his phone off and he is tweeting on a dead phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can claim to pretend to be retarded but we all know it is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not hard to be badass to a triggered trumpet. I wish I could say I could do this to people with average or higher IQs  and normal or high test but nope just the substandard ones like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he tried to pursue it would be like that. But I doubt he will. He likes to talk and sound like he is the boss. He can't be bothered to act and when he does it is comically pathetic. 

I don't blame you for being concerned. But after awhile you will see he is nothing but a demented pufffish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See. You are so triggered you know I am trolling you and getting you upset but your feelings are too hurt to walk away because you are insecure. Just like trump. I can control you just as easily as the elites control trump. 

Welcome to hell snowflake. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never underestimate the incompetence of trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I care, I only post to bait trumpets  

Triggering you guys is too easy. These last few months have been among the most fun. I control you now. I can keep you here as long as I want and keep you butthurt  for days.

That is how insecure you are. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't act either because he loved title for tat. Don't give him what he wants and don't antagonize him.  Just do what China does and have someone meet him in private and tell him how awesome he is without giving him anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't have to suffer this. Trump gets worked up, spews some nonsense, and then moves on to something else. 

Nothing will come of this. Trump will just get everyone in Canada worked up and anxious. He won't do anything. It will happen a few more times and it will become routine where you will just start ignoring him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pressure your government. Pull a Canadian standing rock. I'd recommend not  building any pipeline, it's bad stuff, but if you have to have one do it to China  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying trump and *nonsensical rant* is redundant. You can just state trump said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump doesn't believe in voodoo economics. He believes in nothing. He is intellectually lazy. His policy is his mood at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down. You don't have to do anything. Trump isn't going to shit. He is very vocal and loud mouthed but rarely does what he says and when he even bothers to try he fails miserably. Don't let him rattle you, do what we do and just mock him. He will forget about Canada in 2 or 3 days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He never follows through. He just gets upset, goes on a public cryfest, gets made fun of, and moves on to something else. 

I realize a lot of Canadians are upset right now but really I wouldn't be too worried. I mean in the end he will fuck  over anyone by crashing the global economy or starting wwiii due to incompetence but this isn't cause for concern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would anyone in Canada support that loon? I can see Russians liking him but not anyone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly you probably don't have to do anything. He has attention span of a knat. Bannon probably got him worked up, some other event will distract him in a few days and he will forget all about this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no you don't get it. Oil is fair game. Oil trade is always good. It's non energy related trade that is bad unless it is one sided mercentalist benefit for us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't build it. 

Nobody here except Republicans want keystone anyway. Do us and the world a favor and don't build a pipeline through that area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should punish him by not building it. Seriously, could you guys not build that? Environment wins and trump gets butthurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, so this is you winning? To non-trumpets it looks like failing. 

Anyway keep up the *winning* may trump's next 100 days be as succesful. Watching trump and his trumpets get triggered day after day has been the best thing about the presidency. Your butthurt is only starting so I recommend you get over it. Your butthurt is my amusement

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you are just the person on a anti-trump reddit bitching about it, lol. Talk about insecure. Donald is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *can't win* 

REEE help me putin!

REEEEE trump isn't failing now

The absolute state of trumpets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MUH trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol says the redditor  having a literal autistic fit because trump is a failure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too then I saw trump and realize this is true. It is #sad he has so much but is so pathetic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> muh trump

Imagine being so insecure that your altright viewpoint may not be the be all and end all, that you support treason to cheat to win a fair election with help from a foreign country 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is all just fascism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually Is apparently gave southerners jobs since many of them weren't working </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is putin's  achievement not trump. You seem more insecure about trump than trump even is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice with trumpets they can't speak to Trump's accomplishments because he has none. They can just bitch about the accomplishments of others that have them, like obama.

I'll make you a deal when Trump stops failing and succeeds we can talk. It was nice talking to you too bad we will never speak again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your agenda is saying it is only bad if it is groups you care about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethnic cleansing is part of fascism. You are just trying to make yourself feel superior because a fascist group wrong you. It is fascist in itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically you are excusing other fascism because it didn't target your group. It is pure selfishness. 

*I hate when my group is target of fascist but when it isn't who cares lol*

If you cared about Jewish people you would be against all fascism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. Obama had the gop hell  bent on obstructing him even for things they supported and he succeeded much more than Trump and without looking like an idiot the whole time too. 

Trump controls all 3 branches of government he has no excuse. 

Trump's first 100 days are the yuuggest failures in American history when he has everything going to him. It is entertaining to watch him fail. Bets on whether he causes a shutdown of his own government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are supposed to be impressed his dad gave him millions to invest? Like everything else he was handed his wealth on a golden spoon and didn't earn it, and thought he won it. No wonder they are loser and are so insecure. 

Mediocre  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For someone obsessed with winning they sure always lose. We would all be happy if trump could even reach mediocre instead of embarrassing defeat time after time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Rejects Grading of First 100 Days, Yet He Seeks an A: Despite having the worst 100 days of any president he wants people to make him less insecure by saying his were the best, all why claiming it doesnt matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Rejects Grading of First 100 Days, Yet He Seeks an A: Despite having the worst 100 days of any president he wants people to make him less insecure by saying his were the best, all why claiming it doesnt matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Rejects Grading of First 100 Days, Yet He Seeks an A: Despite having the worst 100 days of any president he wants people to make him less insecure by saying his were the best, all why claiming it doesnt matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Defining Trait is his insecurity: Presidential insecurity isnt harmless, especially for a commander in chief who is obsessed with winning and who seems to see life as a dominance game that they are losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Rejects Grading of First 100 Days, Yet He Seeks an A: Despite having the worst 100 days of any president he wants people to make him less insecure by saying his were the best, all why claiming it doesnt matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Defining Trait is his insecurity: Presidential insecurity isnt harmless, especially for a commander in chief who is obsessed with winning and who seems to see life as a dominance game that they are losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People used to dream of America. Not anymore. Thanks to Trump America is now seen as a terrible place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe it is who is grasping straws, so I guess per your logic you lost. 

Stop using your own personal wants and needs to define ideology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does everyone remember the first war of IS aggression when a bunch of Islamist went down to the freedom loving South and stole all their property for no reason to impose sharia law. The south just cant get a break, they never did anything bad and Islamist keep robbing their private propety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, is that what you do when your agenda is exposed claim this is some time of game and self proclaim you won. 

Haha that's sad

I cant think of anything we ever even argued about. You just kept asking the same question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spenser is that you? 

Just make your case, im listening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He is a hostage of the Jews: Trump angers his alt-right fans with Holocaust Remembrance statement that wasnt anti-semitic like all his previous ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought you wanted discussion, but it became clear at some point you have an agenda. You just want to paint yourself in a better light by saying *yeah im fascist but im not a nazi.* 

The thing is it is pretty boring. If you want to make your case for your fascism im all ears, but stop with the whole, *but Nazism is worse.* It is just lazy. Maybe why you are fascist will be interesting though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS has won: GOP candidates in Virginia and South Carolina enraged by Louisianas removal of Confederate monument compare it to IS taking over US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you my friend make fascism meaningless by not understanding it. You might be cool with it, whatever, but my friend I am opposed to your fascism. You see your fascism always spreads the hate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is using taxpayer dollars to enrich himself while asking Congress to fund his government. Multiple State Department websites were found promoting President Trumps private club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its fascism. It could be africanism, slavism, zionism, etc. Fascism always channels anger against made up enemies while giving superiority. 

What made the Nazis bad was how powerful they were and how delusional their leader was. There were other fascist just as violent and genocidal but unable to cause so much havoc. 

The real point here is fascism must be crushed, all forms of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is using taxpayer dollars to enrich himself while asking Congress to fund his government. Multiple State Department websites were found promoting President Trumps private club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mussolini was the first so they generally call regimes with somewhat similiar goals fascist. There is no real hard criteria. 

It is most reactionary, against progressive and *decadent* values, obcessed with decline and reversing it, restoring glory, nationalism, militarism, imperialism, authoritarianism, corporatism, class colloboration, government controlling big industries but letting them remain semi-private, private property, and fighting both internal enemies and external.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascism is pretty vague, which is why instances vary so much. The thing here is we agree with each other 99%, it is just I dont feel you can compare a group to an idea to an idea. Like what is better, pink floyd or environmentalism?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USSR had good rocketry and the like, but really as military use diminished the USSR would start to fall far behind. Computing they were far behind. 

I agree that the USSR is what probably set back Russian culture. Russian culture was not at the same level as say French, Italian, and many Western countries but it was unique and beautiful in its own way. USSR spent decades discouraging it. And now Russia is now longer shackled by the ideology but the general environment in much of Russia is not too friendly to producers of culture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opposite could easily happening or it could be say Sino chinese killing other East Asians. Or Muslims killing christains. 

Its just fascism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *authoritarianism, Autarky, and Corporatism* no need to say all of this. Fascist suffices. 

And fascism always involves superiority and inferior enemies. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a set of beliefs. Nazis are followers of fascism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bolsheviks are marxist. The parent isn't a person it is an idea. What you are asking is, *is the philosophy better or worse than the outcome* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is nazism is fascism. 

Fascism is the parent of nazism in a parent child relationship. Nazism is an instance of fascism. A subclass if you will. Not all fascist are nazis but all nazis are fascist. 

So no I can't agree because it is contradictory. I'll agree that nazis  were worse than the actual fascist party in Italy under mussolini.  However, the fascism we are talking about is the ideology named after the party. 

Fascism is the ideology. Nazism is an instance of the ideology. It is like saying what it worse *Marxism or the bolsheviks*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada is much wealthier, they could easily build hundreds of nukes and build a military but they would rather use their wealth and scientific prowess which is greater than Russia for quality of life and not annexing their neighbors. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot more fascist groups that worked with nazis  that were as bad. They were just smaller and had less means to kill as many people as the nazis with out bazi help but they were just as terrible. 

Can't we agree to agree all fascist are bad, especially nazis?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada has all of this, except it is more diverse, smaller, has a smaller population density, and even less resources. Yet it is way ahead of russia. 

Russia is pretty much a superpower by default but somehow fails to live up to it which takes a lot of effort. It is like being 6 meters tall but unable to play basketball. I mean they don't even need to dunk they could stand by the net and someone could pass them the ball and they could just drop it in. Yet they can't do this due to bad couching.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. Bangladesh is one of the most populated countries in the world.

Russia is top 10 in population, top 1 in land area, and easily top 3 for resources. There really is no excuse here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compared to central asia  they were cultured but not so much compared to the west and other Asian countries. Russian culture was promising once but kinda fell off the map. 

Scientifically they were advanced in a few areas but overall they were far behind the west. In civ terms it is like a country that goes for advanced military tech by neglecting everything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Memes  are gaining on every currency  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia always was uncultured but the lack of culture or hygiene is what scared Europe and it's neighbors. Rather it was the massive land area, population, and militarism/imperialism which has scared Europe for centuries.

Russia has always been powerful but always crippled by corruption, even now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is making Halliburton great again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is making Halliburton great again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breitbart is not independent: Its the communications arm of the Mercers empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Trump anti-semitism is souring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Trump anti-semitism is souring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Trump anti-semitism is souring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to Trump anti-semitism is souring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breitbart is not independent: Its the communications arm of the Mercers empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Military. 

Economically, scientifically, and culturally lots of countries are way ahead of it. I mean it depends on what makes someone happy, so I guess if your country having lots of nukes is what you want than Russia is pretty great. If you want quality of life, safety net, opportunity, etc. than  there is better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can explain your alternate facts as many times as you want. The real facts remain Putin is a nationalist, understand it or not but that is reality. You can explain your opinion again and again, but the answer will always be this. 

You gave your ignorant opinion several times, I heard it and it was either complete ignorance or long spews about how everyone who disagrees with you is brainwashed. Myself and the rest of this reddit are going to ignore your ignorance. Deal with it. 

  I even forgave that and gave you another chance which you blew. You dont understand Russian history or even the current state of Russia. So stop acting like you do. 

If we're done, and you are wasting your time, then you are free to leave.Let me be clear to you right now, this conversation is going to last as long as you make it. You are free to dismiss yourself right now, you wont be missed but it will be best for you as you are just looking foolish and can cut your losses and run. Or you can stay and repeat yourself, but you were wrong the first time and will continue to be wrong repeating the same wrong ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was implied?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont fight your strawman I reject it. 

You constantly repeating *if you dont agree you brainwashed!* makes you look bad. Putin is a very big nationalist. You dont understand the situation in Russia and you are frustrated that things arent goung your way. Stop being so immature, not only do you look wrong for your stupid alternative facts but you just look bitter and childish with the personal attacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosopher Henry Giroux on the culture of cruelty and Donald Trump: America is a democracy on life support  it cant breathe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would happen? USA would become USSA and Trump would be like Stalin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 and 2 I agree with. 

3 I cant say. A subset of fascist worse than Nazis could emerge. For instance take the Ustae, they werent Nazis but they were just as bad as Nazis. They killed far less people, but that is because they lacked the means too. 

So 3) depends on what fascist we are talking about. if we are referring to all fascist that are not Nazis I cant agree to that because there are other fascist as bad as Nazis, or potentially worse that have already existed, or theoretically could exist.

I will agree Nazis are worse than the vast majority of non-nazi fascist that have existed. 

I would hope no worse group will ever emerge, but knowing history I am sure one will at some point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like you are being stubborn. I dont even know what you are talking about to be honest. I said a few wealthy elite have always controlled Russia's wealth, even during the USSR period. I just clarified the wealth distribution during USSR was bad but slightly better than normal Russia. 

You then proceed to go into a *USSR was awesome!* You then start comparing quality of life between the height of the USSR and the immediate collapse. What you are whining about has nothing to do with my point. 

I never said the USSR was good or bad. It just collapsed because it wasnt economically feasible with their command economy system. This isnt Reagan era propaganda, it is economic fact that is proven by history. Nobody disagrees with it, except you. Not even Putin would disagree with this. 

Like I said you are resorting to *2+2=454 and anyone who disagrees is brainwashed by Reagan era propaganda.* 

You dont even know Reagan era propaganda because a complex economic analysis of why the USSR collapsed is way too advanced for Reagan, the republican party, and their base. 

95 was worse because in 85 the USSR was on the verge of collapse, and in 95 was post collapse. It is like a axe swining toward your leg was 85, and you couldnt move. 95 was an hour after an axe cut off your leg. Neither situation was good, but 95 was worse, but 95 was a done deal before 85. 

Now what you dont realize is I never made this point you keep ranting about. I never said 90s was better than 80s. I just said Russia always had a very few people control all the wealth, even during the USSR except it was a little better. Somehow you took this to say *90s were awesome and rest of USSR sucked.* In fact this whole *fall of the USSR was inevitable from the 80s* wasnt my original point that set you off. It was a sidepoint during your long inane off topic rant. 

So I think I see what happened. You misunderstood me. Ok fair enough. 

But to address your point here. No you are still wrong. In the 80s Russia's situation was like having testicular cancer where your options were either remove the testicles or die. Real shitty situations. 90s was after the procedure, it was worse. Still from the 80s USSR was dead. Killed by its command economy. The economic system was bad. It worked if everyone had a shitty life, like under Stalin, but once life got ok, still far from the west, it couldnt last that long and collapsed. That is a bad system, sorry friend. 

And yes Romania like all other countries that were communist when the collapse happened hurt. that is what happens when your whole economic system crashes. 

Even the nationalist in Russia, like Putin, dont disagree with me. They are angry at the USSR too. They loved how much power and states it controlled but they hate the communism and the command economy that ultimately brought it down. 

Reagan did not beat the USSR, the USSR killed the USSR. It could have survived if it made reforms like China in the 70s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the USA was like the USSR, then yes he, and a few Republicans, would. Pretty scary thought, and he is scary enough as it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a subset of fascism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little better, but it doesnt need your excuses for earlier behavior. Look its forgotten about. 

Secondly, you fail to understand the situation in the 80s. The reforms you speak of are mostly after the USSR already collapsed, you are missing the reforms that matter. The whole centralized command economy stopped working in the 70s, the Russian leadership ignored it because all solutions involved ideological reforms that went againt communism. In the 80s they would have ignored it too, but the whole USSR started to fall apart so they had to do something.

They tried to make reforms in the 80s, but this just gave people a taste for better things, which sped up the demise of the USSR. The reforms you speak of are the ones they came up when the decided to end the USSR, the decision was made by then, or after it collapsed. 

Nobody disagrees the USSR states, and all communist states that were satelites, had bad reforms that did not work so great. The issue though is these reforms were the ones when they called it quits because the command economy couldnt be saved and they wanted to transition to capitalism. The death of their command economy was set in stone long before this happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the ussr  people kept their office until they died, were removed against their will, or were too senile to retire. Than the next bureaucrat got ownership </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mockery of yourself was done by you. Here is some advice like I said don't start out every discussion making personal attacks and calling everyone else brainwashed because you disagree with them or don't like what they say. 

If you felt I was wrong than in a civil manner explain why, and feel free to uses sources. You didn't do this all you did *what you said triggered me so that makes you indoctrinated*. 

It was pathetic of you, and that is why you are mocked now. If you want a do over I'm nice enough to let you try again. Or you can dismiss yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, and you sound like someone parroting some Stlain era indoctrination there man. 

See, boiler plate denials wont help you. I can take your whole comment and change Reagan to any number of Russian leaders and I said something that applies to you and is as stupid as what you said. The fact that you need to do this just shows how weak your argument was. 

Russia was a superpower before Stalin. If it wasnt for Stalin there would have been no WWII, so assuming you are right, and that is big assumption, Stalin saved Russia from the mess he created. 

*But when you say that USSR did not colapse because of the so-called reforms in the 90's , you are either just that indoctrinated (and i say this because i know this was the official natrative in the USA , all the time , but taken to indoctrination and propaganda levels during Regan era) , or lying. USSR never rose to the west s level , but a great part of that was because it was allways locked in a cold war with the west. However , it did manage to rise from the ashes of WW2 and stand up to America for 50 years.To dismiss that is...missinformed? arrogant? .*


Secondly, you proved you are either very ignorant or very indoctrinated. The reforms that are relevant are the ones made in the 80s before the USSR collapsed, not the reforms after it collapsed. Your argument is basically *the reforms made to the USSR after it collapsed caused it to collapse.* Not only do you not understand history but you do not understand time. 

(and i say this because i know this was the official natrative in Romania/Russia , all the time , but taken to indoctrination and propaganda levels during Putin era) , or lying. 

See what I did there? 

After USSR collapsed there was a deliberate effort to ruin Russia, by other Russians, but Russian elites always did this so this was nothing new. Before USSR collapsed there was a deliberate effort by Russians to ruin Russia. Like I said /r/anormaldayinrussia for Russia. Putin is just another corrupt Russian oligarchy that got lucky with high oil prices. If , however , you seem to be getting all your info from Russian propaganda media , you wouldnt know this , as..surprize! Russian propaganda media lies most of the time on anything reguarding foreign politics and things outside and inside of Russia. You wouldnt know that Putins main oponents are anyone that isnt an oligarchy. 

Back to the topic: USSR collapsed because they waited too long to make reforms, and when they make reforms they were rushed and implemented poorly, but either way it was pretty doomed. 

Just to be clear you going *2+2=593 is correct and if you disagree you are brainwashed American!* does not help you. It makes you look bad, and it actually contradicts your point and makes you look brainwashed. Just giving you some advice. Your argument would be better without the ad hominems and generalizations. If you need to resort to calling everyone else brainwashed, then you are the brainwashed one. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia was a superpower before USSR. Imperial Germany and much of Europe was terrified of Russia. 

Russia given its population and resources, should always be a superpower. Right now Russia is much weaker than it really should be, this was also the case during USSR. Russia due to bad leadership never meets its potential. 

And USSR collapsed not because of reforms but because the whole economic system was on the verge of collapse. They didnt decide to do reforms for shits and giggles, but rather they realized the whole thing was about to explode. Granted the reforms didnt really work either, but the USSR was beyond help by then. USSR needed reform decades earlier, and probably at a slower rate. By the 80s, Russia did not have decades to implement slow reform, so they tried rapid reform, and that did not work. There was not going to be a good outcome regardless of Russia did. 

Your typical Russia vs USA, *yes Russia sucks but USA is worse!* is not needed. I realize some people feel the need to always do this, but here it isnt really appropriate. You are not even disagreeing with what I am saying, but just feel the need to arbitrarily compare Russia against something else to feel better about it by thinking it is better. 

Here are the facts. A small wealthy elite has always controlled all the wealth in Russia. Since the first Tsar. Even during the USSR. So really this headline could be called /r/anormaldayinrussia since it is pretty normal. Yeah 90s were tough, that is what happens when your economy collapses, things generally arent good. Still if you knew more of Russian history you would know USSR went through much tough periods than the 90s. As did Russia itself. 

Again you being from Russia, Romania, USA, etc. does not change this. I dont care where you are from nor does anyone else. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk. He seems better than le  pen since it is hard to be worse than fascism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing. You can give me control of all your wealth to do with it as I like and I can give some back to you. I own it now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you are the one is indoctrinated. Soviet Union also had vast inequality and a few people having the wealth. It was just almost everyone was equally poor instead of having wealth gaps, but these existed too between areas. 

I agree Russia had it better at some times during ussr comprared  to a few years post collapse but there big periods during ussr, such as much of stalin's time where it was a nightmare.

Where I am from and where you are from does not change this. So as we see you seem to have either agenda or are indoctrinated   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you prefer Le Pen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin didnt increase the GDP, oil and gas did. Putin had almost no influence on this. 

Putin did invade foreign countries, and it did give him a huge patriotic burst of support, I will cede him this. Wagging the dog works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the 1990s? More like Rusisan imperialism has not changed since 1690s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title should be 22 Russians stole 40% of Russia's wealth. I dont see how this situation is strange for Russia, at any given point in Russian history a few dozen people pretty much controlled all of Russia's wealth. 

Maybe USSR was slightly better, at times, but even then a few hundred people pretty much had all the wealth, and under Stalin 1 person had all the wealth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair though guys are like that too. 

If a girl doesnt look good enough for me ill swipe left. A lot of time it isnt their fault how they look, although I guess if it involves them being fat that it kinda does. 

Still at the end of the day I believe Men are more focused on physical traits than women are. Yeah, they want a tall, good looking, muscular guy, but they will settle for less because they are more willing to value a sense of humor, personality, and especially wealth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a cuck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also label Australia so Trump doesnt accidentally bomb it because he thinks that is where North korea is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from time to time? 

During the post-collapse period a lot of Roman buildings were taken apart to build hovels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is her fault </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't there a movie about this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't like he has ever done so  before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't want his stupid country club to be under water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No just progay  communist and pro north korea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people are expected to march?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you and them think this granny trump thing is clever, but nobody else does. They made themselves sound stupid, and trumpets sound stupid. Not that either is hard to do. And for some reason you are bitter about it and angry.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump and Jeff Sessions ramp up their crusade against black and brown Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump and Jeff Sessions ramp up their crusade against black and brown Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump and Jeff Sessions ramp up their crusade against black and brown Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump and Jeff Sessions ramp up their crusade against black and brown Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His wife clearly cant stand him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never mentioned jfk but I'm sure there are all types of documentaries on jfk that bring up ussr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesn't unless trump declassified it before leaking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really care about what he is into. I wasn't insulting him but rather saying our discussion was not really the place to bring it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. Information is classified a certain way and has that state unless they change the rules for all classified information. And it needs to be formally done. You can't just unclassified something by speaking about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What strawman? They went into the whole transgender  trump rant. I didn't even insult them off it just told them to get back on topic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they really dont. Nixon learned that the hard way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe fbi should look into trump tweeting classified info or dropping it during interviews rather than wasting resources on investigating a pizza place because they have cheese pizza and pizza slices shaped like triangles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened when Pizzagate exploded at my restaurant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Realizes Being President Is Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Realizes Being President Is Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Realizes Being President Is Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Realizes Being President Is Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Realizes Being President Is Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mysterious Case of the Wayward Aircraft Carrier: trump is not in control of US military and nobody knows who is in charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mysterious Case of the Wayward Aircraft Carrier: trump is not in control of US military and nobody knows who is in charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mysterious Case of the Wayward Aircraft Carrier: trump is not in control of US military and nobody knows who is in charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mysterious Case of the Wayward Aircraft Carrier: trump is not in control of US military and nobody knows who is in charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Syria strike clearly broke international law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Syria strike clearly broke international law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Syria strike clearly broke international law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch Looks Poised to Rule That States Must Sometimes Subsidize Churches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch Looks Poised to Rule That States Must Sometimes Subsidize Churches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch Looks Poised to Rule That States Must Sometimes Subsidize Churches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch Looks Poised to Rule That States Must Sometimes Subsidize Churches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump Will Dismantle Civil Rights Protections in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
