<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also keep in mind that pure introductory posts can be removed for not having enough horror. I recently wrote a series that is ~13k words split into three parts. 

My first post had to be removed and edited because it was too much of an intro without a decent amount of horror. It went from ~2k words to 5k words, putting half of what I planned to be a second part into the first post. 

Don't think too deeply on leaving a cliffhanger, anything can be a cliffhanger to someone who is anxiously awaiting the next part because the first one had them hooked. 

Also remember that each update post needs a minimum of 1k words. Long posts in a series are good, they keep a reader more satisfied until the next part comes out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol my most recent series starts with finding a journal in the basement of a house that caught fire. Shot fired. Not really, but I'm curious on your perspective. 

I can see how it would get "boring" to read a lot of stories around the same time with the similar element, but there are different ways to use it that make the story good/original. 

Does the diary thing in total annoy you? 

Or: 

Posts almost entirely detailing the contents of the diary. The diary *is* the story. 

Posts where creepy things happen after finding the diary, but it's not the center piece of *everything*. It just happens to contain some relevant info about the situation. 

Posts where the diary is cursed or something. It *causes* the main action in the story, it's evil. 

Posts where the diary holds all the answers to the weird things going on. It's a means of gathering answers to questions and problems in the story. 

Or all of the above? 

I guess my real question is, is it the use of a diary a framing/plot device in general, or is it the *way* you're seeing it used?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decent human staff are hard to come by, it's more unsafe to be a guest. I'm easy to kill, but a lot of the guests like to have a human around for various reasons. 

My contract has me working for a minimum of three months. Every three months I have the option to go through an *almost* painless process to remove any recollection of the hotel and the things I've witnessed. If I try to quit before an interval, the process is apparently quite unpleasant. I'm not supposed to speak about the hotel, tell anyone where it located, or give any information about the guests who stay here. 

I'm also not supposed to question the guests too intensely. A question here and there is allowed, or information they willingly share with me, but pestering about their species, lifestyle, eating habits, etcetera is frowned upon and could get me into trouble. 

A loophole in the contract allows me to post here, because most of the world outside this forum believe that everyone here is telling tales of fiction. I am advised not to touch the guests, not to seek out any "enhancement" a guest may offer me, not to enter the room alone with a guest who is not of species, but to honor any request a guest might give me within my limitations. 

Including but not limited to: Donating blood, letting a guest watch me for certain periods of time, dressing in specific attire and having a conversation with a guest, allowing the guests to smell me, singing to the guests, bringing food and other items to the rooms, and various other tasks. 

The contract states that the hotel will do everything in it's power to make sure I do not "expire" during any shift that I work, and that they will provide me with the means to cure any negative side effects from coming into close contact with a guest. 

There's many other things, but those are some of the main points. There is also the benefit of a 50% pay increase every time I choose to remain an extra three months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can look into it, it definitely makes sense that someone would know how to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a mistake there, getting only three correct was only possible in the instances where we were betting on one person to live, if that person died but you guessed the order correctly your money was doubled. If they were the last alive and stayed alive, that's when it could triple. 

Edit: I edited the post to clarify.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did make an error there, four correct only stands in the instances where one person gets to live. If the final person dies, then you've only gotten the first three correct and your money was doubled. 

Edit: Clarified in the original post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a linear one, but I plan to occasionally talk about things that have happened at the hotel, and possibly convince guests or fellow employees to tell their own stories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perhaps I Took My Gambling Habit Too Far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bet you $150 that Trent kills himself before we graduate, I looked to my best friend, awaiting his response to the wager. 


What the fuck? Are you serious? He's not even the type. 


Yea, why not? Bet me, you're on the side that gets paid if he lives. You're not doing anything wrong, I shrugged, the bet wasn't a big deal. 


He ended up agreeing to the deal, I'm sure he forgot about it after a while. I didn't though. The news came about six months before we graduated, nearly a year after the wager was made. Trent Nguyen had shot himself in his bedroom. I wasn't happy about the news, but I had seen it coming. Call me horrible if you wish, I'm not the one who killed him. 


There wasn't anything I could do to stop it, he was completely fine until the first month of our senior year. Things visibly went downhill from there. His grades were slipping, he wasn't allowed to play at any of the games because of it, and his girlfriend left him for another guy. Sure, he was obviously becoming depressed, but he had tons of people trying to help him. He was surrounded by friends, family, and counselors. It wasn't enough to combat his dark thoughts. 


I waited a few weeks before confronting Danny about the debt he owed me, I didn't want to seem insensitive. Suffice to say he was pissed that I brought it up. I hated to pester people, but he *owed* me. You make a bet, you pay up when you lose. It's the way gambling works. I nagged at him every so often, reminding him that the conversation about the terms of our wager was recorded. By the end of the year he gave in, he didn't want me telling people that we had placed a bet on someone's life. 


Here's your money, James, He shoved an envelope full of bills at me, Not just for the debt, I put in an extra $50 so you could do me a favor. 


I nodded as I counted the money in the envelope, And what would this favor be?


Never talk to me again. You're seriously a sociopath. 


Sure thing, I shrugged, I would have wagered that our friendship would die out in college anyways. 


I was $200 richer and one friend less. It didn't matter, I didn't need him. He always judged me for my interest in gambling, and I am *not* a sociopath. I just enjoy winning, no matter what the game is. Some may say I have a gambling problem, but I think it's more of a skill.


Over the years I've gotten pretty decent at the games, but cards and chips get monotonous. People are what makes for interesting bets. I'm great at reading people. Most of the time I can tell a lot about a person just from having an encounter or two. When it came down to predicting the actions of a person, I was almost always right. There's always variables that can ruin a bet though, not every gamble is a win. 


I started betting at work. *Dana will quit her job in less than two months. Mikes wife is cheating on him while he's here. The new guy is going to freak out by next week.* The office wagers were fun, I was always a winner. Eventually even that got boring though, it was too easy to win. 


That's why when a coworker gave me an address of a high risk, high pay event, I showed up without question. It was shady, and run by an organization that called themselves *Limited Life Wagers*. The location changes every time a new event occurs, and for good reason. What took place at these events was nowhere near legal. 


The amount of people at the venue surprised me, apparently these events were quite popular. I wasn't sure what we were going to be betting on, but the crowd got me excited. There was a stage set up at the front of the room and the audience members pushed and shoved to get close. I was wary, I wanted to see what kind of game they were playing before I thought about placing a wager. 


A voice called out for silence and the room quickly fell into a hush. The curtain opened, revealing a man in a mask, behind him sat four cages. It was hard to see from my position but there seemed to be *people* in the cages. Now this was definitely piquing my interest. 


The masked man spoke, Welcome, let's start with an introduction for the newcomers.


All noise in the room had ceased, you could only hear the sound of the audience breathing during the dramatic pause. 


Minimum wager is five thousand dollars. We do not accept checks. We have associates in the back to provide cash loans if you did not come prepared. If you do not plan on placing a bet tonight, please leave now. 


He took a break as he waited for the audience to either produce the money or leave. I decided that it would be worth it to try this out at least once. I moved to the back and received my $5000 loan. A few minutes later the masked man spoke once again. 


Please place your wagers in an envelope, and write your name and the amount on the front, Another pause, There we go! As I continue, attendants will come around and collect your envelopes, and your hand will be stamped. Now as for what we'll be betting on tonight, He gestured at the cages behind him. 


The speech that followed detailed the contents of each cage. They were all people who were at the end of their rope, for some reason or another they had given up on life. I wasn't sure how they ended up here, but I honestly didn't care. 


The game was simple. These people would be held captive and subjected to torture, they already hated their lives anyways. They would be offered the chance to end their suffering at thirty minute intervals. The last one to off themselves would have a large sum of money anonymously donated to someone in their life that they had picked in advance. 


The bets were what I found to be the most appealing part. Predict which order they would die in. One correct would get your money back, two would multiply it by 1.5, after that your money was doubled and then tripled. These people were *hopeless*, betting against them wasn't wrong. This was exactly up my alley, reading other people's misery was so easy. 


That first night was simple, attendants came around to record everyone's predictions, and within a few hours the game was over. My money had doubled and I was hooked. For months this was the only manner of gambling I took part in, there was a downside though. The torture aspect made the predictions harder, you never knew what would break a person. 


For months I watched all manners of abuse break down these people. Waterboarding, brandings, nails and teeth yanked out, bloodletting, and even dismemberment. The lengths were extreme, and I kept overestimating my ability to predict the outcome of the games. I found myself owing a debt of nearly $100k to *Limited Life Wagers.* 


The organization gave me one option to pay my debt, and I'm going to take it. I'm pretty good at predicting people, and I think I can make it through. In all honesty, I think they rig the bets. I've noticed lately that a lot of people who have placed wagers have also ended up on the stage. Those games are the most interesting, one person gets to live and collect 90% of the money from the losing bets. That's a huge haul on any given night. 


I'm going up on that stage tonight, and I'm actually *thrilled* about it. I could make more than enough money to pay off my debt, hell maybe I'll go up a few extra times to earn some guaranteed cash. Though, I think I've realized something. 


I have a serious gambling problem. 

**Edit:** As several of you have pointed out, I made an error when describing the winnings. Here's some clarification. 

Correct on the first death: Money back. 

Correct on the first two: 1.5 x your wager. 

Correct on 3+: Double. 

For the games where one was left alive, your money would be tripled *only* if the person you bet on living didn't die as well. 

There has been a few instances where the person intended to live couldn't handle the thought of living with their mutilations, or for some other reason did not make it until the evening was over. 

[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one has ever described it to me, but I cringe at the thought of being compared to her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What actually scares you? (Besides cannibals) 

Why cannibals? 

Suppose I kidnapped you and cut off a chunk of your body to feed to you, which body part would you eat first? 

Fatty Bacon or crispy Bacon? 

What story did you enjoy the most, which one do you think scared/unsettled others the most? 

Edit: I forgot what I came back to add... Shit 

Edit 2: I remember! Which is greater ATL or SWS?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Eric isn't doing much of anything anymore.. 

I'm assuming you're talking about a different Eric and Tim?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the day ended I received more information about him. 

He claimed to be a preacher, but was in fact a Shade the entire time. He lied to the men to bring them to the hotel full of "demons", the men thought he intended to help wipe demons from the earth, but he only wanted a decent sized group to murder. 

His entire goal was to bring victims so that the hotel guests could massacre them as a group. The rules of the hotel were starting becoming more strict, and he wanted to prove that you couldn't deny Shades of their desires. 

That day has become a tradition. No human guests are safe, and the rules are lax for the holiday. They've done this to appease the Shade guests, so that massacres of such a magnitude will only take place once per year on hotel property.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just Canada, but I'll have a lot of time to write, so hopefully my stories remain as quality as they are now c: I'm trying to keep myself pushed to post 2-3 no sleep stories while I'm gone, and to do short scary stories when I have small ideas. I also have a half finished sleepspell story that didn't fit any themes, so I hope to finish that and get it out c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I wasn't going to be out of the country for a month and a half with limited internet, then I'd definitely attempt it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, especially with single part ideas. Just have to push through it and keep moving, we're in the end zone. Or write a poem on days that you just can't handle the stress. 

Good ideas for long posts can always be done after the challenge for when you simply can't handle the pressure of the daily deadline c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be a high chance that you had a relaxing stay at the Good Shade, our team is great at making memories disappear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either by wandering through the forest and stumbling upon it once you've become lost, or being invited. The invitation is usually only directed at Shades though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Hotel Celebrates The Strangest Holidays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Apocalypse Day! Diana greeted me cheerfully from behind the front desk. 


*What now?* I had been working at the Good Shade for several weeks at this point, and had just started to become accustomed to all the things that go on. I could finally check-in guests, and I was learning more about the types of *people* that stayed in the hotel. Not all of them were bad, but most were terrifying. 


I was already starting to lose track of how many times a guest had *smelled* me. On the bright side, apparently my scent is delicious. Perhaps not the best compliment, considering it's probably something that would make me more likely to end up a victim. Diana didn't seem too impressed when she saw such a thing occur to me for the first time. 


A tall, pale woman had entered the hotel a few days after I started the job. She looked like death-- literally. She was beautiful in a dark way, and I found myself compelled to walk up to her as soon as our eyes met. Long black hair cascaded down her back, matching in color with her eyes. If the grim reaper was personified as a gorgeous woman, then that's what I was staring at. 


She was as tall as me, a surprising attribute considering that I'm 61. She leaned close to me as I came to a halt in front of her. Her lips hovered mere centimetres away from my neck, and her breath felt cold on my skin. I trembled due to the fear of what she may be, but also because I was suddenly awash with a deep lust for her. She laughed, a deep and alluring sound as she backed away. 


You smell delicious, young man, She purred as she walked around me. 


I didn't trust my legs to walk, so I simply stared as she took long graceful steps towards Alice. 


Marise, he's new. Don't play with the staff, Alice chastised her. 


Shame, it gets lonely at the hotel. 


No it doesn't, Alice laughed, You bring in more unregistered guests than anyone else. You keep turning people and there will be none left to feed on.


Abruptly I felt the rush of desire leave my body, leaving only the traces of fear. I walked hesitantly up to the women, and Marise glanced at me with a pout. 


What if I get hungry? The pout transformed into a smile, revealing her sharp elongated canines. 


Alice sighed, You know Smith provides for the guests, and I've already asked you once not to mess with our new staff member. Get out of his head. 


Marise shrugged and broke her gaze with me. I stood there confused until she left with her room key. 


Don't let the guests play with your head, Alice scolded me once Marise was out of sight. 


What do you mean? I questioned, still confused about the encounter. 


The desire, her teeth? She does it to everyone. It's not real, you have to steel yourself mentally so that it's not so easy for Shades to get in your head.


I nodded, What about her teeth? 


You think mine are scary? Hers are just plain hideous, but almost equally as dangerous. 


I took what she had told me into account, and have worked on locking down my brain since then. By the time Apocalypse Day arrived I had a minor grasp on how to protect my mind, but at the same time I was plagued with nightmares of jagged teeth. I came into work that evening exhausted, the nightmares had made sleep nearly impossible. 


Apocalypse Day? I questioned with a yawn. 


It's a sort of holiday at the hotel. I mean, if holidays meant a ton of extra work, She was vigorously typing things into the computer as she spoke, Thats the downfall of being in the hotel business though. It makes for an interesting night at least.


I watched as she pushed chestnut colored hair away from her tanned face. She was pretty this way, short and curvy with dark green eyes. She noticed me staring. 


What? 


I'm just not used to Diana yet, what was wrong with Alice? 


Nothing, I just needed to change bodies so I could move on undetected, She shrugged at me as though it was the most obvious thing in the world. 


I'm not sure if I'll ever get used to Alphaea switching names and bodies, it was definitely confusing the first time she came in as Diana. I nodded in understanding at her explanation, but wished she would let me call her by a single name. She requested that I call her by the name of the body so that she wouldn't slip up around other humans. I doubt she ever slips up though, I'm pretty sure she just gets a laugh out of my confusion. 


So what exactly is this so-called holiday? I got back on task, not wanting to be blindsided tonight. 


Years ago-- back in the time of Al Capone-- there was a group of men who thought themselves Demon Hunters, She glanced up from the screen to make sure I was paying attention, Their leader led them to believe the apocalypse was imminent. He brought them here on the claim that this hotel was run by demons. 


I listened intently, her tone made it obvious that their visit to the Good Shade didn't end well. 


I'll tell you the rest later, She cut the story short as two young men entered the hotel. 


Hi, welcome to the Good Shade hotel, She smiled sweetly at the new guests. 


Damn, this place is pretty remote, The taller of the pair spoke, Stumbled on it by luck.


Mhmm, we don't advertise much, The edges of her smile tightened as though she knew what would come next. 


So is the place where that massacre happened? Do you know where they died? He asked casually as they walked up to the desk. 


I took in their appearances, they seemed almost normal. The taller guy sported short blonde hair, he had an arrogant air about him. The shorter one had dark hair, and he practically dragged the bags he was weighted down with. He didn't seem to be as thrilled about being here as his friend was. 


Do you need a room for the night? Diana ignored his question. 


Can you tell me what happened that night? It's the anniversary you know, those men came into this forest, The blonde ignored her in return. 


She rolled her eyes, Do I look old enough to remember that? 


Fine, whatever, we'll take a room. Can we film here, and in the area? He sighed and gestured to the bags. 


The other guests probably won't want to be on camera, but do what you want without bothering anyone. Names for the room, please, She was typing the booking into the computer as she spoke. 


I'm Eric, my friend here is Tim. I'm actually doing research on a mass killing that hasn't been publicized, He leaned in like he was expecting this would get her to talk. 


I take it that means you didn't come here because you found some sort of advertisement or invitation? 


Eric simply shrugged, apparently annoyed by the lack of information Diana offered. She held out a key card silently, and gripped his hand when he reached for it. 


Only use the third elevator, don't leave your room after 11pm, and enjoy your stay in room 217, She smiled, her eyes seemed to turn into deep black pools as she stared into him. 


He yanked his hand away and began walking, Crazy. Cmon Tim, let's go set up in the room.


She frowned, *Not long enough,* She muttered under her breath, Tyler, will you make sure those two make it to their room okay? Third elevator only. The other staff aren't here yet. 


I nodded and quickly jogged to catch up with the men near the elevators. They were trying to enter the wrong one. Eric seemed frustrated, while Tim seemed slightly scared. 


Swiping your key card will only work on the correct elevator, I told them. 


We moved to the third elevator, and I took a few of the heavy bags from Tim. As soon as we entered the elevator Eric began speaking again. 


So, do you know about the massacre? He asked me. 


I'm pretty new here, you're the first person to mention it, I replied. 


He told the story as we made our way to the room. Apparently this occurred almost a hundred years ago, most of the story was small town rumor. A group of men had followed a preacher out into the woods, they believed he was leading them to stop the apocalypse. As the tale goes, the men never came back and their families believed something in the woods had killed the entire group. No one knew where exactly the men had gone, and there has been conspiracy theories about it being a cult that committed a group suicide. 


Variations of the story included the men finding a haunted building and being tortured by malevolent forces, or the preacher turning on them and slaughtering the group. The only solid fact that Eric had was that this forest was the one where the men had disappeared. 


I nodded and made understanding noises at the right moments, this information seemed to coincide with what Diana had been telling me before. I helped them bring the bags into the room, and was about to leave when a question popped into my head. 


Why are you filming at the hotel? 


This is the only place around for miles, no one has ever heard of it, and everyone who has come looking for answers has gone missing. When we stumbled upon this place I figured someone here must know what's going on.


Maybe, I muttered halfheartedly. 


*Oh the people here know what's going on,* I thought. *Why else would they celebrate a holiday called Apocalypse Day?* 


When I returned to the lobby Diana gave me a curious look, Learn anything interesting from your fellow humans?


I suppose, I shrugged, knowing she didn't plan on enlightening me any further. 


I didn't have much time to dwell on the fact that she was leaving me clueless yet again. Guests seemed to pour into the hotel in an endless stream. Human and Shade alike came to stay. It wasn't uncommon to have human guests, people like to roam the forest and are always relieved to find that there's somewhere to rest. None of them remember the hotel once they leave, we have staff that make sure of that. 


The influx in guests was apparently due to the holiday. Half the human guests were out ghost hunting for the missing men, and I wasn't sure what about this day appealed to the Shades. By the time we had gotten the flood of guests into their rooms it was almost 11pm. I was entirely exhausted at this point, and couldn't keep my eyes from closing as I took a seat behind the desk. 


I awoke a short time later to the sound of a disagreement. 


You need to go back to your room, Diana said sternly. 


I was still half asleep and hardly heard the response from a familiar male voice. I stood, trying to collect myself, and saw a group of people enter the hotel. Diana noticed that I was awake. 


Take care of the guests, She barked at me as she took Eric's arm and led him away quickly. 


The group was made up of about ten men, and they seemed angry. It only took a moment of them crying out for redemption upon demons before I recognized who they must be. I couldn't pinpoint which of them might be the so-called preacher. As they got closer I faced a horrifying realization. They were all obviously Shades, and they were mutilated beyond belief. 


Suit sleeves dangled limply, lacking arms to fill them. It was a near sea of red, blood splatter could be found in abundance on each one of them. Eyeless sockets, mouths sewn shut, limbs snapped and mangled, and missing chunks of flesh. These men had been brutally torn apart. I was used to seeing awful things, but hadn't yet witnessed anything of this magnitude. I stood staring, absolutely shocked by the scene in front of me. The gruesome visual was paired with a soundtrack of enraged shouts. 


Demons come forth!


We shall end the bringers of the apocalypse!


The night of your reckoning has come!


My stupefied state was interrupted by the sound of elevator doors opening. A tall man in a pristine black suit came over and stood in front of the gruesome mob. 


My followers, welcome to the reckoning! He gave an eerie smile to the group, who responded by dropping to their knees. 


They sang out praises and gratitude, the man who stood before them was their preacher. By this point a throng of guests had heard the commotion and crowded around the edges of the lobby. The humans were easy to distinguish, they bore panicked expressions and some even screamed at the sight. Other guests held on to them and kept them from running away. 


Friends, The man gestured towards the edges of the room, Let history repeat itself, Apocalypse Day has arrived! 


He laughed like a madman, and the room was suddenly chaotic. Shades descended upon the human guests, tearing them apart or dragging them away. The preacher ran through the room, laughing as his razor sharp nails cut through his flock of mutilated followers. The men dissipated when he made the violent contact, but the blood and screams were not lost. The guests kept the sound alive as they tore each other apart. 


I was backed against the wall behind the front desk, shivering with fear. The guests had gone crazy, this place wasn't *safe.* I don't know how I could have thought I would get used to being around such murderous creatures. Suddenly Diana was besides me, blood dripped from her shark-like teeth and ran down her chin. She looked at me with curiosity, but her eyes were inky black pools. I shrunk away from her. 


She rolled her eyes at me, I had to take care of Eric, he was getting too aggressive while asking about the hotel. I see the festivities have started. 


I stared at her speechless, and she seemed to suddenly realize the depth of my fear. 


This is what the holiday is for, a cheat day of you will. The guests go wild to celebrate the massacre. Not a great day for your kind, but you're safe. You're with me, I'll protect you, She said reassuringly as the darkness faded from her eyes, but the fresh blood dripping from her chin didn't make me feel any better. 


She hooked her arm through mine as we watched the brutal chaos surround us. I couldn't help but feel afraid that she'd suddenly turn on me, I wasn't sure if she was safe to be near. As if the universe had set out to prove me wrong, someone clutched at my free arm and tried to pull me into the disaster. 


Diana bared her teeth at the woman holding my arm, This one is *mine,* She growled in an inhuman voice. 


The stranger backed away, returning to the grotesque show. We sat there and watched until the violence died down and the guests had returned to their rooms. The lobby was awash with blood and bits of flesh, and I felt sick to my stomach. Diana patted me on the back as she stood. 


Congratulations, you've made it through your first hotel holiday, She smiled, Your shift is being extended. We need to check in the morning to see how many guests we lost.


I hesitated before speaking, unsure if my voice would work, Won't people come looking for them?


We have people to take care of that, and people to clean all of this up. Everything is fine, it's just another day at the hotel. You should get some sleep before we check the rooms in a few hours.


I laid down on the soft couch in the office, but I couldn't sleep. I'd never get the scene I witnessed out of my head, and I feared for my life more now than I ever had before. *Just another day? How was this considered a holiday?* I was so exhausted that I couldn't keep my eyes open, and I fell asleep to fearful thoughts. 


How was I supposed to stay sane when I still had nearly two months left on my contract? How was I supposed to get used to their idea of holidays? I didn't understand how they could be so nonchalant about massacring guests. I felt a deep sadness for the human guests who had thought this hotel was a safe haven amidst a dangerous forest. 


This place might end up being the death of me, and every time something crazy like this happens I flash back to the words I was told on my first day. 


*You'll see much worse, trust me.* 


Those words still remain true. Apocalypse Day may have been violent and gruesome, but it wasn't the most terrifying night of the job. 


----


[Related](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6104g9/the_good_shade_hotel/)


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kinda ruined it for me too, surprisingly enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume by the dates on the receipts, even if you were ordering one thing he always took it down on the pad and put those handwritten receipts under the register after ringing them up. 

Probably just kept tabs on who came in more than a few times and counted up their receipts. That's what my guess is at least, they didn't find a huge amount of bodies so I'm guessing it's not often that someone comes in 47 times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thankfully I have a few years before then. I could use a break before my next near death experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might let it get a little soupy before eating, but it sounds so good. What are the chances that more than one ice cream shop stores corpses with the product?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never stop eating ice cream, just let it get a little soupy so you can be positive there are no teeth or other decayed body parts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Club 27? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have all of my teeth currently, I'm fairly sure the tooth in my dessert had fallen from a deteriorated corpse, rather than being put there intentionally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds delicious, I hope it was toothless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing o:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's NaNoWriMo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Was Almost In The Lucky 47 Club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack Meyer was the nicest man I ever knew. He ran an ice cream shop in our neighborhood, and everyone flocked to it year round. He never closed for cold season, partly because it wasn't *that* cold around here and partly because some people crave ice cream mid winter. He was kind to every one of his customers. He was fair on prices, and even gave discounts for larger families-- like mine. 


He was an all around good guy, and he loved making people smile. He hand-churned all of the ice cream he sold, and worked hard to keep his shop open and pristine. Mr Meyer's wife died a few years ago, and since then he's been working hard and running the shop all on his own. Sad story that one was, she had a heart attack on their 47th anniversary. Their love story was adorable. 


That anniversary wasn't for their wedding, it was for the day they went on their first date. They were young lovers-- extremely young-- and had been living next door to each other for their entire lives. As the story goes, a 6 year old Jack asked the 8 year old May out for a picnic in his backyard. Best friends for years afterwards, and their official relationship began in their early teens. I remember how old Miss May would blush when he told people that story. 


*Oh Jack, that was ages ago! It doesn't count!* 


*Of course it does, I swear that was the day I fell in love with you.* 


The whole neighborhood was distraught when they'd heard of May Meyer's death. She was the sweetest woman, part of what had always made the little shop so pleasant. She made my first visit to the shop a happy and memorable one. 


*Hello there young man, who might you be?* 


*I'm Joshua Shepherd,* My young face had smiled up at her. 


*You can call me Miss May, what can we get you?* 


I ordered ice cream for myself and two of my younger sisters who were waiting at a table by the door. I had to run back and ask what kind of ice cream the girls wanted, and Miss May waited patiently for me to return. Mr Meyer scooped up three cones and passed them to May, who handed them to me with a grin. 


*Free of charge,* She smiled. 


I stared at her in awe, never knowing a free treat in my life. She shooed me away with a hand gesture and another grin, and I've never forgotten that small act of kindness. The only reason our parents had sent us off to the shop that day was so that they could fight over finances in private, and my mother seemed both surprised and relieved when we arrived home without spending a penny. I think Miss Mays kind gesture was part of the reason that we splurged a few times a year and bought the whole family ice cream at once. 


Things changed after Miss May passed away, but Jack has always kept a pleasant atmosphere about the shop. The biggest change was her absence, but a notable difference was his new promotion. It was pretty special since it wasn't advertised. On your 46th visit to his store you'd find out that your next visit was free. 


A few weeks ago I hit visit number 46. When Mr Meyer revealed to me that my next visit would be free I was ecstatic, and when he asked me not to advertise it I agreed. Not that the cost was expensive for me-- since I'm living alone and have a decent paying job now-- but I enjoyed being part of something special. I forgot about my free visit until a few days ago, and that's when I realized the significance. The odd number was in honor of his late wife, and it gave me warm thoughts. *How sweet, it's just like Mr Meyer to still be doing kind acts in memory of Miss May.* 


The idea of a free visit brought back my fond memories of Miss May, and I was excited to be a part of honoring her kind soul. I decided to head into the shop the next evening, I didn't want to forget about the special visit. Jack's face lit up as I entered the shop. 


Josh! He exclaimed happily, Lucky number 47!


Hey Mister Meyer, thanks for the free visit, I smiled at him, his joy was contagious. 


Not just a free visit, young man, I also have a surprise! Can't tell anyone bout your visit though, don't want them young ones getting greedy and coming in more just to be in the Lucky 47 club. 


I was excited about whatever he considered a surprise. No one ever talked about having a 47th visit, likely out of respect for Mr Meyers request. I liked that it was a surprise. It's no fun to destroy a nice gesture with greed, it was the random and surprising nature that made visit 47 so much like something Miss May would have done. This deal he offered was not about saving money, it was about honoring her. 


He explained to me the surprise, a serving of a flavor he had created in honor of May called Lucky 47, and the opportunity to come behind the counter and learn how he churned the ice cream. At the end of the visit I would be dubbed an official member of the secretive Lucky 47 club. Suffice to say I was thrilled at the idea of adding the new memory of the shop to the similar memories from when I was young. 


Now I'll give you a bigger serving than normal, you're probably the eldest I ever had become a Lucky 47, He chuckled, but I knew I was an oddity for coming back to the neighborhood I had grown up in just for some nostalgic ice cream. 


He served up a big bowl of the flavor, and set off behind the counter to clean up before it was time to close. I was excited about the portion sizing, it was the biggest I had ever seen anyone get from the shop in the near 12 years I'd been coming here. The ice cream was delicious, a creamy French vanilla with swirls of fudge and chunks of toffee. I couldn't pinpoint what else was put into it, but the aftertaste was odd. Mr Meyer had just gone into the back of the shop to fetch something when I bit into something odd. 


Upon spitting the hard object into my palm I was concerned-- it was a piece of a tooth. I figured the toffee had chipped one of mine, so ran my tongue around my mouth searching for the broken tooth. No dice. I checked with my finger and still found no jagged edge. It suddenly dawned on me that the tooth that I had spit out did not belong to me. I was disgusted and desperately wanted to leave without embarrassing Mr Meyer. He always took great pride in his product, and would be devastated to learn that there had been a major mistake made in this batch. 


*How do you even accidentally drop a piece of a tooth in your ice cream?* It wasn't impossible, but it was repulsive enough for me to bail out on the rest of the Lucky 47 perks. I stood to leave and a wave of dizziness washed over me. Instantly I had an intense feeling of something being *very* wrong in the shop. 


I stumbled towards the door, my vision blurring as my body swayed uncontrollably. I heard heavy footsteps approaching from the back of the shop. 


Hey boy, you didn't finish your ice cream! The footsteps quickened towards me, and I tried to speed up my own tipsy steps. 


I may have been nearly forty years younger than him, but whatever he had put in Lucky 47 was leveling the playing field. Being younger and stronger didn't matter when every movement felt like swimming through wet cement. Before he caught up to me I managed to wrench open the door to the shop and fall onto the pavement face first. 


I had blacked out as I hit the ground, and I later came to in the hospital with a crowd of doctors and police surrounding me. Questions and confusion berated me throughout my stay and the few days since I've been back home. I've told the police about my experience, and how kind Mr Meyer had always been to everyone. 


Since that day I've heard rumors and seen news reports about Mr Meyer's shop. The shop has been shut down, Jack Meyer is missing, and they found several bodies stored in the back freezer with the ice cream. They were all young, kids and teens who had gone missing in the years since May Meyer died. I can only assume that something snapped in Mr Meyer when his wife died. 


I suppose it makes sense that word never spread about Jack Meyer's secret Lucky 47 club, no one lived long enough to tell. 


----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasteless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Begging for attention

That I never receive 

You'd think I'd learn my lesson 

After what you did to me

Asking for permission

I'll do anything you say 

A master of submission 

I'm so easy to sway 

You don't deserve my time

You don't deserve my love 

My heart's stuck in a vice 

I can't help but crave someone

Anyone, anything

Doesn't matter who

I'd do anything for attention 

I'm a simple, tasteless, fool

When everything is over 

I'll move on to the next one

I apologize my dear

I can't help but to crave blood 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try not to, I kinda like you humans 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Sister Didn't Exist Until I Found Her Journal (Final) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This journey starts [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zys6i/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/) and continues [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60niox/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/). 


Apologies for the delay, I've had to work on relocating myself after the incidents that have occurred and meeting my sister. All of that is elaborated upon below, and I believe this is the last time I'll bother you with my story. I'll pick up where I left off. 


----


We decided that one of the other girls would call the police if Allison hadnt contacted us by morning. We didnt want another false report ruining our credibility. In the case that things went entirely wrong, we'd need to be able to go to them for help. If she didnt contact us by morning, then itd be unusual behavior for her. Shes lost her phone and taken off with guys in the middle of the night a few too many times in the past. We had to hope it was one of those instances until shed be gone longer than normal. Then we could involve the police.


So we hurried back inside to the make the call, it was getting late and we didnt want to have to wait another twenty four hours. Once inside I set the phone on speaker in the middle of the table, the girls sat patiently beside me as we dialed. One ring. He answered right away.


Ah, Lilith, its been awhile! He greeted cheerfully.


Dont call me that, its not my name.


Of course it is, no matter if you dont appreciate it. Funny in your situation, is it not? 


What? I didn't understand what could possibly be humorous about the situation at this point. 


Come now child, your mother was a biblical woman, you have learned enough about demons, have you not? 


Im not sure what youre talking about, I replied hesitantly. 


Well, in your reincarnated case, things are not as you may have read them. Mother of demons, created to rule. Seems an unfortunate act of Fate had your polarizing figure created as a sister. You love each other, now that is what makes the situation hilarious, He chuckled at his own statement. 


I honestly have no clue what any of that gibberish means. 


His voice took on a cold tone, Child, it is not gibberish. You are as human as I, as the ones you believed to be your parents for so long. You are the next leader, you are the one who will reign in the End. 


I was skeptical about what he was claiming, but I figured playing along was the only way to get more information, If Im the ruler of.. Demons? I began hesitantly. 


Mhmm, 


Then why are there others trying to kill me?


Ah now, asking appropriate questions, Fair Lady. You are widely considered too weak to rule, your affection for your sister was well known, even as she was wiped from your memories, it remained. Quite the cause of controversy, though there are few who believe it would make for an interesting ruler. He sounded satisfied that I had asked for the information. 


And those are the people who have been following me? I questioned.


Oh no, our kind wouldnt be so blatantly careless while tracking you, those are humans. They seek to destroy you before you awaken, He said it as though he just told me it was going to be sunny tomorrow, so nonchalant and unconcerned. 


Oh.. I had no idea what to say, I wasnt even sure if I should believe any of what he was telling me. 


Yes, yes. On another note, all of your memories should be restored, Eve was quite wise about the journal when she snuck back to that house to place it. Smart little thing since she awoke. 


Wait, what? His mention of the journal piqued my curiosity. 


All in due time child, youve only got about four months before you awaken. Use your time wisely, dont let the humans get to you. You should be strong enough by now to deal with your own kind. He sounded so pleased with himself, and the call suddenly went silent. 


I stared at the phone for a moment, unsure of why he ended the call so abruptly. I looked at my roommates sitting around me, they looked incredibly concerned. 


So, that guy is absolutely nuts? Maya said with a nervous laugh, her eyes darted around as though she was afraid someone would hear. 


Um, yea.. I looked her over, she seemed to flinch away when I spoke, *what the fuck?* All that stuff was super crazy, doesnt make any sense. 


She nodded and spoke softly, Mmm yea, Im going to go lie down. Its late. Get some sleep guys, that call was super weird.


She got up and walked away, and I looked to Raven for some reassurance. She put a finger to her lips and gestured towards our bedroom, I followed in quietly. 


What do you think? I whispered to her. 


I think Maya is fucking terrified of you, and I dont quite believe that guy was crazy. It all kind of makes sense, doesnt it? She didnt look scared, she looked concerned, as though she was worried the flood of information would break me. 


Im pretty sure that Im human, I pulled at the edge of my shirt nervously, the words sounded false when I said them.


Really? Because youre hot as *hell*, She smiled at her joke, and I elbowed her softly.


She was trying to lighten the mood, which was a nice contrast from Mayas reaction. I curled into her on the bed, trying to clear my head and think about the phone call rationally. *Lilith and Eve*, honestly everyone just thought it was cute when we were younger, named of the two first women. What kind of joke had my life become? Midnight had definitely been right about things being different from what I learned as a child. 


I didnt fully understand how this could be anywhere near true, wouldnt I know if I wasnt human? I thought back over my life as I laid there, noting all of the times that people seemed irrationally wary of me. Id had a fair amount of friends though, I attracted people, Ive been told that Im charming. The revelation set in deeper as I realized all the ways people had described me in the past. *Charming, sly, smart, alluring, reckless, daring.* Theres so many other words that have been used, but thinking back on all Ive ever known about demons, it sure seemed that I had the traits of one. Im not evil though. Ive never had the desire to hurt someone, or do anything awful. Maybe slightly rambunctious, with the sneaking around and my past romantic relationships. 


I sighed and curled in deeper to Raven, suddenly feeling cold. Maybe I wouldnt know until the supposed Awakening. Maybe I was just freaking myself out over the ramblings of a madman. I fell asleep curled up there, pondering over my entire life and how it was not what I'd thought. 



I woke up the next morning late for class. I decided to skip for the day, it seemed well deserved after all the craziness. I walked into the living area of the apartment planning to grab myself some coffee so that I could clear my thoughts and figure out what to do next. I noticed that Mayas door was ajar as I walked by, peeking through the opening showed that she was absent from her room. She wasnt in the apartment at all, but I assumed at first that she might have classes that day. 


I went to get my drink and noticed the laptop sitting open on the table. An email was open, with a video attachment. I clicked the attachment and was shocked. Allison was in the video, she was tied to a chair, in the middle of some sort of chalk circle. The floor was covered in odd markings. A group of hooded people surrounded her, chanting in a foreign language that Im fairly sure was Latin. Isnt it always Latin? 


The chanting ended and nothing happened, a few of the hoods look towards each other as though confused. A tall feminine figure with a face hidden by the hood of a red sweater stepped forward from the group of surrounding people. I stopped the video, and called for Raven. A feeling of deep unease was settling throughout my body, and I didnt want to be alone. We sat down together and continued the video. 


The red hooded woman walked to the edge of the room and picked up two things, a wooden box and a gallon jug full of liquid. The horror set in at this point, and I realized I was about to witness something that couldnt be unseen. I couldn't bring myself to stop watching though. The woman walked back over to the chair and set the box beneath it, then she proceeded to pour the contents of the jug all over Allison's body. She started screaming, she knew what was about to happen. 


The woman stepped back into the circle of people, and they all took a step backwards to widen the circle. A short chant began, and suddenly the box was lit. I clutched my face in my hands so that I wouldnt see Allison burned alive, but I could still hear her agonized screams. The sound abruptly cut off, and I looked up to see Raven fastforwarding the video. 


When it began playing again the fire had stopped, and the hooded people were dragging the smoking body away. I didnt understand how a fire could burn in such a way, it wasnt natural. The red hooded woman walked up to the camera, removing her hood to reveal a mask. It was the visage of a porcelain doll, beautiful and haunting. She put a thin finger up to her plastic lips, and then the video ended.


Raven was shaking, and I was so shocked that I couldnt speak. We needed to tell someone. I was about to get up and try to contact the police, but an email came in right as I was going to stand. Without touching the computer, the email opened. Large red text flashed across the screen, *Keep quiet, or end up like this one. Youve already had one follower lost. Followers of Lilith, renounce or be redeemed.* 


What the *fuck?* I could hardly understand, but this was my fault. These fanatics thought that my friends were *followers.* Why was this happening? Eve had been right, I shouldnt have told my roommates anything, I should have left when I started being followed. My guilty thoughts were interrupted by the flashing screen in front of me. The email went white, and before my eyes I saw the page retreat to the inbox. Every message disappeared from the inbox at a rapid speed, the browser closed and the screen went black after flickering for a few minutes. 


I tried to see if it would turn back on, but it was useless. The computer made a sputtering noise when I hit the power button, and a small puff of smoke came from the side where the fan ejected air.I turned the computer over to try and give it air to cool off, but parts of the plastic melted before my very eyes. I reached out to see if I could remove the battery, but the computer was painfully hot to the touch. Whoever had sent the message had done something to cover their tracks. 


Suddenly it hit me what the message had said. Maya. Had they already taken her? I called her phone, hoping against everything that I was wrong. She answered, to my surprise, but my sigh of relief caught in my throat.


Dont contact me again, you disgust me. You killed my friend. 


Maya? Its me, Lily-- I started to tell her, but she cut me off. 


Lilith, She corrected, Leave me alone. I saw what you did to Allison. 


She hung up on me. I didnt understand why she was so pissed at me, but I was still at least relieved that she was okay. I could understand why she blamed me. I wanted Raven to leave too, but she refused. I felt guilty for her staying, but I had nowhere else to go at the time and she wasn't budging. Raven and I spent the next several days trying to read up on demons, it wasnt really eye opening. 


Nothing substantial turned up, and Maya still wouldnt come home. She talked to Raven occasionally, but eventually told her that she didnt want to associate with a follower of Lilith. I couldnt understand how my entire life had flipped around, it had only been a little over two weeks since I found the journal. Between attending classes I read about demons, and tried to contact Midnight again. The number didnt show up on the card again, and the number in my call log gave me a message about it being disconnected. 


I spent a lot of time looking at the last journal entry, but it also provided no help. There was one line, *Fear not, Im coming to save you.* I had no idea how my sister would manage to find me, and what would happen once she did, but it was almost a reassuring message. The days faded into a relative sense of normal. Raven and I were alone in the apartment, Maya hated us, and the car that had been following me before it took Allison had returned. 


The relative peace that had fallen over us for nearly a week was shattered the day Maya came back home. I walked into the apartment after class one day, and everything was silent. It scared me, because Raven was always home before me. The calm of the past week had set me on edge, after Allisons murder, the threats against us, and our minimal luck finding solid evidence against whoever was doing this, calm was the most irrational thing we experienced. 


There was no going to the police unless we wanted to end up like Allison, and there was no explaining to them that I was some sort of demonic heir and everyone around me was in danger. I spent part of the week urging Raven to leave, to go back home to her parents and forget about me, but she wanted to ride this out with me. I wish so much that she had listened and left. I wish I knew somewhere I could have run off to, but my parents house was full of people doing repairs. There was nowhere I could go without dragging more people into this mess. 


I called out Ravens name into the silent apartment, and was met with a muffled thudding noise. I hurried into the room that still contained all of Mayas things, it was where the sound had come from. There she was. Maya was splattered with blood, it dripped from the front of her body, pooling on top of the body beneath her. She sat straddling the corpse, holding the body down as she repeatedly brought down the bloody kitchen knife. She must have gone absolutely insane, Raven was already dead. 


She laid there lifeless as the blade punctured her chest over and over. I lost it. With a sound of rage I didnt know I could produce, I lunged across the room, taking Maya to the floor. She tried to guide the knife into my stomach, but somehow I managed to wrench it from her hand. I held her down with all of my weight, hesitating with the knife over her throat. She laughed then, the blood splatter on her face making the hysterical sound seem even more menacing. 


What did you do?! She was your friend! 


She laughed again at my statement, the sound becoming raspy from the force she used to produce it, You look as you should! She giggled, leaning forward so that the knife pressed slightly into her throat, Im no friend to the followers of Lilith. 


Her hand abruptly shot out from where it was pinned, and she pulled the knife into her. I scrambled away as the blood came forth, and she laughed until the sound died with her body. I was enraged, shocked, and covered in the intermingled blood of my two closest friends. I walked to the bathroom in shock, knowing that there was nothing I could do. Calling the police would only cause worse problems, my fingerprints were on the weapon that killed my friends. I was covered in their blood. I had to leave, I had to go anywhere but here. 


Allison had been gone for over a week, her family was bound to notice her lack of contact and send someone looking. Someone was going to find that somehow, I was the only person alive left living here. I looked in the mirror, prepared to wash the blood off and was taken aback. I saw the darkness receding from my eyes, and I knew for sure at that moment that Midnight had been right about my less than human biology. I understood why Maya had said that I looked as I should. 


I rinsed the blood off, ran to my room, changed clothes, and packed a quick bag. I had no idea where I was going, but I was leaving as soon as possible. I opened the front door to leave and was met with a face that I only knew from memories. 


Hey there, Lilith, Eve smiled at me as though her presence was to be expected.


I embraced her, and revealed my panic over everything that was happening. 


I know, I know, Im here to help. Lets go, She walked out the door with purpose, and I followed behind, sinking into the role of obedient little sister with ease. 


She hopped in the driver's seat of a car, and beckoned for me to get in as well. Once in the vehicle I turned to her again. 


What about the people who have been watching me? How did you get here? Where have you *been*? I listed off the first of many questions that were flooding to the surface. 


Theyre gone, not sure where. I dealt with it, not important, She spoke as she pulled out of the parking lot, I actually was in a psychiatric institution for about three years, when I was 18 I was able to leave of my own accord. The ones possessing our parents didnt have the right to leave me in there, and I stopped talking about the visions. They figured I was sane enough. Since then Ive been around, She shrugged as though it wasnt important, Ive seen this happen already, I knew where you were. 


Why didnt you come sooner? Why didnt you stop my friends from getting hurt? I yelled at her. 


She had been free and roaming for *years*, and she waited until *now*to help me? 


She shrugged again, Youre my only concern. I put the journal in the house back when I set up the fire. They were getting to close to finding me, and I needed you to be ready to trust me. 


Why wouldnt I trust you? I asked, trying to wrap my head around all the information I was receiving at once. Eve started the fire. 


She shrugged yet again, staring intently at road signs as she drove, I was beginning to get extremely annoyed by her attitude towards everything. 


Its just the way things were set out to be, Im sorry about your friends, She placed a hand over mine reassuringly, still staring at the signs.


Abruptly she turned a corner and released my hand. 


Why now? I dont understand.


Youre going to awaken soon, signs should be showing, and the blocks placed on your memory werent weak enough to break until recently, She said it as though it was the most obvious thing in the world, and I supposed that knowing all these secrets for her entire life gave her reason to act so.


Midnight? I said hesitantly, not knowing what question to ask now. 


Ah him, quite a fan of you. Hes been helpful, She didn't seem pleased while talking about him.


Eve, I honestly dont understand most of whats going on. Can you just explain?


When we arrive. 


She stayed relatively silent for the rest of the ride, only answering simple questions. After over two hours of driving we pulled up to a decrepit building in a city I didnt recognize. 


Whats this? 


Abandoned, She stated simply, walking confidently towards the back door, This is where were staying, dont have to worry about anyone finding us. 


The interior of the building was cold and musty, dust sat in a thick layer over everything. 


Ready? She asked as we entered a room containing sleeping bags, a camp stove, and several backpacks of supplies. I nodded, unsure of what I was agreeing to.


You already know what Midnight told you, Im Eve, you're Lilith. Reincarnations and such. Youre going to awaken, meaning youll have all the power of the highest ranking demons, okay? 


I nodded, Id come to terms with this while reading about demons, but it wasnt exactly information I could put to good use. 


Youve got some. Power, that is-- She paused as she opened the backpacks, searching for something, Totally useless right now, far as I know. Youll have more if you awaken. Basically, youll probably cause the apocalypse when that happens, but youll be a ruler. Im pretty much your opposite, they think I make you weak. Not sure on that, havent actually seen past when I found you. 


You stopped having visions? I asked. 


Mhmm, seems so. The last one I had was of your friends dying, that was months ago. 


Oh.. I had no idea how I was supposed to respond to that. You know who has been following me? 


Oh them, yea. Theyre a group of people that consider themselves the saviors to humanity, they want to kill you and anyone who might be on your side. Demon hunters, I suppose, She pulled out some packages and started the stove, sitting down in front of it. 


You killed the demons that took our parents bodies? 


Kinda, not really. I released them, may those bodies rest in piece. Not that easy to kill a demon. 


Why did they take you away?


Supposedly youd be stronger without ever having me meddle in your life. They couldnt kill me, because our lives were tied for 18 years, She shrugged. 


Will you stop doing that! This is still relatively new to me and youre acting like its nothing. 


She sighed, It really is nothing, She dropped some spices that I didnt recognize into the pot on the stove, Until you turned 18, we were tied. You died, I died. They didnt want one side to have all the power if they got to one of us. 


Oh.. I was speechless yet again, and I sat down on one of the sleeping bags so I could sort through this information. Eve She looked up from the boiling pot, Why did they wait so long to come after me?


Once we were untied, there was one more boundary set in play, to keep the sides even. She took the pot off the stove and stood, We can only truly end eachother, Guilt filled her voice, Youre hard to hurt, you arent natural. One born as a miracle, one born of a deal. 


So we'll never die?


She didn't respond right away, she seemed lost in thought, Our parents were so greedy. They couldn't accept what the heavens gave them and had to bargain for more, Her sudden mood shift scared me. 


She looked so *angry*, and she gripped the pot handles so tightly that her knuckles turned white. I wanted to stand, I wanted to go to her side and offer reassuring words, but none came to mind. 


Eve-- My words were cut off by my own scream, searing hot liquid covered my face and upper body. 


I stared at my arms, steam and smoke were coming from my skin at an alarming speed. It was the most excruciating pain I had ever experienced, and I saw that the liquid was eating away at my flesh. I stood, absolutely enraged. My anger made the pain fade away. 


I have to do this! It's my job, I can't let you hurt anyone else! She screamed, brandishing a knife I hadn't noticed before. 


I don't know what came over me, but I lunged at her. Pure rage flowed through the entirety of my being, only enhanced as I wrapped my hands around her throat. 


She struggled to speak, You will bring the End. 


She barely choked out the words as I tightened my grip. I couldn't let her kill me. She stabbed at me weakly, I barely felt the knife enter my body. I felt as the life left her body, not as a loss but as a rush. It was a thrilling feeling of power, and I could sense that it was okay to let her body fall to the floor. 


The first day I reunited with my sister I killed her. I felt her power come into me, and I think it may have sped along the process of me becoming stronger. I suppose I was already stronger than she had expected. She let me lose *everything* because she expected that I would bring the End. 


Maybe I will, if I'm mad enough. For now though, I'm just searching for more of my kind. Followers to lead. It's time I took my place, and show them all that I'm not the weak little girl who was led into a trap with a journal. 


My sister existed before I found that journal, and it's the reason that she doesn't exist now. 


----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much 3 

There is definitely going to be more Good Shade in the future, with fun little hints at characters from other posts c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She killed herself two years ago, but her "ghost" asked him to *completely* kill her. She wanted him to destroy the photo, the last part of her left in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems horror to me, and amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll work on compiling some of my interesting encounters, I'm currently on leave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Beautiful Roses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

As a child I lived in Turkey. Since growing up and moving to the United States I have realized that many people know nothing of the country. It was not the best of places, nor the worst of places, but that isn't important. The one spectacular part about that country was that it is pretty much the only place in the world where you can find black roses. 


I adored the flower, I found them so deeply beautiful. It wasn't long before I decided to grow them around my own home. I lived alone with my father, and the first time that the flowers bloomed outside our home he was unhappy. He thought they were hideous. I ignored his displeasure, these flowers were the one thing in the world that brought me joy. 


My father was a cruel man, he was not good at raising a daughter on his own. I did the housework exclusively, and I made all the meals. He told me that it was my place. He let me tend to my flowers as long as I was obedient. I did my best to do everything correctly, but more often than not I faced severe punishment over miniscule errors. There were many times when I was punished for nothing at all. 


My father bore a hatred for the world that I never knew the source of, and as I grew older I realized that he also bore a hatred for women. He took those hatreds out on me, I became both servant and wife. I was entirely miserable, but so very afraid. My only solace was tending to my roses. They were the last beautiful thing in my life at that point. 


One day when I neared the age of 15 I met a strange woman on my trip to get food for our dinner. She looked like a gypsy, and she fell in step with me as I walked. 


Child, I know you have been hurt, She looked me over from head to toe, Hurt quite deeply.


I nodded. 


Your roses can help you, and this, She held out a bundle of strange looking flowers, Witch hazel. 


I took the bundle hesitantly, What for?


A few of these, and one rose under the bed, each night. Save yourself, She abruptly turned and walked away. 


I didn't understand, but decided to try it just to see what would happen. That night after father was done with me and had fallen asleep, I snuck into his room and placed the plants under his bed. I did so every day for a week. Each morning he complained of being sicker, and he seemed to grow too weak to bother punishing me. 


On the seventh day he didn't arise from his bed. I found him in a puddle of his own blood, it had seemingly spewed from every orifice. My pain was over. I've made sure to always grow black roses since then. They truly are the most amazing flower. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh thank you, I will move it c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what's wrong with it, I've written something similar for this sub before. Should I move it to sad stories?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Learn From Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had an insatiable desire to write. I longed to weave tales that would unsettle, chill, and terrify. When I first began, I felt a lack of creativity. I had so many *ideas* and no idea how to execute them. 


I didn't know how to describe the way a river of blood could erupt from a wound. I had no idea how to tell someone what the taste of flesh is like, how it might feel to pull meat from the bones of another human. How could I display the fear a victim feels when they are being hunted at night by a stranger, and the emotion that rushes through the stranger when he watches the life fade from the eyes of his prey? 


There are so many details that go into creating something that truly makes a reader feel afraid, repulsed, or even happy. Some of us take sick pleasure in reading about the gruesome end of other people. We judge a piece of work by how well the writer displayed the emotions and actions of the characters. How could anyone just *think* of such things? They're awful, surely no one could simply imagine such horrifying and grotesque scenarios. 


That's what this place is for. The one place in the world where you read about these victims witnessing and experiencing the most horrifying things, and where sinister folks tell the tales of the prey they hunt. I never meant to become the type of person who could post here, my intention was to seek inspiration. All I needed was experience so that I could surpass my writer's block and accurately describe any scenario. I did so by getting involved in said scenarios. 


I visited hospitals, stood by as I watched families grieve over the death of a loved one. I watched as broken and bloodied citizens were rushed into the emergency room. There was blood, bone, despair, and the sense of urgency was nearly palpable. Being there gave me some sort of idea of how I could portray the physical pain of being dangerously hurt, and the emotional toll of death on a loved one. 


It was a great first step, it helped me figure out how to begin writing my book. I came to a point not long after where I realized that I didn't have enough information. I couldn't put any more words towards the book. My limited knowledge was expended and I was faced with another block. I needed to seek out another angle of research. I needed to witness a death, preferable a violent murder. I know it sounds wrong to seek out such a thing, but how else could I create an accurate account for my book? 


I roamed the dark streets at night, walking through the most violent part of the city. I saw aggression, violent fights, and the shadiest of interactions. I had yet to a death. One of those nights I was driving around looking for a place to stop and wander, as I pulled up to the side of the road I saw a girl around my age run out of an alley. A tall man was yelling and following her, she was in tears as she ran in front of my car. She was lucky I was already stopping. 


I beckoned out my window to her, Need a ride?


Apparently the man following her was not keen on the idea, he picked up his pace and began telling louder, his words intermingled with enough curse words to make the foulest mouth feel envy. The girl quickly ran to the passenger side of my car and scrambled in. 


Thank you so much Miss, please, please just drive, She pleaded as soon as the door was shut. 


The man began running towards the car, and I sped away. She told me where she lived, and I asked if the man would show up at her house. She sheepishly admitted that he was only a one night stand that got aggressive when she tried to leave. He shouldn't know where she lived. We made small talk as we drove-- about the college she was attending, and other meaningless things. 


We pulled into a parking lot behind her building, and I asked if she wanted to be escorted upstairs. She declined the offer, but I got out of the car anyways to light a cigarette. Her keys fell under the car as she hopped out, and I went to assist her with the light from my phone. She leaned down next to the open car door, groping the ground for her keys. On an impulse I quickly slammed the door shut, her head between it and the car. There was a sickening crunch, and her body crumpled as I released the door so that it fell open. 


I glanced around the lot, not seeing anyone. I quickly leaned over her body and pulled out the small pocket knife I kept for protection-- a lady can never be too prepared-- from the glove box. I crouched next to her body, checking for a pulse. None to be found, the force I'd used on the door seemed to have snapped her neck. I was pleased with the ease of the action, my next task was a little harder. I used the knife to carve out a steak sized chunk from her thigh, placing the meat in a ziploc bag from my purse. 


I closed the passenger door, got in the driver's seat and drove away. I was thrilled, I had so much new information to write about. I could feel my creativity flowing already. My next course of action would be the cook the meat and taste it, I had to learn the flavor and texture. Once I had done that I could write, and plan out what type of information I'd need to learn from my next victim. It was a beautiful start to my ability to write as well as I do now. 


You may think this is extreme, but honestly think about it. You read a lot of awful things, right? Could you pop accurate descriptions of those awful things off the top of your head? Of course not! It's not an odd thing to do at all. 


Sometimes writers need to learn from experience. 


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try to compile some tales of our more "interesting" guests for the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When the Good Shade finds out about the existence of a Shade that has never been a guest, they will send an invitation :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, Alice has visited this sub before but she was using a different name then. She's actually the one who pointed out the loopholes to me. 

I'm not sure how a romance would go haha, I'd need to make sure I constantly had a vial on hand to avoid side effects of being with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh, I always love seeing your comments in this sub. 

The song is too fitting for my experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll definitely be back to talk about some of the more... *interesting* guests that I've encountered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Personal stats: Updated 05/9**

Appeals: 2 

Total posts this month: 9

Subs: 3

*Posts by sub:*

**Nosleep**: 4

**Youpoetried**: 4

**Shortscarystories**: 1  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Good Shade Hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was out of work and looking for something to pay the rent until I could find a new job that was in my field, when I saw the add. I'd been scrolling through job listings when it caught my eye, *Several positions open at The Good Shade Hotel. $40+ per hour.* Well damn, that was way more than decent pay to work in a hotel. I was shocked that they'd even have open positions if they're paying that much, but it seemed to be my lucky day. I mean sure I lived in a huge city, but it was odd that I'd never heard of the place when it obviously was making a lot of money. 


I figured it must be extremely classy and high maintenance, and I was prepared to put up with some rich jerks if it meant a sweet paycheck. There was no address or phone number, just an email. I shot out a reply containing my resume, and kept looking through the other offers on the site. Before I found anything else that might be worth applying for, my inbox pinged. The people at the Good Shade were quick in their response. 


*Dear Mr. Stephens,* 


*It has come to our attention that you would like to apply for a position at The Good Shade Hotel. Your resume has been taken into account, and we require you to answer several follow-up questions so that you may be considered for the job.* 


Then came a series of questions, some were normal and others were extremely odd. I thought maybe they were trying to rule out anyone who might be crazy. No one wants psychotic hotel staff after all, right? 


*Have you had prior experience working in customer service and/or hospitality?* 


Yes, both. Prior experience in a small motel. 

*Would you be comfortable filling out an NDA form?* 


Yes. 


*Would you be comfortable working in a remote location?* 


Yes. 


*Are you willing/able to drive a long distance to attend work?*


Yes. 


*Are you willing/able to work night shifts?* 


Yes. 


*Which type(s) of position(s) are you looking for?* 


Any available, preferably not housekeeping, but willing if need be. 


*Have you had any issues with mental illness?* 


No. 


*Do you take any medications? If yes, please list.* 


No. 


*Do you believe in paranormal/supernatural/extraterrestrial beings?*


Not really, there's no proof of them. Unsure of my beliefs in the afterlife. 


*How many people live in your household?*


Only myself. 


*What is your marital/relationship status?* 


Single, never married. 


*Have you ever heard of our hotel?* 


Only in the job listing I responded to. 


*Do you contain 100% human genetics?* 


As far as I know, yes. 


*What caused you to apply for work here?* 


I am unemployed, have experience in this type of work, and could honestly use the money. 


*Please list any questions or concerns below your responses, we will respond to your application promptly. An affirmative response to your application will come with an email containing the details of your job placement, and a few documents requiring signature. Thank you for applying at The Good Shade Hotel.*


*- A. Smith, Owner   Manager.*


Like I said, some super odd questions. I wasn't about to turn it down though, I needed the money. I didn't think much of the odd questions anyways, the only logical explanation was that they had a bad experience with a psycho employee or two. If I was paying that much to employ someone, you're damn sure I'd want to make sure they didn't think they were E.T. I answered every question as truthfully as possible and sent the email back, confident that I'd be getting the job. 


My confidence was not misplaced, I received the affirmative response within the hour. I was overjoyed, this job paid so well that I'd never want to look for a different one. The new email gave me an address that I was to be at at exactly 4pm the next day. I would be working as a receptionist-- 40$ an hour to answer phones, put reservations into computers, and give out room keys-- it would be simple. Maybe not the most stimulating work, but tolerable. 


The drive out to the address I was given was odd. I passed through a tunnel I had been through a few times before, but I could swear that I didn't recognize the area I was in after coming out of the tunnel. I pushed my confusion aside, figuring that the landscape had changed since my last time in the area. I arrived at the address after over an hour of driving, it was remote and surrounded by forest. 


The building itself was grand. 15 stories high, beautiful architecture. The trees surrounding the hotel were probably the tallest I'd ever seen in my life, they seemed to scrape the sky. Somehow the hotel managed to look perfectly normal amidst the beautiful natural environment that stretched far into the distance. It was the only building for miles around, and it was well hidden. It occurred to me that the guests likely paid very well for this sort of seclusion, it was deeply peaceful. 


When I entered the building I found it to be dark and elegant. The place was so classy that the paycheck suddenly seemed reasonable. It wasn't the biggest hotel, but it was probably the fanciest one I'd set foot inside in my entire life. The lobby seemed cavernous, and my steps seemed to echo as I walked up to the front desk. 


Behind the desk stood a pretty redhead, she smiled as I came forward. 


How can I help you, sir? She asked politely in a sweet sing-song voice. 


Oh, uh.. I'm here for the receptionist position, I shook myself mentally, I had been staring. 


She giggled at my flustered state, I'll let Mister Smith know you've arrived. 


I resumed my staring as she walked away, there was something different about that girl. She returned with a tall man in tow. We shook hands and introduced ourselves, but I found myself distracted by the smiling redhead. Mister Smith seemed to notice my waning attention, he led me behind the desk and into an office. 


Quite the nuisance that Alphaea is, He chuckled fondly. 


Alphaea? I questioned, the unusual name felt odd on my tongue. 


Ah yes, I believe she is calling herself Alice now. Kind creature, when she wants to be. She's here from time to time to help out, you shouldn't experience any negative side effects, He replied, seemingly lost in thought. 


I had no idea what he meant, but I assumed he meant the immediate attraction I felt for her. She must have a history of fellow employees lusting after her. 


Ready for your entry meeting? He asked abruptly, apparently back on track. 


I nodded, and the meeting that followed left me confused and-- to be entirely honest-- a little freaked out. He went over the questions from my application, we discussed them in slightly more detail, and he provided more information about the job and its requirements. I had to sign a form before we even began talking about the position. Fortunately, a loophole Ive found in the contracts does not disallow me from posting my entire experience in a place that most of the world thinks is for fictional tales. I know that this place holds the truth, you know it too. This is the one place where I can freely talk about my experience, and Im so thankful to be able to get it all off of my chest.


Anyways, the rest of the meeting brought to light some of the reasons why I may not be allowed to speak of the job or the guests, but it initially made me wonder if perhaps my boss was insane. 


100% human genetics? He questioned as he looked over my application, Very good, the guests have been missing having someone of your appeal. 


Then he began listing the details of the position. I would mainly be working at the front desk, there may be occasional instances when I am requested by a guest to deliver items to their room. They may also request too *look* at me for a maximum of 5 minutes, with zero physical contact. I am to avoid any physical contact-- including accidentally brushing against the clients. The contract requires three months minimum attendance before I may opt out, and opting out comes with what he called a mandatory deconditioning. Opportunities to opt out and be debriefed are provided at three month intervals, attempting to quit before one of the intervals breaks the rules of the contract. 


He listed off the consequences of breaking the contract at such a speed that I barely understood them, and followed up by saying, I think youll do wonderfully here, Mr. Stephens. 


I was kind of dazed from all the information, but signed the contract. My boss might be a little crazy, and the requirements might be slightly odd, but the money wasnt something I could pass up. How bad could it be? 


My first shift was that very evening, I'd be working the desk alongside Alice. Mister Smith came up to the desk as I adjusted the nametag he had given me, *Tyler Stephens, H.S*. 


Alph-- Alice, He sighed, Be nice to this young man, it's hard to find people like him. 


She pouted for a moment, then nodded. Smith shifted his gaze to me and held out his hand. It contained a small vial of milky liquid. 


If you start to become delusional, a drop in each eye, He turned and walked away. 


I looked to Alice in confusion, It's in your contract, She said, That'll kill any negative side effects if you happen to touch the wrong guest, or spend too much time with me.


She gave a wide smile, and for a moment her teeth looked unnaturally sharp. I slipped the vial into my pocket, feeling incredibly skeptical about the entire job. It was too late to back out though, I had already signed the contract. The beginning of the shift was slow, no guests had come to check in or out. I found myself staring at Alice again, her nametag caught my eye. *Alphaea, I.C.* 


No last name? I asked. 


She glanced at her nametag, Don't have one, at least not one that would fit or make sense on a nametag, She shrugged. 


And the letters? H.S, I.C? 


*Homo Sapien, Illecebrsa Cur.* Scientific name in your case, the Shades decided mine, She said nonchalantly, typing something into the computer. 


*Illecebrsa Cur*? Shades? What? I laughed, thinking it was some kind of joke on the newbie. 


Charming Mutt, She said dryly, Their sense of humor is immaculate. It doesn't pay to be one of a kind. 


I stared for a moment, looking for a hint that she was joking. Her face remained completely serious. 


Oh I responded, not sure what to say. 


She started laughing at of nowhere, and I was relieved for a moment. 


You really have no idea what youve gotten yourself into, huh? 


Im a really overpaid receptionist, and Im the victim of the weirdest hazing ever? I said with a nervous laugh. 


She giggled again, I could tell you, but I think itd be more fun to watch you gradually realize what youre part of, She paused, looking around the empty lobby, Ill tell you this though. The name has a reason, all of our guests are Shades of some sort. Im one as well, in fact youll probably be the only person roaming around wearing an *H.S* for the entirety of your employment. 


I have no idea what a Shade is, I told her. 


Her response was a wide smile, revealing rows of shark-like teeth. I took a step back, letting out another nervous laugh. I was afraid. 


They're real, wanna touch? She asked, the amusement on her face was plain to see. 


I shook my head no, unable to respond. She shrugged and turned back to the computer. I wasn't sure what to think, but I was now wholeheartedly aware that this girl was *not* human. The room fell silent, I had no idea how to start a conversation after seeing that. 


Alice's voice broke the tension, Sylvia should be here in exactly two minutes. 


I nodded, still not trusting myself to say something that wouldn't have me eaten by those teeth. She was right though, I watched the clock on the far wall tick the time away. Exactly 120 ticks later the front door opened. 


A girl who had to be no older than 12 entered. She was a horrifying mess. Covered in dirt and blood, her left arm was bent at an unnatural angle and a bone was protruding grotesquely from her forearm. She dragged her right leg behind her, the ankle quite obviously broken, and a deep gash in her forehead was pouring blood. My first instinct was to scream, and my second was to run to help. 


Alice yelled for me to stop, but I ignored her. I ran to the young girl.


Ohmygod, are you okay? Do you need me to call you an ambulance? What happened? The words erupted from my mouth, hardly a space for breath between them. 


She stared blankly into the distance, not acknowledging my panicked questions, I reached out for her and Alice yelled from near the desk, *STOP!*


Too late. I gripped the girl's shoulders and stared at her. Her eyes were glazed over with a milky white, and she let out a piercing scream when my hands made contact. Before I could blink she was gone. My hands were grasping at empty air. She had simply and entirely disappeared from the lobby. 


You moron! Alice yelled at me again. 


I started at her, nowhere near understanding what had just occurred. 


She sighed as she saw my face, Now she's going to loop. She'll be back in an hour. 


What? 


You're not supposed to touch the guests, She stated, sounding annoyed. 


We need to call the police, she was seriously hurt! I was freaking out. 


She was seriously dead, She said dryly, The phones here don't make calls to 911 anyways. She's a Shade. Stop panicking. You'll get used to it.


I couldn't think of any response to that. I still hadn't fully grasped what this job was all about. I suddenly realized that I had no feeling in my hands, I clutched them close to my chest to discover that they were cold as ice. Instantly the feeling spread, deep into my chest and up my arms. I was freezing, and began shivering violently as I walked back to the desk. 


Alice glanced at me when I arrived beside her, and let out another exasperated sigh. 


Give me the vial, tip your head back, She ordered. 


I pulled it out from my pocket while she took an eye dropper from a drawer in the desk. I watched as she squeezed the end of the dropper to pull liquid from the vile. The milky substance turned a pale purple as it entered the dropper. I leaned my head back and allowed her to put a drop in each of my eyes. As she tucked the vial back into my pocket and put away the dropper I felt the cold leave my body. 


When Sylvia gets back I'll deal with her, She said calmly, Maybe you should just watch for the first couple of days. There's a lot to learn about the different types of Shades that we room. 


I nodded, and sat patiently. I looked over the fine print in my contract while we waited, *Early dismissal from any staff position will result in an extremely painful deconditioning process. It is highly recommended to wait the entire three month period so that we may provide a nearly painless process.* Based on what I had already seen tonight, I didn't want to know what these people considered a painful process. I'd stick out the job for three months, and quit if I couldn't handle the insanity. 


Soon enough Sylvia came back. She looked exactly the same as she had an hour ago. I resisted the urge to both scream and vomit. Alice called out to her. 


Hi Sylvia, sweetie! She walked over and knelt in front of the mangled girl, Welcome back to the Good Shade, I'm sorry to tell you again, but you're dead. 


Sylvia's head snapped toward Alice at an inhuman speed. She nodded, seeming to think for a moment. 


We have room U344 available for you, Alice told her, holding out a key card. 


The girl nodded again, took the key, and shuffled her way towards the elevator. When the doors shut behind her I let out the breath I hadn't realized I was holding. Alice walked back over and sat at the desk. 


There's no one else scheduled for tonight, you could probably nap until the shift ends.


Yea, I might I started, then curiosity got the best of me, U344? 


Oh, Mister Smith forgot to tell you? Well, we have 50 floors of underground rooms, She told me, A lot of the guests prefer it.


I don't know why it surprised me, after everything else that had happened. I was sitting next to a girl with shark teeth, and we had just let a mangled corpse into the hotel. What else? 


I don't know how I'm going to manage the next three months without having nightmares, I laughed, but the statement was entirely serious. 


Oh honey, Alice giggled, You'll see much worse, trust me. 


I stared at her sharp teeth and felt a chill run through me. She wasn't wrong about that. 

----

[Aphaea's Post](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ux2ut/how_to_drive_a_boy_crazy/)

[Hotel Holiday](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61xh3y/our_hotel_celebrates_the_strangest_holidays/)

[Delivery for the Good Shade](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/649wuc/a_delivery_to_the_good_shade_hotel/)

[A New Employee](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/67ra3h/this_job_has_given_me_more_than_just_money/?ref=share ref_source=link)


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you dead OP? Did he come back for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This entire story is in hindsight, as I've said before. The events that took place in these first two posts are already a week or more in the past. The only things that have happened while posting my journey are some of the events which will be elaborated upon in my next post. Nothing is really being posted "mid-action".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drag me into the darkest depths, 

Take me, suffocate me

Gasping, clawing, reaching for breath 

Life shattered, please replace me

-//-

Sing the song of my demise

The soundtrack of each piercing slice 

Watch my body crash to the floor

Take me under

My life is yours 

-//-

Hear the call of death itself

The screeching in this silent house 

The scratching, creaking, whispery noise 

The cries of those without a voice 

-//-

Take me away from my pain

Tip the king of my chess game 

The pounding heartbeat finally stops

No more time left on this clock

-//- 

Rushing, racing, 

End awaiting 

Life ticks by

I fall, complacent 

Death looks up to me 

From the pavement



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could work, but the driver of the car seems to keep a close eye out for cameras  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Others are trying to get rid of me, I think I can catch up to where I am currently in the next post. It'll explain a little more about why I'm not missing/dead yet. 

At the point when this part of my story takes place, I have no idea where my sister is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as far as we knew at that point, we had no solid proof that she was really missing. She's prone to taking off with boys, so the rational solution was to wait until at least morning if she didn't contact us. That way we would have reason to be concerned, because then it wouldn't be so close to her normal behavior. 

Even if one of the other girls called right away, it would look bad on us if the police came to the apartment and realized I was the girl who had already called in "false" reports twice. Especially about a person who bailed on us relatively often when she ran into someone. We didn't want them to not look for her thinking that we were trying to prank them "again". 

And also to be honest, it was partially because none of us knew if you could report someone missing with no solid information, and so soon after you couldn't locate them. According to the information I've found for our state, we weren't entirely wrong about waiting. You usually need sufficient reason to report an adult missing, and depending on department policy you are supposed to wait 24 - 48 hours. 

So if the department near us enforced that policy for non-vulnerable people, we'd still be out of luck. The chances of us getting turned away until she had been gone for an amount of time that was unusual were very high. 

Also it's been nearly two weeks since she went missing, I'm not reporting my experiences directly as they happen. Far too late now to worry about her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Sister Didn't Exist Until I Found Her Journal (Part Two) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you missed the beginning of my fall into the rabbit hole that my life has become, it can be found [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zys6i/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/).


I apologize in advance for how slow my updates come along, honestly things have been absolutely crazy for me. I can hardly keep track of the days, I've only had the journal for a few weeks. I know I said a few months ago was when the fire happened, but I wasn't expecting to be able to tell my story so soon. The fire happened early February, and I got into the house in the beginning of March. Just a small timeline for anyone confused, maybe you can keep track for yourself. Time means nothing at this point. Anyways, Ill continue catching up where I left off.


After a thoroughly exhausting discussion about finding the journal and what it could mean, we all went to our rooms. I was so tired that when I curled up in Raven's bed I fell asleep instantaneously. I woke up suddenly in the night, checking the clock showed the time as nearly 1am. I was about to tuck myself back into Raven and sleep again, but a glint of silver caught my eye. 


It was the card that Id left on the end table. I picked it up for a moment and looked it over, there was something that I hadnt seen before. On the back was a phone number. Yet another confusing thing to add to my day, because I was positive I hadnt seen the number earlier. I debated calling to see who on earth this guy may be, but a second glance at the clock ticking the minutes away towards morning made me decide to put it off until daylight. 


When morning arrived I chose to attend my classes for the day, I didnt want the weird things going on in my personal life to set me back. On my drive back to the apartment afterwards I could swear I saw the car that had followed me. It was parked a block down from my building, *so much for evading the stalker.* I nearly turned the car around and left, but I realized that there was no point. If the car was here then they already knew what building I lived in. I wished I hadnt asked Raven to drive it home for me, but I needed it to get to class. It had felt like there were eyes on me constantly throughout the day, and the feeling didnt subside when I arrived home.


It seemed that things were just going to become more strange and frightening for me no matter how I tried to avoid them. When I got inside I told the girls about the car that had followed me the day before, and Raven chimed in about seeing the Mister Midnight guy by my car after Id ditched it. We all came to the mutual agreement that this was insanely weird, and I suggested we call the number on the card. 


Maya looked at me in confusion, There is no number on the card. 


Yea there is, I noticed it last night. Hold on, Ill go grab it, I ran into my room and picked the card up off the table, but no matter how I looked at it Maya was right. There was no number on the card. 


I returned to the living room and let the girls know that I had probably dreamed there being a number, but on the inside I was *positive* that I had seen it. We discussed other options. We could follow the car that had been stalking me, run an extensive search for Mister Midnight online, or confront whoever was driving the strange car. When the third option was brought up it felt like a cold hand raked down my spine. *Bad idea.* I didnt know why the feeling was so strong, but I knew that we *definitely* should not approach the car without knowing who was in it. 


The other two options seemed simple enough. Well, the online research did. As for stalking my stalker, the only time I had seen the car was when it was following me, or sitting parked nearby. How were we supposed to follow a vehicle that was just following me around? Wed be going in circles. So for the time being, we didnt do anything ourselves about the tail. Nothing had come of it yet, and whoever it was already knew where I lived and likely knew where I went to school. There was nothing else that following me would reveal to the stalker. Though it was creepy, whoever it was hasnt actually *done* anything except follow and keep a distance. 


Probably not the best mindset, but there was a simple option to deal with the stalker. I called the police. Unfortunately that didn't pan out well. Whoever was in the car wasn't technically considered a stalker because they hadn't attempted to make any sort of contact with me, and I had literally zero proof of someone following me. I was told to inform them if the stranger made any repeated attempts of communication, threatened me, or I could provide proof. I made a mental note to write down the license plate and try to get pictures. Other than that the police were absolutely no help to me at that moment.


Over the next few days I kept to my mental notation, every time I saw the car I looked for the license plate number. To my dismay I discovered that I was either being followed by several cars of the same model, or the person following me changed license plates to avoid being tracked down so easily. I made note of at least four different license plates, and contacted the police department again with the information. Honestly the woman on the phone seemed exasperated with me, but I suppose I might seem a little paranoid being that I still hadnt been able to get a picture. 


Not for lack of trying though, every time I pulled out my phone to take a picture, the car sped off with a screech. I ended up with a series of pictures too blurry to be reasonable evidence, or no picture at all. It was frustrating to say the least, and Im sure it made me look insane. Apparently my pestering worked, because the woman asked me to hold while she ran the plates. After a few minutes she came back on the line sounding extremely annoyed.


Maam, it is not appropriate to waste valuable police time on false accusations. Please stop calling our department unless you have a serious matter and *actual* evidence to report, She said it as though she was about to end the call on me.


Wait no, I quickly chimed in before she could hang up, What was wrong with what I reported? 


She sighed heavily, The last time you called, you had no proof. Now your version of *proof* is license plate numbers from four different vehicles. All of which are registered to different people across the state. None of the vehicles are in any way the vehicle that you described to be following you. Next time you try to pull one over on the police, think up a more elaborate lie. One more false report from you, and you *will* be charged. Youre lucky that Im not having you charged right now. She abruptly hung up the phone, there was an audible *thunk* sound before the click of the connection being cut off.


That was not at all what I had been expecting. I didnt even think of how bad it might look for me by reporting so many license plates and claiming they were all from one vehicle. Clearly the stalker had thought well ahead of me. The police road was a dead end, unless I received an obviously traceable threat, or some really compelling proof, I was fucked. Calling them was no longer an option, Id probably have to be in imminent danger for them to believe me. I was incredibly discouraged. 


Our next resource was the web search for all things related to Mister Midnight. Unfortunately that was almost as much of a bust as contacting the police. The girls had only managed to find one site, and even that was nearly bare of information. They showed it to me when I arrived home, they had found a single web page. It was identical to the card I had received several days prior. I was annoyed and went to click out of the web page, when a flicker caught my eye. The script that read, *Well call you* had changed. The message now read, *With a name like Midnight, you ought to be aware of these things known as hints*. 


Well *shit*, if that didnt make it obvious enough. I instantly recalled seeing the number several nights prior, sometime between midnight and 1am. Im not normally one to believe in things that seem like magic, so I convinced myself that the business card functioned with some sort of time lapsed optical illusion. Which sounds equally as ridiculous as a magical business card, in my opinion. I wasnt sure if we should contact him right away, but the others convinced me, *tonight is as good as tomorrow, until tomorrow is too late.* Raven and her way with words. 


There were still several hours until midnight, so that gave me some time to look through the journal a bit more. It had been several days and I figured, as Raven had said, tonight is as good as tomorrow. Though when it came to the journal sooner was better than later. With all the discoveries that this book could and had already uncovered, it was probably my most important resource. I wasn't sure if reading more could bring up or cause anything worse because things were already so far from normal. The other girls started to cook dinner, so I slunk off to my room to do some reading.


I pulled up the journal and flipped to the next page.


*If you've come this far then you already know something is wrong, and by this point you're not alone. Unfortunately it's not the type of company that you're hoping for. You're not surrounded by life. It may be better for everyone around you if you left as soon as possible. I already know you won't though. There's nowhere for you to go, and I'm sorry that I brought all of this onto you.*


Then came the memory trigger. 


*I never wanted to leave, but when our parents got taken I had no choice. I had to go where they sent me.*


The memory hit hard and fast like all the others. Before the direct memory there came a broad revelation. I recalled that around the time I turned 11 not only did my parents change and become secluded, but they changed towards me and my sister. It was mostly Eve though. They started acting like she was some sort of evil that was living in their house. Over the next two years the tension rose, and the house felt like a coffin. It was suffocating to be at home, there was constant disapproval, constant beratement, and for Eve there wasn't a thing that she could do that was right. 


Our parents started pressuring me to let them know whenever Eve had made a claim about telling the future. In the past it had just been something silly that was pretty much ignored, or on certain occasions something that would make our mother strictly tell us, Do *not* run around saying such things, you are good little Christian girls, and you do *not* lie about that devil magic nonsense! 


We always joked about how mom was too serious about church when that happened, but we were passed the time of being reprimanded that way. Being a good little Christian girl no longer mattered at this point, we had stopped going to church and our mother had generally stopped preaching to us at home. The closest she came to her old ways was whenever we did something bad and she brought up the fact that wed to go to hell. That was never a threat in the past, but she became so fixated on it as we got older. 


The true memory that played behind my eyelids started late one night. Eve and I were in our room sleeping-- well not really sleeping, but pretending at least-- and when the house got quiet we assumed that our parents were asleep. That's when it would be safe to whisper. Eve started talking about how she had a prediction. She saw something but she didn't know what it was, it was like a darkness that came into the house. She told me that she'd been trying to tell me for the last two years, but she hadn't had a chance because of how much things had changed and how afraid she was. 


Apparently it was the same prediction that she had when I was only seven. She told me that she saw a darkness come into our house at night and enter into our parents bedroom, and it never came out. It never left at all. The next day the people who came out of that bedroom weren't really our parents. They had been taken-- or so she said. I found myself once again confused by what she was saying, *what did she mean our parents had been taken?* They were still right here with us. 


She saw my confusion and tried to clarify herself, The people in our house look like our parents, but only the bodies. Mom and Dad arent inside anymore, and--


Before she could finish her explanation our mother walked in the room. She walked over to my bed first, her footfalls sharp and quick. I was instantly terrified. She leaned over and pressed her hand into my face, gripping me by both cheeks, her nails digging in.


You were supposed to be asleep, and I know that you're talking about those ridiculous fantasies that Eve has been having again, She looked at me, her eyes appearing to have no whites or pupils. 


They were entirely black, and the terror that coursed through me intensified. I was not only scared due to the pain from her nails digging into my cheeks, but also the look of anger on her face which seemed absolutely inhuman. 


Lily, stop listening to your sister, she's crazy. This the last straw. I think it's time that she got some help, She let go of my face abruptly and my head fell back and hit the headboard with a loud thump. 


I was stunned, pain blooming from the blow as well as the crescents her nails had left in my cheeks. She walked over to Eve next, and I heard the whisper that wasn't meant for my ears. 


You already know too much, and if you could have just shut your mouth then maybe this wouldn't need to happen. I'm happy it ends this way. Tomorrow you're gone. I'm not dealing with you getting in the way of everything, She followed up her threat by smacking Eve across the face, the impact of the slap was hard enough to seemingly echo through our bedroom. 


When she left Eve only said one hushed statement to me, I told you that you'd forget, and I told you that you'd remember. I'll miss you, we should go to sleep now, She rolled over and buried herself in the blankets. I didn't reply, yet again I had no idea what to say.


The next morning Eve was shipped off to a psychiatric institute. The entire morning was tense-- to say the least. I hardly spoke for fear of what my mother might do to one of us if I said something out of line. People showed up at the door and took Eve to a car, she waved goodbye to me but I didn't wave back. I was distraught. I still didn't fully understand the situation, I almost believed that my parents were right about her being crazy. That didn't make sense though, what about the safe? What about all the other things that she had said to me in the past that had come true? Most important of all, what about what our mother had said last night about getting in the way? Why would they send her away with so little warning?


After Eve was gone my mother gave me an acid dipped smile, Don't be upset, we're going to see a good doctor today and you won't have to think about this ever again. 


Her grin widened, and once again I watched her eyes turn dark. I was afraid. My whole family was gone, my parents were not my parents, and my sister had been sent away for knowing the truth. I ran from the room and hid. I had no idea what they were going to do to me. Hiding was no use, when it was time to leave the *thing* pretending to be my mother fetched me with ease. I had been curled up under my bed, hoping they would ignore me, or at least be unable to find me long enough for me to sneak out of the house. She wrapped her hands around my ankles, digging her sharp claw-length nails into my skin again, and pulled me out with an incredible amount of force. 


My face scraped roughly against the carpet, and I vaguely wondered what this supposed doctor would think of my injuries. She clutched my wrist tightly enough that I thought the bones may crack, and pulled me out to the car. I spent the entire ride rubbing my sore wrist, and running my fingers lightly over the crescent shaped cuts that speckled my cheeks. Eventually we arrived in front of a small brown building, it kind of looked like a walk-in clinic. My parents took me inside and introduced me to a man that they called Doctor Midnight. He smiled at me as I sat down in his chair, and I noticed that his eyes were almost as dark as I had seen my mother's become.


The last part of the memory was him leaning in and whispering to me, *This could be temporary.*


When my vision cleared it took me a moment to gather myself. I paged through the rest of the book, but it was all blank except for one other page. The memory solidified the fact that we needed to call that number. It turns out that I *did* in fact know who Mister Midnight was, he was the reason that I couldn't remember anything about my sister before finding this journal. Maybe he knew more about what happened, but regardless of that contacting him was the most logical next step. I had to know why he had come looking for me, why he took my memories, and how *exactly* he knew that my memories would only be stolen temporarily.


I relayed my most recent memory to my roommates, and we waited until midnight. I pulled out the card after the clock ticked a few seconds past the hour. As if by Magic the glittery script appeared on the back before my very eyes. There was his phone number. I went to gather the girls so that we could all call him together, but Allison was nowhere to be found. I showed Maya and Raven the number that appeared on the card, then I asked if either of them knew where Allison had disappeared to. 


According to Maya, she had apparently gone outside almost an hour go to have a smoke. This put me into a panic, and I looked outside to see if my constant watcher was still sitting out there. For the first time in days there was no car sitting outside the building. My stomach sank. We rushed outside to see if she was anywhere to be found. No such luck. We all tried calling her phone, only to find it had been tossed beneath a bush. 


Upon closer examination I noticed that her lock screen was set to something unusual, it was a picture of text. Looking closely it read, *Stop trying to meddle. This one isnt coming back. She wont be the last.* I thought that maybe this would be worthy enough to go to the police with, but again I realized how ridiculous it would sound. They already considered me a liar, and this was an accusation that could get us all into some serious trouble. There were various reasons that wed have to wait to make a report. She had only been gone an hour, and sometimes people dropped their phones. 


Shes only 19, for all anyone knows she could have run away with a boy-- shes definitely the type, and it wouldnt be the first time. Hell, she even could have written the note herself as a prank. I was already unreliable in the eyes of the police, so Id have to wait until something more solid came up before we could ask for their help. My only worry was that if this whole situation continued the way it was going, theres no way that I could tell them the whole story. I would sound absolutely insane. 


For a moment I wondered if maybe I was, maybe my friends were just humoring me because my parents had died. I questioned Maya and Raven, but they seemed to be taking the entire situation seriously, memory stealing doctor, future seeing sister and all. We decided that our best option was to go through with the call. It was the only source we had that may give us answers, he could know who has been following me, he could know who took Allison. My only hope was that he was at least a neutral party in all of this, or else we could be digging an even deeper hole. 



Thats all Ive got time to post right now, sorry again for the delays. I hope to be able to finish the catch-up in my next post, and get to the current insanity Ive been dealing with. 


----

[Final](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61ihg4/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/)

[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mixing acid with other chemicals is a normal part of the lesson plan, as far as we were taught. 

They are kept in a sort of cupboard type thing that can be locked, but it is opened during class so that students can take chemicals to work on reactions for the assignments. 

I'm fairly sure it's quite common to have acids accessible for the lessons, because we learned a lot about how to neutralize the acids in case of a spill, and how to dilute them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm having a lot of fun with it, loose themes are my jam c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue eyes, blonde hair

Perfect smile, skin fair

Liked by all, loved by none 

Pretty girls are heartless ones

-- //

Sweet words to public eyes

A pretty face

Most classic disguise 

Charming voice tells ugly lies

-- //

Classic stereotype

Rings so true

Mean girl clich 

Is once again proved 

-- //

You hated me so 

You told me to die 

Harsh pretty face 

Bid me goodbye 

-- //

Wrote me off

And cast me aside

Then acted aloof

When they discovered I died 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
