<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1702</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'til *he's* off, and *she's* on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over bashing is more of a concern. I can look at her leaving Fox, writing about her experience of sexual harrassment at Fox, and her speaking up against Bill O'Reilly in an email, as heroic. Is Megyn Kelly a "*Hero*"?....,...Is she Heroic? Sure, this is heroic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Joy Reid and her guests discuss two new investigations being launched in the wake of FOX paying five women $13 million after they accused Bill OReilly of sexual harassment (which he denies).* *Duration 10:55*




AM Joy Reid and **her bipartisan political pundit panel** discuss the implications of sexual harrassment scandals onto **Conservative Political News network FOX NEWS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OReilly faces investigations after settlements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it say Weedend, or Weekend...looks the same to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I know it's cool to do that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Passover and Moses would do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not fair! when you're pinned into a high profile gig with money and fame and public sway, that few women get, acting "complicit" *is* a result of the sexual harassment, a result of the environment of all the men, co-workers and bosses and CEO's at Fox News, Pawlease! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rep. Barbara Lee joins Joy Reid on her mission* ***to repeal the AUMF, which she calls a 'blank check' for presidents to go to perpetual war.*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Lee: Congress is missing in action on AUMF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL Weedend Update Rips Bill O'Reilly For His 13 Million Dollar Sexual Harassment Settlements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to give her a chance at notFox, no expectations though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, okay, i took the relevant excerpts, and the hill reported on the Nytimes article here: http://thehill.com/homenews/news/328949-megyn-kelly-left-fox-in-part-due-to-oreilly-report </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~I think this nytimes article is free/doesn't count towards free ten or whatever, but not certain~~ *NOT FREE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **From nytimes:**

"Look, its open season, he said, visibly irritated, when asked about a recently published book by Megyn Kelly, his colleague at the time. In the book, Ms. Kelly provided an account of being sexually harassed by Roger Ailes, the networks former chairman. Later Mr. OReilly added, Lets whack the Fox News Channel. Ive had enough of it. Its a good place to work. All right?"


"The comments set off a media firestorm and frustrated Ms. Kelly, who sent an email to Fox News executives complaining about his behavior and the chilling effect it could have on women at the company and beyond, according to four people with knowledge of the email who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal matters."


"Despite Ms. Kellys complaint, and a plea from a producer that Mr. OReilly not be allowed to make similar remarks on his prime-time show, Mr. OReilly delivered a second public scolding on the program that night."


"If you dont like whats happening in the workplace, go to human resources or leave, he said."


"That experience, along with a deep skepticism about whether the network was truly committed to changing its culture after Mr. Ailes was forced out, was a factor in Ms. Kellys decision to leave Fox News for a new role at NBC News, according to two people familiar with the matter.""
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OReillys Behavior Said to Have Helped Drive Megyn Kelly Out at Fox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "His absence has not made advertisers hearts grow fonder. Even with Dana Perino hosting Factor on Wednesday and Eric Bolling leading the program on Thursday, the show has featured approximately 10 national commercials each night. In the month prior to the disclosure of the settlements, OReillys program carriedan average of 33 national ads totaling more than 14 minutes, according to Kantar, a tracker of ad spending."


"Some of the Madison Avenue scatter from OReillys show may be more for show than for real. The advertisers appear to be using a tactic that is common when Madison Avenue wishes to avoid negative publicity associated with a particular program, but in fact likes the results derived from advertising on the network that shows it. Marketers decision to keep money at Fox News suggests some of them may be waiting to see if a return is possible."


"Even so, those defections ought to be taken seriously. In mid-2015, marketers including General Mills, Yum Brands Pizza Hut, PepsiCos Pure Leaf Iced Tea, Choice Hotels and Crayola LLC all publicly stated they had removed their commercials from 19 Kids and Counting, a TLC reality show that spotlighted the Duggar family, in light of news that the oldest boy in the family had sexually assaulted teenage girls. But none of the sponsors pulled their ad dollars previously earmarked for TLC or other properties owned by its parent, Discovery Communications. The show was eventually canceled"


"A network can keep any series on the air it chooses  if it has the willpower. In 2008, a handful of sponsors pulled out of Swingtown, a CBS drama that examined spouse-swapping in the 1970s, among its other elements. The network filled its advertising holes with direct-response ads for Time-Life 1970s music compilations, and soldiered on."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Bill OReilly on Vacation, Advertisers Still Avoid Fox News Factor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @Andy Richter: My daughter couldn't make it today but she made a sign for us to carry #TaxMarch #taxmarchla </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay if people want to believe this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump wirepooped his pants, source: BBC.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does it mean, *to play us out?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Affairs and Malevolence  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is well-read cool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old dogs smell their own butts it goes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humpty Dumpty fell off the wall... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (CNN): "Now that Neil Gorsuch has taken his seat as the 113th Supreme Court justice, his judicial life is going to change in many ways. One striking difference is he will no longer be subject to a written ethics code, as he was as a judge on the 10th US Circuit Court of Appeals..."


"Members of Congress have repeatedly called on the justices to adopt an ethics code. Most recently, Sen. Chris Murphy, D-Connecticut, and Rep. Louise Slaughter, D-New York, introduced the Supreme Court Ethics Act of 2017, which would give the court six months to "promulgate a code of ethics" based on the Code of Conduct for US Judges already in effect for the lower federal courts..."


**"Instead, the objective of a code would be to set discernible standards for the justices' conduct so that the public could know the norms to which the justices are holding themselves."**



"Is it acceptable for justices to speak at charitable fund-raisers or to solicit contributions? To vacation with litigants during pending proceedings? To comment on legal issues or cases pending in other courts? To accept gifts from political activists or to criticize candidates for office? All of these events have occurred and others -- such as providing anonymous leaks to the press -- have been suspected. Although the public may consider certain conduct problematic or unethical, there is no authoritative statement from the court itself about limits on the conduct of the individual justices."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Gorsuch can forget about ethics code for court now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look, its open season, he said, visibly irritated, when asked about a recently published book by Megyn Kelly, his colleague at the time. In the book, Ms. Kelly provided an account of being sexually harassed by Roger Ailes, the networks former chairman. Later Mr. OReilly added, Lets whack the Fox News Channel. Ive had enough of it. Its a good place to work. All right?"

"The comments set off a media firestorm and frustrated Ms. Kelly, who sent an email to Fox News executives complaining about his behavior and the chilling effect it could have on women at the company and beyond, according to four people with knowledge of the email who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal matters."

"Despite Ms. Kellys complaint, and a plea from a producer that Mr. OReilly not be allowed to make similar remarks on his prime-time show, Mr. OReilly delivered a second public scolding on the program that night."

"If you dont like whats happening in the workplace, go to human resources or leave, he said."

"That experience, along with a deep skepticism about whether the network was truly committed to changing its culture after Mr. Ailes was forced out, was a factor in Ms. Kellys decision to leave Fox News for a new role at NBC News, according to two people familiar with the matter.""
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OReillys Behavior Said to Have Helped Drive Megyn Kelly Out at Fox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look, its open season, he said, visibly irritated, when asked about a recently published book by Megyn Kelly, his colleague at the time. In the book, Ms. Kelly provided an account of being sexually harassed by Roger Ailes, the networks former chairman. Later Mr. OReilly added, Lets whack the Fox News Channel. Ive had enough of it. Its a good place to work. All right?"

"The comments set off a media firestorm and frustrated Ms. Kelly, who sent an email to Fox News executives complaining about his behavior and the chilling effect it could have on women at the company and beyond, according to four people with knowledge of the email who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal matters."

"Despite Ms. Kellys complaint, and a plea from a producer that Mr. OReilly not be allowed to make similar remarks on his prime-time show, Mr. OReilly delivered a second public scolding on the program that night."

"If you dont like whats happening in the workplace, go to human resources or leave, he said."

"That experience, along with a deep skepticism about whether the network was truly committed to changing its culture after Mr. Ailes was forced out, was a factor in Ms. Kellys decision to leave Fox News for a new role at NBC News, according to two people familiar with the matter.""

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OReillys Behavior Said to Have Helped Drive Megyn Kelly Out at Fox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Brinksmanship** is a great, fun word. While his opinion is somewhat subjective, it comes from a wide perspective of being a reporter of politics forever, giving him that objectivity when editorializing where the facts are actually leading, fair objective warnings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't sure at video start, but he really says it all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Dan Rather, host of The Big Interview on AXS Tv, talks with Rachel Maddow about how Donald Trump's actions are being perceived by Americans and around the world, and what is motivating those actions.* 


***A big difference between evolution and confusion***



**Dan Rather:**  "Donald Trump sold himself, one reason he got elected, was he presented himself as a person he doesn't back down, he doesn't back up, he doesn't turn around. Well, since he's been in office, that's practically the main thing he has done; back up, back down, turn around...everything from Chinese money manipulation, to his opinion of NATO and the federal reserve, you read part of the list, but the list is longer than my arm."


*Rachel's 2 minute List from [MSNBC YouTube Erratic Donald Trump Unbeholden To Past Declarations](https://youtube.com/watch?v=Kuh_Dd9Xwqs)
 

"He's jumping around like grease on a hot skillet, now, unpredictability can be an important part of leadership, but being erratic, and coming across as confused, to not knowing not only what you believe, but where you want to go. For example, it's one thing to drop all these tomahawks, 59 tomahawks on Syria, well to what purpose? What is the strategy? What is the overarching strategy in Syria?"


"...What concerns me, and concerns a lot of people Rachel, these two bombings, the Syria Tomahawks and the Afghanistan bombings, let me make clear, as one off military operations I have no argument with that. But with those, the, I'll call the Beltway Class in Washington, and some other people around the country, who are cheering the president's military posturing, you might want to call it positioning."

"Now, we know it's a fact, that president Trump, more than some Presidents at least, he basks in admiration. That raises the question, since he's been getting some pretty good press about dropping these bombs in these places, and a concern, that he'll base his decisions, war and peace decisions in North Korea and other places, on the fact, *you know what, I've been getting some pretty good press the past ten days.*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some misreading Trump confusion as evolution: Dan Rather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rachel Maddow reports on a plan in Arkansas to perform four pairs of back-to-back executions in the span of 10 days* ***with a drug they've never used before that is set to expire at the end of the month.*** *Duration: 6:25* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arkansas plans blitz of eight prisoner executions over ten days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAN FRANCISCO (AP)  *A federal judge in San Francisco will hear arguments in the first lawsuit challenging President Donald Trump's executive order to withhold funding from communities that limit cooperation with immigration authorities*

*U.S. District Court Judge William Orrick has scheduled a hearing on Friday on San Francisco's request for a court order blocking the Trump administration from cutting off funds to any of the nation's so-called sanctuary cities.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge to hear arguments against Trump sanctuary city order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fafafooey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.Anderson Cooper, 2.Lester Holt, 3.Matt Lauer, 4.Chris Wallace, 5.George Stephanopoulos, 6.Robin Roberts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now!! I was going to say that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess all the sexual harrassment settlements are changing public opinion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THR.com:

*Trump and Clinton supporters were asked if they felt favorably or unfavorably about top broadcasters in a recent National Research Group survey commissioned by THR.
Bill O'Reilly has been voted the most unfavorably viewed news figure, according to a poll conducted by the National Research Group and commissioned by The Hollywood Reporter. Of the 1,000 respondents (all frequent news consumers, split 50-50 between Trump and Clinton supporters), 24 percent said they felt "very unfavorable" toward O'Reilly.*

*At 20 percent of respondents, Sean Hannity ranked as the second-most-unfavorably viewed news personality. Megyn Kelly and Rachel Maddow both tied at 17 percent "very unfavorable" responses, and Brian Williams was viewed very unfavorably by 14 percent.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bill O'Reilly has been voted the most unfavorably viewed news figure, according to a poll conducted by the National Research Group and commissioned by The Hollywood Reporter. Of the 1,000 respondents (all frequent news consumers, split 50-50 between Trump and Clinton supporters), 24 percent said they felt "very unfavorable" toward O'Reilly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV News Poll: Bill O'Reilly Viewed Most Negatively Among News Figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV News Poll: Bill O'Reilly Viewed Most Negatively Among News Figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Lawrence O'Donnell talks to Democrat Jon Ossoff, a 30-year-old, first-time candidate who has raised $8.3M and is currently leading in Georgia's 6th district special election. Ossoff explains why he thinks hell win despite Republicans holding the seat for 38 years.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Democrat leading in a red Georgia district special election: Jon Ossoff, a 30-year-old, first-time candidate who has raised $8.3M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like filthy Jeff Sessions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rachel Maddow reports on the outpouring of support for Maribel Trujillo, an undocumented mother of four American citizens, including a 3-year-old girl with special needs, who has no criminal record but faces deportation under Donald Trump's anti-immigration policies.*

Rachel also explores Jeff Session's planned remarks at the U.S.-Mexico border, the original speech, that he did not read aloud, stated: "take our stand against this filth." While Sessions did not have the nerve to say "filth" out loud, it reflects the Attorney General's way of thinking and making policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ICE targets mother with no criminal record for deportation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mar-a-Lago Got 13 Health Code Violations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Word with Lawerence O:
Published on Apr 12, 2017

*O'Reilly's Fox News career hangs in the balance because Wendy Walsh spoke out about sexual harassment. Wendy Walsh and Ana Marie Cox join Lawrence O'Donnell.* They react to Bill O'Reilly's Vacation as well as the possibility of more sexual harrassment claims from more women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MSNBC | Wendy Walsh Reacts To Latest Bill O'Reilly Developments | "Women's experience matters and is real" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Western Democrats are pressuring President Donald Trump not to rescind land protections put in place by President Barack Obama, including Utah's Bears Ears National Monument."


"Obama infuriated Utah Republicans when he created the monument in late December on 1.3 million acres of land that is sacred to Native Americans and home to tens of thousands of archaeological sites, including ancient cliff dwellings. Republicans have asked Trump to take the unusual step of reversing the designation, saying it will add another layer of unnecessary federal control and close the area to new energy development."


"In a letter this week, nine Western Democratic senators wrote Trump to say that weakening protections for Bears Ears or any other national monument would be a direct affront to local communities and stakeholders." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats pressure Trump to keep national monuments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems that it is not necessarily "first" that matters so much as most eyes plus substantial interesting comment. It would seem plausible that OP of each post is likely to make the first and most substantial and relatable on-topic comment or/and that the first five comments might be those that are most interested in the topic or are simply the first to point out an obvious and relatable reaction--not just being firsty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a phoney  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Kimmel: Guess Where Bill O'Reilly is Going on Vacation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third! Third is best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I am a bit weird. I just saw Bernie sweater, thought I like that sweater, thought *sweaters are progressive* has rhyme to it, and then thought of it like a protest slogan against business types. Thematic like slogany? Ya somewhat satire, but not in the insulting way it might have come off, I would really hold that sign at the appropriate pro-Dem rally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best case is he's on the side of evil corporate business self-interested himself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawrence: The Madman Is Still Loose In The White House: "the most unpresidential elected official in American history" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually extremely well said, and really sums up the legalize argument very efficiently. I inititialy responded to each individual point, but your argument does not rely on individual points, but all four points at once.  

I think, (and I'm not sure,) it is not a bad idea to take on the "pot makes you lazy and aloof* debate, to allow the legalize debate to be framed that way with the pushback to that argument you have given. 

I also think, there's that argument, that when you suddenly legalize something(and it's not that sudden anymore) that because the education is behind and the experience is less, that you will at first have more incidents of stupidness, or the appearence of more stupidness, due to the legal accessible pot at first...of course as the people catch up the education/experience that after not long the incidents are less than when illegal. And, again, your 4 points are the argument against "*stoners equals more stupid accidents.*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Rachel Maddow reports on how U.S. journalists can make leaders of less-free countries uncomfortable, and points out Secretary of State Rex Tillerson's failure to stand up for the American principle of press freedom and defend US journalists on his visit to Russia." *Duration: 8:35*


*Maddow points out some recent moments (2005 and 2016) where journalists were defended out of country, in contrast to a smirk Tillerson gave after a Russian scolded an American journalist during his visit yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secretary Tillerson fails to defend US journalist in Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um..okay, that's all good stuff, but i don't follow how that relates to *progressives wear sweaters*?" I certainly was not sumarizing the video I shared with that statement; it was an after thought pointing out that Bernie is wearing a sweater and not a business suit and tie, that sweaters are chill, what's wrong with that? I'm not trying to make a large all encompassing statement, but why can't *progressives wear sweaters* be a slogan that means a certain "political professional attire" is not necessary to run for office? I'm not saying it's the best or most important point to make, I just dig the Bernie sweater in this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans are human </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweaters are progressive! Out with Suits! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Senator Bernie Sanders tells Chris Hayes Democrats have to take their fight all over the country.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders: Dems win if we mobilize   educate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Beautiful...(*chocolate cake?*)...babies" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On par with any late night comedy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But my Spicey means resign quietly to a beach because that's what he thinks happened to Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trump essentially has four kinds of Republicans in top roles: ideological conservatives like Vice President Mike Pence; more party-establishment figures like Chief of Staff Reince Priebus; his son-in-law Jared Kushner and daughter Ivanka Trump, who had few deep ties to the GOP before Donald Trump started running for president; and the Bannon wing of nationalist-populist ideology. **The personal feuds may be compelling, but theyre much less important than whether Trump starts governing mostly through one of those GOP styles  or whether he sharply abandons one. So watch not for the decline of Bannon, but for the decline of Bannonism.**"


"Whats Bannonism? The former Breitbart editor opposes broad international trade agreements and favors an adversarial relationship between the Trump administration and the news media, as well as between the administration and the federal bureaucracy. He wants very tough policies on illegal immigration, has called for limiting refugees from the Middle East from coming to the U.S., and has expressed deep concerns about the rise of Islam, both at home and abroad." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It Doesnt Matter If Bannon Stays Or Goes. It Matters Whether Bannonism Does. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nova Seed: First 5 Min.- a post-apocalyptic tale follows a lion-man who must save the Nova Seed, a mystic force of nature in the form of a girl, from Dr. Mindskull </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Representative Ted Lieu, D-CA, speaks on the meeting between Rex Tillerson and Vladimir Putin. He also discusses the United States policies regarding Syria.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Ted Lieu: If President Trump Cared About Syrians He Wouldn't Ban Them | MSNBC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on a theory that Conservative philosophy is racist, sexist and unfair in all practices, that the means to get to the moral or whatever ideal end, is always paved with hate inequality and unfairness to others. And I think perhaps that the current GOP is more like pieces of that Conservatism inside of moderate liberals.

 So, as a Democrat, what will you do to stop evil Conservatism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Audio: Fresh Air with Terry Gross:**

*With the Federalist Society, Leonard Leo has reared a generation of originalist lites. The selection of Neil Gorsuch is just his latest achievement.*

"New Yorker staff writer Jeffrey Toobin discusses Leonard Leo, the conservative lawyer who is responsible, to a considerable extent, for one third of the justices on the Supreme Court."

Toobin discuss his New Yorker Article, [THE CONSERVATIVE PIPELINE TO THE SUPREME COURT](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/04/17/the-conservative-pipeline-to-the-supreme-court)

Toobin writes:
 "No one remembers who John Hancock was, Gorsuch said. But they know that thats a signature because he wrote his name so bigly... Gorsuchs invocation of one of Donald Trumps trademark utterances, apparently accidental, prompted an explosion of laughter from the audience."


"Seated toward the back of the hearing room, Leonard Leo smiled. Theres one sound bite, he whispered to me, then added, You know, the hearings matter so much less than they once did. We have the tools now to do all the research. We know everything theyve written. We know what theyve said. There are no surprises. Gorsuch had committed no real gaffes, caused no blowups, and barely made any newswhich was just how Leo had hoped the hearings would unfold."


"In the light of Leos perspective, **the possibility that he would put forward a Supreme Court nominee who would turn out to support abortion rights seems nonexistent.** Roberts and Alito have voted against reproductive rights; so, in all likelihood, will Gorsuch. As Edward Whelan, a prominent conservative legal activist and blogger, wrote recently, No one has been more dedicated to the enterprise of building a Supreme Court that will overturn Roe v. Wade than the Federalist Societys Leonard Leo" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh Air Audio: How One Man Brought Justices Roberts, Alito And Gorsuch To The Supreme Court; The Federalist Society's List </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Audio: Fresh Air with Terry Gross:**

*With the Federalist Society, Leonard Leo has reared a generation of originalist lites. The selection of Neil Gorsuch is just his latest achievement.*

"New Yorker staff writer Jeffrey Toobin discusses Leonard Leo, the conservative lawyer who is responsible, to a considerable extent, for one third of the justices on the Supreme Court."

Toobin discuss his New Yorker Article, [THE CONSERVATIVE PIPELINE TO THE SUPREME COURT](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/04/17/the-conservative-pipeline-to-the-supreme-court)

Toobin writes:
 "No one remembers who John Hancock was, Gorsuch said. But they know that thats a signature because he wrote his name so bigly . . . Gorsuchs invocation of one of Donald Trumps trademark utterances, apparently accidental, prompted an explosion of laughter from the audience."


"Seated toward the back of the hearing room, Leonard Leo smiled. Theres one sound bite, he whispered to me, then added, You know, the hearings matter so much less than they once did. We have the tools now to do all the research. We know everything theyve written. We know what theyve said. There are no surprises. Gorsuch had committed no real gaffes, caused no blowups, and barely made any newswhich was just how Leo had hoped the hearings would unfold."


"In the light of Leos perspective, **the possibility that he would put forward a Supreme Court nominee who would turn out to support abortion rights seems nonexistent.** Roberts and Alito have voted against reproductive rights; so, in all likelihood, will Gorsuch. As Edward Whelan, a prominent conservative legal activist and blogger, wrote recently, No one has been more dedicated to the enterprise of building a Supreme Court that will overturn Roe v. Wade than the Federalist Societys Leonard Leo" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How One Man Brought Justices Roberts, Alito and Gorsuch to the Supreme Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So deep, so off the cuff, so weird, so real and unreal, one insightful sour shoes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was what it was, what is there to say really, it was just a nice show moment, with deep track Sour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably...when there's big developments, maybe a couple more Bill O'Reilly stories should hit *politics* before it's over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I eleboratrd, that I meant, potential of addictive-ness and overuse was my devil's advocate argument, but you are correct that I did not phrase it that well for a long form debate and I was half kidding at the start  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Kimmel Can Hear the Voice Inside Sean Spicer's Head During the Disturbing Hitler Gaffe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Kimmel Gets Inside Sean Spicer's Head During the Disturbing Hitler Statement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He buts in a lot, but I like group interview with Howard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thsts what I heard, maybe he said more than that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Howard said something like, "And now [Spicer's] got the media defending Assad" because they are saying, no, no, no, Hitler was worse than Assad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said it all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer: "I'm gonna get fired the same way that Hitler got fired." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoop whoop! Rob Scheidner joining Sandler in-studio! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer is clarifying that by "get involved in Syria? No." Trump didn't mean he won't continue to drop bombs on Syria when he sees beautiful babies on TV............apparently..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cake is a lie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The narrative is there is no narrative, the president is meaningless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how long until we send 59 tomahawk missiles........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *His comments, aired* **Wednesday** *on Fox Business News, come less than a week after Trump ordered a retaliatory* **strike on Syria** *based on U.S. evidence that Syrian President Bashar Assad attacked civilians with chemical weapons*

*Trump said, "when I saw that, I said we have to do something."*

*But he also appeared to rule out deeper involvement, saying:* **"Are we going to get involved with Syria? No."**


*Trump also warned that Russian President Vladimir Putin,* **in backing Assad,** *is supporting someone who is "truly an evil person." That, Trump said, is* **very bad for Russia"** *and "very bad for mankind" and the world.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says US not going to get involved in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my impression, and legalizing would slash funding and costs of arresting and locking up low level criminals as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, Sour Artie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't taking Bill O'Reilly stuff on /r/politics if anyone is wondering..at least for the most part at this point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rachel Maddow reviews in grueling detail White House spokesman Sean Spicer's ineptitude at speaking for the White House and cleaning up his own messes, with Secretary of State Rex Tillerson doing his part to make ridiculous statements as well. Duration: 10:48* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maddow Skewers Spicer's Many Gaffes: White House ineptitude represented in its spokesman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking forward to Adam Sandler part 2 today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suspenseful opening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill O'Reilly announces he's taking a vacation amid sexual harassment scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Spicer: I'm going to get fired, like Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitler Spicer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing wrong with looking in the mirror. *Fades into setting sun* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold!  
The irony is, it is probably just the $$$$ that will win legalized weed, and it was probably just the money moralizing lying Republicans were seeking when hating weed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats an important point to legality I think, part of the argument for why people should have choice. But when someting is already illegal, it's already in that moderated system, you can't exactly use that same logic to undue it. if you saying everything should if could be moderated, you might not be able to add everything that is bad to it, but what is there you wouldn't take it out persay. You saying something here tho for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure I wasn't really trying to say that, I *was* trying to defend weed without defending all drugs or all freedom  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Therefore Trump is bad and should be illegal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya precisely. But then we can fall into all drugs and murder should be legal. The point Solidarieta was making that I avoided, is that humans should have a freedom to make moderate choices. But ya, you can't start giving examples of things conservatives would take away from you, if they could, to defend weed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Maybe 2. Ya maybe your right in this case, generally I don't like the lesser of two evil or whatever alcohol comparison, but maybe about addiction being illegal 3. Absolutely! 4. i don't know what you mean by personal, if lots of people are personally problemed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Ya that's well said. No better argument than a smart stoner!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, if EVERBODY is drinking too much water and killing themselves, it should be illegal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, education is the answer. I don't think the argument was working, because if you say one thing is destructive and legal doesn't mean another thing destructive should be legal too. In this comment reply chain, I am playing devil's advocate as stated at the outset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More of hypothetical of why weed is bad. The only somewhat worthy illegal argument is that it is somewhat addictive and sometimes leads to overuse. Lots of personal vices are illegal because many people have those personal vices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda, but if playing too much video games is destructive maybe it should be limited by laws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya but just because I can drink myself to death doesn't mean I should be stoned, more of a, do neither, why have two, why have another. 

That's cool that it is going pretty well in WA and CO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very good. Education is very important and when something is shunned, you don't know much about it when you come across it, and, AND, it's not fair to punish people for what they donno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll play devil's advocate. I smoke too much weed and don't do very much, therefore weed is bad and should be illegal..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya but those things are mostly evil, particularly as applied to the low level drug offenders who would be freed by legal weed. So the Sheriff's have the power of good and more money against them... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "**States are addicted to cannabis tax revenues.** According to a new report from New Frontier Data, states with legalized marijuana are on track to generate approximately $655 million in state taxes on retail sales in 2017. Within that tax figure, $559 million will come just from cannabis taxes, much more than from alcohol taxes."


"The report also forecasts that tax revenues in states with legalized marijuana will reach $1.8 billion, of which $1.4 billion will be from cannabis specific taxes. **This money isn't easily replaceable if the Department of Justice reviews its current approach to marijuana. Plus, the Trump administration is calling for deep cuts in many programs with its proposed budget and this puts further pressure on state governors to continue providing services its residents have come to expect.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $1 Billion In Marijuana Taxes Is Addictive To State Governors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Some five dozen companies have said they wouldn't advertise on O'Reilly's show following a report in The New York Times on April 2 that five women had been paid a total of $13 million to keep quiet about harassment allegations against cable television news' most popular personality. O'Reilly has denied any wrongdoing."

"It has left his show with a more unusual array of commercials than you'd typically see for a popular program  like Monday night's ad for a device that clears ear wax." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advertisers are fleeing Bill O'Reilly, but viewers aren't </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I know that Spicer loves Hitler... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No and I have no idea what you are referring to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duck season! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
*Rachel Maddow reports on upcoming special elections to replace members of Congress who took jobs in the Donald Trump White House, and the panic among Republicans to stave off unusually ascendant Democratic candidates. Duration: 3:24*

Polls open at 7 today in Kansas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems aim to flip red seats in Georgia, Kansas special elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rachel Maddow reports on the swearing in of Neil Gorsuch to the stolen Supreme Court seat of Obama nominee Merrick Garland and what it means for future Supreme Court confirmations.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
