<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone figured out how to watch the Super Bowl in 4k? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me (black 325ci) with two friends at a DC BMWCCA - Autocross </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you just have a gif of the pencil moving around, you can photoshop a picture of anyone in different layers. Blow the mind of the person when you show the gif to the person who is in the picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is attacking anyone, why so hostile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a german car, this guy is as good as it gets, from customer service to no BS evaluations to speed of service bostonmotorwerks.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like someone is already doing this: https://twitter.com/maturetrumptwts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this is just brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like we are heading towards another civil war...but since we are so lazy we prob play it via battlefield on Xbox..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird - I can't even find that roast on torrents...it has been permanently deleted from the record </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was even funnier when Jeff Ross told that joke to Trumps face on the Roast of Donald Trump on Comedy Central - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nf5BKAS5o6A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this guy would be great at adding you to famous movie posters...I want to standing next to Arnold in Commando holding like a minigun or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it have to be Peter?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea well I just bought the book, so it worked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always use the 'throw a bag full of goodies over the fence while your friend waits on the other side' trick. Never had an issue as long as you find a quite place to throw it over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a beauty!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'and mechanically perfect' famous last words of a BMW owner...but all jokes aside keep an eye on oil leaks and suspension issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was there as well - did they cut 'Can't Help Falling in Love' from the set? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I ask why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I confirm, drink a bottle of cab a night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watertown!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For his music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stupid question here - but will this work just as easy for women as it would for men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoying them this morning. Thank you for pointing them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 35 and this will be my 3rd Roo. I am actually excited about the EDM line up because the sets are enjoyable to watch. Acts like Major Lazer, Flume, Marshmello etc put on a great show! Its raw emotion catered to the ADD culture. Works for me. Plus U2, The XX and RHCP will give us something to sing along to. This is going to be a good one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear you waiting for the Manual! Keep the art alive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting to know what the original TG spend per episode on average for reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did they spend all the money?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read they are spending between 1 to 4 mil dollars per episode, a number that seems outrageous but compared to a typical episode of TG it seems TGT is no where near as sophisticated and/or elaborate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that sound of connection...and then 'You Got Mail!' .... and then typing 'so...you want to cyber?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a eto shto za hyi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Tesla, can you make a motorized bicycle please? Thanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Chainsmokers this year!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With out repeating most of the acts already mentioned, I will add: 

Dick Dale (boston)  
 
Sunset Music Festival (Tampa) - Jack U, Galantis, Chainsmokers (worth repeating)  
Guns n' Roses / Lenny Kravitz (Boston)  
Paul McCartney (Boston)  
Gary Clark Jr (Boston)  
Gogol Bordello (Boston)  
Bonnaroo  
Twenty One Pilots (Boston)  
Bush / Chevelle (Boston)
M83 (Boston)  
 
Flume (Boston)  
Made in America (Philly) - Rihanna, Coldplay, Lil Wayne etc  
Kaleo (Boston)
and then some </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reversing is generally easier for both parallel and regular parking as long as you learn to use all three mirrors (sides and rear view) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instead of answering 'Oh the food was great' to my waiter, I wish I could tell them how I really feel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Reddit CEO got trolled by the r/the_donald sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a G35 with a body kit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rented from Maritza's Car Rental with no issues, used the Jeep Taxi to get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 02:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The earthquake that's supposed to break california off the mainland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visiting GF's family in Southern California and can't help to think the big one is going to hit any second...how do you live with this stress?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 02:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mono Lake, California [4608x2592] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kicker is the map is upside down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and Pete Davidson is their son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it looks like Brady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For when you can't afford official NFL gear in Boston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's a lot of numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 12:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl bottom left is stroking out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like a commercial for the last 15 years of my life minus expensive cars and tuxedos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coooool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 02 325 ci - Clutch pedal dropped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick story - I was getting off the highway entering my work's parking lot when the clutch pedal dropped and had no pressure. It was mid switching gears and I was rolling in neutral. The car was moving enough that I was able to push the stick into 2nd by rev-matching and got it to my parking spot. The issue is most likely the slave cylinder (located on trans) but I could not do any repairs myself in the parking lot (the car is lowered). I decided to make it to my mechanic 30 miles with no clutch pedal. Once I started the car, from a dead stop, I put pressure on the first gear and the car slowly started to move forward before the gear was engaged, eventually the gear engaged once it was going about 5mph. Controlling my revs, I switched it to 2nd and then 4th (3rd the gear grinded and didn't force it further). I got to the highway without stopping (lucky green light) and kept it in 4th until i got off highway. One redlight screwed me up but I pulled it out of gear to roll to a stop and pressed the first gear to get it moving (it takes about 10 seconds before I could get the 1st to engage with Hazards blinking). All in all I made it and it didn't seem like I caused too much harm to the trans. Just in case any one here is in similar situation, it can be done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
