<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I was about to edit my post with the same thing. While I like the first special more, the second one is still amazing. Though I have to wonder how much I liked the first special is colored by the build-up to Bill Cosby being a rapist. I love how he got on this serious and impassioned rant, that in its own right is important, that is a segue to another bit. Fucking hilarious.

I know I'm excited for the third special, at any rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wh... what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually not sure why people like the second set more. I've read that people like that it's similar to the old stuff but.. after a decade being away, why WOULDN'T you want something new and different like the first special? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what makes me cross is the word "circlejerk"... fucking stupid word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only is this thread unoriginal and posted daily, it's got an obnoxious title. Cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have Dotabuff because I am not a nerd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see you come down to this shit hole and play games where Legion doesn't do anything for 15 minutes and then duels 1 v 3 and dies, feeding the enemy team over and over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kewl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even get further than a few pages into In Search of Lost Time because of this. It's not hard to read but the sheer length is mind numbing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean if I die the least and have the most farm but keep losing because my teammates keep trickling in one by one to die.. uh.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot win when you're the lowest deaths on your team at 0 or 1 deaths and everyone else has like 7-10 deaths a piece. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hey I saw this in the /r/place thingy so I thought I'd drop by and ask for some really good puzzle games in the vein of Cut the Rope :x not played an Android game in a while  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, I can understand why you'd never do do it again if you actually had two tons of books. I've never had a library that large, though, always throwing away or donating the books I don't want anymore. So even before getting a Kindle, I've never really had the need for an entire room of books. Just one or two bookshelves suit me fine, as I said just buying physical copies of absolute favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear his non-gameplay videos are far too long. Jim Sterling released a similar video at 20 minutes in length and I don't imagine TotalBiscuit's additional 40 minutes have too much value that Jim didn't mention.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually really interested in this, thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you actually suicidal or just testing their dedication to the job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh most people who jungle don't know what "pulling" or "ganking" are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I forgot about that. One of the more clever bits of season 1, for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the feeling this is an anthology show, is it? That could be rather interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait does the orb also count for breaking the shield? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounded pretty interesting, not sure why I didn't watch it when first released. Might watch it tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OK how do I shut down the effectiveness of shields from Rein or Orisa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was already annoying when it was only Rein and now there's Orisa to deal with. You take a fun game and slow it down by needing to destroy some roadblocks.

I'm typically Mercy or Zen, so I can't exactly do much myself. What can I do to lead my team to make shields more of a non-issue? I hate just standing at a choke point until a shield is down. Incredibly boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I started with Franny and Zooey as my second Salinger book, I think I'd honestly suggest going with Nine Stories. Some of the stories in that, particularly For Esme and The Laughing Man, are so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not offended. I don't really give a crap. Just calling it like it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find him annoying and that's what is so fascinating to me. Salinger is an excellent writer in that he can write a teenager so convincingly. When I read more contemporary stuff that tries to do teenagers (John Green as an example), that doesn't at all feel like a real person. At least with Salinger, even if I don't like Holden, I'm very impressed by his ability to create a character.

In fact, I was so impressed that the first time I read Franny and Zooey, the writing floored me. For a second I confused the character with the writer and said to myself, "The guy who wrote The Catcher in the Rye can write like *that*?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also the promoting of racism/classism by separating kids into houses at Hogwarts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think that's an unpopular opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to say this is automatically wrong, there is certainly good genre fiction out there - but I get the feeling that MOST people who say this are fans of trashy YA like John Greene or Suzanne Collins who are mad their favorite books aren't taken "seriously enough." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the prologue last night. The constant footnotes to pointless shit really annoyed me, however I can see how this might make for a good movie next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which special was the first to have the intro that shows the comedian walking from a street on to the stage or something similar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought this was a bit annoying. I'm watching Richard Pryor: Live in Concert right now and, to my surprise, this was a thing even in 1979. What's the earliest example of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adaptation, Moon, and 12 Monkeys are shit? That's news to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] What are the best foreign TV shows on Netflix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a user review of this new show called Ingobernable that says "Latin America is exploding with great production lately, but this isn't one of them", which has me curious what ARE the best from Latin America and other non-English speaking countries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does this game have shields similar to Overwatch (i.e., Rein, Orisa, Winston)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is the most boring mechanic I've ever seen in a game, needing to destroy shields just so you can keep fighting. I know there are ways around it, but that's only if you have a coordinated team, and let's get real: that's rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tbh I'm still impressed with Mr Popo's singing in "Make a Man Out of You" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's actually Lani singing and not a friend of TFS, he's got some pipes on him for real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm kinda slowly thinking the same. I can spam Void or something and buy courier/wards with extra money and make more of a consistent impact than playing Venge/CM/Ogre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of that is the game's fault. The tutorial introduces NO concept related to supporting. It's absolute trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you even need to know such a thing? It's released when it's released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 1k mmr he's almost always a mid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many deaths should a Pudge have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get so tilted and annoyed when I see a Pudge on my team has like 15 deaths, especially if I can't tell which ones are real deaths and which ones are denies. And even the denies seem like they're PROBABLY not necessary most of the time... like, shouldn't he have better positioning instead of rushing in all the time just because he's a tank and using denial as an excuse? Sure they didn't get anything from killing him but he's still off the map for like 40 seconds or more.

I don't ever play Pudge, so maybe I'm wrong and all the rot denies are justified on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many deaths should a Pudge have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get so tilted and annoyed when I see a Pudge on my team has like 15 deaths, especially if I can't tell which ones are real deaths and which ones are denies. And even the denies seem like they're PROBABLY not necessary most of the time... like, shouldn't he have better positioning instead of rushing in all the time just because he's a tank and using denial as an excuse? Sure they didn't get anything from killing him but he's still off the map for like 40 seconds or more.

I don't ever play Pudge, so maybe I'm wrong and all the rot denies are justified on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see a video game where each level has a new green light traffic person and the level design for each would be inspired by their respective locations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only whacko who notices a resemblance to /u/siractionslacks- ?

What if Slacks **is** Elon Musk? Raving lunatic by day, top-class genius by night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't tell if I'm getting older and don't find April Fools funny or if everyone is just getting lazy with their jokes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know of editions of Dubliners/Portrait/Ulysses that have good notes with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with romance in a lot of fiction is that it's unrealistic. In my experience, whether my own relationships or what I've seen from that of others, it's not ever as smooth as depicted in a story. I want romance in a book to be as rocky and as uncertain in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5 how does kiss cam work.. like.. did she just have the ring and hope they would get on the cam, and if they didn't, oh well I'll do it another time? Is there a way to manipulate the cameramen to be like "hey, look at THIS couple"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't lie, House of Leaves was once my favorite book. When I tried to re-read it.. yeah.. what a gimmicky piece of trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is probably an immature and stupid question, but can Jane Austen be enjoyed by men? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never read anything from Austen, partially because there's this reputation about them of being the "chick lit" of classic literature. The synopses of them all seem to suggest there's a lot of marriage and love in them, which seems to explain the stereotype.

Now I don't necessarily hate those things. "Chick lit", however, implies to me that the characters are one-dimensional and don't have much to them. Is this true at all or are her novels just as good as any other classic? Northanger Abbey in particular sounds pretty neat, in that it's supposed to be metafiction/parody about Gothic novels of the 1700s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a 4k player coach me for a few games (1.5k here) and tell me that harassing is actually more important than last hitting because I can drive out the enemy and make it a lost lane for them. I was Void in safelane with a jungler, so I was effectively playing offlane. 

Perhaps he didn't specify that offlaners in particular should focus on harassing? All I know is I feel like my decisions (with his help) really helped me win that game 10 or 15 minutes more quickly than I would have otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, while I've never read past the first couple pages of Portrait, I assumed that's what was happening since the language was bizarre and childish. I really need to read Joyce one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wouldn't premium matchmaking just make people even more toxic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see it now, you'd get assholes saying shit like "You guys are so bad. Now I'm wasting not only my TIME on this loss, but also my MONEY. Why are you fucking idiots even paying for premium if you're this bad??? ff gg" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you that in a traditional forum this repeat of questions and topics would be much less annoying. The ability to upvote something to the top inevitably makes things very similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats, this is the most highly downvoted comment I have ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know off hand which ones are written by Holmes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aha, so that explains a scene in the recent series starring Benedict Cumberbatch where Sherlock is quite annoyed a magazine got a photo of him in the hat.

I really need to get around to reading the actual novels/stories. As far as I know, most/all of them are written by Watson, right? Reminds me of how Nick Carroway narrates The Great Gatsby, a side character observing the "main" character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your name Jim Sterling, by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I feel like /r/books is the worst for this... every goddamned day there seems to be a thread upvoted to front page about the superiority of print vs digital books. It was amusing at first, now I really just do not give a shit. 

Same for "What is a book that really changed you?????" every other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, that's the thing. You assume everyone does this by default and they do not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "When game is going full retard, you can only go with it. If you start going against it, if you start going half retard, you're fucking done for." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a quote from n0tail, a pro Dota player. I've always wondered just how serious he's being here, but joke or not, there's a bit of truth in here and I think it can apply to Overwatch just as much as Dota.

If you are a Winston, for example, and see that your team is still at the first chokepoint on King's Row and you're frustrated they're not taking the point... you aren't actually doing anything helpful by charging to the point to "contest" it. The only thing you're doing is helping the opponent build ult charges with your every death. So honestly, if your team isn't listening to your demands on mic to follow you - stick with them instead, get a couple picks, and find your opportunity to push.

Because if you do "the smart thing" on your own, you're only helping the enemy team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "When game is going full retard, you can only go with it. If you start going against it, if you start going half retard, you're fucking done for." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in my mind they're a little related because sometimes my stun is the last hit. But if I'm the only one in range, I'm not about to let that fucker run away at 10% hp just because a carry isn't around to get the kill. :x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing. As a support, I hold on to my stun until the end because I know the average teammate is going to blow all their spells too soon, not even attempting to chain stun. So instead of me stunning first and then everyone else stunning immediately after me, I wait until AFTER their stuns so I can use mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It stuns them in place, too, so I guess you could use it on someone you don't want to contribute to a teamfight and then take care of them after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get this game to stop crashing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since Orisa was added to comp, it feels like, I've been crashing every few matches. I get 90 fps and 20 ping so it's not like my computer is stuttering or something. It's either working smoothly or not working at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, you can mute them. And if they're toxic enough, they're going to feed down mid for the entire game because you "stole" their role. This is why I support in 90% of my games, because I don't want to put up with that childish nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something that is perhaps ironic is that I have trouble reading classics on a Kindle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modern stuff, I can read that just fine. With classics, there is this strong desire in me, at first subconscious and now I've fully realized it, that I must have a physical copy. The way I see it, if it's something good enough to re-read over and over, I should have a copy that will last. The reason I find this a bit ironic, of course, is that you can easily read these for free in the public domain... but it's hard to really pay attention to something when you don't have a physical copy, at least for me.

Anyone else feel this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume that the cast range talents also affect warding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/WritingPrompts is basically "here is an idea I had, and since I'm too lazy, can you please write the story for me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tbh, one thing that I hate learning about this game is attack ranges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is partly venting, partly asking how to remember them. This is one reason I tend to stick to the same heroes so I have a very good feel of their attack range. When I try a new hero, and the range is shorter or longer, I get disoriented. It's really my least favorite part of the game.

How do I remember these ranges, exactly? Is it just one of those things where you have to play for a long time and get a feel for them? I've played for probably around 2000 hours over the past couple years and this is still tripping me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing with Dota 2 is you're spectating pro games. As far as I know, there is not a way to do that in the Overwatch client (yet?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! If I saw ANY jungler do what this guy just described, I'd love junglers. You can ping to death to get a jungler to help you for a second, and they'll ignore you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that will never get you to level 2 in two creeps anymore, sadly. They changed how much experience they give. Even the hellbear camp doesn't work for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most people don't mind a jungle LC when she gets a smoke at 6, ganks midlane then rushes blink

I have never seen this. Sounds like heaven compared to most junglers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately, it's barely fun when ahead either. OK cool another game where 5 English speakers stomp 5 Peruvians.. cool.. Peruvians are still ruining my games just in a different way. All I want is an evenly matched game, a fight to the death as you said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to get the game to work consistently at below requirement specs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm typically at 90 fps 20 ms ping, despite being under specs. I'm on a GTX 580, 4 gig ram, i5 2500k CPU. But every couple days, I'll get insane lag, where I can't even see any heroes or gun fire, just the map. I don't really know if it's my internet or my rig, or both. 

Could it hopefully be something as simple as upgrading my ram, since my frames are usually just fine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm afraid of them when they're on my team because the few times I've had them, all they did was jump off ledges to lose/derank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Overwatch have a low priority punishment pool, similar to Dota? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a platinum and his friend down at bronze level. Entire game, all they did is jump off a ledge, respawn, jump off another ledge. Clearly trying to derank and/or very tilted. 

Yeah, there's the week long ban... but you can still go to quick play and ruin games for players there. I'd love for these toxic fucks to be in their own shadow pool until they win a set amount of games. There is no excuse for this shit, makes me wonder if the report system in Overwatch really does anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really fucking easy in Dota. Peruvians get mad so easily at their teammates. It's kinda funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not according to reddit. I have seen many people say quick play is meant to be played just as seriously as competitive. Makes me wonder what is the point of the mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda makes me wonder if I'm missing out on part of the experience since most modern versions of classics don't have the illustrations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the first editions of 19th century novels have illustrations/drawings in them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed, for example, Mark Twain novels from Modern Library will have the original illustrations included with them. But this seems rather childish to me so I have to wonder... do they come from a separate edition for children or did all copies of books have these illustrations? Was it just something books from that time period did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you even listening to the words coming out of your mouth, tbh? If they were to impose "if enemy chooses x hero, you MUST choose y hero to counter", that is going to create the most stale and rigid meta imaginable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is absolutely not an area in which Blizzard should intervene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be happy this is your biggest problem. Some of the interactions in Dota are so headache inducing (i.e, what projectile attacks can and cannot be disjointed by blinking away) compared to anything like Zarya's ult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would argue what's toxic behavior is someone who whines about it, because as has been said many times (and need I remind you it's actually the basis of this thread) : you can't control your teammates, you can only control yourself. So don't bitch and complain, find a way to play around that by protecting him. It's on to the next match in a few short minutes, win or lose, so why get so hung up about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The funniest thing about this game is hearing "I'm sorry for being an asshole at the start" after a comeback. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hilarious because I doubt that's true at all. They're gonna do that shit again the very next game when they think all is lost within the first 10 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just one example. If someone is really good at Genji or Hanzo or whatever, then why not let them play that hero? It's just like Dota: yeah, counters matter at high MMR. But at low skill, all that honestly matters is that you can outplay your opponent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, if blizzard themselves believe it is toxic simply to main a hero, not flaming your team or intentionally feeding or anything, then I am fucking done. This game seems so strict, like they forget it's a game. If I want to play Mercy all the time, there should be no limits on me to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, like I said - have you EVER seen a basketball/football team say "we give up"? If esports wants to be taken as seriously as other sports, "gg" should not be a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. I have never seen a sports game where a team says "nah, we out, we can't win." The fact that pro Dota can do it, makes the game a joke. People want esports to be taken seriously, but how can it be when there's that option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah alright, Dota is currently an incredibly positive experience... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked this one enough to give it four stars back when I watched it. Her more recent special, eh I dunno it wasn't terrible but I didn't like it as much. She and Bill Burr both disappointed me with their recent ones. Come to think of it, so did David Cross.

I think the big thing is sometimes (especially with the David Cross) is a special can sometimes be too long, partly due to feeling like they're stretching the material thin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea of joking with the enemy team TOO BAD THEY'RE ALWAYS PERUVIAN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez this is a lot more than I'd thought I would get, thanks a lot.

A lot of this is stuff I can't explain away because I know I suck, but I'll attempt to describe why I did what I did at 3:15, and that is I'm too nice. In the back of my head I'm ALWAYS thinking I shouldn't be stealing farm from anyone, so I'm afraid to hit anything... even if it's in a solo lane, apparently. That's the same reason I tend to build tranquils almost every game, because I'm locked into this mindset that I'm going to be roaming, even when that's not the case. 

So part of my problem is I need to build more greedy items in some games instead of the medallion/force staff thing. I'm not really good at figuring out which games that would be a good idea, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK sure PM me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I got so stressed out wondering why Luna isn't in lane with me that I didn't think to focus the Sniper - and you're even more right I should have prioritized the stick. I'll try to remember your advice for next time because this shit with someone jungling and abandoning their one support happens every 5 games, or at least feels like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The fuck's a condom?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jtGkhZU7DNs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone check out the first 7 minutes and tell me how I could have handled this better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.dotabuff.com/matches/3077983579

Or is this one of those unwinnable scenarios? I hope not, because this type of thing happens at 1k mmr far too often than I'd like. I pick support, someone picks jungle. So we have a dual offlane and then I'm 1 vs 2. I don't think I died during laning phase, but Sniper and PA managed to take a tower and a half from bot lane off the back of this - because what the fuck am I gonna do against that alone?

I was the Venge, btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a question for any HARDCORE fans of Edgar Allan Poe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a YouTuber who goes into EXTREME detail about minor details of Paper Mario 64. It's kinda fascinatingly pointless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I don't understand all the bickering at low MMR. It's a complex game and we're ALL making mistakes. Why whine at your teammates about them instead of saying "it's ok, I would have probably done the same thing in your shoes"? In fact, I'd say this one attitude change alone has helped me win more games. 

The only time I really get mad at teammates anymore is when they do something like Nature's Prophet jungle, because while I can forgive a lot of supposedly dumb shit and say "this is 1k, we'll find a way to make it work", jungling still seems like an absolute waste of time to me. Especially when I am our only support who is going solo against a dual lane because of their selfish decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This community thinks Quick Play is as equally serious as Competitive. Does it *really* surprise you people would also treat Arcade modes seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand the disbelief. I've met a lot of people who say they hate to read and say it's a waste of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck does this even mean, more stimuli? So basically you're ADHD and need a lot of flashing lights to be entertained? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you meant. It's insulting they'd kinda treat their fan base like children. While I don't say "gg ez", I don't cry when someone else does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, that's a bit insulting... but on the other hand, it's hilarious. So I guess my feelings are neutral, after cancelling out my positive and negative opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people at low MMR even allowed to play heroes like Naga and Meepo? There needs to be some kind of IQ test for it. "You've completed this many bot matches with this hero at unfair bot difficulty, with these stats: ok you can play it in ranked." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Naga Siren generally a worthless hero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I've seen her do some cool (but boring) shit in pro games - but in my games, she is pretty much the most worthless hero in the game other than Nature's Prophet. I'd say Io but no one picks Io. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're probably right. They don't assess the situation and just think "well... this is my build, I'll just not be as shit as our LC." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can sliiiightly understand how someone could mistake Legion for a man - even if it's still really dumb - but how the fuck can anyone look at TA and think "Yeah. Totally a guy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always known the value of sentries, but too often I'd be like "ok I need to finish my boots and THEN get sentries." I feel like this logic cost me games in the past, whereas now I'll stay poor on a wind lace and magic wand and get as many sentries and dusts as I can. At least at 1.6k mmr, this pays for itself immediately. You don't even need items when the idiot enemy shadow blade carriers don't learn from their mistakes and keep waltzing up to you.

It's for this reason I'm confused why their reaction is usually to get shadow blade on another hero. Like, dude, we've been raping your Legion - what makes you think we aren't also going to rape your Slark or Troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, so why show the SR during quick play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched the series twice and neither time did I get the impression that Light gave a shit about Misa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give me one logical reason for exposing SR without an option  to hide it, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck is this being downvoted? Does this toxic community PREFER seeing MMR so you can whine about your teammates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, alright. Thanks for telling me shows from the 90s like Buffy and Ally Mcbeal are "new." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, all I want is teammates who will help me buy dust against the three shadow blade users on the enemy team. I'm not a nerd with illusions that he'll go pro. I'm not going to treat this game like it's a job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How (if at all possible) can you hide your SR on your profile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I love about Dota is it's OPTIONAL to display your MMR. This is great so people in unranked can't whine about how my skill level isn't acceptable to them. As far as I can tell, this isn't possible in Overwatch - so if you've been on a terrible losing streak, people are gonna whine about it in Quick Play when all you want to do is have some fun.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've not played Dota for so long that I don't know what is "new meta" and what is 1k MMR nonsense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maelstrom on CM? Atos on Lifestealer? These are just two examples of things I've seen that SEEM insane, but I've not really played much since the end of December, so for all I know these are new builds that people saw from a pro.

What *are* some new item builds that I've missed out on? I know there's Ember Spirit being a magic damage dealer, is there anything else wild and funky like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've not played Dota for so long that I don't know what is "new meta" and what is 1k MMR nonsense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maelstrom on CM? Atos on Lifestealer? These are just two examples of things I've seen that SEEM insane, but I've not really played much since the end of December, so for all I know these are new builds that people saw from a pro.

What *are* some new item builds that I've missed out on? I know there's Ember Spirit being a magic damage dealer, is there anything else wild and funky like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That... sounds like my reaction minus the laughing. I don't think I laughed at any of it, but I kept watching it out of sheer curiosity, trying to figure out if this guy was an act or not. Like... I thought I was cynical, but this guy is just out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why even have a Quick Play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm becoming more convinced that Icefrog doesn't oversee Dota anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These patches are coming out a lot faster than they used to. It's so uncharacteristic, kinda makes you wonder if a new team is running the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Monkey King: Spring winding up sound effect can be heard by nearby enemies


I'd never even considered such a thing, but yeah, this should have been there right from the beginning. Makes him much less of an unfair hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why? For what possible reason does anyone need to know my SR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How (if at all possible) can you hide your SR on your profile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I love about Dota is it's OPTIONAL to display your MMR. This is great so people in unranked can't whine about how my skill level isn't acceptable to them. As far as I can tell, this isn't possible in Overwatch - so if you've been on a terrible losing streak, people are gonna whine about it in Quick Play when all you want to do is have some fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Emily Bronte more difficult to read than her sisters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read Jane Eyre and bits of Anne Bronte. Didn't have any trouble at all with them. Then there's Wuthering Heights and for the most part I'm quite confused and I feel stupid. The grammar is so different. 

Was Emily paying homage to a different, earlier style of writing? Or is her style just simply more difficult than her two sisters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've read Jane Eyre and loved it. I tried to read Wuthering Heights last night and the grammar was so bizarre and hard to understand (and I don't just mean the Yorkshire accent) that I couldn't follow much of it. I thought maybe I'd got more stupid over the last year. Then I read the start of Anne Bronte's two novels to test it out, and nope, those are easy to understand.

Was Emily paying homage to a different, earlier style of writing? Or is her style just simply more difficult than her two sisters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he's dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IIL] Sia [WEWIL]? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's incredibly famous and it's obviously pop music, yet I get this indie vibe from her that I can't explain, like her music doesn't really belong on the radio. It's very nostalgic sounding, wistful, sometimes even slightly creepy (Elastic Heart's melody for example) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it working? What does the report system in Rocket League even do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok? Thanks?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that news would be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.6k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Are there any underrated and unnoticed standup comedy shows on Netflix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's Dave Chappelle, Louis CK, Bill Burr, John Mulaney - is there anything else REALLY good on there? 

I know there's Bill Hicks but I feel these days he's a bit preachy - and Aziz Ansari has good moments but his high pitched yelling grates on my nerves after a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I was kidding - the real point is I want even, close, suspsenseful matches. I fucking hate stomps, whether I'm the one winning or losing. Why is matchmaking so broken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... most of the change is good, but why did you shave that magnificent beard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tbh, the game is kinda boring now that it's all Americans vs all Peruvians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, it's cool that everyone on my team speaks English... but Peruvians are so bad that it's get boring to stomp them into the ground.

Maybe give us one Peruvian per match, so there's a challenge again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still failing to see the point of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is there are legit bigger numbers. I lost a match and lost like 80 fucking points, while I win and get like 12 points. Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it true that gaining or losing SR is based on win and loss streaks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read this from a few people on /r/OverwatchUniversity and that would explain why it seems like I lose more SR for every match I lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL 2015 is back in the day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I believe elo hell does exist in one way - communication. The lower you go, the less likely anyone is to use a microphone and communicate. So the more you lose, the harder it is to play as a team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair... all that boring fucker has EVER talked about in his shows is food and TV. It's not a stretch to assume he'd mention Netflix just by extension of being Jim Gaffigan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if they wanna go just to brag, then fine, whatever... but damn, let some real fans sit in front.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't bother to Google if Prince made music since the 80s before making this bullshit post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Buckethead an example of HailCorporate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's always wearing a KFC bucket on his head... hmm.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have 10 insanely broken spells at your spells, any one of which would be amazing alone, but are for some reason all on one hero. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your username is ironic because this sounds like the most "reddit" thing in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play Mercy 90% of the time and had never realized you could do most of this. In my head I'm always thinking "Man I'm so slow, I wish I had someone to fly to", when I could use quite a few of these descents to get caught up to my team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you use Mercy's Angelic Descent? And is it ok to solo rez someone on control point maps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first question is kinda self explanatory

As for the second question - I like to solo rez tanks on control maps, just kinda makes sense. Seems to be a good decision most of the time. Am I just getting lucky or is it a good idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still convinced they KNEW he was broken on release and left it that way for a while to sell arcana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that is a partial explanation why you get people butthurt whining that I'm only 1.5k mmr and that I'm somehow the reason we lost. At least in ranked, we're ALL the same shitty MMR and I've never seen anyone flame about mmr in ranked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm beginning to think I should stick to ranked. Opinions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd been playing quite a bit of unranked, thinking "oh ranked is so toxic and competitive I should just play unranked"

But after a while unranked is also toxic and competitive, which is bizarre since it's just unranked.

THEN I realized perhaps what is toxic and competitive... is probably me. So I'm playing ranked again and actually having a lot of fun because people want to win. As long as I start off with something positive like "hey guys I'm gonna support and we're gonna win", people actually don't bicker like children too much.

Does unranked really have any use once you can play ranked, especially if it stresses me out much more than ranked for some weird reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I swap out Void every time. Maybe it's because I'm low MMR and the team is uncoordinated to be there and help out the Void, but he's so disoriented that he's never going to get anything done after I swap him. And I'm not about to swap in myself and let him kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know many comedians who would drop the jokes for something serious and profound like that, for quite a while, and then use it as a build up to a joke. Fucking hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spam Venge, not even for climbing purposes or anything, but because I think swapping is fun as hell - and the funny thing is, so often I'll first pick her, then someone else on the enemy team will pick Void.

Are low MMR players under the impression Void counters Venge or is it just a happy coincidence?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your flair explains why you like PA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a Paperwhite for almost two months now, and honestly... I kinda zone out when reading most books. Something about not owning a book and just having a copy in my hands makes me not really care about what I'm reading. I think I'm going to start using it as a way to sample if I like a book, then buy real copies of the ones that really intrigue me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I switch all the time. But when we really need heavy firepower, I like to damage boost one of them to give us an edge. I'll focus on damage boosting until I see someone needs heals, then go back to boosting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I agree with you entirely that there's nothing else to an FPS other than aim and awareness. People will say there's a lot more to it in something like Overwatch, but I don't really understand how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never considered this, but you're probably right. I main Mercy and like to pocket someone and I have trouble sometimes figuring out who that should be - because while it's ideally (at least in my opinion) someone like Soldier or Reaper and damage boosting them, that's not always the case if they're bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably my favorite video of his and I think similar thoughts EVERY time I hear a Christian talk about medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what? Hogwarts.. is a fake....? :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK so this is theoretically going to give me less Peruvians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the game now default to "region: auto" every time I reopen it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this Valve's sneaky way to get players back on to US East? Because I'm going to pick US West every time, no matter how much you try to inconvenience me, Valve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tbh I have no interest in googling something if the person who referenced it is pretentious enough to use an obscure acronym, thinking everyone knows what they're talking about already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I love random capitalized letters, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why are team-based games popular when most people have no desire to play as a team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In any team-based game I've ever played, I'd say half the team is off doing their own thing in some bizarre part of the map. There's no interest to work as a team, they just want to try to find solo picks and then end up dying because 1 v 6 isn't gonna work.

Since these people clearly want a deathmatch situation, why don't developers see this and make more deathmatch type games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even give a shit about language barriers, all I want is a game without Peruvians spam pinging me or my teammates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't book publishers divide larger books into separate volumes? Is there not a market for such a thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a Kindle for a while now and I've come to the conclusion that I actually prefer print books - but only if they're easy to hold in my hands, let's say under 500 pages. For books like Don Quixote, Monte Cristo, Infinite Jest - as much as I want to own them and hold them, it's just too cumbersome.

Is there a particular reason long books are sold as bulky tomes like this? I mean, I know I've read back in the 1800s that larger novels were published in three parts. Why did that practice fade away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is true, but I've heard that shitty intro with Amy Pond is specifically for the US release. A bit insulting, if you ask me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this show even ABOUT? Reading the little Netflix synopsis tells me literally nothing. He's out of prison... and then what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was only "YouTube drama" because nothing happened. If their insane plan actually worked, that would be a slippery slope for any small YouTuber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it... incompetent cops in England are a less serious issue than incompetent cops in other areas of the world? What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
