<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1811</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god.... I thought I posted it a long time ago- I'll do it when I get home I guess. Oops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that's what I thought. But the , tripped me up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you talk to someone random on the street that will probably be the last time you talk to them before they die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So the offer?", I questioned him, "Who's house am I delivering it to?"

"It's not in your room to question me, and you will not know where you are going until you get a text sometime in the next few days."

A pause.

He continued, "When you get there, all you need to do is drop off the package on the front door, ring the doorbell, and leave. Don't open the bag, don't stay on the porch, and *do not* look into why you are doing this."

For some reason, my eyes started to tear up. What the hell am I getting myself into? It sounds like I'm dropping off a bomb at this house. But nevertheless I was stuck, "I'll do it."

His cheery smile returned to his face and he said, "Great! The package is in the Audi. It's parked the next street down on the corner. And thank you." He nodded to himself then turned away. Before he disappeared from my sight he turned around and shouted to me, "Enjoy your money!"

I turned away from him and started towards my house, when I remembered the Audi. Sure enough, there was a dark blue, two door Audi parked on the corner of the road. For the next week I didn't spend any of the money and I only drove the Audi once- and that was only to take it home. Max's dark grimace never left my mind and two days after I received my threat I started having nightmares with Max as the central orchestrator in my doom. Finally I broke, I had to spend the money. To keep it simple to explain, I dug myself in a deep money hole.

And then that fateful day hit. I was out with one of my friends. We were bored so I got in her car and we drove around the city. When she got to my house to pick me up I could tell she saw the Audi, but she didn't mention it. Did she put the two-and-two together? Probably not, as I could barely believe that I had an Audi parked at my house (even considering the conditions).

So we were driving when I received a text. Three words. 121 Crimson Place. For a few minutes I fell into a strange silence. Then I alerted my friend to drive me home.

"Immediately," I said.

"For what?" She countered.

"My credit card."

"I told you not to involve yourself with that."

"Yes, I know it was a mistake. Now drive me to my house."

She did, albeit slowly, but she did. Would Max be angry at my sluggish pace? Shit.

I got in the Audi. The key was still in the ignition. I sat down and floored the gas, not bothering to put on my seatbelt or worry what was in the bag. The Audi had a built in GPS, so I plugged in the address and to my joy, the house was only five minutes away. Turns out five minutes seems like a lifetime if you're as scared as I was. Every turn I made to get closer to the house my fear grew ever more.

The houses turned from low class to high class and beyond. When I turned onto Crimson Place, there was only two houses on the small road. The closest, 123, was a tall gothic building. It looked like a haunted house from some cheesy horror cartoon. My main focus, however, was 121 Crimson Place. Damn... that place looked like Bill Gates put all of his money into it. It is safe to say that at least a hundred of my apartments could fit comfortable in that house.

I decided to get it over with so I idled the car on the curb and opened the trunk. Inside was a small yellow bag. It looked normal enough; like a gym bag. When I picked it up it felt surprisingly light and empty. I threw the bag over my shoulder and walked up the path to the front door. I tried to appear normal enough, but that was before I heard the blood curdling scream coming from inside the massive house.  




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget shipping and handling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
