<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite true, my cell tethering gets around 100 MS on average, and as low as 60-70. These aren't great, no pro player would play with this, but an average/casual player should be fine.

I have read ATT latency is pretty crappy though, like averages 150 ms (making VoLTE a non option atm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut the warm segment in half and you have mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, to be fair a lot of people in more rural areas don't feel the deprioritization at all, it all depends on your tower/areas congestion. Some people roar past 28 gb pulling 20+ megabits/s steady all day everyday. Some people get lowered to a crawl till night, I'm more in between.

Also for unlimited 4g lte tethering it's pretty much the only option IIRC, though YMMV from congestion.

BUT I do get you're point. T-Mobile doesn't really have the network to provide truly unlimited (no deprioritization, which also to be fair is different than a cap but is hugely YMMV). I'm not sure if any network can handle absolutely no strings attached unlimited LTE to everyone at this point though, would bog down their backends on most towers to a crawl especially in just about any decent sized city.

Edit: Most months I end up (via cell phone tethering) burning through 50+ GB of data, mostly used on my PS4. And at only extra 25$ ontop of my base phone bill it's the cheapest way to tether that much.

Shoot, my highest month I tethered like 150 GB data, at 70$ base phone bill plus 25$ for one plus 95$ to tether 150 gb is friggin great. With Verizon that would have costed me like 400$. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, care to clarify a bit more? I just ask because I'm not sure if you're saying you're on T-Mobile one or something similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I suggest to every new owner to go with 2 TB sshd's. I just feel it's a near necessity personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the guy above me said, and not everyone wants to redownload/reinstall games constantly even if they do have good internet.

I just upgraded to a slim and already have over a TB installed. 

ESO is damn near 100 GB on it's own. TLOU is another 40, Until Dawn is another 40, DA:I is another 40. And it just adds up realllllllly quickly.

Edit: To be fair I said IMHO. I consider myself a casual gamer, pretty damn casual actually compared to many people I know (irl and online) and 1 tb isn't enough for me. 2 tb in the long run is pretty damn questionable, but works for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know would if it offered a 40-50$ experience. I don't buy any game without extensive research first though. Shit only game I may ever preorder is TLOU2. I preordered TWD S3 by TellTale, but after rethinking it I cancelled my preorder and decided to wait for all episode releases and to read up first. At which point if it lives up to s1/2 I'll happily pay full price for.

Any, I got a bit off track but I think there is definitely a market it there for B+ through A (so one notch before AAA) games for that price point at release. Developers who risked it would have to approach it smartly though. You need enough features, polish, and gameplay without going overboard (to where they struggle to profit) but without under delivering too. Video game development is a risky business though so who knows if many will attempt it, much less create a market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better for sure, but I think a 39.99$ may have been the best point to go for between selling it for as much as they could/gamer value for what they got sweet spot. I was honestly thinking right after I posted my last comment that 30$ for the game just released may have been "too good" of a price. I think 49.99 is still "too high" personally though.

One things for sure, if they had released at/within first 6 months of launch they could have sold it for 60$ and go over really well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which, if true, is fair enough. But with enough foresight (which isn't something easy to just have obviously) they could have sold it for 30$, once it was a couple years after launch, and had things go over way better at the game's release. Granted a lot of money had been sunk into it at this point and it may not have been easy as sell it for 30$, I dunno. I just personally think it would have bolstered sales and greatly improved it's reception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think it shows graphics aren't everything. I mean it had more going than just graphics obviously but between everything it offered the majority of gamers felt/agreed it just wasn't enough to warrant 60$.

I hope lesson learned by the devs is don't sink all your $ into uber amazing graphics, stepping down $ spent on graphics to offer a longer game, better AI, etc will probably go over way better with gamers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd second this, I mean there are quite a few games I think that fit his bill but D3 probably has the best replay value that would fit his guidelines.

Also you can keep doing the story over and just progressing further via paragon, online coop which is a bit dead but manageable if you really try, and rifts if you get tired of the story. An almost endless gear upgrading system, especially on console with no seasons (yet) to give free high tier gear. Plus all the different classes, it's easily a simple enough game to casually sink the next 3 years into it (people have easily done it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked it up since it was free but haven't downloaded it yet. It sounds amazing but could anyone give me a rough estimate of the download size? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, always better safe than sorry to do a full format if possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I have no help to offer, just wanted to say this sucks. 

One thing I can offer up is I THINK there is a small pinhole at the bottom of the controller you can stick a safety pin into to reset it (you'll need to resync)

Hope you're able to get it figured out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen quite a bit of hate for these games (I've seen positive too, but more people seem to resent/even hate them this is also just my experience, so sorry if it isn't the norm and they're generally loved) which is sad.

I enjoyed both immensely and ended up really loving Beyond Two Souls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may sound like a weird suggestion for 1-2h/w but Diablo 3.

Story isn't so long and is pretty good. My friend played with his fiancee (who really isn't into games at all). She ended up having a great time of them putting in only a few hours/week. I think they finished it in a bit over a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll one better you, brojobs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have the money stick the biggest HDD (or SSHD or even SSD) you can afford to buy into it. 2 TB SSHD will provide better speed than just a normal HDD (still no where near a good SSD speeds but way more affordable than a huge SSD) and double your storage. Storage is key this gen, 500 and even 1 TB isn't enough IMHO if you're even a moderately casual gamer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a cell hotspot in itself but T-Mobile offers unlimited 4G LTE tethering via T-Mobile one with One Plus (70$ for base service, 25$ for One Plus addon) , with a few caveats.

First you need T-Mobile reception where you live ofc.



Next for the unlimited it can NOT be done via an "internet only" device (IE tablet or cellular hotspot) it has to be done with a phone with hotspot capabilities.

You can't use the phone only for Internet, you have to make a few calls on it a month at bare minimum.

Lastly if you go over 28 GB data usage you get "depriorized" which may not affect you at all, or if you're area is highly congested can have a pretty big affect. If you go over 28 GB in a month of total data also at least half must be done on the phone itself, not through the hotspot. IE if you use 58 GB hotspot you must use 59 GB data on the phone itself.

That being said I'm also in a situation where my only net options are satellite or cellular data and have found the unlimited 4G LTE on T-MOBILE to be friggin great, but YMMV with congestion, signal, and all the stipulations and how acceptable they are to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't play too many "kid friendly" games but out of what I do play I have to agree with everyone saying any Lego game (my personal favorite is the Harry Potter series, then again I've loved Harry Potter since the 1st book was first released so bias there) and Minecraft.

Coincidentally those games are pretty enjoyable by adults too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 26 here, I love the Lego games. Just recently bought Lego: The Hobbit. Own and love the Lego Harry Potter series, Lego Jurassic World. Heard good things about the ones I don't own/haven't played. Those games are just good for all ages 5-99+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap, do you know what started the fire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first time doing a survey VIA Google Forms, I set results to public but I don't know if people can see them before I end it so if not for anyone who may be interested

16 responses so far
14 not failed yet
2 failed in 1 month

Super small sample group, and I'm not sure if anyone really cares but since people have taken the time to fill it out I figured I give an update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
