<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5571</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God works in mysterious ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that an AI developed by the University of Toronto wrote its own Christmas Carol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually loved it too. It was straightforward without being simple. Like you don't automatically hit just because you swing a weapon. Maybe they were forces to be creative with combat mechanics due to a lack of technology available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true actually, I still didn't enjoy them as much but Skyrim as a whole province did feel like a cohesive environment. Everything had its place, the dungeons made sense at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean look at Morrowind. By far my favorite game to date but... *and I still haven't found every cave and dungeon* ... the graphics date so poorly, and the lack of physics engine is hard to get used to the more i play newer games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it gives me hope that they are learning while trying out new things. TES VI will no doubt have other issues but it will still be good. I was impressed with the skill tree system they brought about in Skyrim, it was finally something being given back as opposed to just winding down weapon and skill types. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that aspect I would give them credit at least. Yes each game has flaws but i really did feel like they *tried* with every new game. I have to say though, you get used to graphics really quickly and God Rays mean nothing if Azura's star becomes one of the easiest things to acquire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Staff Room: Rant/Share/Discussion - Bank Holiday Weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT - Make an "off limits" list for decision making during times that you are going to be dieting or under some great emotional burden. Include things like 'gym membersip' and 'career' so you don't quit something impulsively simply because you're not your usual self. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be a matter of taste. One person may not notice what the other didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good way of looking at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyrim makes up for what Oblivion lacked but the opposite is also true. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pointless to offer critcism of Oblivion for its flaws at this stage because it has all been said before, although I still regard the game highly. I believe that, where it failed, Skyrim specifically makes up for.

Instead of a main character who merely facilitates the success of the real hero "Martin", you play a Dragonborn and take center stage in the story. The leveling system with enemies is lot fairer once more. Magic has a much more primary role. The main story itself is a lot more enthralling. The landscape is unique and well designed.

However, Skyrim is not without its flaws. Where it fails, I think we can look to oblivion for clarity.

The dungeons are far too repetitive, there are only 3 or 4 individual styles that don't change very much as you continue to explore. Oblivion, while still repeating similar styles of dungeon, offers a more varied layout. While the theme of Umbra's dungeon is used repeatedly, the specific layout is unique, especially the floor trap design.

So much effort was spent creating unique NPCs that their stories don't go far beyond that. Most  unique quests offer little more than delivering something across town or kill the bandit in that cave. In Oblivion, when you had to run a small errand, you can be sure something weird was just around the corner. Retrieving the ancestral sword, reuniting and liberating the home of the brothers etc. Granted they were wacky at times but every side quest felt like the most important job you had to do. I would offer that the side quest were better designed than the main quest but... *walks away whistling*.

Finally, while I understand Skyrim is MEANT to a divided province, there is little cohesion between anything outside of a town. The lack if cross city guilds plays a big part in this. As a result, each town tries to offer its own variety of quest which just ends up the same as the others. In Oblivion, the thieves guild took you everywhere, into the heart of the political sphere. Each faction forced you across every part of the world and gave you an extra piece of a puzzle that eventually fit together as one piece. Essentially the quests were fun. Silly, but fun.

I Ioved both games but I hope time will be a bit more even handed with them than modern criticism seems to be.

**Edit: On "Magic has a much more primary role".**

*What I intended by this comment was that I felt Magic was a much more effective and balanced power than in Oblivion. Where I feel that playing a straight mage in Oblivion is tediously difficult, requiring a massive amount of fortify Magika to cast top tier skills, requiring a lot of Magika for relatively ordinary spells etc. In Skyrim it's more possible to play as a straight Mage.*

*That being said, what you're left with in terms of Magic in TES:V is a very diluted version of magic, an entire school being abolished among other problems. I recognize the flaws on both sides (hence my argument) but my main point here is simply about the feasibility of using magic in Skyrim.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What gave you the strength to carry on after the death of a loved one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean as a teacher, yeah same here. Everything, saves your ass in the long run. Wish I was told that instead of learning it the hard way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That works with teachers too sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I think one might lead the other in some cases. For me, a lot of my favorite subjects were defined simply by teachers I got on with or respected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ there's no way ide get away with suggesting that in the staff room here. I imagine it could be a good idea if done right though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man that's actually good advice. Students should really be told of places to look for work for college benefits, restaurants, book shops etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe wee the exception I don't know. Most Irish schools are Catholic run and seeing our peers in pyjamas might give us all notions if become sex crashed drug addicts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. More to the point, you may meet people in the future, the cool kids or the dorks and most of the time nobody cares. If hlyou had an issue with them in school you as a grown man or woman can't hold that with you when you meet them on the streets with a bunch of kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, although I don't think enough kids realise it at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus What's pyjama day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought that to be a double edged sword. Yeah we need to learn to be self sufficient but if you're in any way weak you can be left behind in the dirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good or bad, what was a valuable life lesson you learned during your time in school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your process or inspiration for naming the aspects of your world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's clearly a variety of approaches and inspirations that I've seen here. Some more common than others. I'd like to know what inspires you to name the various places, people and other artifacts of your world's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher shortages in key subjects are set to get worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schools' religion barrier is 'untenable' - Council of Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The majority of Irish adults now believe an education in STEM can lead to better career opportunities according to a survey for Tech Week 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 percent corporate tax would give us 550m more for education - TUI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young teachers warn unequal pay driving them out of Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tusla criticised for cuts to school completion programme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats your opinion? - Secondary teachers vote against series of strike days next month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Staff Room: Share/Rant/Discussion - back to school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A place to share your opinions and get something off your chest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wire: Sheeeeeeeeit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an accountant so I'm ready for someone better equipped to jump in and correct me.

But you don't get tax back for not working over summer. You can claim tax back every year regardless of who you are. It's important to do it as a teacher who doesn't get summer pay because you've probably been on emergency tax for some of the schools you subbed in. Happens to me all the time.

You should start to claim tax back around this time of year because you should get it by summer. Also you get holiday pay if you've subbed in one school for a long time but you'd have already gotten that by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exam corrections and supervision are a big cover for summer income. You don't get all of it then and there but it helps.

Officially the superintendents are selected but many schools need support for special centers so ide ask your local schools and let them know you're available for that for the exams. You might have a bit more time with exam corrections.

Alternatively run a summer grinds course. Advertise it as intensive exam preparation. I don't do it myself but I've seen it advertised from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easter weekend events on across the holiday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 things to do over the easter break 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher awarded almost half million pounds after being hit over the head by skateboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> List of recognised qualifications: http://www.teachingcouncil.ie/en/Registration/How-do-I-register-/Post-primary-Options-Ireland/Option-B/Qualification-Requirements-for-Post-Primary-Teachers-Qualifications-Awarded-in-Ireland-Applying-for-Registration-on-or-after-1-January-2017.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post Primary:

* Tell us about yourself
* Why did you become a teacher?
* How do you introduce [subject] to a new group of students?
* If a parent wanted their child to do one thing but you had advised another, how would you approach the confrontation that would follow?
* How important is it to make links with other subjects? In what ways have you done this in the past?
* What is your knowledge of IT and hiw important do you think it is in the curriculum?
* Have you experienced working with students of clearly different levels of ability? How do you identify these levels in your subject?
* Describe ways you have identified to assess pupils in your classroom.
* What is the function of regular assessment for students?
* Describe two teaching strategies which have yielded successful results so far.
* How do you deal with an individual that is not interested in the subject you are teaching?
* What is your attitude to discipline and behavioural management?
* How would you deal with a case of bullying that you saw?
* What do you consider to be your strengths and weaknesses?
* What is your Golden Rule?
* How do you guard against discrimination in your teaching?
* What was the best lesson you taught?
* What extra curricular activities could you bring to the school?
* What did you learn from [small course listed in CV]?
* Do you consider mobile phones an issue in class?
* What did you think of the previous [subject JC/LC] exam?
* What do you think of the new Junior Cert? Is it needed?
* What is your classroom management style?
* What are your top 3 policies and where would you access them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] We're looking to compile a list of Interview questions, submit yours below! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started off, I found the questions being asked in interviews were much more nuanced than the samples I would find online, but many of my colleagues were being asked the same sort of questions as I was.

Submit any questions you were asked during an interview that may help others, clarifying whether you are primary, secondary or third level. Once finished I will upload a master list for future use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is F4 survival mode vastly different from FNV survival mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found survival mode a little tough to get used to at the start with NV but after a while it was just as easy. The ammo weight was the only real difference. After a while it just wasn't that much of a challenge.

Is it any different with F4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 things you can do with Google Classroom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Interesting Ed-Tech tools to incorporate into the class. How many of you use resources like these in your day to day lessons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: DirectX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: DIRECT X </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted, I didn't pay proper attention to the tools clearly. Thanks for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hasn't changed anything I'm afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot on in Galway, food festival from Friday to Sunday, it's usually pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your plan for easter? Getting some down time or catching up on work? Let us know! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would be interested to hear from a SNA on this: SNAs fear causing harm to pupils over presumed nursing role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shortcomings in new special needs teaching system claims Sinn Fin TD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to receive mod mail for removed posts. I have tried a few ways that haven't worked yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is literally my setup below. I don't want to add a threshold for karma right now. 

What I primarily want is to receive mod mail each time someone's post or comment is removed.

I would also like to receive mod mail for all comments, posts and reports (its a small community) but the three pieces of code I have entered at the bottom don't seem to have any effect. But the main issue is the mod mail for removed posts/comments.

---
    author:
        account_age: " 7 days"
    action: remove
    comment: In order to keep our community spam-free, we have set certain restrictions on new user accounts. Your post has been removed because your account is too new. Please wait a week before posting and then try again. Thanks!  

---
    type: comment
    modmail: "New {{kind}} in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}"
---
    type: submission
    modmail: "New {{kind}} in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}"
---
    reports: 1
    modmail: "A {{kind}} has been reported in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to approve specific users by name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My spam filter is blocking certain posts but when it is clear that an individual is legitimate I want to unblock them individually and not have to set a karma rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. And sorry about the spam filter. Theres been some trolls leaving abuse on this page. If you're saving for a mortgage and are the sole breadwinner maybe put it off for a bit. It's an unstable career in the beginning, rewarding yes. You sound like you'd have no problem in the job, just make sure you and yours are going to be okay financially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm still not working, I added the quotation marks too. Do I need to put my own subreddit into the brackets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you expect the most from the moderators of your communities? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did in game secrets first start to be referred to as "Easter Eggs"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Automoderator is not sending me any notification for my subreddit despite my setup. Yes I have full permissions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My setup - The first part works fine, its the three modmail sections that haven't done anything.

###

---
    author:
        account_age: " 7 days"
    action: remove
    comment: [My message - This part works fine, user post is removed and this goes up under their comment]


##### Below is exactly what I have written in my config. My grasp of the code/language isn't great so I don't know whats right or wrong ####


---
    type: comment
    modmail: New {{kind}} in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}
---
    type: submission
    modmail: New {{kind}} in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}
---
    reports: 1
    modmail: A {{kind}} has been reported in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}


###

What I would like is to be notified each time there is (in order of importance in case not everything is achievable)

1) A new submission
2) Any report whatsoever
3) A comment

This may seem extreme but it is for a small community. I borrowed this code from an older post, automod saves it but nothing happens. This may seem stupid but do I need to edit anything in the line "modmail: New {{kind}} in /r/{{subreddit}}. Link  {{permalink}}" specific to my subreddit or leave it?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that helps a lot.

By the way is there a point to a karma threshold when there is an age restriction? Surely someone won't wait a week with a throwaway account to spam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As educators, by putting our students needs first we can often forget about our own. The staff room can be a lonely place for some. If you find yourself struggling, get in touch, know that there are others that have struggled with mental health issues and gotten through it, you will too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am looking for a way to restrict spam accounts from accessing a Subreddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem I am having is twofold:

1) Spam accounts are trolling the subreddit and going through each comment and down voting everything. I would ideally like to set up something for Automod that would restrict users being able to view the subreddit unless their account is 7 days old.

2.a) If this is not possible (i may have to live with the down voting issue for a while) I want to block users from at least posting unless they have a certain karma level and account age.   days again. 

2.b) I would also like to know how to add a comment explaining why it has been removed.

2.c) Lastly, I would like to receive mod mail when this occurs so I can deal with it straight away. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Teachers' Forum: A place to seek advice and share your experience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Are you a newly qualified teacher looking for advice on the job?

* Are you simply looking to get in to the profession? 

* Are you a wise owl looking to pass on your wealth of experience?

The Teachers' Forum is a place to share any useful tips you may have picked up along the way and seek help for those little things and big things too, speak your mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of recognised qualifications for anyone considering going in to teaching from the 1st of January 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I really thought she was going out of her way to show a "different" side of travelling and how it can be can alternative to white privilege. But to be honest I didn't never thought of it as that. The info in the article is good but yeah she's a bit much alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, you came to the right place.

1) I'm assuming you did higher level maths for the LC as well as physics? Yes that should be more than fine for both subjects. You'll have to make sure that your course is recognised by the teaching council to teach those subjects. Sounds like they will but you should check the .pdf "teaching council curricular subject requirements" for yours to be sure, just google that. As long as you're competent your skill won't be an issue, it's just a matter of getting to know  the curriculum.

2) No. God no. I would say here, before I go any further, to consider why you want to go into teaching. Do you like working with kids? Do you like teaching? If yes to both then thats good. Your salary starting off on a contract won't be that. And that's if you get a contract. You'll most likely be subbing for 3 years maybe 5 (I know people who have subbed longer it's tough sometimes) but you could be lucky. You might be looking at 25k or a lot less depending on how much you work. That kind of salary takes a while, I'm not on that yet.

3) The one thing I'll say is make yourself useful. Make yourself an asset. Have stuff on your CV they can use, maths and IT are good for that, after languages they're probably the more sought after subjects. Learn up on the competitions in your subject areas, Maths Olympics, anything in programming, the lego league etc. 

But you need to like working with kids. It sounds obvious but I've met so many people go into the profession because of a love of their subject but couldn't handle teenagers and their attitudes.

You sound like you have a good job at the moment with a better salary than most new teachers. Before you make a big decision consider that. And feel.free to ask if you have any more questions. Best of luck pal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right indeed. These figures are not necessarily misleading but they're meaningless when put beside our cost of living. Yes the pay is higher compared to other countries bit that's merely one metric. I doubt teachers in any European country are paid and exorbitant amount compared to cost of living.

And as you said, I don't think the work hours are taken into consideration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> INTO Link: http://www.into.ie/ROI/InfoforTeachers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TUI Link: http://www.tui.ie/welcome-to-our-website/salary-scales-second-level-.2098.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Important information on pay scales for second level. To clarify I will post TUI link in comments if anyone has concerns over balance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify for a large percentage of us under 35, and pretty much everyone under 30, We're not on holiday during easter and summer, we're unemployed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The do's and don'ts of teaching English abroad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New r/IrishTeachers subreddit for professionals working in the education sector in Ireland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aim of r/IrishTeachers is to provide teachers working in the Irish education system a supportive community that offers the professionals a space to share advice and take part in meaningful discussion about their careers.

r/IrishTeachers is for anyone working in primary, secondary or third level education. Are you a newly qualified teacher looking for advice? Are you working abroad, teaching in a foreign country? Let us know what your experience has been like!

Check it out r/IrishTeachers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wire - Fuck Scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish teachers amongst best paid in world, despite 'austerity' cuts - OECD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young Irish teachers flock to the Middle East to make cash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3$? Jesus you must have gotten them on sale. No it was 29.99 for both. Or maybe it's a US thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dealing with sunburn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't much sun in Ireland but lately the weather's picked up and I'm a bit concerned about our Whippet. I've read that it's recommended to use sunscreen for children or sensitive skin (anything that doesn't have zinc oxide). We have used a bit on her but she got a little burn the last day while out at the beach. I'm not really sure how much, how often or where to spray. Have you any advice regarding this and your whippets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want something that won't sound like Emma orly of her commands. Jess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primary school shake up to focus on play led learning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The UN has called Ireland out on religious schools discriminatory admissions policies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you there. I think this archaic, militant approach isn't really helping anyone. It wont encourage Catholics to be better in their practices and it unfairly makes non religious people think poorly of the religious in our society. I'm not religious myself but I think it's incredibly unfair how individuals that are openly, proudly catholic are treated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. It's very out of date. My experience of this is B.O.M. blaming a lack of resources for not being able to provide for these students and parents that don't want their children to opt out. But it's simply an excuse so that they don't have to accommodate anyone that has a different set of beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my career as a teacher I have found that those who are pushing for students to attend mass are not doing it for the good of the students but for their reputation. Unfortunately anyone can derail the student-centered agenda.

I have listened to overtly religious colleagues and school management belittle students and their parents for not practicing, students pressured into going to mass and taking communion when they really don't want to. 

I've sat in on meetings about school trips where parents changed an entire day's schedule around finding a catholic church for the students to attend mass because they felt it was a Catholic School and their children should attend mass. The staff didn't want this because there were activities planned out but management caved in. No one asked the students however.

There are people on both sides, parents and teachers, who are only out to further reputation and social standing. A minority, I hope, that put their own needs above the children. It's awful because it gives a bad name to Religious people who by and large are lovely normal people like everyone else.

The ethos in each school varies. I have taught in CEIST schools that could have been completely secular for all you would know. Religion teachers that were honest and open. I've also taught in places that were run like a prison. But I believe choice in where we can send our kids in the future, Educate Together etc. will ultimately benefit the kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant thank you enough, greatly appreciated man. Go raibh mle maith agat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah of course, *smacks head*, a .png is better without a colour, that sounds better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked there. It says 

"icon must be 256x256 pixels. PNG or JPG only." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know I guess large would be fine, I think it's just a circular .png for the mobile app. Oh and if the background begind snoo's could be a lime green like the boarder ide appreciate that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thanks, yeah I would really like a mobile app Snoo, the one you created, like just the face. There's no rush and I really appreciate it bud! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheers to Steak_59 for our custom Snoo! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! Im going to see if I can get someone to do up that Snoo (just the face) as a .png Icon for the Reddit App if that's ok with you. (asking as it's your work) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
