<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2930</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are extremist in every religion.  Just take Christian extremists Ku Klux Klan, Lords Resistance Army, National Liberation Front of Tripura and the Catholic Reaction Force/Protestant Action Force.  That doesn't make all Christians part of a cult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beliefs of Muslims

Islam teaches the importance of both belief and practice; one is insufficient without the other (except for some Sufis). The following six beliefs are those that are commonly held by Muslims, as laid out in the Quran and hadith.


    Belief in the Oneness of God: Muslims believe that God is the creator of all things, and that God is all-powerful and all-knowing. God has no offspring, no race, no gender, no body, and is unaffected by the characteristics of human life.

    Belief in the Angels of God: Muslims believe in angels, unseen beings who worship God and carry out God's orders throughout the universe. The angel Gabriel brought the divine revelation to the prophets.

    Belief in the Books of God: Muslims believe that God revealed holy books or scriptures to a number of God's messengers. These include the Quran (given to Muhammad), the Torah (given to Moses), the Gospel (given to Jesus), the Psalms (given to David), and the Scrolls (given to Abraham). Muslims believe that these earlier scriptures in their original form were divinely revealed, but that only the Quran remains as it was first revealed to the prophet Muhammad.

    Belief in the Prophets or Messengers of God: Muslims believe that God's guidance has been revealed to humankind through specially appointed messengers, or prophets, throughout history, beginning with the first man, Adam, who is considered the first prophet. Twenty-five of these prophets are mentioned by name in the Quran, including Noah, Abraham, Moses, and Jesus. Muslims believe that Muhammad is the last in this line of prophets, sent for all humankind with the message of Islam.

    Belief in the Day of Judgment: Muslims believe that on the Day of Judgment, humans will be judged for their actions in this life; those who followed God's guidance will be rewarded with paradise; those who rejected God's guidance will be punished with hell.

    Belief in the Divine Decree: This article of faith addresses the question of God's will. It can be expressed as the belief that everything is governed by divine decree, namely that whatever happens in one's life is preordained, and that believers should respond to the good or bad that befalls them with thankfulness or patience. This concept does not negate the concept of "free will;" since humans do not have prior knowledge of God's decree, they do have freedom of choice.



FYI I'm not even Muslim but have many friends that are.  That being said you are free to believe whatever you want.  I just don't appreciate people spreading ignorance on subjects that you do not completely understand.  If you don't understand something it's ok to take the time to either learn about it, you may still end up feeling the same but don't miss some of the major facts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your title doesn't make sense. Being Muslim isn't a cult, that is the type of ignorance that causes the problems we have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't "have to" do that, you choose to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DRUNK guy gets TACKLED by a Coach (HIT HARD!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the Bay Area and this happens everyday...I hate the drivers out here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's pretty awesome.  Did they saying anything to you guys for doing that?  It looks like a Southwest flight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love these old commercials, things are to serious now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> come to California and tell me there isn't a problem with the climate...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then do that for American Police....smh http://imgur.com/sIKEG05 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but the message was strong and worth sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
