<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8567921
Please! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nose Picking. No need go deep but a pick isn't so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom took my playstation power cable. I stole one from a friend. When my mom found me playing games she thought I stole it back from her, she went and found where she had stashed it. She beat me with it until I confessed that I stole the new one from a friend and then drove me over there to return it and apologize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This I saw at a friends house. I remember going over to his house after school one day and asking, "uh where's your door?" he responded with, "I didn't make curfew last week."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up until 14 I never would do my chores. When my parents would yell at me about not doing my chores I'd throw a temper tantrum. They tried to reason with me and said things like, "we pay for your food, clothes, and your shelter. The least you can do is clean your room and rake the leaves." So one day I was supposed to clean my room and rake the front yard. I did neither. My parents get pissed, I start yelling. It was around dinner time and suddenly there's no place setting for me. I double down and start yelling that I didn't want dinner anyway. Then my mom tells me to take off my clothes. After some hitting and yelling, I'm standing in the corner in my underwear. But of course I'm still sobbing and yelling at the top of my lungs. Then they tell me to get out of the house until I calm down. I'm mostly naked, it's a frosty northeastern autumn eve, and my mom is holding the door open for all the neighborhood to hear and see a 14 year old half naked kid yelling and screaming about room cleaning and leaf raking. I was outside for about 3 minutes before I calmed down. It was so damn cold. But holy shit did I ever learn my lesson. I can't imagine what the neighbors thought.

I did ask my mom about the episode a few years ago(about 20 years later). She did not remember. My older brother did, however, and said it was hilarious from his perspective. This was of course during a time when "child abuse" and "parenting" had some overlapping themes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a friend in high school that asked me to read her essay for her reach school, an expensive private college in the northeast US. She was from a Vietnamese family that owned a series of nail salons. She explained in her essay that sometimes to help ends meet she'd have to work in the salons after school. She went into meticulous detail about giving women pedicures, especially when they had nasty feet. 

I learned a lot that day. I also didn't eat much. At first I was disgusted. I had nightmares from how she described some of the old womens bunions, calluses and ingrown toenails. The smell, the texture, the sensitivity she described was just overwhelming. 

Then it hit me. I was only reading about it. She actually had to do it. All the time.

It was obvious she was a great writer, but I had to tell her that this may not get her into the school. She got in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muh gains!@ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow I think this story is relevant.
Back in the 50s my grandfather was finally making money as a physician. This was after school and serving as a stateside doc for 4 years during WWII, and then working at a hospital for vets for a few years after. He and my grandmother decided to extend their family as they only had one child, wanted to get to 4, and time was not on their side. Part of this dream was to sink a large amount of whatever money they had into a nice house. My grandfather found a plot of land about an acre in a philly suburb and hired a firm to build the house. Things were going well and they thought they had timed the birth of their second child such that the house would be done. My grandfather would swing by the construction site every day on his way home from his office to check on the progress himself. Sometimes he'd clean up after the workers a little. Sometimes he'd make notes and send them to the foreman. But the main goal was to make sure the house was built before that baby came out. So he'd hide beer around the site. Especially in areas that were ahead of schedule. I'm sure this violates some rules somewhere, and there may be some exaggeration, but apparently my grandmother gave birth 2 weeks early and the house was done 2 days prior to that.
What's my take? Treat people well and they'll give you what you want.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wrong." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I buy lotto tickets(once or twice a month) I feel foolish. I know I'm smarter than this. I know saving/investing the $5 would be better. When someone points this out I usually say something like "I know the lottery is just a tax on stupid people." 
But then I get to day dreaming about hitting that $100m jackpot. That the cash option is only about $50m and after taxes it ends up being closer to $25m. But damn...what I could do with $25m... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 4 months of dating we had a long talk about our futures and what we "wanted out of life". I thought we had shared a moment. We didn't really talk too much for the next 3-4 weeks. a few texts, maybe an IM. For some reason I didn't think too much about it.

One night I'm chillin with some people, including the girl that set me up with my gf. She says something like, "how long are you going to be depressed about her? she dumped you like a month ago." First, I didn't think I was acting depressed. Second...she dumped me?! when?! 

Turns out that deep conversation was her telling me she wanted to break up cause she didn't know what she wanted or something. 

EPILOGUE: less than 3 months after she apparently dumped me she started dating a guy she ended up marrying less than half a year later. She invited me to the wedding...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can use it for soup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 01:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was worried after I posted it that it would be misconstrued as something sexual. For those that are not aware, tears are also a "salty discharge".

I don't know why. But something about this brought me to tears. Not like wailing, uncontrollable, crying. Just...I was filled with emotion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me after watching that:
[](http://images-cdn.9gag.com/photo/am9AjV4_700b.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use this at work all the time:

"Well I'm not calling you a liar, but.......... but I can't think of a way to finish that sentence." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Steves makes a response video to LePage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I keep from getting sick while traveling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice Restaurants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey All,

Planning a bachelor party for MLK or Pres. Day weekends and looking for advice on restaurants. I'd like to lead the group(maybe 8 people?) to a nice restaurant one night. I've heard good things about the french place in EPCOT. Any advice? We won't have any fancy food passes or anything and I figure for one meal we'll go all out, so price may not matter too much.

Thanks!

EDIT: thanks for suggestions! I'll look into all of these. When I googled fancy restaurants at disney world Victoria and Albert's keeps popping up. Anyone been? Is it too off the beat path? Is it like $100 a plate? Is there secretly a better place and V A's is just a trap?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whys it gotta be ***black*** magic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not using turn signals.
It's not that hard to flip the switch. It is illegal to not use them. They help communicate better with the rest of the people on the road. Yet for some reason I can't go 10 minutes on the highway without seeing someone changing lanes without their signal. I don't care if there is no one else on the road, use the damn signal. It's the guy you don't see(and doesn't see you) that'll get ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved my 91 integra. drove like a go-kart. I could fit under most of those arm barriers for parking lots. Could go up sidewalk ramps and stash my car between buildings while I was in class. Drove that thing til it had over 275k miles on it and something just blew. So sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time for an update: [History of Japan](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mh5LY4Mz15o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I would take a no man's sky key. I really want to play it but don't want to pay so much for it.
Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 08:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once saw a porno where the girl said she made out with all of her best friends because it was girl code. So, that must be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 08:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other people should have children so that I don't have to. But we'll see when I turn 30 how I feel. Maybe still no. Probably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 08:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 min answer
1 min rebuttal
12 min of interrupting

So why does it matter if Mark Cuban is there? And will the moderator be "calling out lies"? Is that part of the moderators job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The rules of the first Presidential Debate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 04:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Thanks. And it's effective Jan 1 2016! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
