<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject723</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I walk into a room and there's a birthday cake on the table, I assume someone baked it.  Oh, sorry, I forgot you don't do analogies...

T=PR for a cylindrical vessel, T= PR/2 for a spherical vessel....looks like SOMEONE made a vessel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a prophet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I guess we've reached the point in the discussion where you pretend that you have no idea what an analogy is.  That's fine.
Analogies pertaining to the discussion are very pertinent-and not being able to engage in them is very typical of atheists.  It just demonstrates a rigid, terrified, inflexible mind.  Since the best you can hope for is eternal oblivion, I don't blame you for that.

So, rather than just copy and paste your post and interject my thoughts in between each statement ( lazy, and worse, boring), let me sum up:  I contend matter is here because an omnipotent being willed it so and you contend matter is here because..., oh, science will figure it out one day.  That's where YOU'RE faith lies.
Science is great!  We can do way more stuff with it than without it.  I use it every day to keep people alive.   In fact, I use laPlaces Law every day to determine what setting I want to use for ventilator.  What I understand and you do not is that it simply can't answer the question I posed it.  It still won't be able to answer that question millennia from now when the molecules that used to be your body are something else entirely-stardust you like to think, or maybe a toilet.  
Atheism has intentionally ignored the search for primary causes because it is too humiliating for them.  Hilariously, they discover laws and don't think to ask, "why this way and not that?".  The answer to that question is the same one that bedivils them in regard to primary causes, the existence of matter, the existence of energy-because that's how God designed it!  That must be frustrating for you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine.  I was just letting the OP know that mine stops leaves too.  I probably don't have mine in ideal conditions either.  Still on the pot.  Next to kitchen window.  Water it once a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you're wife is there because you can smell her cooking dinner, and you know she's there because you know her intimately, you talk to and listen to her.  They aren't mutually exclusive.

I am not interested so much how matter came into being, the mechanics, because according to every observation ever made by a sentient being, you can't have something come from nothing.  

You are placing your faith in science.  You will always say "science just hasn't got there yet"-and the can will forever be kicked further down the road with the most obvious of facts out of your reach because of pride and arrogance.  You can't extend you life by an hour or keep your own hair from turning gray but you will look at an incomprehensibly vast creation and think you understand the tiniest sliver of it and pronounce "there is no God".  

Newton was right in his statement "*Planets, and Comets, could only proceed from the counsel and dominion of an intelligent and powerful Being."-and you could further distill this wisdom into "quarks and the laws by which cosmic inflation and dark matter operate could only proceed from the counsel and dominion of an intelligent and powerful being".  No offense, but you are hardly a Newton.

You can't tell me my wife doesn't exist when I'm eating the steak she made me or when I'm lying next to her in bed at night.  You currently are just attempting to explain how the heat from the oven interacted with the beef to make it medium rare.  You haven't even thought to ask why it is on your plate at all.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe.  That's just what mine does.  By no means am I an expert on succulents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got that same one at home-it drops off the lower leaves as it adds more on top. Had it for several months and haven't killed it yet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost killed by a herd of buffalo on that island! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kid needs to go on Conan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aston Kutcher for good, Trump for evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They though Jesus was coming back in their lifetimes.  When the Church starting spreading they understood they would need to write these things down for effective, reliable communication of the Gospel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your very informative and detailed answer.  The existence of matter doesn't necessarily argue for the existence of God, per se, but it does argue for a beginning, which your excellent explanation postulates began with various forces obeying certain laws.  This then begs the question, where did those laws come from?  Where did heat come from?  Where did energy come from?  Right?
You simply can't get away from the realization that there must have been nothing at some point, or something at some point from which all the other somethings we observe relate to in some way.  
My point is that the current persistent assertion that "it just sploded " makes no sense according to all the laws we've been able to observe.  This doesn't mean "THERE IS A GOD", but it does mean that "THERE IS A GOD" is amore valid an argument than anything science has been able to put forth-it explains what is observed perfectly and cannot be disproven.  
Your answer, though very thoughtful and interesting, doesn't really explain anything at all.  You've simply said, "not matter, energy", which is utter nonsense.
I just believe in God because I happen to know Him.  You can too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain how it got there to my primitive little mind, if you would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Move on, nothing to see here...TRUCKER HAT!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That terrible.  I'm not against guns or hunting, but elephants are over the line.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll never argue someone into belief, but we are called to defend the faith.  We should be fit and ready in that regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's what you do in between active witnessing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go gramps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the simplest of terms, you can't explain matter without a Creator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So where did matter come from again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who moves  DVDs anymore?  Don't you have Netflix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have been a Catholic Priest-he'd be on a nice sabbatical now instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this an application to work for the Trump Administration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a rifle, not a shotgun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth exists.
Therefore God.

If/then exists.
Therefore God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, she's terrible.  Just not as terrible as Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just look for the short busses and rebel flags in Wal Mart parking lots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So..., what was the happy news? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stole my point!

You shall not steal.
Exodus 20:15  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The RCC equates the authority of church tradition with the authority of the Bible.  Rather than elevating the traditions this practice degrades the authority of Scripture.  
So, they don't take it seriously.  How could God disapprove of them?  They go to mass, the go to confession, they pray to Mary,  buy indulgences...whatever.  Despite what they say, it is a form of works righteousness.  That means it's NOT the Gospel.  That also frees them up to go to psychics, have mistresses, participate in organized crime, pay and expect bribes; all vices we associate with that generation of RCC.  Lots of mobsters were "very devout" Catholics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really appreciate his touch when interviewing people.  He takes them out to coffee, just calls to see how they are doing, really listens to them.  He is great!  I'm glad you appreciate him too.
I can't wait for some updates in season 1.  The little bit of shoe they found dredging the lake has me intrigued... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably need to drop the Christian (Cross) tag on your handle if you're going to treat people like this in a discussion about climate change.  People don't always agree with you-abusing them rarely changes their minds.
The fate of the human race is in Gods hands.  We know it will survive AND we know God is going to destroy these heavens and earth with fire.  We should be good stewards, but every single human soul is going to outlast this planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creating an alternate reality for Wal Mart employees and NRA members. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your points, but not sure I'd use the parable of the Talents to support your argument.  The principle laid out in the parable is to use everything you have to further the Kingdom.  The servant who sought to simply preserve what he was given and not multiply it was rebuked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pppttthhh.  Whatever.  "Completely human caused"?  You are being gullible.  I'm not going to debate you, but one thing most people don't get about data is understanding it's limitations.  Most of what you have access to is interpretation, not data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So without works you are damned.  Logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal opinion is that climate change is real, cyclical, and built into the planet.  I think the human affect on climate is real to a degree, but overstated.
I do think that God uses human activity to further His will, and so your theory is possible.  Ultimately, though, we'll know when it happens!
The more interesting question is do you think we can delay the end by changing our emissions?  I think not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These subs won't moderate themselves, people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice!  Thanks.  Will definitely check them out too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawdy!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe too obtuse for all but the most discerning connoisseurs of spousal abuse.  Glad you got it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the guy that does SOMEONE KNOWS SOMETHING (SKS).  His name is David Ridgen.  He's Canadian, but he  can't really help that.  
That guy is a good journalist, a good interviewer, a very careful and deliberate storyteller, and he really seems to care about the subjects.  He develops relationships with the families as he investigates and you can just tell he's a quality human being.  They just finished season 2.  You should check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we command you, brothers, in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ, that you keep away from any brother who is walking in idleness and not in accord with the tradition that you received from us.
2 Thessalonians 3:6 ESV
Now such persons we command and encourage in the Lord Jesus Christ to do their work quietly and to earn their own living.
As for you, brothers, do not grow weary in doing good. If anyone does not obey what we say in this letter, take note of that person, and have nothing to do with him, that he may be ashamed. Do not regard him as an enemy, but warn him as a brother.
2 Thessalonians 3:12-15 ESV


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the prices like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never even heard of it!  Exactly the kind of response I was looking for.  Thanks  a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, you can read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have thunder in Ireland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for him!  What a prick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were a better fan this wouldn't keep happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap plants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to Hanna's on 280 today and left empty-handed and in a foul mood.  So expensive!!  Suggestions for cheap plants around town? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one understands the Trinity.  It is accepted on faith because it can't be really grasped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Jesus certainly believed in hell.  Was He wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure.  If you've been in 2nd or 3rd world countries recently or if you start having weight loss too then I'm not kidding.  Totally treatable-will destroy your life if you have it and don't treat it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Presidential... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha Justin Beiber! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill it with fire!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah-Asia Minor.  Present day Turkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump fail-time to start blaming other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A soul has a start.  It is created by the Word and exists forever after that in paradise or torment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God only knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ followers that hate ANYONE are just wrong.  They need to be corrected by their brothers/sisters in love and they need to repent.
As a Christian, I apologize for them.  I hope you come to find the love of God.  Realize He is actively pursuing you right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I understand.  Submit to your parents leadership and establish in your own mind if and how the Pastors behavior is anti-Christian.  Talk about it with them, of course.  If you submit to them
in a Biblical way, they won't "despise your youth", also in accord with the Scripture.  
Remember that God desires unity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  Obey the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the doctor.  It could be TB and you 
might  be infecting everyone you know and love.  It's treatable too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our lives are lives of repentance and our goal is complete dependence on Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither will save you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A church member breaking the law is subject to the punishment prescribed by the law-they should admit in court FULLY what they've done in public and then submit without complaining to the ruling.  
THEN they are subject to the discipline of their church prescribed in the New Testament.  Just go read it.  It's all right there, step by step.  Realize that the goal of the discipline is their good and reconciliation.  The LOVING thing to do is the discipline.
It's all laid out in the Scriptures if you care to look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 things to revolutionize your life:

1.  Don't bring your phone to the toilet.
2.  Don't bring your phone to bed.

Changed my whole day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Pastor sounds like a fool.  I would submit to your parents if they wanted you to continue to go-but guard your heart from him.  God desires unity, not division-so someone who claims the role of a leader but is needlessly divisive is NOT performing Gods will and doesn't reflect Gods attitude, so that makes you wonder how close to God he really is.  See Ephesians 4 (the whole chapter, ESV ONLY!).
God Bless! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to answer a single one of your questions, but to give you confidence and reassurance:  we are to glorify God with our minds, our hearts, and our wills.  Each of us has greater or lesser portions of each-but we can glorify Him just as well as ANYONE else by surrendering what we do have to Him.  
I'm convinced that some people just CAN't be Calvinists-they don't have the processing power.  I'm further convinced that a lot of people who do have the processing power SHOULDN'T be Calvinists because they don't have the willpower to resist the pride and arrogance that comes of being more correct than everyone else.
In short-we should bear with one another as Paul writes to the Church at Ephesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  I would add that He is speaking to you through your own story too.  Everything that has happened to you He has ordained so that you can glorify Him with it!  This is a very intimate thing-your life isn't just random events until you die.  It has a course charted by God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  Trump fails-there will be some blame to be cast.  If you can count  on one thing, it's Trump having zero character and being the sorest of losers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a little cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that episode of Scrubs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The colors of the furniture and the country kitchen go so nicely!  Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why couldn't Christ followers just agree on the basic one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this atmosphere of distrust, alt-facts, and fake news an accurate title would be best, don't you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  I'm wrong about all of the things that separate us?  You shall know them  by their fruit-the fruit of the RCC is thousands of children raped by priests, idolatry, confusion, works-righteousness, and idolatry.
Your verses for the classification of sins just don't work that way in context.  You misunderstand holiness.   It's never partial-it's binary.  You are clean 100% or you are damned.  "Be Holy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why not the Lord's Prayer, OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ventilator weaning and APRV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Reformed Christian, we believe the classification of sins as mortal as venial is false.  Salvation is not a work you do, but one that God has done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you are coming from.  Job felt that way too-Behold, I cry out, Violence! but I am not answered; I call for help, but there is no justice" in Job 19:7.  But Isaiah says the Lord of hosts is exalted in justice, and the Holy God shows himself holy in righteousness" in Isaiah 5:16. 

Still, we should not forget that God is far above our ability to judge and that Holy means separate, completely pure.  For my thoughts are not your thoughts, neither are your ways my ways, declares the Lord" in Isaiah 55.   God's justice doesn't sleep, but we don't dictate the timing.

As to suffering-God works suffering in our lives to His purposes.  We don't understand what those are during the suffering, but can often look back and see His hand guiding us through it to where we are now.  We know that He allows it, but we trust that somehow it works for our good.

I will praise a God like that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chosen one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you thought it was fake news-TrumpNuts live in alt-reality with alt-facts.  Eventually the actual facts show up and kick you in the nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paying for wifi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?  What'd you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah-that's bad-A 4chan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fiend!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who got away with a serious crime and have never been caught-how did you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think about a third of them would be jealous of redemption.  Sorry to disagree with your dead guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who got away with murder-tell us how you did it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boiled egg, apple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
