<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4276</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study provides insight into the causes of self-sacrifice in violent conflicts around the world, from holy wars to gangland violence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA clears up skies with new fuel. A new report shows scientists were able to reduce particle pollution from aircraft exhausts, a discovery that could reduce the climate effects of such emissions significantly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are 'bad bots' weaponising data centres to spread fake news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Reporter to Trump: Will 'America First' Weaken Europe? Why Do You Cite Fake News? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schools should teach pupils how to spot 'fake news' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 09:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you type into Google what heats ocean water? And you will find that what your saying is completely wrong. Especially your first comment which strangely gets upvoted by people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would people up vote disinformation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which shows the changing climate. This article is even more relevant regarding the cuts to climate research. No need to say more, have a read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The earth experienced the second hottest February on record in 2017 in spite of the fact that there was no El Nino effect warming the planets waters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The earth experienced the second hottest February on record in 2017 in spite of the fact that there was no El Nino effect warming the planets waters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump, why are you shrinking the EPA when Defense Secretary Mattis believes climate change is a national security threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate had a hand in shaping the human nose. Researchers examined the size and shape of noses on people with West African, South Asian, East Asian, or Northern European ancestry and found that differences in nose shape across these populations are greater than can be explained by chance alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Til The average temperature of the Earth's surface has increased by about 0.85C (1.4F) in the last 100 years. Thirteen of the 14 warmest years were recorded in the 21st Century, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fitch: The debt ceiling will be raised to $20,000,000,000,000 just in nick of time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Disasters Emergency Committee (DEC) appeal for the crisis in East Africa has raised 12 million in less than 24 hours, with money continuing to pour in from the public. Drought and conflict have left 16 million people on the brink of starvation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research helps predict early warning signs of drought. Better forecasting could help relief agencies avert humanitarian catastrophes in less-developed regions of the world, where droughts are a matter of life and death for millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drugs costing 8p a day could be hit by 'devastating' NHS rationing plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The chameleon effect refers to nonconscious mimicry of the postures, mannerisms, facial expressions, and other behaviors of one's interaction partners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House seeks to cut EPA budget 31 percent as Trump targets regulation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> East Africa Crisis Appeal: Queen donates to help millions starving amid drought and conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> East Africa Crisis Appeal: Queen donates to help millions starving amid drought and conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The average person has about 48.6 thoughts per minute. That adds up to a total of 70,000 thoughts per day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disasters Emergency Committee launches east Africa hunger appeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The prospect of losing a smartphone stresses people out almost as much as the fear of a terror attack, a new study has shown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From rising levels of air pollution to increased water contamination and a widening range for disease-carrying mosquitoes, climate change is making people sick, a coalition of 11 US medical groups said Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saved, looks interesting thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, thanks though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spiders eat 400-800 million tons of prey every year. With more than 45,000 species and a population density of up to 1,000 individuals per square meter, spiders are one of the world's most species-rich and widespread groups of predators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me please what the president of the most powerful country in the world said about climate change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a source for this please or if anyone else does, id be interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Climate change is impacting stability in areas of the world where our troops are operating today, Mattis said in written answers to questions posed after the public hearing by Democratic members of the committee. It is appropriate for the Combatant Commands to incorporate drivers of instability that impact the security environment in their areas into their planning.

Mattis has long espoused the position that the armed forces, for a host of reasons, need to cut dependence on fossil fuels and explore renewable energy where it makes sense. He had also, as commander of the U.S. Joint Forces Command in 2010, signed off on the Joint Operating Environment, which lists climate change as one of the security threats the military expected to confront over the next 25 years.

But Mattis written statements to the Senate committee are the first direct signal of his determination to recognize climate change as a member of the Trump administration charged with leading the countrys armed forces.

These remarks and others in the replies to senators could be a fresh indication of divisions or uncertainty within President Donald Trumps administration over how to balance the presidents desire to keep campaign pledges to kill Obama-era climate policies with the need to engage constructively with allies for whom climate has become a vital security issue.

Mattis statements on climate change, for instance, recognize the same body of science that Scott Pruitt, the new Environmental Protection Agency administrator, seems dead-set on rejecting. In a CNBC interview last Thursday, Pruitt rejected established science pointing to carbon dioxide as the main driver of recent global warming.

Mattis position also would appear to clash with some Trump administration budget plans, which, according to documents leaked recently to The Washington Post, include big cuts for the Commerce Departments oceanic and atmospheric research  much of it focused on tracking and understanding climate change.

Even setting aside warming driven by accumulating carbon dioxide, its clear to a host of experts, including Dr. Will Happer, a Princeton physicist interviewed by Trump in January as a potential science adviser, that better monitoring and analysis of extreme conditions like drought is vital.

Mattis statements could hearten world leaders who have urged the Trump administration to remain engaged on addressing global warming. German Chancellor Angela Merkel is scheduled to meet Trump on Friday.

https://www.propublica.org/article/trumps-defense-secretary-cites-climate-change-national-security-challenge?utm_source=Daily+Carbon+Briefing utm_campaign=2016c9ce4d-cb_daily utm_medium=email utm_term=0_876aab4fd7-2016c9ce4d-303476449 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which speaks for itself regarding the issue of climate change and the affects it is having and will have on the world. This subject is relevant to everyone and will be for future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Defense Secretary Cites Climate Change as National Security Challenge. I agree that the effects of a changing climate  such as increased maritime access to the Arctic, rising sea levels, desertification, among others  impact our security situation" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Defence Secretary James Mattis says climate change is already destabilising the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Defence Secretary James Mattis says climate change is already destabilising the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Defence Secretary James Mattis says climate change is already destabilising the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Defence Secretary James Mattis says climate change is already destabilising the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public sector workers first to face cut in real pay, says thinktank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People with ADHD are quick to lose their patience. Several of the participants in the study cited boredom in their previous jobs as a reason for setting up their own company, where they could follow up on their own ideas whenever they wanted. One woman reported that she had introduced 250 new products within just a few years. In situations that would be highly stressful for others, such as difficult meetings with important customers, many of those surveyed felt at ease and stimulated. "Their impulsiveness, resulting from ADHD, gives them the advantage of being able to act under unforeseen circumstances without falling into anxiety and paralysis," says Patzelt.

Most of those surveyed act without thinking, even when making far-reaching decisions. One of the entrepreneurs described buying a friend's company over lunch. He only learned of the friend's plan to retire during the meal. Other participants reported that they make investments with no strategy and commit large sums of money to projects with highly uncertain outcomes. Some entrepreneurs believe that this kind of quick decision making is the only way to be productive, and are willing to live with setbacks as a result. Some have difficulty coping with structured activities.

"A marked willingness to try out new things and take risks is an important entrepreneurial trait," says Patzelt. However, the respondents' impulsive actions led to success only when they focused on activities essential to the development of their businesses. One disadvantage of their impulsiveness was mentioned by all of them: problems with routine tasks such as bookkeeping.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ADHD Characteristics May Help with Business Success. Their intuitive decision making in situations involving uncertainty was seen by the researchers as a reason for reassessing existing economic models. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisiana wetlands struggling with sea-level rise 4 times the global average </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which highlights the dangers of surveillance and how without regulation it can become out of control with far reaching consequences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK public faces mass invasion of privacy as big data and surveillance merge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost 40 million UK consumers will remain in the red this year as unsecured debt hits 240bn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Til In WW1 a handful of journalists risked their lives to report on the realities of war. As the Government sought to control the flow of information from the frontline at the start of the war, journalists were banned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you show me the repost please with the link of the same study? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuroscientists have used brain scans to spot the difference between people who committed crimes on purpose and those who broke the law through sheer reckless behaviour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs10584-017-1934-z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats and Republicans draw different conclusions when seasons are too hot or too cold. Attitudes about climate change are more pronounced when people reside in states experiencing unseasonably warm (or cold) temperatures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to a study by 2091, the Arctic will see a dramatic 50- 60% increase of rain precipitation. The cycle feeds itself  warming temperatures lead to more rain and more melting ice, which leads to more open water and even more rain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to a study by 2091, the Arctic will see a dramatic 50- 60% increase of rain precipitation. The cycle feeds itself  warming temperatures lead to more rain and more melting ice, which leads to more open water and even more rain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mozilla: people have no idea how to protect their privacy and security online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? im not to sure about this. How would you prove this. If anything ( from my point of view)  technology has made it easier not use your brain, for example a calculator when doing maths. Mobile phones, just press a key and the number is on your screen. No hard thinking involved. Also attention, with the vast amount of information at the click of a button scanning a subject in my opinion is easier than going to the library  researching what subject and choosing book, ( so much more mental effort involved) .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Leaders Conspire To Keep Trump In The Paris Climate Agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is Big Oil Backing The Paris Climate Agreement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There are currently estimated to be over 46 million people worldwide living with dementia. The number of people affected is set to rise to over 131 million by 2050. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of vulnerable people held unlawfully in care homes -report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joining the ranks of former Exxon CEO, and now Secretary of State, Rex Tillerson, the chief executive of another big U.S. energy company, ConocoPhillips, is saying that the U.S. should stay in the Paris Climate Agreement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can i ask, how come you got hold of this? Its interesting, the article is  old though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, that read of your link was terrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Science Denial Network Funds Toxic Chemical Propaganda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover how neurons tell each other to die under trauma, disease. The study suggests that axons coordinate each other's destruction, thereby contributing to the degeneration that makes neurological diseases so devastating and permanent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Fermi Paradox is the apparent contradiction between the high probability extraterrestrial civilizations' existence and the lack of contact with such civilizations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And interesting article which highlights the concerns of the founder of the web. Here  he discusses his three main worries and how we are all affected according to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir Tim Berners-Lee explains the future of the web on its 28th birthday. There are three big threats to the world wide web as it currently exists  sharing personal data, misinformation, and political advertising. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK political parties at risk from Russian cyber-attacks, GCHQ warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs, Toddlers Show Similarities in Social Intelligence. Dogs and children similarly outperformed chimps on cooperative communication tasks, and researchers observed similar patterns of variation in performance between individual dogs and between individual children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA office flooded with phone calls after Scott Pruitt's idiotic comments about carbon dioxide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team has documented a case in which a terminal patient removed from life support continued to experience brain wave activity for approximately 10 minutes after they had been pronounced clinically dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Democrats Who Got Big Gifts From Oil Industry Gave Big Gifts Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SXSW panel opens window into dangers of facial recognition software </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From an analysis of more than 20 million health records across the U.S., researchers have uncovered a link between marijuana use and an increased risk of stroke and heart failure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native Americans take Dakota Access pipeline protest to Washington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress again pushing NSA to reveal number of Americans under surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress again pushing NSA to reveal number of Americans under surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study has determined that psychological momentum significantly affects performance among male stock traders but not among women, which may account for exaggerated risk-taking in financial and business endeavors among men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Obama science advisor expresses fears about changing climate policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study of groups in tension or conflict found evidence that people are willing to share a society with those of differing beliefs as long as they believe that those groups share a commitment to universal moral values such as fairness and harm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://insights.ovid.com/crossref?an=00041444-900000000-99596

The scientists now want to investigate more closely what the links are between the DNA and social phobia. "In order to achieve this goal, we need many more study participants who suffer from social anxiety," says the psychologist and study coordinator Stefanie Rambau from the Clinic and Policlinic for Psychosomatic Medicine and Psychotherapy at University Hospital Bonn. Information about the study is available at http://www.SocialPhobiaResearch.de. "Those who take part will help to research social phobia. This is the basis of better diagnosis and treatment procedures in the future," says Stefanie Rambau. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with social anxiety avoid situations in which they are exposed to judgement by others. Researchers have now found evidence for a gene that is believed to be linked to the illness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting warmer. Trumps EPA chief isn't sure humans are causing global warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans are confused on climate, but support cutting carbon pollution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danish consumer council refers Google to Data Protection Agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early deaths from childhood cancer up to 4 times more common than previously reported. A study has found that death within a month of diagnosis is more likely in very young children and those from minority racial and ethnic groups even independent of low socioeconomic status </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A look at the weather in the US for February where usual patterns were seen and several records were broke or nearly tied. I find it interesting we are seeing these patterns and the current political climate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra-Warm February Nearly Beats US Heat Record. Chicago had no snow, Oklahoma hit 99 degrees and NOAA said local weather stations broke or tied warm temperature records 11,743 times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra-Warm February Nearly Beats US Heat Record. Chicago had no snow, Oklahoma hit 99 degrees and NOAA said local weather stations broke or tied warm temperature records 11,743 times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra-Warm February Nearly Beats US Heat Record. Chicago had no snow, Oklahoma hit 99 degrees and NOAA said local weather stations broke or tied warm temperature records 11,743 times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra-Warm February Nearly Beats US Heat Record. Chicago had no snow, Oklahoma hit 99 degrees and NOAA said local weather stations broke or tied warm temperature records 11,743 times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Air pollution 'urgent public health crisis' warning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ok, however i would of thought the logic being now a president threatening to scrap the Paris accord has made it a Science story. I have a feeling that this subject has  been politicised if we like it or not, such is life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has Trump not threatened to scrap the Paris accord then? Im sure he has. If so how can the headline be sensationalised?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv replied to the mods, with queries and evidence. However we have seemed to hit a brick wall. Regarding the initial removal , no way in the title is it biased or sensationalised . In fact it is taken from the article. And every word of it is fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regulators Demand Repair of Leaking Alaska Gas Pipeline, Citing Public Hazard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Council bosses are planning to ban swearing in Rochdale town centre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The polling study is the first in-depth climate change research in multiple European nations and involved interviewing more than 1,000 people in each country, with the results then weighted to be nationally representative.



The citizens gave near identical answers to the question of when the impacts of global warming would be felt, with 60% answering that they were already here. At least two-thirds of them supported their nation being part of the Paris climate deal and they were at least two to one in favour of penalising countries that were not, perhaps via the border carbon taxes proposed by some French politicians.

People see that if there are free riders, that is not a very good thing, said Pidgeon. Earlier in March, the US state department snubbed the UNs climate change chief when she requested a meeting.

Subsidising renewable energy with public money was popular, with 70% support in the UK and Germany, 75% in France, and 87% in Norway. Increasing taxes on fossil fuels was supported in oil- and gas-rich Norway, but opposed two to one in France and Germany. In the UK, people were evenly split over tax hikes for fossil fuels.

Some may find this graph rather interesting of the unusual temperatures over the North pole 8th Match 2017

http://cci-reanalyzer.org/wx/fcst/#GFS-025deg.ARC-LEA.T2_anom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change impacts are already hitting us, say Europeans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change impacts are already hitting us, say Europeans. New polling study also shows support for financial penalties for nations that refuse to be part of Paris climate deal, as Donald Trump has threatened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jcpp.12693/full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research strengthens the link between long-term stress and increased risk of obesity. Researchers found that individuals who had persistently high levels of the "stress hormone" cortisol over long periods of time weighed more, had a higher body mass index (BMI), and a larger waist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which highlights how the  recent Australian summer has broke lots of climate records. The report highlights how over the years this is likely to get worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australians endured another intense summer, with more than 200 record-breaking extreme weather events driven by climate change, the Climate Councils latest report has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The past summer in Australia has been dubbed the 'angry summer' by climate scientists who found that 205 weather records were broken in 90 days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The past summer in Australia has been dubbed the 'angry summer' by climate scientists who found that 205 weather records were broken in 90 days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The past summer in Australia has been dubbed the 'angry summer' by climate scientists who found that 205 weather records were broken in 90 days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple to 'rapidly address' security holes as tech companies respond to CIA leak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than half of councils equip staff with body cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost half of all deaths from heart disease   diabetes linked to diet: JAMA study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Administration Seeks Big Budget Cuts for Climate Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 tips to encrypt your entire life in less than an hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facial recognition technology is turning people into human bar codes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study by the WHO discusses the dramatic impact environmental factors have on child mortality, with 270,000 children dying during the first month of life due to environmental pollution. Many households in the developing world still rely on burning coal or even dung for heating and cooking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK shoppers cut back on luxuries as inflation pushes up cost of food and fuel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots in indian army: Army to get self-reliant, autonomous robots soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One in three Australians report health problems from fragranced consumer products. The results mirrored those from similar research Professor Steinemann conducted in the United States, which found 34.7 per cent of people experienced health problems when exposed to fragranced products. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump supporters are the buyers driving the stock markets record run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Purge leftists: Trump supporter Rep. Steve King wants the president to root out those who oppose him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK carbon emissions drop to lowest level since 19th century, study finds. Ditching dirty coal benefiting environment as gas and renewables increase their share in electricity generation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jcpp.12694/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physically abused kids struggle to learn about rewards. These children stick to what they learned early in life  that rewards are rare and unpredictable, but punishment is always imminent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://www.smh.com.au/cqstatic/guqxlk/herold.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2008 financial crisis is still killing off 8,300 in wages for families every year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil and Gas Lobby Fights California Regulators to Keep Injecting Drilling Wastewater into Protected Aquifers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Widespread conflicts of interest among patient-advocacy organizations uncovered in study. Over the past few decades, hundreds of patient-advocacy organizations have emerged in the United States, promoting disease research and influencing FDA and health insurer policies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Claim About Obama Wiretapping Offers No Evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An in depth look at the Great Depression and the after effects of it. It highlights parallels which some could argue that are here today both in the political and financial landscape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Great Depression reveals about our future. It was the biggest setback to the global economy since the dawn of the modern industrial age. But did the worlds reaction worsen the effects of the 1929 Crash? And have we learned from those mistakes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphins have a language that helps them solve problems together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The effect of the internet on voting behavior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The effect of the internet on voting behavior. The internet can reduce political participation and thus affect legislation in labor and other areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artificial Intelligence Can Now Accurately Predict Suicide Attempts Two Years in Advance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First yearly CO2 forecast predicts one of biggest rises ever. It is just four years since the peak level of CO2 first exceeded the troubling milestone of 400 ppm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since January 1, 2017 there have been more than 50 accidental releases from pipelines and oil and gas facilities in Alberta. These spills and leaks, ranging from large to small, from hazardous to non-hazardous, happen almost every single day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands travel to the capital for national NHS protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0747563217300493 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High levels of narcissism and a weaker sense of peer belonging is leading millions of young adults to take part in deceptive like-seeking avenues on Instagram, a recent Western study revealed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 35 percent of UK jobs may be at risk from automation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found that eating at least three portions of vegetables and two servings of fruits daily was associated with lower risk of dementia in older adults. Dementia is estimated to affect around 47.5 million people worldwide, and this number is expected to more than triple by 2050. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study https://www.researchgate.net/publication/297742112_Parenthood_as_a_Moral_Imperative_Moral_Outrage_and_the_Stigmatization_of_Voluntarily_Childfree_Women_and_Men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds participants feel moral outrage toward those who decide to not have children. Data representing individuals from across the United States indicates that U.S. adults are increasingly delaying the decision to have children or forgoing parenthood entirely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House supports renewal of spy law without reforms: official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A short article which highlights how the Antarctic is breaking heat records today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Argentine research base near the northern tip of the Antarctic peninsula has set a heat record at a balmy 63.5 Fahrenheit (17.5 degrees Celsius), the U.N. weather agency said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Argentine research base near the northern tip of the Antarctic peninsula has set a heat record at a balmy 63.5 Fahrenheit (17.5 degrees Celsius), the U.N. weather agency said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Argentine research base near the northern tip of the Antarctic peninsula has set a heat record at a balmy 63.5 Fahrenheit (17.5 degrees Celsius), the U.N. weather agency said on Wednesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One-off test cuts bowel cancer risk for at least 17 years. The study followed more than 170,000 people for 17 years on average and more than 40,000 had the bowel scope test. It is the longest study ever done on the effectiveness of the test. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House supports renewal of spy law without reforms: official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shuster: $1 Trillion Infrastructure plan not all gov't money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm wouldnt  the act of sex in itself be led  by positive emotion? I mean unless people are having sex with a partner surely they must be positive towards them on whatever level ( physical or mental ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What country are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure about that. Conspiracy theories spring up especially from the internet. Western countries have internet access as much as the US. It still isnt addressing why more sighting in UFOs especially in the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0146167216684124 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has revealed that it's general exchanges of words and signs of affection following sex that directly cause increased long-term happiness and more life satisfaction in couples who have sex at least once a week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this doesn't address the statistics about UFOs. Why are they seeing more in the US  compared to other Western countries who have access to the X files and other programmes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study came out today 

http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0146167216684124 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting look at the statistics of UFO reporting across the globe and also focusing on why in the US there are far more sightings. Read with an open mind!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ufo sightings have risen across the globe over the years. However in the US its 300 times higher than the global average. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I am marching for the NHS on Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Childhood cancer survivors are living longer. Now research shows they are also less likely to develop second cancers while still young. The decline followed a sharp drop in the use of radiation therapy for treatment of childhood cancers.

Between the 1970s and the 1990s, the percentage of pediatric cancer patients treated with radiation fell from 77 to 33 percent. The average radiation dose also dropped. Their chance of having second cancers within 15 years of the first fell as well.

The study included 23,603 five-year survivors from the Childhood Cancer Survivor Study. The survivors were treated at 27 medical centers in the U.S. and Canada. The federally funded study is based at St. Jude. Gregory Armstrong, MD, of the St. Jude Department of Epidemiology and Cancer Control, heads the study.

"The most ominous late effect of pediatric cancer treatment is a second malignancy," he said. "This study shows efforts to reduce the late effects of treatment are paying off.

"The risk of second cancers for survivors increases with age, so it is good to see the reduction emerging early in survivorship while survivors are still young."

https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-02/sjcr-art022317.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Childhood cancer survivors are living longer. Now research shows they are also less likely to develop second cancers while still young. The decline followed a sharp drop in the use of radiation therapy for treatment of childhood cancers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to Sign Executive Order to Begin Dismantling Clean Water Rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online Retailers Have Dumped 3600 Trump-Related Products since the Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost 20% of Palestinian youth have faced arrest after online postings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston Dynamics unveils 'nightmare-inducing' hybrid robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN health agency reports depression now leading cause of disability worldwide. Prevalence rates seem to peak in adults at around 60 years of age, but are also seen in teenagers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A look at how Shell knew without doubt how climate change would affect the planet in future generations. Something which the world can relate to now. Despite this they carried on with their philosophy of burning fossil fuels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shell knew: oil giant's 1991 film warned of climate change danger. If the weather machine were to be wound up to such new levels of energy, no country would remain unaffected, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A newly discovered trove of 16 engraved and otherwise modified limestone blocks, created 38,000 years ago, confirms the ancient origins of the pointillist techniques later adopted by 19th and 20th century artists such as Georges Seurat, Vincent Van Gogh, Camille Pissarro, and Roy Lichtenstein. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. By the way, you put up some interesting links. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a link. Please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a link? pictures? Im interested. Please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. Very relaxing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a AK47 but before give them two loud vocal warnings, and if they dont compromise. Shoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study https://academic.oup.com/bioscience/article/67/2/147/2900179/Doses-of-Neighborhood-Nature-The-Benefits-for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People living in neighbourhoods with more birds, shrubs and trees are less likely to suffer from depression, anxiety and stress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how you get windowed. From the side or from above makes a hell of a difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stand  still beside the mannequins in your depart store window, then something will happen to you. This something is windowed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not extreme at all. Your stating your own facts on life. I hope things are improving. Im glad you have people and dogs who have got your back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear about that. Take care of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Window people?  You mean mannequins?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  2nd Paragraph down

The chemicals in question are per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFASs), which are used to make consumer products nonstick, waterproof and stain-resistant. Think carpets, upholstery and weather-resistant clothing. Previous research has found associations between exposures to PFASs and kidney and testicular cancer, low birth weight, thyroid disease, decreased sperm quality, pregnancy-induced hypertension and immunotoxicity in children. The chemicals have become somewhat ubiquitous too, detected worldwide in water, soil, sediment, wildlife and human blood samples. The study that Peaslee co-authored tested hundreds of fast food packaging samples for fluorine, a marker of PFASs, finding the element in about half of paper wrappers and one-fifth of paperboard samples.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married People Are Healthier Than Those Who Are Single: The findings support the belief that single people, including those who are divorced or windowed, face more psychological stress than married individuals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which focuses on unusual  February weather patters which is causing alarm amongst the science community. It shows how above normal temperatures for this month has had an impact in various areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single-day record highs as well as multiple-day heat waves broke more than 248 month-to-date records for February in spots across the nation, according to the National Center for Environmental Information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single-day record highs as well as multiple-day heat waves broke more than 248 month-to-date records for February in spots across the nation, according to the National Center for Environmental Information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Fast food packaging contains chemicals harmful to human health, environment. Previous research has found associations between exposures to PFASs and kidney and testicular cancer, low birth weight, thyroid disease, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phone surveillance in 2017: Are you being watched? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Really, how do you know this? And no im not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those who add managers as friends on Facebook i would of thought are in a minority, most people i would of thought are not that stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draft Bernie Sanders movement invites Keith Ellison to join new party push </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netherlands Looks To Join The Super-Snooper Club With New Mass Surveillance Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the question is  why would you be looking on your employees social media page in the first place ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Government Puts Broadband ISP Internet Snooping Measure on hold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
