<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No real world equivalent?  He is literally Hitler.  Not "literally hitler" but ACTUALLY literally Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each night,

 my father fills me with dread,

When he sits at the foot of my bed

I'd not mind that he speaks

In jibbers and squeaks,

But for 17 years he's been dead
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with education degrees is that you can really only do one thing with them--be a teacher.  My wife is a teacher, teaches English, and unless she goes back to school for another degree (which she is very much considering right now) she's qualified to be a classroom teacher or an expensive tutor.  And keep in mind she scored very high on her Praxis (teacher bar) so much so that she could teach in any state.  But the entire Teacher system is broken but I won't get into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying, and 300 lb is a bit much for even the largest and broadest naturally occurring human, but remember it was only 50 years ago that we started to implement our understanding of  nutrition into our daily lives, increased no our average height by nearly a foot in some parts of the world.  NFL players are definitely on steroids, but you still need a perfect musculoskeletal system to get to their size WITH steroids.  Steroids can't change your bone density (yet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in shape and weigh 300 lb. then yes it is.  You need to be build like a gorilla to be a linemen and most of that comes from musculoskeletal shape, so genetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Galick Gun is a pretty good comparison to the death start beam.  The Galick Gun pools a lot of energy into the initial blast and pours less behind it.  The Kamehameha is a steady stream, the front has as much energy as the middle and as the start.  If Goku's Kamehameha stops the laser, it's only a matter of time before the constant energy from it reverses the beam and destroys the death star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a difference between training and training with a deity.  It's a running theme in the show that divine entities somehow speed up the training of whom ever they train in not-physical, non-Ki ways.  We see this from Mr. Popo, Kami, King Kai, Guru(a.k.a super ultra mega Kami guru), Supreme Kai, and Whis.    There's also the fact that Vegeta is royalty.  In most fantasy, Asian fantasy and mythology especially, royalty has a divine link of some sort.  

Point is, they never explained exactly how Vegeta did it without the ritual, but it's not as unbelievable as you'd think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yu Gi Oh is heavily based off an ancient game played by sorcerers and other magic users who were able to bend reality and able to pit real monsters against each other.  On top of summoning real monsters, the Wizards would use their own magic to further influence the battle (magic cards), use curses to set traps for what their opponent and their monsters would do(trap cards) and employ further magical tricks that were evolving often to stay on top of the game.  The loser, having expanded all their power and life energy, would be dragged to void realm by the very monsters and powers they employed in their Faustian dealings.  

Of course we all know this is simple mythology and we have no idea how the rule of Pharaoh Yami ended or where he is buried.  The modern day card game is just a silly game like Monopoly is to real-estate and checkers is to battlefield tactics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Vader genocides a lot of people.)[http://i.imgur.com/e1LArSXl.jpg]  A little context, this is Vader surrounded by an entire rebel battalion, tanks and all.  Vader is feared because Vader is a force of nature.  Fighting him is like trying to fight a hurricane or a black hole.  All you can do is escape him and hope what you do is beneath his notice.  Vader is feared because he is the Empire's "You Lose" button.  If Vader is there, you are not going to win. (Prophesied children not-withstanding) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of the silver bullet as a hot coal.  If a hot coal was chucked at you and bounced off your face(assuming it didn't stick to your skin), you would be surprised, it would give you, maybe, a first degree burn, and that's it.  Now imagine someone, somehow, accelerated that hot coal to ~350 fps and it hit you square in the chest and lodged itself into your heart.  That's the basic premise for silver and werewolves.  If you chuck a silver bullet at a werewolf, you now just have a startled and upset werewolf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  I should have included a breakdown like that when correcting /u/privatechicken when he said Sauron wasn't below his pre-ring power when he lost the ring.  It's also that the One Ring gave him ~even more~ power, borderline mind control, over anyone wearing one of the lesser rings, which he cleverly have to royal humans and dwarves, ( elves made their own using his techniques, it's complicated) giving him control over kingdoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfectly good explanation, better than the two I suggested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauron was weakened by the creation of the One Ring.  Maiar, ainur, and elves all put a piece of themselves into the things they create, weakening themselves in the process.  This is the central theme of the entire Silmarillion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes he could have.  Maiar (and Ainur and elves) must put a piece of themselves into anything they create, from rings, to children, to boats.  Theoretically, Sauron could spread the power distribution out over several rings of power that, when all worn at once, do the same thing as the ring does.  But he didn't do that.  And while we don't k ow exactly why he didn't do that, we could guess that it would require more of himself if spaced over 8 rings rather than one, leaving him weaker than if he simply made one, or perhaps he didn't want to risk losing one of the 8 rings of power set he made (as he did with the dwarf rings and some of the men rings.).  Sauron was a Maiar of Aule, The Crafter.  What ever reason Sauron had for pooling his power into one ring rather than many are most likely very practical and logical, not born from hubris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right in that drug related crimes are very close, number-wise, between race.  And you're right that blacks are arrested more than whites for these crimes.  But the reason isn't broad racism, it's geography.  1/4 of the people up and down my grandparents holler are, in one way or another, breaking a drug related law.  That's hundreds of people in an area that a cop car will drive through once a week or two.  Everyone is white.  In inner cities, where demographics shift toward black people, police have the funding for daily patrols through problem areas, undercover drug operations, and proper investigating.  A dead body could sit beside the road for over a week before the police heard about it near my grandparents, let alone the pot plants behind their house (helps with granny's arthritis.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, mostly.  In D D most places have laws against the things the orcs/goblins/kobolds do and, as a result, these groups are considered outlaws, meaning the laws of society don't apply to them.  So you can enslave goblin women for your perverted needs, butcher entire Orc families, and even make kobold tail hubcaps for your wagon.  This doesn't make you any less of a dick, though.  In fact, this is where then infamous alignment system shows it's worth.  You can rape and pillage lawfully, but that still makes you, at least, not good.  So if a neutral good sorcerer decided he wants kobold slaves, I wouldn't make him chaotic good, I'd make him true neutral as he isn't break any laws, just morals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but designed specifically for a man's butt to hit their prostate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 23:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming it was just 8mm reels, that's only about 10 minutes of film time (2-3 minutes per reel), pretty low quality film at that.  That's a pretty small fraction divan iPhone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 15:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my great grandfather smoked 4 packs a day and lived to 102. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this real?  Goku pulls punches so the shockwave doesn't destroy entire star system.  His fight with Beerus almost destroyed the universe.  Goku is the pinnacle of physical strength in fiction, only reality warpers or OnePunchMen can hope to beat him and they still have to contend with a Goku can casually hops dimensions and moves faster than light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're clearly made this vs with a bias for one over the other.  In the the recent DBZ super episode, Goku literally beat a dimension-hopping, time-stopping assassin.  Goku would move faster than DIO could think to stop time.  If drawn into another universe, Goku can just IT out.  It's well established that only supreme, universe-level hax can beat Goku and DIO just isn't packing that kind of power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relavent

http://i.imgur.com/UEMoyI2h.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the exception of Bardock:Father of Goku.  Toriyama said those were cannon until he released a comic saying they weren't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's easy!  The astronaut is most definitely Major Tom.  His skull was bejeweled like saints were when entombed, drawing a parallel between Major Tom and Christian Saints.  Bowie was pretty much saying "I'm going to die and I'll be revered as a saint after" and he was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did do that.  Native American reservations are exempt from state and federal law and even have their own constitution  (though these laws overlap anyway) and the government also offers a generous amount of state and federal assistance to Native Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part time and close to minimum wage pays a little over 600, but you have to keep in mind the cost of gas, babysitter, etc. and, at first, I did make slightly less raises come quick in my current field and were in a much better financial situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my long-winded explanation for Myers-Briggs tests: It's not scientific fact, more akin to lines drawn in the sand that then got washed over in the high-tide.  It's fun but so is masturbating and I wouldn't put much professional or personal stock in either of those things.  It can tell you more about yourself if you're extremely unaware about yourself but the problem is you're answering your own questions so yeah you're more likely to get a bias.  I've taken it several times over the years and always got ENTJ.  I'm extroverted, that's obvious; I'm fairly intuitive in my work and home, constantly coming up with small inefficiencies to correct entirely on my own;  I'm good at coming up with my own plans and schedules that are very good coupled with my N; and I'm a judgments bitch.  Girl you don't even know, mmhmm.

Point is, it's bullshit because I can give examples of how I am an ISFP as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best fight scene, for me, will always be Goku vs Master Roshi.  The fight scene is beautiful itself but it has so much: Roshi blowing up the moon, Goku first us my the Kamehameha, and Roshi beating Goku, the clearly stronger fighter, by using his brains over brawn, which Goku still falls for to this day.

https://youtu.be/QMbKjI76pTk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on welfare for six months.  When my newborn son was 3 months old I was lucky enough to get laid off, leaving us with only my wife's income (brand new school teachers don't make much above minimum wage!). So we applied and were accepted, we got hundreds of dollars worth of food stamps and over a hundred dollars in baby supplies (formula and diapers all paid for) and any job I took would have ended up costing us money because our benefits came out to almost 600 a month.  But I didn't want to live like that, got a new job (new career, actually) and haven't been on welfare in over 2 years.  But it was hard and I can see where some people would just kick back, suckle the government tit and not get a job because: I really enjoyed the time I got to spend with my son when he was developing a personality and becoming a person.  But I couldn't live with myself taking and not giving.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 09:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that jaw

Your mother was too selfish and lazy to breastfeed you.  FUCKING WOMEN FROM BIRTH TO DEATH REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE

http://health.usnews.com/health-news/blogs/eat-run/2014/08/29/breastfeeding-builds-a-better-jaw-and-other-benefits-for-babies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 09:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just now got why it's called incel!  It's short for involuntary celibacy!  I just though it was a random string of letters.  Boy do I feel dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won with Harry Potter and the Chamber of German Dungeon Porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 23:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/peoplefuckingdying is a satire sub and just silly, totally sfw and pretty funny.

/r/watchpeopledie (NSFW/NSFL) is the sub you're thinking of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 22:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was out deer hunting with my step dad and a few of his friends.  My stepdad and I were walking to his deer stand when he stops and gives me the signal to stop (usually when there are deer nearby).  Suddenly, he lunges at me screaming "get down" as the trees all around us started getting sprayed with buckshot moments after he hit the ground.  Turns out one of his friends emptied his gun at a deer and didn't know we were headed to the stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that.  Once a month I buy a small cake or a tub of ice cream and just eat until all sweets are ruined for ~30 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need, like, a pound of marshmallows to make enough fondant for a single cake, and marshmallows keep well if sealed.  My friend who runs a bakery could go through this bag in a couple weekends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, for a lot overweight people it's not that they consistently eat a lot of calories a day, but their average comes out to 3-4K a day.  One day they might eat 2300 calories and then have half of a pizza two nights a week, with ice cream one night (kid's party) and beer the other (adults party) and they take in over 3000 calories in an hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not hard to do without realizing when you have HAES blinders on.  Say you drink a soda with all three meals a day instead of water, that's an extra 375from liquids.  Add two more as snacks and that 625 from liquids.  Now you up your desserts to twice a day, daily, which adds 250 calories a day.  Now you cut out exorcise, 175 calories a day.  Let's add a bran muffin to our breakfast, 350.  We're up to 1300 calories and haven't even touched the HAES habit of grazing yet.  ~11 lays potatoe chips give you 120 calories, and I doubt most people would eat just eleven when they have delicious soda to wash it down.  Let's say she eats 33, that's 360 more calories.  At dinner, she gets rid of asparagus and makes mashed potatoes because their a vegetable too, right?  Serving size is a cup, she eats two, that's an extra 420 calories (210 per serving).  I forgot second snack between lunch and dinner.  We're up to 2080 extra calories, but we prefer something sweeter as the day goes on.  She eats a pop tart.  There is the 400 calories were looking for.  10 more calories from the grapes she ate to be healthy.  2500 calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 13:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets dispell once and for all the fiction that QVC doesn't know what they're doing, they know exactly what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unsubscribe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I feel you.  I load flatbed trailers all day, outside, on a forklift.  A drafty closed can doesn't do much below zero, on top of jumping in and out ever minute or so.  I wear thermals, thick pants, wool socks, a sweater, and a coat for anything below 20.  Popping into the cold is easy in jeans and a sweater, existing in the cold takes careful planning and proper clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go buddy.  Straight from the horse's ass

http://www.cnn.com/2016/09/07/politics/nuclear-facilities-bad-conditions-photos/index.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently rewatched The Hunchback of Notre Dame and I have to say, hands down, Frollo is the most terrifying Disney villain in all of Disney.  An evil lion, a conniving counselor/sorcerer, a Hates; these are all evil in fantastical ways.  But Frollo reminds me of people I've met and people I've read about, many of them in positions of power not dissimilar to Frollo's.  The reality of Frollo makes him so much more terrifying than any other Disney villain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very hard to learn just my pouring over the rule books.  The best way to learn is to find a group that is willing to teach you while you play.  Second best is to watch videos of people playing, preferably new players playing.  While doing either of those two, keep your rule books close and use them as a reference rather than a whole book to be devoured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 15:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't true at all.  A degree in Gender studies lets you teach undergrad gender studies!  Also a lot of retail/grocery store management just requires 'a' degree, doesn't matter in what.  This is one of the reasons retail sucks so much, all the management has useless humanities degrees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would keep all of them at the price they currently are.  The point of these gold sinks, especially the talent respeccing cost, is to, essentially, tax the hardcore players who are wiping in raids and respeccing throughout the week.  By reducing the large sums of gold these players would normally have, and by making them farm to get gold, you are keeping gold reserves down and keeping mats in the AH priced lower as supply keeps up or out-paces demand.  This lets the casual player, who doesn't have alts with maxed professions, able to afford things from the AH and continue their casual existence.

Retail has players with max gold because they removed all the gold-sinks hardcore players have to endure to be hardcore players, muscling out casual players and leading to rapid inflation in the AH.  Fresh players, starting wow for the first time, will be greeted with 10g+ level 7 greens in the AH, and the price only goes up from there (and Light help you if it transmogs into something cool). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ffs, TBC didn't balance the classes.  TBC still had worthless talent trees, unbalanced DPS, and Healer Master Race in pvp.  remember how paladins skill counldnt do shit but heal in a raid? WotLK balanced them (mostly) and they did that through class-homogenization.  My druids use HoTs, my bears have huge hp pools, and my rogues top the DPS charts.  Thats the way it should be because, otherwise, you end up with little-to-no class distinction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [citation needed] on pretty much your entire post.  It happened on PVP servers much more frequently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beerus still wins.  I don't know how Vegito stacks up to Beerus power level wise, but as we saw with Tien in the Cell Saga, technique and ability can wreck someone regardless of power level.  As long as Beerus has godly abilities like Destroy and who knows what else, Vegito doesn't stand a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hobbits have an affinity for puzzles, riddles, and words of all kind.  This is like pitting a champion try climber against a lazy Chimp--yeah the climber is impressive but he's just out of his element against the chimp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should give it a reread, it's a very good book, if a bit dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We see Shrek, Donkey, and a few other fairy tale creatures go back to Farquad's castle one Halloween where it sits abandoned and left to decay.  The area around the castle seems to be thriving so I take it that his holdings have become self governing or that Shrek has become some form of very hands-off king (as he did marry a princess.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 04:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People seem to keep forgetting this.  Once Trump is in office and the 9th on the SCOTUS is chosen, Republicans will hold ALL three branches of the federal government.  Democrats still have a loud voice but they're now sitting at the same table as the Green Party and Libertarians--they hold no cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with this idea is that the amount of material is very small and many of the things would degrade or outright make parts of it useless.  The salt will dry up the holy water, the salt water will rust the iron and tarnish the silver, the wood will turn to ashes when the metals around it super-heat when fired.  If you already have a bullet press, your best bet is to get different colored shells filled with different repellents (because, again, such a small amount isn't going to do much against most). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has said he wants to look into Crimea instead of imposing broad sanctions because it looks like a majority of crimeans want to stay a part of Russia.  He also said Russia is done advancing into Ukraine when he is president.  That doesn't sound pro Russian at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sincerely think they would.  McCain is not friendly to Russia but he pales in comparison to the War Hawk that is Hillary.  McCain is probably the most anti-war senator you'll find, Hillary involved us in more than one international conflict we had no business being involved in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not being anti-Russian doesn't make you pro-Russian.  Just because Trump doesn't want to involve himself or the U.S. in the Ukraine/Crimea international conflict doesn't mean he supports what Russia is doing.  The US isn't the world police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waterproof boots.  Waterproof also keeps the cold out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  And in tired of this "Russia supported Trump".  No they didn't.  Russia supported Not!Hillary.  It could have been McCain, Sanders, or even Strein and Russia would have helped them indirectly by hurting Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with a complicated relationship with their older brother, this episode hit me so much more than Jurassic Bark.  Jurassic Bark is so accessible--everyone has lost a pet.  But I think the The Martian is so much more powerful to people like myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like that could be Kaiser's dead sister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same reason why the military doesn't step in during end-bringer attacks--end-bringers don't hold back against normal humans.

Imagine you're Leviathan.  Now imagine you're just tearing through New Orleans without a care in the world.  Oh but what is this?  A dying parahuman who is being assisted by someone.  Should you turn them into butter?  Well my programming wants be to encourage shard conflict as well as cause apocalyptic destruction.  It's a parahuman that makes insignificants think they've met before in a positive way.  Well let's crush his voice making thing, see how that works.

Oh but what is this?  Two insignificants, one dying and the other trying to help them both escape?  Now they are insignificant paste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're from down south lol.  But you're right about the overkill.  I'd probably remove a layer or two for anything around 0 and only bring this out if the windchill drops below -20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived up north on Lake Superior and down south in West Virginia.  Honestly, the clothing I got down south was, usually, much thinner than what you'd find up north all year round.  The outfit I described should get you through -40ish temperatures and would be much too hot for 20 degrees.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just dress in layers and don't have exposed skin.  Typical cold weather from bottom to top:

Feet: thick socks and thick boots.  Preferably waterproof.

Legs: underwear, tight long underwear, jeans, overalls.  Your socks will go over your long underwear 

Upper body:  long sleeve shirt (tucked into pants), sweater (under the overalls), wind breaking and insulating coat.

Gloves: tight pair of gloves over your long sleeve shirt, thicker wind breaking and insulated gloves to be taken off for dexterous things like using the phone, etc.

Head: ski mask( tucked into sweater, over shirt), thick beanie, hood from your coat.   Goggles if it's windy.

Make sure your layers going up are loose enough to not cut off circulation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purse your lips when breathing in through your mouth, exhale through your nose.  When your mouth gets cold, switch to breathing in through your nose and out your mouth.  Switch back and forth as one gets too cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, start at episode 100 and go from there.  But your best bet is to find something that interests you the 100+ episodes and watch it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he mentioned that in every debate?  And, like Bush Jr, she should be charged with war crimes for what she did in Libya and who knows what else we don't know about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon music is pretty good.  It doesn't have the library the Spotify does, but it takes second place easily.  Just like Amazon video to Netflix, actually.  I guess Amazon is the king of second place media? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's a lot better than what I look like naked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for sure this doesn't apply to all heroes, but it applies to most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because comic book Herod are the epitome of healthy, on Average.  All the men are very muscled with low body fat and flexible musculature, they all are able to grow full beards, have loud booming voices, and are virile( dat bulge).  All the women are muscled with low body fat and musculature, they have wide hips and ample fat deposited on their breasts and buttocks, and they have healthy hair and skin.  

The type of person who usually decides to become a hero is the type of person with good genetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Fusions follow a pattern of pangenesis inheritance in that the resulting fusion takes the whole of each person and combines their traits.  While we don't know exactly how sayin genes interact with human genes, it is safe to assume they work the same as terrestrial life in that it follows mandellian inheritance.  So just as you are not a 50/50 mix of your parents, the resulting fusion would not look like Trunks or Bra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NPC teleporters since there's only a few dozen or so places that require flying in TBC.  WotLK would be impossible, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ain't ready for shit with all that breathable cotton.  You know what the fuck a windchill is?  You're about to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah you have to marry the hot blonde from the Capital.  She has the most HP out of all housecarls  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean best starting zone?  Vanilla Mulgore is a treat so long as it is only done every now and then.  I imagine most, like myself, will blitz a single character to 60 before starting with alts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dwarven zones have a fairly decent spawn rate and mob count for most quests.  Unfortunately this is so because two races start in this zone.  however, dwarf and gnome are also the two least popular vanilla races.  GO DORF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good comparison, but Hulk's strength numbers are off.  Hulk's strength is best described in a formula.  Where 1 is the strength of a normal person.  Strength = 1500 + (R x 50) be here is rage.  As long as he gets angrier, he gets stronger.  His strength is boundless and doesn't seem to have any diminishing returns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If his relationship is anything like mine then he's probably tried all that.  Some people just don't want a sexual relationship, sadly.  Kinda sucks when someone who has no interest in baseball marries someone in the MLB but... Yea I got nothing, it just sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two types of cold of people: poor people and stupid people who don't know how to dress for cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 12:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that like its a bad thing!  Slutmogs tend to be rare and expensive, rivaling the "coolest" looking sets.  A rare slutmog is just as impressive as any Tier-set.  And dat ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope this treatment of her is deliberate to make her fall so much further.  Crossing my fingers for that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm banned from several subreddit I've never participated in just for posting here.  How is that at all fair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the hottest it gets in summer is a breezy mid-upper eighties.  Nothing will prepare you for a UP winter, though.  -40 wind chills will give you frostbite in minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elves ages, but they age differently than humans, dwarves, and hobbits.  Elves, like Maiar and Ainur, put a piece of themselves into everything they create.  Children, boats, priceless jewels, all of these take a part of the elf who created them.  Regardless of how much of himself an elf has spent, he does not physically look older.  However, if an elf puts too much of themselves into their creations, their body will go to sleep and die, letting their spirit pass into the halls of waiting.  We see this happen with Faenor's mother after giving birth to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty chill tbh.  The closest comparison is rural New England in that everyone is laid back and is a weird brand of snow-redneck. Also everyone has boats around the coast.  And everyone hunts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the books, they weren't ghosts but tribal mountain men.  But back to the movies; short answer no.  Aragorn can block their attacks because his sword is magic.  His sword is magic after Elrond reforged it as most elven creations have a bit of magic imbued in them through the crafting process.  So Aragorn would roll over the human settlements but hit mirkwood and suddenly his ghosts are getting mowed down because they are used to just charging and that goes terrible against a wall of arrows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will get buried but whatever.

My maternal grandfather and grandmother fled nazi Germany before WW2.  My grandmother was Roma gypsy.  My grandfather was from the Southern Germany( Bavarian).  He was part of an old rich family in Germany.  His whole family were staunch nazis and many were members of the SS.  I think of this every time I look in the mirror and see my blond hair and blue eyes.  They exiled my grandfather and grandmother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 05:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ties in with enhancing the user's natural ability as Sauron was originally a Maiar of Aule the Crafter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With sound

https://youtu.be/r4mA6WsFJQE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trevally herding a school of fish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this may have been the original reason, Tolkien later expanded the reason for the invisibility as the shadow lands explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This election was memes. And Killary was playing tic-tac-toe while God Emperor Trump was playing 34 dimensional hyper-chess.  Sorry you lost the meme-war you cuck.  Enjoy being deported because you're illegal.  Also your illegal wife will cheat on you with black men and give birth to a son isn't yours.  And she will give birth on the other side of the wall which is totally going to happen, so no anchor baby for you.  Also something about the Jews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there, I wrote papers on it in college, I've even shitposted there. It's 90% stupid shit, 9% abhorrent shit, and 1% truth.  /pol/ is always right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Obama got elected, the shift was in full swing.  By the mid-term elections, /pol/ had taken on these values.  Also they are okay with traditional (white) religion in a Lutherian way, down to the antisemitism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ring gives power. It enhances power and gives the user the power to dominate wills.  On Gandalf this would be most disastrous as he already has the power of voice and spirit from his patron Ainur Manwe.  The ring also, as you sad, commands the ringwraiths (Tolkien wrote in a letter that the reason Sauron didn't send the nazgul to Mt. Doom is because, being so close to the source, Frodo would be able to command them to stop.). It doesn't make you invisible so much as fade you into the shadowland, having you exist in two realms at once.  Frodo turned invisible because he was spiritually weak.  Aragorn or Gandalf would have remained visible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say more like comparing a 3rd round draft pick to Payton Manning, but there's a lot of analogies you could use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
