<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a university professor in a fairly multidisciplinary field. We (academics) are good at talking and like the sound of our own voices. It would probably be easier to list the topics I couldn't talk for an hour on:

1. Sport

2. Literature/poetry

(I didn't say it would be interesting or enjoyable...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another drone Kickstarter that won't get off the ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another report on the same:
http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-31/donald-trump-sacks-attorney-general-sally-yates-travel-ban/8226054
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany is sort of like this. On highways you can do 20km over the limit before penalties start. In urban areas they start straight away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to buy in bulk, the canningvale wholesale markets on saturday. There is a lot of low grade leftovers but you can also get great fruit at rock bottom prices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e.g.: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-18/drone-mustering-tested-by-queensland-farmers/8130612
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by tickling my son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine only leaks fluid from the controls for the aftermarket (Chinese) FEL. The engine breathes a bit though.
It is certainly a tough tractor. I have pushed mine pretty hard the last couple of years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone recommendations for mustering/stock work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone on here use a drone for mustering/stock work?  Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ford / New Holland 6610 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone on here have / had one? Mine is no show pony, but I can post some pics if anyone is interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mother was a hamster, and your father smelt of elderberries... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Student would do little or no work all semester and fail. Student would then spend hundreds of hours lodging lengthy appeal documents through the university system and/or the courts. They would repeat this every semester.  
The mind boggles why they didn't just do the required work in the first place. 
I have known 2 students like this. They should have studied law instead of engineering... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christians. Terrorising muslims since 1096. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to the above, the best way to save money would be to buy a reasonably priced older car (e.g. $2k) and maintain it yourself to make sure it lasts as long as possible, rather than just drive it into the ground without maintenance.
 
Do your research and buy a car that is known to be reliable (e.g. most honda / mazda / subaru).

Learn how to check a car - oil / coolant / brakes / etc... so you can look for signs of how well it has been maintained.

Manual transmissions (if you can drive one) generally last longer and use less fuel than automatics. 

Most of the cost of car maintenance is labor. However most car maintenance is very easy to learn and can be done with a few basic tools. There are lots of online forums and youtube videos that can show you how.

My cars range from 1966-2009. None of them have been anywhere near a mechanic in the time I have owned them. I have owned one for 24 years. I would spend less on maintenance in a year than most people who only maintain one car using a mechanic.   

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree Steak is serious business, but it has to be one of the easiest foods to cook... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep reading comments on reddit about cooking steak being difficult. e.g. today:

https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/5px3he/what_is_one_thing_your_so_hid_from_you_until/dcuptba/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only reason I ask is that cooking a steak isn't really considered difficult or a skill here (Australia). But then again, maybe we eat more steak. My uncle has a steak for breakfast every morning.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of reddit - why do you all seem to think that cooking a steak is difficult or requires skill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is going to be 104 here tomorrow (40oC). Does that count as the air hurting my face?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to this, any attached sheet flow (and sediment in it which could erode the rock), is moving slowest when it crests the waterfall then accelerates.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me but a close relative...
Her (hopefully soon to be ex) husband hid the fact that:

* He was addicted to meth
* He had a criminal record for violent offences
* His brother is currently in jail on CP related offences
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She loves baked beans... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The best way to warm up a car is to drive it (gently). You just want to idle it for 30-60s until the oil gets to the top of the engine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the flip side, I was doing a (university) German course years ago, and the lecturer got onto the topic of Kaninchen (Rabbits) and Hase (Hares). He told us that they were the domesticated and wild forms of the same animal, respectively. 
I took a friend's game cookery book to show him next lesson... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't check against class lists, but you can't take the exam paper out with you after the exam, so you would have to memorize it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
