<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7930</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Yeahhh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was about to announce another Worlds Fair. First time I was excited this entire speech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electric pen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think Trump has ever cried? Genuine question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really the time or place for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure-unadulterated division.
Goes great with Trump steaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He literally just promised heaven on earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just heard someone in the audience vomit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They have taken advantage of our country no longer" talk about tense-sion in the room  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm getting too old for this shit" -the Supreme Court Justices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clapping for himself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LAUGHTER IN THE FACE OF DEATH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible to watch the contrast between Pence and Ryan's facial reactions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uproar as Canadian constable cleared of on-duty rape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Democratic women are wearing white  a symbol of womens suffrage  to Trumps speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I meant. Except the two girls in particular that I dated in high school actually rode, one very competitively. Every free moment she had she was at the barn. Half of our "dates" or just hang outs in general took place at the barn. If a show she had didn't go well, our relationship don't go well for at least a week afterward. We did not last very long. I couldn't compete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful. Thank you for sharing that.
And I hope you're doing okay and maybe even well! Life is full of painful and beautiful moments like you just described, so thanks for the reminder that unexpected beauty can come from unexpected pain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What situation forced you to believe that people are in fact capable of change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she owns a horse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 130 Years, Harvard Law Review Elects a Black Woman President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they were focused so hard on politics that they didnt get the act together at the end, President Trump told Breitbart. It was a little sad. It took away from the glamour of the Oscars. It didnt feel like a very glamorous evening. Ive been to the Oscars. There was something very special missing, and then to end that way was sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that 16 year old Auli'i Cravalho was the last person out of hundreds to audition for the voice of Moana. Cravalho has stated that she was initially not going to audition for Moana because "there were already so many great submissions over YouTube". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I thought so too! A rare perspective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find your lack of faith disturbing..

You're totally right though. Damn internet spider caught me in it's digital web again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's it huh? We're some kind of Best Picture Nom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvey Weinstein On Oscar Races   The Truth Behind Shakespeare In Love Vs Saving Private Ryan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ruined the flow, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is happening to his hand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/Jqiw_CxvIys

Moniker- Milestone 2 (Skux Life)
It's an original composed for the movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J.J. Abrams thinks Mark Hamill will win an Oscar for "The Last Jedi" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I just saw this movie a couple of nights ago and really loved it, and wanted to share about it on this thread, where I've found out about a lot of great movies other people have similarly shared. 

So. That's what actually happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lots of talk about Taika Waititi lately- Hunt for the Wilderpeople is full of clever pop culture nods and manages to successfully combine humor with sincerity to create a genuine picture of loss and acceptance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dungeon Master.

It's a BDSM thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What task are you actually much better at performing while drunk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer once said that banning media outlets is something only dictatorships do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Fantastic director Matt Ross to adapt cyberpunk murder mystery novel 'Tomorrow and Tomorrow' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely don't work for Walmart but I also understand the ambiguity of the title. At least the ad was only a minute long? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. You are totally correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't think that the author is arguing that John needs to become a character with legendary literary depth, I think the point he's making is that characters are most interesting and memorable when they undergo an arc. It's just a basic fundamental of storytelling. For example, while it's obviously a different movie, the characters in Hell or High Water are not particularly "deep", but they do have satisfying arcs, and that makes them interesting and memorable. 

I think the author is saying that it would be nice to see John have some kind of arc so that we can remember him as an interesting, well done character in an interesting and incredibly well done action film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] If you want to be a genius.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump Just Boasted About Winning Polls at CPAC. He Lost 6 Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Problem with the Ending of John Wick: Chapter 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "final" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayyy lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People often use the phrase "don't take it for granted" in a general sense when talking about youth or college or love, but what specific thing would you remind someone to never take for granted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same goes for me honestly /: but I appreciate and respect the animation and felt it was still a project worth bringing some attention to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your craziest public restroom experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kellyanne Conway Says Modern Feminism Is Anti-Male and Pro-Abortion' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deported man commits suicide jumping off bridge near U.S.-Mexico border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Three Gods Riddle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That book is incredible. Completely superseded my expectations. I've actually read it several times because it's so rich and detailed and surprisingly emotionally resonant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. For me, the Hollywood pictures or awards advertisements just distract from what very well may be a wonderful book. A book should be free to stand on its own merits, not by association with a film, which is a completely different medium of storytelling. I very much often still want to read the book, and I'll hunt around the inter webs until I find an edition that isn't marred by advertisements  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing! What was your job on set? And we're the light bulbs changed to keep in line with the yellow glow or..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unwieldy? Seems like an unwieldy use of an adjective yourself. 

Things can be intriguing in an obtuse or even poorly constructed way. I felt that the way Villeneuve created intrigue in this film was brilliant. Thus, brilliantly intriguing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies adapted from books end up making me less likely to buy the book. Nothing ruins a cover like "NOW A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE" plastered across the front. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am excited for this, 110% against my better judgement  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 40 Hi-Res Kong: Skull Island Images Preview Massive, Colorful Monsters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess that was part of my problem, I'd seen Enemy first so I couldn't help making comparisons the entire time I was watching The Double. Interestingly enough, both are loose adaptations of books. I've read Dostoyevsky's The Double but haven't read the book Enemy is adapted from  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spider is also present in the opening scenes of the film, and spiderwebs (as well as other spider related images/concepts) are present throughout the cinematography of the entire film, making the ending all the more satisfying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually loved enemy and found myself a bit bored by The Double. You liked both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In light of the success of Arrival- Enemy is another brilliantly intriguing film by Denis Villeneuve that showcases his mastery of the craft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had you never seen a black man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds terrifying. Who did you believe was watching you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made you believe that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I've never counted to 1000 myself. For all I know, your child self might be right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
