<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna try this right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 03:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually use maschine actually but I have opened it up in ableton fl studio and maschine they all have the same problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 03:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that would be Asio. Unless you mean my daw in which there shouldn't be any eqing happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 03:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if I sound like an idiot but what eq settings would you be referring to? There isn't any on the hardware.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 02:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh that's interesting still Ive never heard of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interface only picking up high frequencies and very low volume. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 02:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a shitty problem today, my interface is not working properly. Tried multiple cords that I know work. It's a Steinberg ur22 only one year old. Nothing has happened to it as far as I know but for some reason it's not picking up all frequencies and I have to turn the input and output all the way up to hear anything. Anyone have any ideas? It's not the usb connection because when I play sound off my computer it goes through the usb and interface and out my monitors. Going to call Steinberg in the morning. Currently re installing drivers but I don't know it that will do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 02:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the usb because when I play music on my computer off say soundcloud it still goes through the usb and out my monitors fine so maybe it has something to do with the inputs on the actual interface. I'm going  to give Steinberg a call in the morning and see if they have any ideas. Maybe some dust and dirt got into the inputs?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 01:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you hear this? Never heard of that, i have windows 10 always never had any problems like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 01:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never had any problems with windows 10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interface only playing high frequencies, very low volume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 01:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a shitty problem today. Went to go make a beat and my interface is not working properly. Tried multiple cords that I know work. It's a Steinberg ur22 only one year old. Nothing has happened to it as far as I know but for some reason it's not picking up all frequencies and I have to turn the input and output all the way up to hear anything. Anyone have any ideas? Currently re installing drivers but I don't know it that will do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 23:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is really awesome to see actually!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 23:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow been using maschine for over a year now and never knew about that double button </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 22:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks brother appreciate it. /r/makinghiphop doesn't accept singles though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 20:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect bro!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buttered Popcorn [INSTRUMENTAL] someone tear this up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 20:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you've made it so far, think about last time you caved in. Think of how guilty and shitty you felt the next morning when you woke up. The feeling of knowing you were back to day 0 after all that hard work. And don't downplay that part at all. This took alot of hard work to make it this far. It definitely wasn't easy. Go for a run and eat a nice meal. Go buy a new video game. Do whatever you can to take your mind off it. You got this man you made it this far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this app is for cigarettes but I kinda switched it around to work for marijuana. It's called Smoke Free on the play store. Pretty much you put in your last time you smoked, how many cigarettes (I just thought of those like bowls) you smoke a day, and how much a pack cost (I just thought of a pack like a gram). Everyday I check it and seeing the numbers rise really helps keep me in line. I never really noticed how much I smoked untill now. Today is day 6 and Ive already skipped almost 50 bowls!! That's crazy to me! It also has many other cool features that help me out, I recommend it to anyone who's trying to kick the habit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This app has really kept me on track </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 18:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you disconnect it brings you to the main menu
Edit: you can reconnect after that but your scores lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 17:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dope video, anyone know what Danny brown track he produced?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 16:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way definitely ordering now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 16:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this happen before too, luckily it wasn't an elusive target though. Spent the longest time doing suit only, silent assassin and was on my way to escape and the game disconnected from the Internet... What is the point of a single player game if you need to be online the whole time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 07:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't think so, just wasn't sure about the refrigerant. Never hurts to be safe as I don't mess with co. It's a Danby DPA085B1GB, seems like a pretty standard unit nothing special.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 07:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks. I'm actually in school for Hvac right now but we don't get into refrigeration untill next semester so I had no idea about the properties of freon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 22:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L theanine, Valerian root, sleep Rx and lorazepam when it's really bad. Go for atleast a 3k run in the evening. I've quit multiple times and with this regiment I sleep so easy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit confused what your actual question is? Go to goodwill and buy an old cassette deck and vhs player and play around with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 22:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I do the same. I sample from vinyl/cassette recorded into vhs. Rewind and them resample through sp404 while playing around with the tape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a simple numark ttusb, no mechanical arm or anything. I'm gonna open it up today and see if I can lube it up maybe? Not to concerned as I have another direct drive table I use more often but it's just annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 17:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 16:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 07:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 06:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol did you actually just say ableton has no competitors... Smh

PRO tools is the industry standard for mixing and mastering. And why would you bounce to ableton to master that doesn't even make sense...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 03:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao this made me laugh out loud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 03:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn thanks for posting man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tone arm super stiff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 22:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually keep the door to my studio closed but accidentally left it open last week and the cats got in and ran all over my turntable. Not sure what happened but  ever since then the tone arm has been super stiff. Tried taking the weight completely off and it still won't move very easy. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 21:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol and that took less time then it took him to type this post

Edit: lol he actually made an account just to ask this smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 14:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/petioles is for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search bar and side bar, Google and YouTube. No one is going to go out of there way to teach you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly most people aren't gonna listen to more than 2 Mins of a beat and if you release longer beats you risk people just straight up jacking them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup mpk mini seemed like such a good purchase at the time...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 12:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate it bro! This one's actually sample-less!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 04:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/ustincox/sunday

https://soundcloud.com/ustincox/buttered-popcorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 04:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea why do you ask?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underachievers type beat I made completely in maschine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 03:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 01:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way!!! Good wood cartways is 15 Mins from my place! Used to go there all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a professional soccer player maybe...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 03:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't actually millions. He said he spends 2k everytime he goes to the club. Also he said he goes around 150 times a year. One dumbass writer thought that $2000 x 150 = $2,100,000 and then a bunch of other websites started reporting it too. When really $2000 x 150 = $300,000.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 22:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sp 404 og... Loving it, amazing fx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got really lucky on kijiji. I was on kijiji and eBay for like 2 months waiting for a good deal haha. It came without the power supply and faceplate but they arent needed as it runs on batteries and the faceplate is just for looks. Picked up a power supply for 20 bucks from Roland and they had the faceplate for 30 but I decided I didn't need it. 
One more thing I forgot to mention about the sx is you can use SD cards while the og is compact flash which can be tedious as it has a 1gb max(more than enough) and certain brands don't work with the sp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erick arc Elliot is a God when it comes to producing. He is the backbone of flatbush zombies they wouldn't be where they are today if it wasn't for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background sounds capes and other very subtle background noise, lots of them. Try layering and loopong a field recording in the background just to give it some more character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 16:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARCstrumentals!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your trying to decide between og and sx the main differences are the speed of the workflow, fx and price. The og has a greatly slower work flow (probably 5x as slow, and annoying having to resample) but it also has a couple fx that are just too nasty to pass up, it's pretty hard to emulate the ogs vinyl Sim. Also I found that the og is usually cheaper than the sx, I picked mine up for 150. 
It's really what you want to do with it, are you going to mainly use it as a way of producing? Or just looking to get a new piece of equipment to mess around with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rstudioz.habits here it is on the play store, might not have an ios version though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is one of my main ways to keep going. Just keep thinking how much it would suck to start over again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [we got stronger beer](https://youtu.be/2E064kb3UnU)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you pay for one you're not going to get it in a month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn what was it like getting caught torrenting lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a tough call, I picked up the og because I got it for a good price. Kinda annoying how you can't copy samples and have to resample it each time to get It onto another pad. The fx are definitely better but the work speed is quite slower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 1... Never had nausea like this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well back at day 1 again... Been an everyday smoker for around 5 years, the last couple weeks have been pretty bad. I was literally waking at 5 in the morning the smoke bowls just so I could sleep again. Usually I ease off of it but this time I quit cold turkey. Last bowl was about 12 hours ago and I'm a mess right now. The anxiety is bad and I can't eat anything. These were expected but what I wasn't expecting was the constant nausea and feeling like I'm going to vomit. I've never had this before, tried taking a Tums but it didn't do much. Hope everyone's having a good day stay strong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey nyck, how was that part in the church video filmed? The one where you are waving to your father. That gave me chills man. Hope your doing good. Know you don't remember me but we met in Toronto, all I can say is you love the Henney haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool that's good to know! I had tried growing when I was in highschool but had no idea what I was doing and gave my seedling enough nutrients for an apple tree and killed it within a day so I really made sure I was taking it easy on them this time. I'm growing in [vigoro all purpose potting mix](http://m.homedepot.com/p/Vigoro-1-25-cu-ft-Potting-Mix-74337920/203715547).  Also using a generic 3-1-2 blend. Kinda cheaper out on somethings to stay on budget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I'm growing in a space bucket type tote just using mostly hardware store supplys such as [vigoro all purpose potting mix](http://m.homedepot.com/p/Vigoro-1-25-cu-ft-Potting-Mix-74337920/203715547) and some generic 3-1-2 nutrients. Right now they are doing pretty great as far as I know under around 94 watts of cfl but I am hoping to add 150watts of led for flowering, but for my first grow I'm trying to keep it low budget and I've already exceeded that haha. 
Guess I got real lucky for my first grow as both these seeds werent feminized and I only planted the two! 
Edit: adding led at flowering not cfl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Definitely got pretty lucky then I only planted the 2 and they weren't feminized. The slight burntness is only on a couple new leaves, I upped the amount of nutrients last watering that's probably why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's easiest to use ductwork from home depot. Also don't use this method you can make it with carbon screen, activated carbon, duct tape and some ductwork </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 06:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father has been pardoned for his possession charges he received in his younger years. That is the main reason why I ask. He specifically broke the law but was still approved for a pardon. That was the main route of the question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 05:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrible rolling...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool thanks for the info!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 04:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When do you start training? Or do you just leave them? This is my first time I'm just experimenting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone ever use genkit to find sex of plants early? Sounds interesting but I'm skeptical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 05:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha there's a landscape company in my town with the same name  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn thanks bro, there were a few I missed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sp 404 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea definitely right about the possesion/trafficking part. I know my dad was charged with possession when he was in his teens and was able to get a pardon, but that is different I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I would hope so as well, atleast give a chance to all the non criminals who have been screwed by the system a chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that really sucks. I am hoping that Canada being as awesome as it is that they will be more lax about it then them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When cannabis is legalized in Canada, will people with prior possession charges be able to apply for a pardon of some sort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any charges against me but am just curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 16:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyday all day with my roommates  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 04:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottawa for school from t.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 04:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea the temp was a problem but I just fixed that yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using a generic 3-1-2 fertilizer from home depot and I upped my amount on the last watering and obviously over did it a bit. Do I flush right away with phed water? Or wait till the next watering. The curling on the leaves is from the heat but has been corrected  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My lights are off at the moment but I will once they come on in a few hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the new ruling on medical growing can new patients grow their own medicine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I just found some signs of note burns on one of my plants. Should I flush right away or wait till next watering to flush? Didn't want to make my own thread just for that question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 17:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same problem, spent all week finishing 12 escalations just for that gun and never got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 16:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never done maschine masters but maschinetutorials.com is really good if you're looking for good tutorials. You can subscribe by the month and Saint Joe still updates it. Getting through most of the content should only take a month or two though and then it's pretty useless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Canada they have this feature  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any uses for the Bohemian disguise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 21:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't found any uses for it yet or how to use the joint you can pick up. Lol mostly just for fun but maybe it is used in the elusive targets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it's part of the main sample! Just eq-ed it to bring it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 17:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time grower, 2 northern lights autoflowers under 100 watts of cfl. Actually 16 days from germination. Not sure if this is just more leaves coming in or early female hairs. I will post more pics right now all I have is my phones camera though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol if you are just experimenting go on youtube or soundcloud and search boom bap beats. No producer is gonna waste there time on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, isnt much of a question... people sample everything... vhs to n64 games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this with a vcr its really easy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Instrumental] Sunday - Jeech Beats (rappers needed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday - Jeech Beats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any turntable... If you want the "best" turntable it will probably cost you thousands of dollars though. Go buy the cheapest one you can find on kijiji  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 14:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a vst for it I forget the name I can check later  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 14:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it's so obvious too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I third this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that sounds awesome and like it would take a lot of work. If you are feeling generous enough you should share haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice thanks for the feedback, il probably cop it on the next sale/voucher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol what? Albert Hoffman accidentally sythesised it in 1938 in Switzerland... Nothing to do with the American government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said real Lsd, not research chemicals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nitrous oxide, morphine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 17:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real Lsd is not cheap enough to give away... This isn't the 70s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens every week on the Sunday sample Facebook page! Every Monday a sample is posted and everyone has untill Sunday to flip it. Theres a voting board on there website where everyone votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I saw the email and got so hyped but once I actually checked it out and heard the demos I wasn't that impressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New maschine expansion QUEENSBRIDGE Story by havoc of mobb deep. Inspired by kanye, biggie, 50 cent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 18:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 14:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Macs sells Phillies and backwoods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just called Roland and they will replace it for 35$ which isn't bad. Gonna leave this here in case anyone is searching for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Onlinevideoconverter.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maschine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 03:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome you just confirmed what I was wondering. I don't have my scripts anymore but I still have my bottles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow haha I just flipped that sample the other day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's usually for collecting whatever left over cause it's hard to scrap up a dab. Works great if you make your own oil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to buy sp 404 faceplate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 03:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know if anyone here can help me but would anyone know where to buy the faceplate for an sp 404? I'm buying a used one this weekend that comes without a faceplate and I kinda want to get one so I don't break it. It also is missing a power supplu but I heard you can buy them from any electronics store for cheap. I read in the manual it takes 9v 300mA, is there anything else I should look for in regards to the charger? Canada links would be appreciated but really anything will do. I couldn't find much on google. 
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 03:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
