<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9926</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your money isn't long enough to drive a e30, can I suggest a bus pass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $40,000 Lego block </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This car could be neon green, with flashing lights festooned all over it, and it would still be still be the cure for insomnia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This car was way ahead of its time. Turbo charged 4 cylinder muscle car decades before the Eco boost. 

A modern eco boost owner can trace the lineage of being called a fag by 8 cylinder GT owners directly back to this car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modestly sized penis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I switched back to iPhone I tried to find a lightning cable that was as well built, and couldn't find anything. These things are tough as hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can they please test PIP mode on the ipad? I have the pro, and it is annoying that they won't allow it to shrink down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the terms. If you don't go at your allowed time on the 21st they will restock, and I assume sell your phone. It seemed very unprofessional way to set it up. It will be a zoo down there the 21st.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there was a post not long ago on R/T-Mobile where some poor guy got his phone swiped. The ups guy left it in front of his apartment in a bad side of town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the clear case rigid, or more of a malleable material? I have gotten the spigen ones, and they always get slimy, and gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very boopable nose there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing in this world can get more cozy then a lab with a full belly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyday is the right day for a mud bath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great name ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our yellow lab is named henry also! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took the old man on a hike in mountains today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one sentence just really relaxed me for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am way too grimey to use that case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What mods?

This sub is abandoned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First party Samsung brand silicone case quality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run the apple case on my iPhone 7+ and it is just about perfect. Has anyone gotten the Samsung cases? Any comment on the feel, and durability of them?

http://www.samsung.com/us/mobile/mobile-accessories/phones/galaxy-s8-silicone-cover--silver-ef-pg950tsegww/#

Wish they had better colors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to best buy, and purchase a moto g5 then return it when s8 ships </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fyi these are the highest quality cable for any device I have ever bought. 

https://www.amazon.com/AUKEY-USB-C-Braided-3-Pack-Google/dp/B01C2NNG12

They are stiff as hell, but built like tanks. Looking forward to coming back to USB c to use them again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nvidia really deserves all the Kudos they get. Every product of theirs I have owned, while not perfect, got great enthusiastic support, and they stood behind. They also seem to be breaking huge new ground on a regular basis, in a pretty mature market. Sort of reminds me of a certain other company that used to do the same, but then has become complacent lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 10:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a deal breaker for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sums it up nicely. Some amazing work. 

Who is her team? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I gave this cunt a pageview on accident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like forty seventh hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which was my point they designed the wagon on the short wheelbase for no reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw Keeny Loggins live about 6 months ago. Fucker didnt sing danger zone despite me whipping up my whole section of the crowd chanting it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a member of the itty bitty tittie comittiee and a freckle lover she is right up my alley  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honored I guess.

BBQ chicken Pizza is probably the least snobby ingredients I use though, so I will be back lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S8+? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty bummed out but I will probably just go ahead and do it. Even though I will certainly be getting iPhone 8. 

I guess it will end up costing $130+ 5x$30 payments so $280 to run the phone through October. 

I doubt used s8+ will be worth more then $570 by October. However I wish I could take advantage of one of the EIP deals like Sams Club that brings the phone down to $700.  The Verizon guys are certainly getting a better deal the JOD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did JOD guys end up paying the $130? I'm wondering if it is even worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoked chicken BBQ, with ricotta, Maui onion, and hot sauce drizzle on whole wheat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst Korean product since the exploding Note 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This car looks cool as hell from about 40 feet away. When you get close and scrutinize the details of the design it becomes ugly AF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe someone without the most tacit understanding, of the worlds issue should have never been allowed to lead it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you black everything out to look cool, or in desperately trying to hide how shitty your car is, like a ostrich sticking it's head in the sand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still saving up those Reals for the letter F, and the modern saftey equipment I see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that this was the protg of the Pontiac Aztec. It sold about as well, and is held in about the same regard, so all those years of training paid off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be even more stealth if you pushed into the bottom of a lake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow simultaneously smaller, slower, uglier, less reliable, and more expensive then a Gti. 

In the end it is just a fat sausage eating German guy putting on a shit British accent, and forcing you to sell your body every time you walk up to the parts counter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just hold out for a few more years. Soon with virtual/augmented reality you will never face rejection again. Your robot Loli hologram girlfriend won't judge you for being a unkempt, dorito crumb covered, recluse who lives in your mom's basement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a second hand car, and a second hand kid. 

Really knocking life out of the park.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps the last puzzle piece, in unlocking the mystery of cold fusion is gathering up enough of these in one place that women's vaginas get cold enough to cool a nuclear reactor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't lose the race to the base Camry, you were just being stealth. Flying under the radar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even get mine to walk down the street half the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you buy out a JOD lease, can you still JOD to another phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having dish TV and sprint phone would just be masochistic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So probably not until iPhone 8? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will s8 be compatible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternately it looks like they mostly share a asshole. I would be salty if I had a Kale salad, and some oolong tea, and my Siamese twin washed down taco, bell with Indian food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interior of this POS makes driving a bumper car, feel like driving a Bentley.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the tied up door to door vacuum salesman in the trunk ride for free? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used grey 335i come with a welcome kit in the glove box. Included is a tight v neck t shirt, some sort of metrosexual hair wax, helpful tips, and tricks on how to grow out a patchy, but well coiffed beard. 

If you flip this pamphlet over to the other side you will find a few useful hotlines. One will give you FAQ, on how to come up with $3,000 every other year for a new HPFP. The other is a support line for when your metrosexuality eventually tips over the line, and you end up blowing a couple Latin guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler is spinning in his grave that they made his people's car FWD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clifford the big red slam pig.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would highly recommend you skip the V20. The protruding camera glass in the back is very susceptible to cracking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with bill credits, you will be stuck with s8 for 2 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 10:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't fault the OTT guys exclusively. The super minimalist remote works well for a curated experience like Netflix, where you have the illusion of choice, but in reality never dig too deep. 

With cable you have 100 channels, and want to move around myriad options, quickly. The remote just isn't up to task. OTT really won't make sense until it is all on demand, and only your favorite stuff is presented to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump would even stab himself in the back if he wasn't so fat, and out of shape, that he can't reach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad so far almost all the original content on prime sucks compared to Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is my problem with T-Mobile. I am actually ok with the coverage. For the most part I can deal with the dead spots in unpopulated areas. This certainly isn't ideal and will be a big issue when I travel to rural PA for a month later this year.  Day to day, I rarely leave the city. Credit where it is do, I drove to a bunch of places this weekend that used to suck, that they have recently filled in. 

However they really need to upgrade their backhaul. I never realized how charmed my life was when I was on unlimited, and everyone else was on tiered plans. Since the one plan launched my data is crawling everywhere I go. 

Hopefully VZ's more ideal spectrum, and head start will stop the same from happening to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made my day with this comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the kind of car a Persian Guido would drive around NNJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a tampon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article has a pretty celebratory tone considering he lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The area around boiling pots is def the best part of Hilo. Can go downtown for a few drinks, and walk home, plus it is nicely situated to get to everything. You will still get rain, but that area isn't as bad either. The closer to shore the less rain. 

It is also the most expensive area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is some bull shit. They could easily just build a parking lot. Why cut off access to one of the few hikes we have left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How will all the turmoil VZW affect its customers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a week away from moving over from T-Mobile. All the reports of bad stock prices, layoffs, store closings, bone headed acquisitions etc, have me a bit nervous. 

Will this all blow over, or will these factors start cutting into their capex, and CS budgets? With 5g on the horizon I don't want a provider who is behind the times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly the thought of some suit tossing and turning at night, because I get to stream as much as I want, is excellent. 

Fuck them. You plans of enslaving people to data caps are foiled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer really needs to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP states that he is only getting 600kbps from VZ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the guys phone number is enough for the police to find out who he is. The thing is that the burden of proof is on you, and you 
need to plead your case to the police. Did you have any email, or text correspondence with the guy? If he agreed to terms over text that may be enough.


I won't chastise you for this. People suck, in general. For future purchases, try to agree to meet, at a VZ store. Also ask to see ID, and draft up a bill of sale for anything over a few $100. It certainly is awkward asking people to make something casual seem much more official, but you will protect yourself in the long run.

Good luck, I hope the police are willing to help. If not you can always sell the phone for parts, and I believe that even if it is blacklisted on VZ, it may still work on other carriers so you may still be able to sell/give it away with a thorough explanation of the situation.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SS= Shit  Sandwich? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #teamgreenbubbles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know your truck is trash when Mexican day laborers laugh at you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know Verizon is pretty shady about how they pay off your phones. They give you TIV, then space the rest out over bill credits. 

I am in the process of switching, and I cannot use my phones (Iphone 7+, and one plus 3) I have found that I am better off selling them off private party, then utilizing VZ offers. 

All of VZ versions of promotions seem to be modern day contracts that lock you into 24 months of bill credits. If you are the type that keeps phones, then that is fine, but I change all the time so paying retail is better for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is nuts. I have walked into random banks with $100 bills, and rolls of quarters, and they helped me with no hesitation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have outgrown the radios but, love the software so much that I still use it as my main router.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly the same speed, but in the same ballpark. The DSL is uncapped, and more consistent, with a lower ping.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of you guys have no empathy for a shitty situation. Sorry that happened to you OP. 

Personally I would text the guy something along the lines of. 

"The phone you sold me has a outstanding balance on it. I'm sure that you intended to take the money I gave you, and pay it off in full Immediately. Because otherwise that would be fraud, and I will be contacting the police, and this will escalate from there"

It won't take a lot to find out all the guys information from just the phones serial number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S8 pixel is fugly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media0.giphy.com/media/qk0iGDYM5JOwg/giphy.gif

OP is a illiterate cunt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was more then the east coast my auntie just got home yesterday after trying to fly back to Hawaii from Seattle. Somehow she got bumped from 4 seperate Delta flights. 

She got $45 in food credits, and the cold shoulder. 

It also took her daughter 3 days to get from Boston.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy some moto g5 plus phones from BB, and return them in a few days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me I have 4 lines SC unlimited at $150 plus fees. VZW is unlimited for $180. Well worth the extra $7.50 per line for the increased coverage. 

Now that JOD has $130 deposit on flabgships that benefit is over. 

The only feature that T-Mobile has over other carriers is international data. I will sorely miss the free throttled data. I am luck enough to travel often, so this will add up over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S8 will have access to many new network technologies that a iPhone 6 will not. 

Just a fyi my GFs one plus 3 has not been the greatest on T-Mobile. I am a serial phone switcher, and I routinely get better service then her. Probably best reception I ever had was note 7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 38ms ping
4mbps down
3mbps up

Honolulu Hawaii
iPhone 7+
Outdoors right down the street from a tower. 

This is actually better then usual 

Supposedly we are a gigabit LTE market. They have some work to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do these hold up? I had the Spigen one and it got really slimy quickly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is great news, everything Le Eco touches turns to shit. I wouldn't call myself a Vizio fan boy, but I have been really happy with their products over the years. Recently picked up a 70 inch E series 4k TV, to replace my 55 inch Samsund 4k TV. Despite being the budget model, the PQ is better on the Vizio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would gladly switch to Windows, but  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tried all the cord cutting services sling tv, PS Vue, and now direct TV now. 

I just cancelled DTV now effective early next month. I find the interface of all of these services terrible to navigate with my ATV remote. Also one thing to consider is that unless you live in a major market you will not be able to stream network tv. 

My isp is offering a insane deal right now so I will be going back to traditional cable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would recommend Sam's club over BB. They give you a $150 gift card on the spot vs bill credits, and also waive the activation fee making it $185 off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps if you want to future proof your purchase, but if there is a large price difference then don't bother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a muscle car you like for its personality. Looks arent everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully costco starts selling 6 packs of high pressure fuel pumps for 335i owners someday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the leader of the free world, my base's so called religious views make me want to cut off funding for birth control to these regions for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pixel was a cool phone in a 2 year old body, and a outrageous pricetag. If it looked like a s7e, or was priced at $650 out of the gates, it could have been a contender.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't make Dr money, but there are certainly times when $800 doesn't scratch the surface of what I will lose if I am not on this flight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If apple can find a way to support gifs, google can find a way.

I personally would have no issue switching to whats app, but I understand why none of my friends would choose to come over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck getting several large groups of people to switch over. In my world it is SMS, or FB Messenger. No one has the apetite to try anything else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Sucks about the $130 deposit on s8+. I anticipate the same thing on note 8, and oled iphone 8+

I am moving away from tmobile, now that they  changed the policy on JOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest thing I will miss is gifs. Have never had much luck sending sms gifs on android. 90% of my communication is sending memes, and reaction gifs to my many sms group chats.

Hopefully someday android will be as good as imessage. 

i am looking forward to antagonizing people with my green bubbles again though ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no scenario where China will be OK with us placing Nukes in S Korea.

I don't know enough about the ramifications of the other options. My gut tells me that assassinating Un would be the worst idea. However this ends, it needs to be diplomatically. 

Also the longer he stays in his hermit kingdom, the longer Asia doesn't need to deal with the fallout of millions of brainwashed N Koreans fleeing the country. Not to mention the mad race to secure whatever nuclear materials they have produced thus far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no reason for it to be covered with a giant piece of glass


http://cdn01.androidauthority.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Huawei-P10-blue-840x560.jpg

iphone 7+ Huawei p10 etc every other dual camera phone implements it with a much smaller glass cover, for durability reasons.

As far as raising the price it was already $800 so they should have been able to find the resources for a better material </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling this week is going to get back to Russia. There isn't any SC bombshell to distract, and this bombing story doesn't have much legs IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only was on iphone because of how annoyed I was over the note situation. Coming back home. Wish Samsungs had this kind of resale, looks like I will have no issue getting $650-700 for my base iphone 7+. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks insanely fragile. I will be putting on a case day 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way in hell 5g will do 4.4GB per second. possibly 4.4gb, but never approaching even 1 GB. Single mode fiber is just now reaching 10gbps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am moving away from tmobile to VZ. I am in one of their markets that will have it. Too bad the towers are so oversold, that you will never see a fraction of those speeds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are women with a super high libido, who genuinely enjoy getting lots of D. Don't hate on them, because attitudes like that will cut off the taps for guys in the future.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh bed bug resistant sheets are a great investment. After a BB scare at work I got one that wraps my whole expensive matress, and has holes too small for the bugs to permeate. 

I don't see the issue here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love philliadelphians. We aren't down with the fuck shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This car is a bit of a optical illusion, it looks like a spacious wagon, but somehow manages to have less interior volume then even the abortion called the 3 GT.  

X drive ruins the handling too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know that Sigmund Freud ever wrote on the correlation between the automobile, and masculinity. I'm sure he would probably have a lot to say if ever asked to address the corvette stingray. His thesis was that almost everything a man does is in worship of the phallus. 

This is a long winded way of telling you that your car looks like a giant cock, and balls, on wheels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly having him flip flop to a democratic president, and catering to liberal causes would be excellent on many different levels. The highest one being seeing the still beating heart ripped from the chest of his more principaled supporters.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
