<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a little kid, I HATED taking baths. It got to the point where I smelled really bad, so my mom would always tell me that if I smelled bad, nobody would want to be my friend. It got me to bathe regularly, but now I'm constantly paranoid that I smell bad. 

Plus side is I have really good hygiene, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 07:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an H cup. It happens like 50,000 times a day and I notice every time, even if they think they're just glancing for a quick second. One millisecond in real time is like 15 minutes in boob time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 07:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peach by The Front Bottoms. Used to listen to that and sing along to each other whenever I was in the car with my ex girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 07:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 17 I snuck into a bar and got smashed. Woke up the next morning with a fork in my pocket.... It was different from the ones that the bar I went to had, so I have no idea where it came from. I still have it, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 07:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moose.. If you're driving and you hit one, you're done. They're like 7 feet tall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dated a boy that was 3 inches shorter than me for over a year and the only person that ever commented was him. He was super insecure on top of that though, so I don't think anyone else really cared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on Prozac, Zoloft, you name it. Most of them worked for about 2 months before things went downhill. I've been on Trintellix (called Brintellix outside of Canada) for almost a year now and it's turned my life around. It just takes trial and error to find the one that's right for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About two years ago I had been talking to this guy for a couple weeks when he told me that he didn't believe in mental illnesses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hdmi cables.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel as though your life will be exponentially better if you never find out what toe jam is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immediately asked the waitress for separate cheques and skipped out of there, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple years ago I went on a date with a guy that had a toe jam fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your loss. I hope you're doing alright now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in retail. When you ask us to check if we 'have it in the back' we really just walk back there and scroll through Reddit for 5 minutes before coming out to tell you we couldn't find it.

Edit: Since everyone is yelling at me, I'll elaborate. Speaking from my experience only, there isn't extra stock in the back. "The back" is the staff room. Most customers insist we check anyways, so that's where the reddit comes in. Relax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
