<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject82</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've read it seems like it was more of a morale boost and part of a code of honor, like the [Combat of Thirty](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Combat_of_the_Thirty), than anything else. The Battle of [Kulikovo](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Kulikovo) opened with single combat between two champions, both died, and the battle took place soon after. Also, the Battle of [Badr](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Badr) started with three champions from each side engaged in combat and again the battle proper began afterwards. 

The Battle of the [300 Champions](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_the_300_Champions) is really interesting because this was actually intended to prevent Sparta and Argos from committing their entire armies to battle and risk massive losses as well as settle the dispute politically.  Well, through a series of events both sides claimed victory and a full scale battle happened anyway.  

It was also traditional for Japanese Samurai to challenge each other to single combat.  A samurai would control a unit of foot soldiers and challenge opposing samurai, the defeat of the samurai would often cause the whole unit to retreat and change the overall course of the battle.  This continued until they had to change their fighting style during the Mongol Invasions of Japan.
According to our manner of fighting we must first call out by name someone from the enemy ranks, and then attack in single combat. But the Mongols took no notice at all of such conventions. They rushed forward all together in a mass, grappling with any individuals they could catch and killing them.

**TL;DR:** It depended on the era and if the leaders of both sides kept their word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah they're brave. If I ever going missing, that can be put on the list of places that people won't have to bother checking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing for twelve years and still can't read a *lick* of sheet music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of the Fremantle Prison Riot, an organized diversion for a planned escape. Prisoners started fires as part of the diversion which unintentionally prevented the escape. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't post this in OldSchoolCool, but lasers are still as popular as ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post this to /r/conspiracy and see how long it takes for the words "chemtrails" and "cover up" to appear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was quoted as saying,  "This is a bag of shit, I just wanted to show you this so you'll recognize it later on throughout the day". He did it in reference to the quality of music he felt was appearing that day of the festival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that while performing The Reading Festival, the vocalist for The Dillinger Escape Plan defecated onstage, put it in a bag, threw it into the crowd, and smeared himself with the rest. The set was one of the highest reviewed of the year and included in a list of the top performances of the decade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Gallipoli](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gallipoli) Peninsula has seen battles fought there over and over through history because of its strategic importance as a main route between Asia and Europe by way of the Dardanelles. Battles here date from the Greco-Persian Wars of the late 400 BC's all the way up to modern times. The Gallipoli Campaign of WWI probably makes this one of the bloodiest locations by itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vandelay Industries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago Is Colder Than Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
