<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is these are not my ideas, it's contributions from fans iv'e seen around forums and stuff... Its awesome though that the nrl does tend to listen to the fans regarding changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New York Toy Fair New Releases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG this would be awesome

"Uh wow, yuu look so sexy parmela" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of investment and performance sam tomkins was instantly overshadowed by at least 10 other NRL fullbacks.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't care as long as it does not use gears in the internals! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A) Shorter season (Everyone plays each side once)


B) Change to golden point for regular season (If scores are tied at 80min, each side gets a point... if there is a winner of 10mins extra time they get an additional point)


C) A 6 man bench (Seriously necessary cause of the new concussion rules)


D) A overhaul of player eligibility rules for SOO and Test footy. And revised international games/schedule so there's some prestige about it and granting funds to smaller nations so they can get the likes of Milford etc. I currently do not give two F's for test footy since every year it's OZ's comp to lose.


E) A virtual grid for the bunker to check offsides. 


F) A short 2 round NYC draft (Though will require alot of work and overhaul of the current system, no point in the warriors developing a talent another side can nab)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my sister thought mellisandre from GOT was a white walker when she took her amulet off and turned into a old lady.... my sister is in her 30's :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drac has a video on this kit, I was interested in the curved priming rod but however it's not bent exactly like the stock one and rubs on the shell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you seriously underestimate the ability of queenslanders when given the opportunity to get munted at suncorp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the metal pricier one they plan to release could be, this however for its price-range looks like a good entry level sealed kit for smaller spring loads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> since maloneys been getting some love lately (not disputing, he's elite) i'll compare his 2016 to SJ's...

SJ

Tries - 10

Try Assists - 18

Line Breaks - 15



Maloney

Tries - 5

Try Assists - 9

Line Breaks - 7

Maloney played x2 less games than SJ but his team finished way higher on the ladder and they destroyed the knights twice when they met. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tariq Sims had huge wraps and is now just a journeyman going from club to club.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that he was awesome last year and is one of the next most clutch halves behind cronk   jt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought an xplorer longstrike top style priming grip a while back, it doesn't look like its sold anymore and anyone know if there's a demand for those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kahu on his trails this year now CP13 is done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wonder how many times motherfucker will be written in the script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reminds me of sironen, don't get the hype with this guy...... however he can prove me wrong since he's still young, someone he should hope to emulate is cordner who keeps getting better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the friday the 13th movie should go PG13 for 200mil with mark wahlberg and dwayne johnson in mecha suits racing to stop a giant beam of light in the sky from destroying the planet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stahp trying to play psychologist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen videos on it, just i'd have to drag my fat ass to the store and find what i'm after which is also gonna cost me bus money.

I'd also rather get something less ghetto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LF 3D Printed Spacer for Hammershot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for something like this and i'm keen to buy x3 pieces.

http://www.thingiverse.com/thing:904814

If you can sell, please send me some pics of what they come out like and let me know what color options are available to me. I'm located in Australia BTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think jet blaster are doing a full length dart, sealed breech kit.... i'm not sure if its going to drop into a longshot shell though.

also just a heads up, a metal artifact boltsled will set you back $50 straight away but is top notch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheap Thrills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imagine playing indoors in pitch black darkness with that scope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The matildas were flogged 7-0 in a friendly game to the newcastle jets u15 boys haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything it would be a joke if the NYC stays the way it is and we start pumping money into a womens game. 

In tennis they fought and eventually got equal pay (even though mens grand slams can go for 5hrs, to about 2hrs for womens). If Serena Williams played the best 15yo boy in the world and lost, I wonder if they would have kicked up a fuss in the beginning? 

But yea I'd rather money goes into growing our game overseas and a higher quality comp for the NYC before (gurl power, we can too... its 2017) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that ring which goes inside the plunger tube any good? 

i'm really interested to find out if its a useful piece to extend the life of the plunger tube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like what ive seen from lamb, very hodkinsony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone in nz know in how many hours it starts? im shit with timezones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dumb And The Dumber

2 Dumb 2 Dumber

Dumb And Dumber: Aspen Drift

Dumb   Dumber

Dumb   Dumber 6

Dumb 7

The Fate Of The Dumber
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking 'UP' a "heartwarming story about a lonely old man and naive child" by disney had a shoehorned villain to move the plot forward when it was entirely uneccesary. Really makes you appreciate the movies by studio ghibli.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dedicated to the people of ethspania </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> League keeps getting richer and SOO is a huge product. I can totally see league being of such a high quality with great salary for players that if you make it, it would be silly to "try and play for the wallabies" or "win rugby sevens in the olympics" or something.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your right, it requires a overhaul of the current system/contracts which could be possible if the game continues to grow... but unfortunately might not be in my lifetime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we keep track of these so that in like 20 years we can compare all the rookie classes? it makes me want a draft in the NRL sooooooooo bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why some out of the lot can't pick up the learning curve, there could be some good props and wingers over there...

I honestly think that if the NRL was serious about pushing the game over there they need to send some ex players and training/coaching staff over for a tour of about 5-6 of the more prominent college football schools.

There they register interest from guys playing for their college and go through drills and fitness levels and pick out some standouts. At that point they can go "If you don't enter the draft or get drafted at all, your invited to come down to australia and attend a league camp". At that point they would get some hopefuls that will go through rugby league training and potentially go play reserve grade.

If there is financial backing from US something like this can be done once every 2-3 years, down the track they can pool a US team together in reserve grade.... and just maybe the US could take an interest in supporting the side further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm totally for this, and they should scrap the trial games.

This is a big wishlist and probably never going to happen, but I wish the NRL would take over develoment of grassroots footy/NYC so we can get a draft in the NRL. Would work the same as NFL/NBL but only go for 2-3 rounds and whoever wins the nines can also get an extra automatic 1st overall pick with priority over the team that finishes 16th on the ladder. If you finish 16th, but win the nines you can effectively pick out the x2 best players in the NYC straight away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The adding ski onto words in Ted?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea thats true, but they're all quite good honestly... the ones that have outright bad handling don't make it to first grade in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catching is overrated, there was a game last year where val holmes dropped three catches for certain tries. Even the guys with greathands do fups and at critical moments too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mau </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
