<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that they added tracer rounds, so you can tell if you're still on schedule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deep dish always gets an upvote.  Looking great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arby's just came back with a special "Philly" with roasted red and yellow peppers as well as a "garlic aioli". [garlic redundant]  I like peppers.  Even tomato and lettuce is a good addition.  Not required though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like mine over the top and over the hash browns and two or three over easy eggs on top of that.  Oh, and sausage in the gravy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's...beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not raw. SAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like mine like I like my women.  Saucy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  awesome experience of having a fried egg on top of/alongside breakfast foods and the way the yolk melds with everything else, and wanted to see what else that would be good with.
 It's also a nifty-looking presentation and something that might make a menu item pop for the customer, leading them to purchase it.

Yeah, I had fried egg with leftover steak the other morning and it was great to drag the steak through the yolk and eat. Also, it's a big FU to Guy Fierri. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd eat that with some tomato sauce on wheat chip.  Good job, have an upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those look nothing like the sardines in a can for like a buck that I ate the other night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else see the face in the upper left? Also upper right looks like a small duck. Not sure which is neeps and which is tatties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not know how to eat this. Sauce on head on shrimp seems messy. How do you get the shell off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, more skrimps next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that as feet next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Ate] enchilada platter (right) at frontier in albuquerque. frontier beef burrito on left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, how did you do this OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those bacon wrapped peppers look great. Are they anaheims, or poblano? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only marrow I've had lately is from a lamb thigh steak. Cook the steak normally, and don't forget to suck the marrow from the bone. It's so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I see that hole on the first and 3rd slice on the left and I'm like Rotisserie!  The roast looks perfectly done.  Did you pull it at 135f? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, no cheese.  So, no OP yours is chili mac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lurv pot salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said you're a whore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you style your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is . . . beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (I ATE) lunch at Frontier on the UNM campus in albuquerque. beef enchilada platter for me and frontier beef burrito </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I had a fish like that at a mexican place in Denver a couple times. It was really f**king good. I should have explored the face for more deliciousness. No batter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember liking the shaker salad. You can do the same thing at home in mason jars, they're fun!
edit: if you really want to you can shake it up and dump it on a plate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/wewantplates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks super great.  
/there's a way to get your picture to post in the thread.  Read up on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really good. I especially like the olive dressing that I can see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, not finishing a calzone and sides is a Jeep thing?  TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A tostada is basically mexican pizza.  Think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arby's alt-gyro is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sopapilla are a lightly fried light dough that when fried (not sure how folded) puff up like a Yorkshire pudding/popover.  They are usually served with powdered sugar and honey for desert/snack at a Mexican restaurant.  
In New Mexico, there is a stuffed sopapilla which is a dinner entree stuffed with beans, meat, veg, etc. and probably sauced and cheesed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a great recipe.  Your photo is just as good looking (you're so good looking).  I've never had any luck with pork tenderloin.  I always turns out tough. (mostly starting with Hormel marinated packages). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you be my huckleberry OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should probably cook it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom usually has the French-Canadian style meat pies at Christmas.  They're made with pork and potatoes with clove.  They're a little difficult to get used to with the clove flavor, but hey, pork and potatoes what could be bad about that.  After a while you get a hankering for that flavor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/wewantplats

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is looking super great and authentic also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically at a steak house or other restaurant or your kitchen at home a steak used to be seared in a pan, and then finished in the oven for even cooking and no excessive burning on the outside.  
The reverse sear works better because it creates more rare or medium-rare beef.  Start in an oven to say rare (112-118f) and then finish with a fast sear in the pan on the stovetop to temp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it looks great.  If it were me I'd have made the patty with increased diameter, but they shrink (It was cold!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might have been a tapeworm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can start with canned potato cubes.  No need to cook them, a big time saver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that In-n-Out squirts prepared mustard on the burger after it's on the grill (in the pan for you) and then when it flips the mustard cooks in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slice it across so it opens like a book to make it more evenly flat.  You could stuff it with say cheese (goat/mozz), proscuitto and crushed nuts (pinion/pistachio).  Roll it up and grease w/olive oil before cooking.  That would probably be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That salad looks excellent as well as the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not frozen, but the Perdue brand nuggets and fingers are probably the best.  I find them near the kielbasa.  like this https://i5.walmartimages.com/asr/872941a7-73b7-49f3-b2aa-2dcf59925df1_1.068c7b0def3709d9256676827f489cf4.jpeg?odnHeight=450 odnWidth=450 odnBg=FFFFFF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popsicle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I didn't mean you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no whiskey and no lid, not a smart kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, that's a Farberware!  I got one off of ebay a few years ago because my father used one during the MN winters.  How important is this asian wine in your recipe?  Any suggested subs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess they don't tortilla in Ireland (edit: or Scotland for that matter).  That's a problem.  j/k  The restaurant near me has a dish called divorced eggs.  One egg has red sauce, the other green with sopes and beans.  Then they have the "df" huevos.  Does that mean they're dtf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made the Lady Bird Johnson Pedernales River chili once.  I wasn't impressed, find a different one.  Or do it better than I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my safeway has raw dough, it's near the deli.  Take a look or ask, it'll turn out nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pass the honey, honey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> boneless short ribs (beef) with carne asada seasoning in a foil oven packet for 4 hours or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That dish really shouldn't take so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CO: try some edibles.  They'll knock your socks off  
Also Buffalo steak/burger and pork green chile (sorry NM-couldn't say rocky mtn oysters cuz WY stole it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ice cream is BURNT!  Ok, maybe just the marshmallow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the snow?  my goodness, over 22 feet in January, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think yours sounds really great.  Maybe I'd rather have a steak with a mushroom and onion sauce for the main.  So, surf and turf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what a robot would say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looking great!  I'm sure it tastes the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's in my heritage though so that's ok for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, just kidding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crust on this pie looks really perfect for me.  The thickness is pretty darn deep, thanks to OP and to Moderator for making this thread great again!  Deep dish is the pizza of my memories/future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's from KFC, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a bottle opener on the end of your fork, or did you temporarily misplace that from Disney? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was introduced to this dish at the company lunch buffet a few years ago.  Yours looks great!  What is the kind of yellow melon looking stuff?  Potato maybe, the ones I've seen used french fries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, you'll love it with shrimp.  I've also made the rotel/velveeta dip (I think they have velveeta in smaller packaging now), and really like to make a chunky guacamole like this: http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/ree-drummond/guacamole-recipe.html  
Super easy as most groceries have pico de gallo in the deli section...
edit: probably should buy some avocados tomorrow so they'll be ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  rusty bread, toasted, smush the fish onto the bread like tuna fish, and then sprinkle with a spritz of fresh lemon juice.
 With sardines, if you smush the fish up like tuna fish, you wouldn't really notice the innards and spine. They're soft and they mix right in.

I like the pickled herring.  In my store there's some (jarred in the fish section) with wine sauce and onion or sour cream and onion.  It would be great on bread, but I do Trisquit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you're a roadie or in a band.  Amiright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> baked scorpions:  
deseed and half the jalapenos  
insert cream cheese  
top with a raw shrimp peeled and deveined  
wrap with 1/2 slice of bacon  
bake in oven 350f or more till bacon is done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it.  Looks super easy and plenty of sauce (I tend to think bisquits are too dry). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $14-16 here.  for a 14" w/onion, white american and steak $14.  Add tomato and onion, $15.  w/onion mushroom and peppers $16 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a chinese/american buffet lunch place and they had "black pepper shrimp" which was pretty small shrimp, shell on with black pepper.  I got some and tried to peel them and couldn't.  I didn't eat them, and asked the guy as I left "do people eat them with the shell on" and he said yes.  Can't say as I didn't try them, but they were small so there's not much poop chute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He photographed it in Hebrew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried to make scallops for years.  Can't get anything close.  I just make poo  lol

Try scallops, gentle sweet lobster-like flavor but different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a rabbit with the chicken, yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really look like mushrooms.  But the main question is how is that roast so black on the outside while rare/medium in the middle?  Beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pizza looks small but delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks really great.  I wouldn't have gotten chicken tenders at a bbq place, but hey they look great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, one might say it was a Sunday, Bloody Sunday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks really great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dem belly full, but we hungry.  Hungry man is an angry mon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that, it's just "Thanks Obama" because is sounds so much better than thanks trump or thanks bush. Obama sounds really jammin', like vacation time in the islands. I try to save some energy, infact all of my bulbs (most anyway) have been CF since 1997 or so. My energy bill didn't go down though. They say you'll save, but no you won't. And if you do, the electric company will raise the rates so you won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, new guy came and asked for regular household bulb.  I happened to as what for because those are outlawed (thanks Obama) and I knew he was from the BDC (bus driver coalition) so I gave him the 12v version.  It really helps when you're trying to get things going and it's 5 AM and -10 degrees F.  edit: they are similar to a 100w household bulb, but 12v. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything is a butt plug if you try hard enough.  You're going to try hard, aren't you comrade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time someone rigged up a ski pole with a bungee through the wheel well to hammer the starter on one of our trucks.  That was awesome and worked fine for a few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ash me that one more time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whole inspection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got 12vdc bulbs.  We use them in a box that contains pneumatic door cylinders for heat.  They are 100w. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like eels, at least it's not penii
/wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what Maklube is, but most of the white stuff looks like penii. lol.
edit: added lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping they were standing up because of broth in the bottom.  Maybe the correct thing to do is to pick it up and take a slurp of broth and then a bite.  Sounds like fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very cool story.  It sure looks like it has a great portion of beef, which I like a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prepare KD according to box directions. Transfer and hold. Steam some spinach, then fry chorizo in some oil.  Combine and stir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sandwich is sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
