<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4719</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My professor told us not to work. its a lot of stress during your first experience in the classroom. I quit my weekend job while student teaching, but i lived at home so it was easier. if you can get financial aid to help instead of work, i'd do that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show her the video "what teachers make" by Taylor Mali on youtube :) thats what got me through college during tough times!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving in with Boyfriend - need advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I'm moving in with my boyfriend in 6 months (June) so of course i'm already worried about it :P I am a high functioning depressed person, but I use home to defuse a lot. Considering that, home will become where I see my boyfriend. I am really afraid of burdening him with my depression, because its something i battle with daily. I understand that I cannot tell him each time I am depressed why i'm depressed, sometimes it is a battle with myself and I do not want him to feel so helpless. I know that if i want to share why, it has to be something he can comfort me about. 
My plan is, when we sit down to talk about the actual move to say something like the following "I get depressed a lot, and you haven't seen that yet. I promise that when it is something I need you for, I will tell you. Otherwise, I know how to cope and I will be able to get through it. I want you to trust me on that." 

What do you think? Any advice? Am I on the right path? What has your experience been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I feel this so much. May I ask you a question? How do you cope with depression around your husband? I am planning to move in with my boyfriend in June and I'm really worried about that. Ive read a few articles and asked a few friends and the feedback i've gotten is you make face for your significant other and decide very careful when to share how you're feeling (ie in situations when they can actually help). What do you do? 

Thank you and stay strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes! please let her know she's not alone. theres a lot of us who deal with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she starts seeing a therapist the state has NO authority to cut her out of working with children. Many teachers see therapists, I used to too!! Many teachers I know are on medicine for their depression or anxiety, and thats fine. 
Since she is an adult she cannot be forced into a psych ward unless she winds up in the hospital for a suicide attempt.  

She should seek help. The only way she'll lose her career is if her therapist breaks confidentially (which is illegal, so.... it wont happen)

Teachers are people too, we are allowed to seek treatment for our ailments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduated November 2013 with that same degree. I got lucky finding a long term sub march 2014-june 2014 and once more feb - march 2015. I landed a fulltime job August 2015 at a private Catholic school, super low pay (35.8k), but experience is important. It is HARD to find a job if you dont know people who know people. A good starting salary can be 40-45k + depending on your state (google!). Good luck! dont give up! 

If you want me to look at your resume i can do that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for replying, stay strong!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for replying!! Stay strong 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for replying! 
"I'm afraid people think I'm joking because of how outwardly together I look" me too man, me too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Functioning Depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know too many people like me, who are diagnosed with depression   anxiety but are very high functioning individuals. i.e. - I have a wonderful stable job which I am good at   love, an amazing significant other, good friends, independence, I'm very responsible... but I'm still incredibly depressed and riddled with anxiety attacks. Its very easy for me to fool people that I have it all together because i'm able to function so well, and the cover of everything going well in life is enough to not draw attention. 

Anyone else like this??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i used kahoot a lot when i taught 6th grade! they loved it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> buy a lock for a cabinet and store stuff in there. Take valuables home all the time. I have what seem like trustworthy students but I still do that! you never really know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know, first year will be exhausting no matter what. It will get easier and you will get more time off when you get more experience. What i've found helpful is to only work at work. I do not bring work home - ever. That meant during my first year I was at work for 11 or 12 hours oftentimes and NEVER worked on the weekends.   BUT this created a very clear work is work and home is home. I really recommend you do that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont tell my coworkers about my depression or anxiety, I fear/know that they will look at me differently if I do. People talk, even trustworthy ones, and the last thing I want is being the center of workplace gossip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me!! I teach 16-18 year olds, I'm 25   have a babyface. People outside of work constantly mistake me for a high school student. At work I ALWAYS wear business casual clothing and try and carry myself as an adult. It helps! a little! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently had to sit through a PD about Google drive, Google docs, Google Slides and Google forms..... It was awful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wrote a nasty mean reply on a post that was supposed to be here for support.  I cannot hear your tone,  I cannot detect humor when you say all those mean things.  Just sounded mean.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't clear at all....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry,  I don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my area subs do not have to have a teaching degree. So...  I'm coming from that pov.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Message me if you wanna chat:) first year is super hard and anxiety triggering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So happy for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad you're back to work   back to loving it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That substitute sounds incredibly bitter. You're not naive or irrational. You are a teacher, as new as you are, you still have a degree and education. Yeah, you'll never be perfect, but no one ever will be! That's just silly. These ARE your children. All of your students will always be your kids. Always. If not, you're in the wrong profession. Always try, always teach. 

Everything that sub said is why this person is a sub, not a teacher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! A troll! how original!!! Wow!!! never seen one before!! SHOW ME YOUR HATEFUL WAYS OH TROLL, TEACH ME TO BE LIKE YOU! lol bye Felicia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome!  Stay strong!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are so very welcome!  I'm glad you took the steps to get help,  it will make you feel better and it will have an amazing impact on your work:) Stay strong fellow pedagog!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We certainly do not!  Thank you right back:)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
