<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1510</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I am 99% sure you are right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am all about that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Horror and comedy can be a thin line. Can't say I laughed at this one haha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cat with Hands was the first one I saw. It is pretty great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? haha. Where did that come from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I remember seeing a graphic showing where they could hit in the US. But with the understanding that they had the ability to be actuate within a few hundred miles or something. Hopefully they don't try and shoot near something to flex and accidentally hit it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intervening in individual cases seems like a no brainier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet she can run faster than me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow... Usually it seems like there is so little response to these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So glad they did this to the Bates Hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know! sorry. I found it looking for something else :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Form Shifting Alien by Douglas Barlowe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didnt Draw this but... also could not resist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally understand. I like them but haven't bought any either. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taco in space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does sell them: http://www.shapeways.com/shops/joabaldwin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sells them through shapeways. So... Probably not? I could link the shapeways shop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conrad Ruiz, Overload, Watercolor on Canvas, 2009 Obama Flying on a Corgi Shooting a Lazer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Test Your Awareness: Do The Test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 01:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! I was surprised to see it had not been shared in 7 months. Different url. Makes sense now. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice Dog Portrait by Chad Keith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 01:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 00:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assassinate is the word Wikipedia used. There was a short plan, in that he fled and they went after him to kill him at the airstrip. But, yeah, its kind of splitting hairs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 00:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I am bad at learning :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 00:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bjorn Barends - Ah! Meant to add that to the title then forgot. He has lots of cool stuff I was just looking at. somebody posted this one on instagram

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brother Max Moorman has become obsessed with nature photography, driving all over the state at all hours of the day and night, and I love this shot from La Plate Peak, CO [2000x1300] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also lived in a prison to understand what it was like to be a prisoner. Real impressive guy. Wish he would have survived.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that one of the only senators ever assassinated was Leo Ryan who was killed by Jim Jones's cult members while they were in the process of committing mass suicide. He had come to investigate reports from concerned family members. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool yeah! I like them a lot. My roommate had one that she never watered and no one notice is had died for like a month.  They cant live on no water! just very little. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend makes some beautiful 3D printed air plant planters. This is one of my favorites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha! indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you become a zombie does it cure your diabetes, or does your diabetes just make you a shitty zombie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> terrifying machine zombies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 19:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much man! That is really awesome. And very appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 07:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really awesome to hear that Schmigglepop! Quite a complement! Unless of course it is also the only stop motion film you have seen. haha. Thanks so much for contributing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 08:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a lot. definitely intimidating. But we are on track so far. Averaging more than 300 a day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 07:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ForeignVR! Brothers Quay are Excellent.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 07:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 05:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But still 24 days to go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 05:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot Vegetaman! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 05:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for the contribution! 

About the budget. Its actually very bare bones for what will end up being over 100 minutes of animation. If you look at a movie like Coraline its budget was $60 million or about $600,000 a minute. The budget for this, after kickstarter fees and money that goes to fulfilling rewards, is $8805 per episode, or a little over $1000 a minute. Of course, I am not making something at the same level as Laika. But I am hiring professional animators and VFX artist, puppet makers, voice actors. They all have rent to pay, one has a kid. I don't want to ask them to work for free. 

I spent 8 months making the 1st one. I did almost everything myself. When I had full monitization on it and it was getting 500-700 views a day it translated into around 60 cents a day. Not nothing. Not a lot. If I had maximum monitization turned on for the whole time, it now has 550,000 views, I might have made around $500. Its a long way from sustainable unfortunately. Funding from youtube makes sense if you can make a video a weak. And I should make a making of video. That is an excellent suggestion. I hope I can keep building enough to fund it that way.  But right now it's not impossible. 

Edit: missing word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bierluvre! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks startedbackin77! Really great to have people see it and want to support it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for backing Demonstien! Very much appreciated. Hope I get to deliver something excellent and terrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 02:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot WhatDoesStarFoxSay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Stubee1988! It is still called set design. The main character is about 10 inches tall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Argothar! I liked Ident a lot. Kinda wish they still did more like that. Not that they aren't still doing great stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to the original short [Operator](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xavcTEwk3VQ) if anyone has not seen it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent 8 months making this 7 min stop-motion short about a man being attacked by a biomechanical parasite. I was thrilled by reddits incredible support, so I spent the last two years (between working other jobs) writing 15 new episodes. With dreadit's help I am finally ready to start making them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 23:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thanks so much for supporting it! it means a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Rndmtrkpny! If your birthday involves helping fund it on [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator)! haha, either way glad you liked it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ZappatheGreat! I submitted it to festivals last year. Won Best animation at New Filmmakers Los Angeles 2014, and the Idaho Horror Festival. Which was cool. Right now I am trying to [Kickstart](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator) new episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thanks!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 06:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much backing LordApocalyptica! It really means a lot and it can't happen with out you. Good luck with the animation!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I love reddit so much for attacking those guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks GoodbyeAndGodBless!I have never played Half-Life. But a lot of people have mentioned a similarity. I don't play too many games aside from GTA. And stupid phone games sometimes when I am bored and sleepy haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Zaexithos!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks foxycheese202! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks DalekaniumEgg! Do you mean what the loud speaker is saying when he is falling behind? in that case he thinks just let go. As that was the policy. But when they infect everyone with parasites they shoot anyone that manages to avoid infection. The company was a normal comany but now it is enslaving its workes with parasites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Poe-fan! [Kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator) is at 14%! No a bad start but still a long way to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks KindredGamer!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ProcStyloideus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks t_rosen! I use a 7D and after effects. I should have used DragonFrame, but didn't know about it at the time. Here is some more info about making it copied from comment above:
You definitely want a skeleton. Which is called an armature. The cheap option is using armature wire, which bends and holds its shape well. The expensive option is ball and socket. which never breaks down, as the armature wire does but cost like 150 a puppet. I use both depending on the puppet. I sculp my puppet heads with sculpy but then make casts of them in foam latex or more recently silicone. Here is a link to a [gif timelapse](https://www.instagram.com/p/BBHCgZ0Qjto/) of me making the most recent one. Here is a [good video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uimF41CrMXM) of how to make an armature .
Generally clay is hard to work with. its heavy and malleable. But, its an easy place to start. The body of my puppets is usually foam latex.
The puppets are about 10 inches tall.
Most of the set is physically constructed but little things are added in post and the last shot in this one is expanded a whole bunch by duplicating the same set a bunch of times. I make mine out of film core, posterboard, sheet metal, parts of computer cases or anything else that seems to work. I use clamps a lot to holds things in place.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAAAAHHHHHHHH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks furniturevodka! Nice name! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Thanks MaelKoth2015! Thats awesome! Here is the [kickstarter link](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit GwarBeastly011! You stole my idea I got after watching the fine bros! ok... I'll take it down...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was shot because he got rid of the parasite. If you listen to the audio at that point you can hear the anoucement saying workers at x doors, including his, have "avoided integration". Then he gets shot. Then some others that got rid of the parasite get shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks sgnirpsnodrazil! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks qwe7791! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks MexicanInParis! Yeah, totally. If I manage to compete some more successful episodes I hope they could be open to partnering. I don't know if its funny enough for adult swim, but, I suspect they are awesome enough to move a little out of their wheelhouse if they are excited enough. They have definitely had moments of dark stuff on a lot of their shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lit zuzu4yuyu! I plan on spending as much time as I can on it. Cant afford to spend 8 months per short anymore, but I have also gotten a lot faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 1000 hours on the 1st short. I don't know how many on writing. A lot! thousands more between writing and building puppets and everything else for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome Thanks! Good to know they could be open to it. I will definitely post there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks giantjerk! Glad too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Douchewafer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks digital_end! thats awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks adviceKiwi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Littlemightyrabbit! I mean, Peter Chung is awesome. I am sure he has influenced me. I just re watched Aeon flux a few weeks ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot Pinetreecaravans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BAM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for the comment The_Funki_Tatoes! I am not super into jump scares. Dont get me wrong, I am all for using any gimmick if it serves the story(I will be using 3D sound in the new episodes), but startles for startles sake is kind of dull in the end I think. Very please to hear it held you in those states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means a lot bigborris! I am glad your not dying! Hearing that I have made something that is worth someones time is excellent. Dying or not haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much man! Thats excellent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 10:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Sydskidoo! Thats awesome! and very much appreciated. I hope a can deduce the redundancy of film watching at least a little bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 08:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so man man that  is awesome! And very much appreciated!

You definitely want a skeleton. Which is called an armature.  The cheap option is using armature wire, which bends and holds its shape well. The expensive option is ball and socket. which never breaks down, as the armature wire does but cost like 150 a puppet. I use both depending on the puppet. I sculp my puppet heads with sculpy but then make casts of them in foam latex or more recently silicone. Here is a link to a [gif timelapse](https://www.instagram.com/p/BBHCgZ0Qjto/?taken-by=operator_web_series) of me making the most recent one. Here is a good video of [how to make an armature](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uimF41CrMXM). 

Generally clay is hard to work with. its heavy and malleable. But, its an easy place to start. The body of my puppets is usually foam latex. 

The puppets are about 10 inches tall. 

Most of the set is physically constructed but little things are added in post and the last shot in this one is expanded a whole bunch by duplicating the same set a bunch of times. I make mine out of film core, posterboard, sheet metal, parts of computer cases or anything else that seems to work. I use clamps a lot to holds things in place. 

It is a lot of work but I love it! Good luck!
 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 08:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't when I made this. I didn't know it was so awesome at the time. Which is one of my only regrets about this film. I have used it lots since then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks EatMorTurkee! Thats really awesome. Hope I can deliver! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Hard_Reptile! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, man it is really great to hear! As someone who has sat through very many short films that I wanted to like, but couldnt get into, that means a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Carnalkid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks sydomination! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much drewdrew4247! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That was really fucking weird. Which is not something I often say about anything. Also totally amazing. I had not seen it which seems ridiculous. I had seen the cat with hands and the separation  which was also great. But this one is at another level. I am going to have to watch it again. Thanks a lot for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 06:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks drewrykroeker! I have had some soul draining jobs for sure. haha. 

I shoot with a 7D. I have been doing stop motion for about 9 years. Although I did live action and other kinds of animation for a lot of that time before focusing on stop motion after making this short.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 06:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot jincow! Thats awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 04:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lee Hardcastle is amazing. I would be into that for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 04:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats really awesome thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 04:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot cynderchick! I plan on it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 04:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great question! 
First off, to clarify why am I doing a kickstarter, I have finished writing the episodes. I haven't made any, which is the part that costs money. Sorry that was unclear. 

Why so long?  I released it 2 years ago and people liked it a lot. I immediately started working on new episodes. I also got a lot of attention from people who were interested in funding more. Ranging from major studios to small web based companies. Some of them I wanted to work with, and was really excited. This turned into having a lot of long slow negations with those people that eventually went no where. Everyone loved it, no one was will to take the next leap. Turns out this is very normal in Hollywood. Meanwhile I kept writing and rewriting, while working other jobs, until I got really happy with the script. which was a few months ago. I decided to stop waiting for someone to tell me I could make more and try to raise the funds myself. So I spent the last few months preparing the Kickstarter which brings us to now. 

Hope that answers the question? 

TLDR it took a long time to write new epsidoes while working other jobs and I got lead on by people who said they would fund it but never pulled the trigger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent! Human_1914. Nice username.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Kami_Ouija!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone wants to see some new clips of puppets freaking out and parasites attacks from the upcoming episodes. Or hear more about what I am doing with the series. here is the link to the [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator). 

Pledging would of course be awesome too but no pressure. I know people don't come to reddit to have things sold to them which is how it should be.

Edit - rephrasing, spelling
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I_lack_common_sense! I am sure tool has had some influence on me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I am of course bias,  but. yes. Why is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks HarlanCedeno!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, awesome Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Malfunkdung! Yeah, it can be tedious and slow. But I get so obsessive about the details and seeing the frames come together I've decided its kind of a perfect medium for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 23:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I am a big fan of things that are really well developed. So, I try to take a long time getting it right. That said I look back on this one now and see so many things I could have done better. haha. But! the new ones will take it to the next level I hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 23:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man! glad you liked it. Yeah, it will follow some new characters the escape the initial infection as they try to fight back against the company.  It also goes way deeper into what the parasites do to people, and the people responsible for creating them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent 8 months making this 7 min stop-motion short about a man being attacked by a biomechanical parasite. I was thrilled by reddits incredible support, so I spent the last two years (between working other jobs) writing 15 new episodes. With reddits help I am finally ready to start making them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 23:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 01:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. Not to mention that by preventing the spread of STIs planned parenthood is fighting cancer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 23:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, this worked great for me. If you get like 100ft from Ebay not too expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 09:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhhh... Dont light a lighter if your hand is soaked in gasoline? Looks nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 22:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
