<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1203</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you post a photo on social media showing you sitting in a toilet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. and agreed. As much as we would like social apps to connect us, for many of us it just creates an illusion of connectedness, a sort of fake "real" social network.
Not only does most of these apps dosconnect us from each other but it does even create depression.
Just google Facebook Depression.
This is the exact reasons why we wanted to create an app that genuinely conncets us and our friends and family and does it absolutely fast and does not take away time from the real life connections.
Let me know if interested so I give you a link to our app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> weird statue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for commenting. 
It is true what you are saying about honesty. Some want to be dishonest or just show the best parts of their lives.
Unfortunetly, several studies show that showing off on social media negatively affects most of us. We tend to compare our boring life moments with the highlight reels posted by others. 
Thank you for your idea by the way! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crowdsourcing ideas for getting users. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, we have developed a little app that we believe help people connect with each other online in a more honest way. With this app basically you can get your friends to take a picture at the same time and capture in a photo collage what all you did at this particular moment in time. The reason why we think our app provides a more honest way to connect is that here you have to post life updates and photos not when you want it but when your friends request it. We are brainstorming ideas how to best promote this app and we thought we ask the reddit community for ideas. We appreciate any ideas you might have. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best ways to get early users for an app? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your most used or funniest office slang words? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need 50 office slang words for a project. What are your best ones or most used ones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need 50 office slang words for a project. Please help me out and tell me your best or most used ones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[THIS IS SPORTSBRA!!!!](http://imgur.com/gallery/cxDQ4)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. This is so weird. We have just tested it and everything works fine. Did you have good connection at the location you were when you signed up. Sorry for all these questions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Social App: Capture in a photo collage how you and your friends live this moment. Feedback is appreciated! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys,
We have developed a social app that gets you and your friends to take a picture or selfie at the exact same time and makes a photo collage from this shared moment. 
Maybe nonoe of you affected by this, but many studies found a strong correlation between social media usage and depression. This phenomenon happens when people compare their mundane life moments with the highlight reels posted by others on social media. 
When we developed Go Synco we wanted to create a way where users have to post genuine posts and photos about themsleves and mundane moments from their days.
Maybe our app is not the perfect solution but we feel it is a good step in teh right direction.
Basically, Go Synco is a group based social app where any group member can initiate a synco which means that he/she can request everybody in the group to take a photo and add a short caption about what they are doing now.
Everyone in the group gets 5 minutes to respond and when the time is up, all of the group members receive a photo collage stamped with the current time and date to remember when this moment happened.
Now, even though the app is in the stores, both App Store and Google Play, we have a long way to go to say it is finished.
We are currently working on the UX/UI of the app to make it look less like an MVP and more like a real app.
Please download the app and give us some feedback what you like and what you don't, what features would be cool to add and what is waste.
We appreciate all you guys' feedback.
Here you can find the app:
**[Go Synco on App Store](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/go-synco/id1075937699?mt=8)**
**[Go Synco on Google Play](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gosynco hl=en)**
Thanks again! 
Cheers
Peter 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DEV] Get Your Friends To Take A Photo Or Selfie At The Exact Same Time And Get A Collage From This Shared Moment In Time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Redditors!
My name is Peter Mayer and with my friend we finally managed to push our app to the Google Play.
We know it looks more like an MVP at the moment and we actually started to work on bringing its UX/UI to the 21st century and make it look like and work like a modern app.
We need your feedback and suggestions though what are the things/features/design elements you would add or take away and in general what is your point of view so we can consider it in the UX and/or UI.

Some words about our app:
With Go Synco you can capture what you and your friends do right at this very moment and save the collage of this shared moment as a fun, time stamped memory.
The way this app works is whenever you wonder what your freinds are up to at any moment, you initiate a synco which sends out a notification to all your group members and gives them 5 minutes to take a selfie or photo and add a short caption what they are doing. 

As a sidenote, the reason we started to work on this concept was that we were tired of how current social media and their algoritms promote narcissism and fake online popularity that makes many people feel bad. (you can just google facebook depression).

Thank You for your kind feedback.

**[Our app on Google Play](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gosynco hl=en)**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name:**[Go Synco](https://www.gosynco.com)**

Elevator Pitch: **Get your friends to take a selfie at the exact same time and save this time stamped collage from this shared moment.**

Explainer video: **[Go Synco video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ktk7uAQpr9w)**

More details: We have developed the app and it is available for both **[ios](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/go-synco/id1075937699?mt=8)** and **[Android](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gosynco hl=en)**. We are working on changing the UI/UX to make it look like a non-MVP. :)

Are you looking for anything? We would appreciate any feedback from any of you guys. Thank You!

Discount for /r/startup subscribers? The app is free. Hopefully you will like the concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. 
We just checked it and it works on our side. Sorry to bother you about this again, but just to clarify, did this happen when you actually filled out your info at the sign up page and you click on signup or it was before that when you download the app and you can either login or signup?
Did you by the way get any error message? 
thanks a lot!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 11:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you please tell me what device are you using? Android or iPhone? Also what version of iOS or android?
I really appreciate it, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a shitty project. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get you friends to take a pic at the exact same time and see and save this collage from this shared moment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good concept.
One thing I would do right away is to put in plain English on the front page about what happens with the photos after user uploads them and who owns the photos' copyright.
Something like:
"Your photos are in a safe place with us..."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of these Illustrated Pictogram Quotes I made in Photoshop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook vs Real Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
