<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4010</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is great, only problem is that some bosses are basically impossible for some builds. Like the Darklurker boss, it's near impossible for melee builds and easy for mages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Souls 2 have a big variety in bosses that ruins the gameplay for one build while being better for another build. The first boss that comes to mind is Darklurker (which is an optional boss) who is basically impossible for melee builds and peace of cake for mage builds. I've been going through DS2 the last weeks with a friend of mine and most of the other bosses seemed easy for me while some were hard as ball for my friend (who plays a mage btw). For the last 3 days I've tried to do Darklurker (which you can ONLY do alone) with my char and I'm so close to giving up. I've leveled up my atunement a ton so I could use more pyromancy spells against her but it barely does anything. Why the devs nerfed pyromancy for this boss is beyond me, it basically makes the boss impossible for all melee based builds. You also need to use a human effegie each time you want to retry the boss AND you gotta go through a ton of hard dark npc's.

TL;DR Bosses fuck up builds, devs fuck up bosses, all fuck up you.

PS This is the only problem I have with DS2 though, everything else is great but this breaks the game for me. Don't want to not kill the boss either but it's basically impossible for me and I've tried everything I can try :L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah where you drop down and meet Darkdiver Grandahl. I saw some videos of that area and they had no statues in the middle of the room, but both of the golems were lit up so does that despawn them or? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Drangleic Castle is it possible to close the doors after the first bonfire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it, got pretty tired of trying to get around the area with 3 sentinels after me and it's really annoying that they respawn after you've killed them. I've only opened up the three doors on the left and the first one on the right, is the last two on the right also filled with a sentinel or is there another area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't download any torrents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 13:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't download ANY torrent, nothing happens when I click the magnet link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 13:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Norway, may be the reason now that I think of it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 13:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am, but usually when it blocks a site it's obvious that it's the ad-block that blocks the site. Here it's like the site is down or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 01:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah no shit, doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A WORKING PirateBay link? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to find a link that actually works and doesn't spam out everytime you click on anything. I remember finding one that didn't pop up a new tab and deleted the previous page you were on each time you clicked and that had a link to a functioning kickasstorrent site. That was about 1 and a half month ago, does anyone have a link or a functioning site?

EDIT: I got it working, apparently my country blocked the site so I couldn't use it. Used Hola! so I could browse from the US, worked like a charm then.

EDIT 2: The site's working but I can't download anything :L Everytime I click the "GET THIS TORRENT" link nothing happens. Been trying to find a activated windows 7 iso but it's damn near impossible... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on pc, don't have a touchphone rn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't any pictures load? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been like this for 2 days now, it just loads the page but the pictures aren't loading at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 00:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If modders can do this with games, why can't the devs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 12:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, I checked up on their current sites and unfortunately they don't have a store for my country(Norway). Yet atleast. So my only option would be to buy it from the sweden store and either get it sent to Norway or pick it up myself :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I didn't even know there was oneplus stores in europe, thought they were only in the US. Makes more sense then o.O Thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 03:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what sites you're using but I've been regularly checking their site the last week and they have never gotten the EU and UK dash adapters in stock at all. Their new phone shouldn't matter when it comes to the charger though, since its most likely an upgraded OP3 the charger is most likely the same as before. :p But still, would be nice if they added some way to tell us when it refills that particular product... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the store never refill it's stock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been waiting for over a month on getting OP3 because I live in Europe and the charger adapter that I need is never in stock. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what the music in this video is called? I've tried getting contacting the owner but he's not responded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 10:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah sorry, never actually been on this subreddit and it was an idea that popped into my head :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could this be Sabines mother? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah that's just it's force field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was like running through a giant apple store </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My pc restarts itself over and over again after I put it in safe mode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started with my pc being stuck updating, not during a startup but when I manually checked for updates. It never moved on or found any updates, just stuck. So I tried to find a solution for that online and one guy said that booting it up in safe mode worked for him. I thought I could try it out and tested it. Now my pc continuously restarts itself IN safe mode (screen is zoomed in, bad graphics, etc), it restarts just a couple of seconds after showing the log in screen and I can't do anything to fix this. Help!

EDIT: I'm adding this solely on the chance if anyone other than me ever gets this glitch or bug in the future. When my pc booted up the only things I could access was either BIOS or the 'safe mode' menu that pops up when you spam f8. I don't remember exactly which of the options that worked but I tried all of them and managed to fix the problem. After that it booted up to a safe mode in windows, I pressed windows button + R, typed in msconfig, unchecked the 'boot up on safe mode' button and restarted. Fixed my problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 14:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a simulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So just because I disagree with what they are doing I'm a 2 year old throwing a fit, and how exactly is me not wanting to play a game that costs way too much immature? Do you seriously think that the price for the complete game is alright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ofcourse I know they want money, but it just seems greedy as hell.. The premium editions cost less than if you'd buy the game and pass seperately, this is just wierd compared to their usual releases. Premium pass for bf1 costs the same amount as Premium  Edition did for BF4 ffs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it even possible to get BF1 Premium Edition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 02:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked it up on origin and it's either standard edition, Early enlister or extremely overpriced edition. Do I really have to pay 1.2 k NOK to get premium? SERIOUSLY? When BF4 came out you could get the game and premium for 700 NOK but this is just ridiculous... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done the Siva strike playlist for the last 4 days and I haven't gotten ANY skeleton keys at all, htf does everyone else get them so frequently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're in the same boat there, I joined Destiny when Taken King came out and haven't been able to do Crota's End or Vault of Glass :/ I think it would open up opportunities and make allot of people happy :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but they should update the raids so that you get end game gear from them aswell. Not 400 light level gear but still gear that can make your current light lvl higher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, just thought it wasn't worth it and that I'd just waste my time :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I'l add you now actually. My PSN is: PsychoticWaylon
I'm free on Sunday so I can do the raid then by the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was thinking that people could get gear from Rise of Iron from those raids aswell, not y1 and y2 stuff. But only Rise of the Machine on hard mode would give gear up to lvl 400 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on ps4 yeah, but as the others said you need atleast 4 people for the raids :L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I mean :D I've only played King's Fall Raid and I loved the bosses and the areas between them and would really like to experience that again with the previous raids. I'm really excited for rise of the machine raid but because I'm not high enough light level (and tired of running the same strikes over and over again) I thought this could be another way of getting higher light lvl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the experience wouldn't be the same and that ain't the point, just to actually do and finish the raids would be nice. Doing it solo would just be irritatingly hard and a waste of time and no one would join on those raids anyway. Would be much easier if they had actual rewards.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bungie should open up the other raids for players who didn't play from year 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Rise of Iron is the last thing to come out before Destiny 2 I think they should re-open the raids from year one and two so that players can get semi-end game gear. 

Since you need a fireteam of 6 people to even do it, playing through it solo is out of the question. (Yes I know it is possible but why should we have to do that anyway)

It's like a part of the story that I'l never be able to play because I first got Destiny when Taken King came out, and since the raids are basically useless no one is going to play it.

If they opened up the previous raids so that you could get gear up to 385 in light level, all of those people like me could finish those stories. Or just make it another way to gear up for the final raid so we don't only have to do the strikes all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone give me the link to Ken Bone's question and response? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to find the entire clip and not just his question, everything that pops up is just reactions or memes... Please don't give me any bullshit.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I posted this I didn't know kickass was down, I apparently used one of the bad versions that didn't let you download but you could still search for torrents. Anyway I'l trust your judgement on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help finding Adobe Activator Torrent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 15:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with finding Adobe Activation torrent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 15:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the graphics card? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would pick Black Flag, the game is much bigger than either of the Metro games and the story and gameplay seem more fun to be honest. Metro is more of a fps game so it really hinges on what you prefer. Both of the games are great and have an awesome story and gameplay but I think that out of the two choices, Black Flag is the better one :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
