<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many people go to the beach around here that GR seems to empty out on a hot weekend.  That said, my dad taught in the inner city and had students who'd never been to the beach (we're a half hour's drive away). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In response to OP's question: this comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American as an English-language demonym [originated in the UK when we were still colonies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_\(word\)).  Back then people referred to themselves as Virginians, etc. in the colonies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, when they blame *us* for our demonym being "America." Bonus points if they call it arrogant.  The *Brits* started calling the colonists that before the Revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Kolaches

This makes me wonder: are Pczki a Michigan and Chicagoland thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget thirsty cows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  See above :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. That's the case in some towns around here, too, and it was like 6 P.M. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round here "fish fry" is a lent thing that Catholic churches and social halls do, and "fish specials" are what the restaurants call it. And yes, in recent years there's been a trend away from fried fish in restaurants that do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, look, Dutch jokes are a Michigan thing, too! The more you know.

Yes, Western Michigan is home to the largest concentration of people of Dutch descent outside the Netherlands.  This is a tightly-knit community that until surprisingly recently still had a first-or-second generation minority immigrant mentality.  The most common stereotype for these people is that they're cheap.  A big piece of that culture is Calvinism, which calls for a simple, non-materialistic life.  A lot of them have farming in their roots, too, and the depression mentality hasn't quite worn off.

I'm a seventh-generation member of this community and I'm one-sixteenth bohemian.  Think about that for a second.  Some part of my family's been in West Michigan for over *150 years* and I'm still 15/16 Frisian in descent.  This is part of the reason the community gets ragged on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to buy liquor on Sunday in South Bend once (Michigan has minimum price laws).  The cashier at Kroger acted as if I'd just brandished a weapon or something.  "SIR YOU CANNOT BUY THAT SCOTCH TODAY." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *TEN* cents, baby!  This one works for me, too.  Going to a state that just chucks them and seeing them all over the ground seems so very off...if that happens here some Dutch or homeless person will pick it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of polish immigrants out here.  Fish specials on Friday are a Catholic thing, no? They're common here too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, No Doubt made that popular out this way for about twenty seconds.  I had no idea people still said it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people in Michigan *do* learn to swim.  We have almost as many lakes as Minnesota and we're *two* peninsulas.  We have a longer coast than you, to boot, though I doubt you'd want to swim along some of it.  

Edit: especially almost half the year.  Brr.

Also, who the hell just downvoted my comments? Have some mirth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...what?!

Everyone knows you put *more meat*, preferably in sauce form, and cheese on a hot dog.

Signed,

Someone on the way to congestive heart failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan here.  I doubt that last part applies to here.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local produce, especially going to the farmer's market instead of the produce section in the summer.  It's been growing for a few years now but back when I was in college (whippersnappers, all of you) it felt like I explained what a farmer's market was way too many times.  I tried to go to one in suburban Chicago last year and it was mostly expensive arts/crafts, soap, and the like.  Where was all the fruit?

I should probably point out this may be more of a West Michigan thing than an all-Michigan thing.  I had a coworker move from Saginaw who had no idea that Michigan grows strawberries.

Also: I'll call it Pop if I want to, dammit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Tom Cruise~~ Vaporeon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, [the FAQ](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonGo/wiki/faq). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a young person tell me recently that they thought "ringing something up" was related to "bling." I kid you not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't see how this is /r/cringe material.


^(I had to.  Don't hate me please.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking, "but there was one for the RNC earli...never mind." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many others have made very good points, but I wanted to add that the US is so big that we also have tons of names from outside English, and many of those follow the same patterns.

We have [a lot of French names](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_place_names_of_French_origin_in_the_United_States), especially here in Michigan--Detroit is named after its river, *le dtroit du lac ri,* "Lake Erie's strait".  Even Grand Rapids has a French name, both words just happen to be [cognates](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cognate) (Same with Lake Superior and dozens more).  

Other places have [Spanish names](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_place_names_of_Spanish_origin_in_the_United_States), and every state has lots of [local native names](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_place_names_in_the_United_States_of_Native_American_origin).  Chicago is famously a bad French pronunciation of a Miami-Illinois word meaning "wild onion," and Lake Michigan's name in Ojibwa is *mishigamaa*.

Then of course there's [Lake Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lake_Chaubunagungamaug).  On second thought, let's not go there.  It's a silly place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My city's largest suburb is Wyoming, Michigan (oddly not named for the state), and there's an unicorporated town named Alaska in our metro.  Kalamazoo has a suburb named Texas (township). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alas, that isn't always true. Our shared neighbor has [four towns names Springfield](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Springfield,_Wisconsin) for some reason.

Edit: Just discovered that there are [250 Washington Townships](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Washington_Township) in the US.  250. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you need to ask yourself *why* you're arguing it's comparable.  If X did 1,000,000 bad things and Y did 1,005,000, does X's track record affect Y's at all?  Both were bastards, and the topic at hand here is the Chinese and Japanese, not the Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they do! But also, don't forget boats can [exit via Chicago](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Illinois_Waterway). Still, better to be able to control both ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 03:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude tweeted [a whole minute ago](https://twitter.com/HIDEO_KOJIMA_EN/status/756299636298702849)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 03:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.09 meters rounds up to...4 feet (It's 3'7", but do play along). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 03:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is a Pokestop](http://www.panoramio.com/photo/38049647) on the campus of my alma mater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 03:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um...[what](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Megabyte)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 03:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to go deeper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 03:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are your newest ones.

It's in the FAQ, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 02:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the Marketplace.  [Medicaid can be applied for at any time](https://www.healthcare.gov/glossary/open-enrollment-period/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The CDC keeps track of this stuff pretty closely](http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/access-to-health-care.htm).  Data from the [National Health Interview Survey](http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/databriefs/db208.htm) shows that a lot of the assertions being made here are at least weaker than they seem when filtered through people's personal anger on the subject.

[Here's a report made for my state government](http://www.rockinst.org/ACA/states/Michigan/2014-12-Michigan_Baseline_Report.pdf) (PDF Warning) which calls it a mixed bag but does say it's helping people (then goes on to point out problems like yours) Look at section 4.1.

Finally, I work in a low-income health center.  I know this is basically anecdotal, too, but we have a ton of patients (I can think of at least 50) who were in critical health but are now on the mend because we were able to get them insurance and then see them.  These people were going to the ER 3-4 times a year, now they have a doctor.

And I'm not saying you would (how would I know?) but just in case: please don't go all "CDC has a bias" on me.  I've already been downvoted in this thread for linking to them.  It's their job to get this stuff right.  And I'll remind you Michigan has a Republican governor and legislature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal poverty level for a family of **eight** is $40k this year.  I suspect you've been given some bad information there.  If you truly have no income then you are at 0% FPL and should qualify for Medicaid regardless of where in the US you live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you spoken with a navigator? You aren't supposed to be required to pay more than 9.5% of your income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying I disagree with you, but you just advocated anecdotal evidence over empirical.  Just saying.

I work in a low income medical clinic.  These policies are, in fact, helping people.  I'm stunned at how much misinformation is in this thread.

I'm sorry for your situation--I really am.  But you are not 300 million people.  You aren't qualified to say it's helping no one.

And FYI, the deductible and the fees you describe go to the doctor, not the insurance company.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try again now.  Medicaid generally only counts whether you had income high enough in the last thirty days.

EDIT: -1 for stating a verifiable fact.  Never change, Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To an ethics-agnostic corporation that's the same thing.  It's the same reason (WAY off topic and less important) Disney just canned their Infinity line.  It's not that it wasn't making money, it just wasn't meeting projections, so Disney took that as *losing* money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obamacare is not an entity that pays people.  What are you talking about (no, seriously, can I get a link)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and all the comments in here are SOOOOO positive.  Upvotes != agreement, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting.  Can't say as I've ever been accused of obfuscating my political leanings before.  Wouldn't be commenting so much in this thread if it were the case.

I went back and edited out a particularly bitter sounding part of my comment. I apologize for making it.

I think you need to take a step back and realize that this is far more than red team vs blue team.  Democrats and Republicans are not natural enemies, and most who say otherwise have something to gain from there being a fight.

As for me, I'm not some slithering snake come to whisper in your ear about the goodness of social programs.  What I am is someone who has to work with the ACA--both its good and bad parts--every day, so I'm plenty sick of all of the misinformation and bickering.  It makes my job that much harder.  It also makes the ACA's problems that much harder to fix.

Seriously, take a step back and look at how you sound.  Then go out and smell a flower or something.  This kind of vitriol isn't doing anyone, especially you, any good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it twice already in this thread, so I feel like a shill, but [find a navigator](https://localhelp.healthcare.gov/#intro). They will probably be able to help, and it's free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also can't cut you off if you've spent an arbitrary amount of their money and have to cover certain things they didn't before.  And people are getting access to care that didn't have a snowball's chance earlier. I'm not saying it's anywhere near perfect but it's a mixed bag at worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I get some sourcing on these profits? I'm genuinely interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're talking right past me. I'm not a Democrat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because the state got in the business doesn't mean the other options evaporated.  That's not a monopoly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please, you worded it in a way that could easily be taken as a snarky assertion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, a plan [based on something created by a conservative think tank](http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2010/apr/01/barack-obama/obama-says-heritage-foundation-source-health-excha/), first put in place by a republican governor, and modified for national use, then opposed by the republicans...is something the liberals made? 

Edit: removed an unnecessary low blow. The point stands that this is not something that only liberals had a hand in. That's a well established fact, no amount of downvotes will change that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you [looked for a navigator in your area](https://localhelp.healthcare.gov/#intro)? They might be able to set you up with cost-neutral insurance through the marketplace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude...Medicaid is the closest thing we have to a single payer system.  It's taxpayer funded.  When it expanded it started paying out more.  Where is the profit coming from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My clinic is still taking new patients (Michigan).  Where is this two hour drive happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess who was subsidizing this practice?  You.  Long-term, the idea is that if the burden is shifted to the federal government (Medicaid), your costs will go down.  Two years isn't long term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who do you think was paying for those bills to be forgiven? Medicaid expansion was meant to help this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [data does not support your claim](http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/databriefs/db208.htm). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The CDC has tons of data on this](http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/access-to-health-care.htm).

EDIT: YAY Downvotes for providing a resource to well-researched information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your "only answer" is [simply, factually incorrect](http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/databriefs/db208.htm).

The consolidation and loss of smaller hospitals is a symptom of a larger and older problem the ACA is meant to allay, not one that was caused by it.  For instance, [hospitals in states that did not expand Medicaid are worse off in this measurement](http://www.beckershospitalreview.com/finance/the-rural-hospital-closure-crisis-15-key-findings-and-trends.html) and ones in states that did are better off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're sacrificing rent for insurance, you need to[ find a navigator](https://www.healthcare.gov/glossary/navigator/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a low-income clinic that formerly treated people who had no insurance.  Our patients are better off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your definition of long term is the past two years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a [private apartment construction contractor named Polite](http://www.manta.com/c/mm6jqp6/polite) in Dallas.  I can't find a logo or site for them anywhere, though.  Still looking.  

There's also a sign maker in TX named [Colite](http://www.colite.com/about/), but their logo is all wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last tweet I see there is three days old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 00:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Near the Cheshire Grill, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad the [feds split this one up](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_Tobacco_Company) 105 years ago... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They appear to be some kind of [loyalty stamp](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trading_stamp).  These were tradable stamps, the most prominent being the [S H Stamp program](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/S%26H_Green_Stamps), which predated today's rewards cards.  Probably given out as a premium for a certain number of purchases, in other words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a few years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Japanese do. They have an alternate word for four, *yon*, to be used instead of *shi* depending on context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 02:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio much more conservative than Michigan or Wisconsin? Based on what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kentucky was actually pretty evenly split and tried to stay neutral at the beginning of the Civil War, only officially joining the union after the Confederacy invaded them, at which point Confederacy supporters tried to establish a shadow government in Bowling Green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was thinking western/northern PA up to just-past Buffalo (beyond that it's getting Vermontyer) would ideally be part of this conglomeration.  Economically speaking it makes sense.  Ohio has a LOT of industry overlap with Michigan and Pennsylvania/northern West Virginia.  The fact that so many of us are having to cast wider and wider nets as we think about it is a pretty good indication that none of this will ever happen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a hard time, economically or culturally, accepting a map that doesn't include Toronto in the same region as Buffalo, Cleveland, Detroit, Chicago, and Milwaukee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan is the number 2 ag state, and hardly any of your "most of the food" makes it over here, especially this time of year.  We have a rather large amount of water, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flanagan's *is* a Pokestop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the side of a pickup truck capper, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those buttons? They look like some kind of [potentiometer](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Potentiometer) or cellphone camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any state with Great Lake access would suddenly be the belle of the ball for the same reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it definitely is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan, Ohio, Indiana(?), Illinois, Wisconsin, probably Minnesota.  Chicago or Cleveland for our new capitol (tryna start a fight here).  MAYBE Missouri. Pennsylvania and New York are welcome to come too.  Well, at least Pittsburgh, Buffalo, Rochester and surrounding areas (Anything near the Lakes) are.

This is basically the "Rust Belt." Very similar culture, very similar mix of industry and agriculture.  I can also see a slight chance of Michigan, Wisconsin, northern New York and Minnesota joining Canada, Minnesota and Missouri joining the Plains states, and Indiana not wanting anything to do with its more liberal neighbors.

Missouri depends on Kansas City's vote. I think St. Louis would rather go with Illinois judging solely by my St. Louis aunt and uncle's views, but KC also has strong industrial ties to Detroit and Chicago.

Trash talking aside, the Southeast part of Michigan has way too much in common with Ohio to leave them behind.  We are also so close with Ontario that I can't rule out the possibility of us trying to join Canada.  I'm only guessing that could also be the case with the other areas.

If we're talking about parts of states (and we really should be), I have a hard time believing my part (West) of Michigan would want to economically separate from either Detroit or Chicago.  Forced to choose, though, it'd be Chicago all the way.  If states split, Northwest Indiana becomes part of Illinois for the same reason (it's already suburban Chicago).  Northwestern New York and Pittsburgh are Rust Belt areas, too.  Hard to say where  they'd go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a simple proximity sensor.  That was the case in a rental (Suzuki Kizashi, surprisingly good little car) I had recently.

EDIT: Found it.  It's actually an low frequency RF sensor which uses signal strength (like a WiFi radio does when it shows you bars) to determine where the fob is in relation to the antenna.  [Wikipedia link](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smart_key#Inside_Outside_detection). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are your newest ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An American flag flying in heavy wind is a symbol of liberty trying to liberate itself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just a thing someone did once in a post, and it caught on.  [Here's an article](http://www.dailydot.com/unclick/banana-for-scale-meme-history/) claiming one thing, [here's another time someone asked on this sub where the replies claimed another](https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/1qyxuq/whats_the_deal_with_using_a_banana_for_scale/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 02:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is a slippery slope argument, wherein while one race was an existential threat that would not be negotiated with, the others weren't, and this was the creation of one man or a small group of people whose actions clearly horrified our normal characters.

Also, for what it's worth, they *didn't* wipe out the Founders, Bashir found a cure and Odo brought it to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 05:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says it's between Meadow and Glad Valley, SD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 02:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish there were an /r/theydidthemap, because I'd be all over that. I[ overlayed the image with a mosaic Google Maps search of the McDonaldses in the area just to see if I could.](http://imgur.com/a/2SIQl) Now obviously there's something off with my aspect ratio/projection compared with the image, but I did the best I could.  The red dots are Mcdonalds stores I found, the blue circle in the second image is Duluth, and the green line in the first is the shoreline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
