<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8089</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went through an extremely crunchy hippie phase, during which probably the silliest thing I tried was a [crystal deodorant stone.](http://www.thedreamlounge.net/wp-content/uploads/2012/01/DEO-STONE.jpg)

What I was forced to admit after awhile is that the only thing that happens when you use the stone is that you end up with a semi-interesting looking stone that smells like armpit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah.

That drink/shot (it comes in both forms) plus peach schnapps is called a 'redheaded slut'.  Being one myself, I *desperately* wanted to love it, and tried many, many times to convince myself that I did.

Uh-uh.  Jagermeister is just plain wretched, no matter what you do to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut, wut?

Moved to Allegany 2 years ago after living in PG for 20 years and raising my family there.  Probably moving home in a couple of months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome!  This is actually a pretty great place to be, and we need as many like-minded people as possible to move in and fill out some of our congressional districts.

Let me know if you'd like a personalized relocation guide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hogan knows that Allegany, Garrett, and a couple of Eastern Shore counties will have their knickers in a twist over this.  But he also knows that the entire rest of the state, including Frederick Co at this point, would *destroy* him at reelection time if he allowed PP to go under here in Maryland.

His heart and ideology may be closer to the national Republican party platform, but Hogan is nothing if not a pragmatist.  And he's well aware of what state he's governing, even if he doesn't always agree.

source:  lifelong Maryland resident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the way out in Allegany here!  Way to keep the Free State free! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know no one takes anything Omarosa says seriously (or is it literally? I forget which one is the "right" way to interpret the things this administration says), but is anyone surprised by this type of political targeting when [she warned us during the *election* that he was compiling an enemies list](http://ijr.com/2016/11/732006-omarosa-republicans-who-vote-against-donald-trump-will-be-put-on-a-list/)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you're breaking my heart!

These are *indeed* a delicacy.  They are highly prized by many cuisines for their unusually meaty texture and intense, savory flavor.  One dialect of Chinese refers to them as "hen-of-the-woods" because they make an excellent replacement for chicken in virtually any dish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not an accident.  Trump and his cronies have been waging a deliberate full frontal assault on the very concept of a free, strong, **adversarial** press, something that is so fundamental to our democracy that it is enshrined within the First Amendment.  His intent is to utterly discredit even those media outlets that, while admittedly imperfect, have faithfully served the American and global public.

It is hard to identify the most sinister consequence of his attack on democratic institutions, but if I had to pick only one, it would be his intentional dismantling of the free press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really only helps us if it's a small passenger plane -- like an old DC-10, maybe -- so that Pence can be riding alongside him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad trash panda   :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa!

OK, all I'm going to say is that I've retyped my comment 6 times and I still can't manage to make it devoid of innuendo.

I am very envious of your dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An image worthy of the master of surrealism.  The man was a work of art in and of himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost any Billy Joel tune could be a conceivably correct answer here, I think.  The one that sprang to my mind was "Angry Young Man" -- that long intro is mesmerizing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Sqwunched (yes, it's a word now) in the middle is by far the best place to be...the ultimate "nice work if you can get it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David K. Shipler is one of my favorite non-fiction writers.  His books on civil liberties (especially the 4th Amendment), *The Rights of the People: How Our Search for Safety Invades Our Liberties*, and *Rights at Risk: The Limits of Liberty in Today's America* were favorites of mine.  He is also rightly known for *The Working Poor: Invisible in America*.

On a similar topic, Barbara Ehrenreich's *Nickel and Dimed: On (Not) Getting By in America* was an excellent portrait of what it really looks like to be working poor in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arugura! Yum! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm certain he did...his mommy never thought anyone was good enough for her baby boy (he was the youngest of 4) and she said all sorts of vile, far more unflattering things than that about *me* -- anything she could think of, really -- over the course of the 19 years that her son was abusing me.  So yeah, he probably did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The printing on the sign is very faint...I don't know if you can make it out. But as a former longtime employee of the state agency referred to on this street sign, I think the descriptive bumper sticker slapped on there should be of great help to you in deciphering the answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~"Statue of limitations"~~  "Statute of limitations"

~~"On accident"~~  "By accident"

~~"expresso"~~  "espresso" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved from a huge eastern seaboard city to a tiny "city" in Appalachia 2 years ago.

I can't get any motherfucking ph, or Ethiopian food, or any goddamn curry, or Salvadoran pupusas...basically I can't get anything at a restaurant that isn't white bread and mayonnaise-based, and probably deep fried. 

I'm only a little bit kidding when I say it is a big part of the reason I'm moving back home when I graduate in May. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't marry that one.  He's too damaged."

I should have listened.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh.  Add that to the list of things that makes me feel old this week.  Considering that the first Simpsons shorts ran on the Tracy Ullman show in 1987 and I remember them clearly, yes...episodes from 2006 actually *are* newer episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely get that.  In the early '90s, though, the thing everyone was focused on was how much water, land, and energy it takes to produce 1lb of meat compared with 1lb of plant-based food.  Seafood was seen as less of a drain on these resources (when considering a very narrow, particular set of factors). I recall being dimly aware of overfishing as a potential concern, but it just wasn't a front-burner issue at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty long loop...I'm only remembering the ones that made me choke on my salad:

"Caress Me Down"  ~Sublime

"Crazy Bitch"  ~Buck Cherry

"Semi-Charmed Life"  ~Third Eye Blind

"Sex   Candy"  ~Marcy Playground

"Give it Away"  ~Red Hot Chili Peppers

I think they only get away with it because the people eating in there are either young enough to have grown up listening to all of those songs, or over 80 and unable to hear the lyrics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've given this answer previously, so apologies if you've heard the story:

 The first stumble off the wagon was when I got pregnant at age 20 and I had intense, unfightable cravings for seafood. To say I gave into them would imply a choice in the matter I did not have. When the baby was born, we initially raised him as a pescetarian (vegetarian who also eats seafood).

 When my son was 4, we went to a birthday party for a friend of his. Unlike at previous events, the veggie dogs we had brought with us and thrown on the grill were no longer acceptable to him. All of a sudden, he was acutely aware that the hot dog on his friends' plates was not the same as the one in front of him, and he wasn't having it. In a split second, I decided that this was a battle I wasn't willing to pick...I inherited enough food issues from my parents, and I wasn't willing to sow those seeds with my 4-year old over a frankfurter at a birthday party.

 So my son ate a hot dog, loooved it, and that was the first step down a steep and slippery slope back toward full-fledged omnivorousness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local Ruby Tuesday features a playlist that my son and I have dubbed the "Inappropriate-for-Retail Mix."  It's playing every time we go in there, which leaves me to wonder whether their corporate offices decided on this consciously as a marketing strategy, or whether the manager of this location is just the most futile rebel ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't have waited 19 years.

When I look at how much I've accomplished -- and how much our child has healed -- since you've been removed from our lives, all I can feel is self-rebuke for allowing you to steal our joy and harm us for so long.

I hope someday you'll truly, deeply understand what a wretched  human being you really are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah!  Love your highly relevant username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that! I'd never seen any real exploration of this. It's awfully gratifying to think that my intuition was somewhat accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caught me.  I'm so pale I basically glow in the dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> swoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, nope.  Appalachia, though.  So the *ooold* mountains, not the tall ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question:  Is this true regardless of model year?  For example, in the fantasy world where I have the money for classic cars, I totally own a '64 or a '67 Mustang.  Would owning one of those automatically make me a dick, or do you mean from the "Pinto II" era forward? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what you did, OP, but good job making sure Lief's "problem" is being too much of a snuggle-monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm well aware of their shameless pandering to the LGBTQ community in the 90s.

But as an older queer woman, I gotta tell you -- my recollection is that Subarus were verrry popular with my friend group of women in comfortable shoes way back in the mid-'80s, well before that ad campaign.  My sense has always been that Subaru picked up on an existing phenomenon rather than manufacturing it, and that this stereotype is actually rooted in a *kernel* of truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can disprove this one for you.

My father owned a 1973 metallic gold Super Beetle.  (I'm still a teensy bit salty that he never put it up on blocks to save it for me the way he promised to.)

My former next-door neighbor was a man who owned a silver 2004 VW Beetle.  He was also a very interesting character.  When he moved in, he told us he was an insurance agent, but within 2 weeks, he said he had "resigned" from his job to be a full time gambler in Atlantic City.  Within a couple of months after *that*, he had stopped coming home most of the time, since collection goons had started making unannounced visits to his house at all hours. 

So, my (extremly limited) sample size and experience would indicate that some men do, indeed, drive VW Beetles, but only a very particular, prissy sort of man who is simultaneously narcissistic and self-absorbed, yet unaware of how ridiculous he looks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queer woman who drives a Subaru wagon checking in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not so much "popular,"  more "cult classic," but *Stranger in a Strange Land* is pretty badly written and absolutely ***horribly*** edited.  It is full of misspellings, incorrect usage, omitted/wrong punctuation, poor sentence structure, and on and on. It is distractingly bad. 

(Not to mention that despite being able to tell a hell of a story, Heinlein was a total whackjob.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Argentinean tortillas](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/600x315/f7/73/f8/f773f88924b41ee10ca1bd166f6c17c3.jpg) (or "bizcochos," depending on where in the country you're from) -- which are **not** at all what Americans tend to think of when they hear "tortilla."

Rather, they are a flaky, many-layered savory bread that is much more akin to an American southern-style biscuit, complete with buttery layers that peel apart.  Warm them over a low burner and eat plain, with dulce de leche, or literally *anything*.  *So, so* good.

Actually, if I'm being honest, it's most Argentinean baked goods...the sweet ones like piononos, medialunas, and alfajores as well as other delicacies like empanadas of all flavors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of this assumes you are car camping rather than backpacking. I was vegetarian, but not vegan, for a longish time, so here's what I remember.

Foil pouches are your friend.  Fill with veggies of your choice, season, and grill.

Things that are particularly excellent this way are asparagus, mushrooms, summer squash, onions, bell peppers, artichokes (make sure they're small), and corn on the cob.

Vegetarian baked beans and tofu dogs feels like camping food.

Veggie chili and cornbread is always good...you have an iron skillet, right?

One of my favorite things was making falafel [(from a dry mix like this)](https://thetab.com/uploads/2016/03/IMG_3624-e1458523656153-640x853.jpg) pita sandwiches with onion, tomato, and tahini.

And then I did a quick google.  I can't vouch for the recipes in the following links, as I haven't tried them, but here are ["14 Outrageously Good Vegan Campfire Recipes"](http://www.theflamingvegan.com/view-post/12-Great-Vegan-Campfire-Recipes) and several different ideas for ["Vegan Campfire Food"](http://veganstreet.com/vegancampfirefood.html) and the [Happy Herbivore's suggestions for planning vegan camping trips.](https://happyherbivore.com/2013/06/plant-based-vegan-camping-trip-outdoor-cooking/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too live with [an adorable dishwasher kitten](http://imgur.com/a/KjojR) but I can't find the one of him hiding in the back the way Nomi is doing.

Well, actually, now he's an enormously fat dishwasher cat.  But his instant, fervent love for the dishwasher hasn't faded one bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. To what do you attribute the virulent strain of anti-intellectualism currently on display on the world stage and what do we do about it?

2. Since you brought it up (and mine is coming up in the next few months), how *should* one celebrate their 42nd birthday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the spirit!!!  You got this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My *kid* is going to reach the legal drinking age in less than a year.

My 25th high school reunion is scheduled for 2018. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a chick...one who will gladly fist bump you over boozy coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' casual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And whatever you do, do *not* get duped by his diploma-mill cousins, Dr. Perky or Dr. Thunder!

EDIT:  Your username is 2 years old.  How long have you been waiting to make this comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tea is not "technically anything."

Tea is specifically a beverage made from an hot water and cured leaves of the plant *Camellia sinensis*, an evergreen shrub native to Asia.

The word is often misused, as in the phrase "herbal tea," but this is not correct.  Properly, a beverage made from other (not tea) leaves and hot water is an *infusion* or if you are French, a *tisane*.

Coffee, however, cannot be tea.  Technically, it too, is an infusion -- one with its own unique name:  coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so torn.  I think mine is actually coffee, but it *might* be Honest Tea Moroccan Mint iced (green) tea.  It's somehow *more* refreshing than ice water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm.  OK, I get that. As a former bartender, I feel obligated to find an alcoholic coffee solution that will work for you.  What spirits do you like?  Do you sweeten your iced coffee?

EDIT:  Amaretto or Frangelico would both be delicious in iced coffee with soy milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Irish coffee. Or Mexican coffee.  Or Spanish coffee...

Problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy, kindred spirit!  Fellow ginjew checking in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I should clarify that while I was raised in a very observant household and went to private religious school from nursery school through 7th grade, I no longer practice, and haven't in some time.

Yes, the Torah contains admonishments against same-sex activity, as does the New Testament and the Quran, but there are plenty of LGBTQ Christians and yes, even Muslims.

Furthermore, there are 3 main branches of American Judaism:  Orthodox, Conservative, and Reform.  The official stance of reform Judaism is extremely welcoming of LGBTQ individuals and that of Conservative Judaism only somewhat less so.  It's really only Orthodox congregations (at least in the U.S.) that are intolerant toward LGBTQ people.

I'll also point out that the Torah contains a several dozen prohibitions against consuming food considered to be unclean or even "an abomination" -- the exact same language used to describe men having sex with men -- but a whole lot of Jews don't keep kosher, either.  They're still Jewish, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, dude!

And as a girl who only sleeps with other girls, I have to agree...Jim Halpert *is* pretty cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf, we kind of rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's terrifying having no income, but I just keep telling myself that in 8 weeks, I can work again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the same kind I worked with, evidently...because he did *not* use a napkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being an excellent writer.  For me, a person's sexiest attribute is their brain.  If they not only have interesting thoughts, but can also express those thoughts in writing in a coherent, intelligent way, I can become smitten pretty easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked in a call center with a guy who not only brought a whole rotisserie chicken for lunch, but who opened it up at his desk and started chowing down on it...at his teeny, tiny cubicle desk -- while logged in to the phone line as "ready" to take calls.

No carving knife -- just tearing at it like a wild animal with his grubby, greasy hands -- that he also used to type call notes with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My rabbi.

Rumors started circulating within the congregation when I was 4.   This was 1979 and it was about the juiciest gossip the sisterhood ladies had ever gotten their claws into.  Within a couple of short months, he had been forced out of his position.

It broke my heart because I *adored* our rabbi; he was one of the warmest, kindest adults I knew as a child.  All's well that ends well, I suppose.  Not long after that, he helped to establish one of the first and most successful synagogues for LGBTQ Jews and their families.  It turned out to be a hidden blessing, if you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked a full-time job, a seasonal weekend job, and went to school full time for 7 semesters in a row -- until this (my final) semester when I hit a wall.

I kept it up because I had to.  I didn't have a choice.  I went back to school after my ex and I separated because I had a teenage son to take care of, but my salary wasn't making ends meet and I had reached a point in my career where I couldn't get promoted without a degree.

So, I did what I believe is technically known as "humping it" for 3 years.  The first 2 years, I took as many online classes as I could because I was still working a regular 8:30 - 5:00 schedule.  I got up in the morning, worked all day, sometimes went to an evening class, and then went home and did homework or studied for at least 2-3 hours.  Some nights, I cooked dinner.  Other nights, especially if I had class, my teenager did.

Then, when I transferred from my community college to a 4-year school, I moved and took a different (even lower-paying) job that gave me the flexibility to work weird hours around my classes.  That was important because my new school had far fewer online options than my CC did, but I knew that going in and wanted the classroom experience.

This is my last semester; I am scheduled to graduate in May.  At the beginning of this semester -- about 2 weeks in, I realized that even though I have done it so many times before, I just couldn't keep all those plates spinning any longer.  I woke up in a cold sweat at 3:30 one morning, sick with the knowledge that I couldn't keep working and successfully complete the 18 credits I'm taking -- all of which I need for graduation.  At this point, being sooo close to done, failure is simply not an option.  So I resigned from my job and I took a tiny student loan to pay the remainder of my living expenses for the next 8 weeks or so until I can go back to work--any work.

Also, caffeine.  Lots and lots of caffeine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My spectacularly awesome cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've told my story before on other subs, but not here, I don't think.  Apologies if you've heard it previously, but this is a question I always answer when asked.  The following is from a previous post:


 My son was 15 months old when I found out I was pregnant for the 2nd time. My extremely abusive now-ex and I were badly on the rocks (as we would continue to be for most of the next 16 years) and about to get evicted from our apartment. I was still in the grips of severe post-partum depression, and really struggling to take care of myself and my baby.

 Having another child at that point would have been the absolute worst thing I could've done for myself and the child I already had brought into this world...not to mention the one that would be born. I didn't have enough money to provide well for the one I had...how could I do right by 2 of them? I was barely holding on in terms of my mental health day-to-day...if I pushed the reset button on nonstop diaper changing and sleep deprivation was I really going to be able to to hold on, let alone be the kind of mother I wanted to be?

 I don't care how people think this sounds: That abortion was the best thing that ever happened to me and to my son. I have no doubt that it prevented me from deteriorating into either suicide or commitment to a mental health treatment facility. I was terrified before the procedure that I would never forgive myself and that I would always have guilt about it. Instead, I felt instantly better as soon as the procedure was over, and I have never once regretted it.

 19 years later, I am more certain today than I was then that having that abortion saved my life and my son's life in a very real way. I had no car, no driver's license, no family support structure, no health insurance, no money, no paid time off, and a shitty wage-slave job that wouldn't have thought twice about firing me for missing work to accommodate a waiting period or multiple clinic visits.  My ability to easily, safely, and relatively affordably access that procedure using public transportation and about a week's rent was the difference between me and my son having a shot at a decent life and me leaving behind 2 young children to be raised in the system, or worse, by their abusive, dangerously mentally ill father.  I am more than happy that I had it; I am profoundly grateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no, no...

Not your birthday, [your **cake** day](https://www.redditcakeday.com/); that is, the anniversary of the day you created your reddit username.  Do you see the little icon next to your username in your comments today?  That's what that's about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the whole thing.  My heart is breaking for you.  I cannot even begin to imagine the complicated jumble of emotions that you must be experiencing right now. Thank you so much for trusting us enough to share all of that.

I know it probably doesn't mean much right now, and I don't know you at all, but just watching that video tells me that you are a pretty extraordinary person and that you likely have many, many special, meaningful moments and experiences yet to come in your life.  I'm genuinely sorry you were denied this one, though, in a way that must be so bitterly disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you for that pun.  Here's your upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their birthday is your cake day!

Congrats to you and your adorable kids! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know her as the author of *Heather has Two Mommies*, so I did a quick google, and holy crap!

How did I (as an older, Jewish queer woman) completely miss her entire body of work for adults?  Based on their blurbs, it looks like I need to start with *Good Enough to Eat* and *Jailbait*.

Thank you sooo much! I don't know if my classmate will use these recommendations, but I certainly will! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live with a panther now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 41, so I grew up on vinyl records and cassette tapes.  My parents were huge audiophiles, so maybe I learned to listen to albums as whole works because of their understanding of how they tell stories, or maybe it was just because the technology we were using was so much less conducive to to picking and choosing songs.  Picking up and putting down the needle all the time to skip songs on a record was frowned on in my house, and in later years I came to hate playing the rewind/fast forward game with cassette tapes quite a lot.

When CDs became a thing, it was one of the most exciting things that had ever happened to me, because now you could just pick the track you wanted to listen to...or even--gasp!--play the tracks on random.

Then mp3s became the format of choice and you didn't even have to buy the whole album anymore at all.

Somewhere in this glut of musical freedom, I forgot about listening to whole albums.  And it seems like a lot of other people did, too.

What's interesting to me, though, is that I don't think you're alone in rediscovering the joy of listening to an album from start to finish.  Just last week, my 20-year-old son said to me offhandedly, "Y'know, I just figured out how listening to a whole album works.  I never really understood there could be connections between all of the songs that way.  It's awesome."

He's right, and so are you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, yes.  I know and loved this one, too, but forgot to mention it today! Good lookin' out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the written works (fiction or non-fiction) that have most strongly resonated with you as a woman who loves women, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a non-traditional college student at a small state school in a very rural, very red area.

Today, I got into a conversation with a (much younger) classmate of mine and we meandered onto on the subject of LGBTQ literature.  She, like many people I've met since moving here, grew up with a much bigger dose of compulsory heterosexuality than I did and she really hasn't been exposed to writing during her adolescent years that has spoken to her as a wlw.

I started sharing the names of authors, books, and other publications I "grew up on," but I was a teen in the late '80s through mid-'90s, so the names that spring to my mind are Audre Lorde, Joanna Russ, and Adrienne Rich...and magazines like "On Our Backs."

While I mentioned these (and many other) works to her, I can't help but feel that much of what was so meaningful to me 25+ years ago may not have the same impact on her.

So, raptors, if I could share them all with her: What books or other written works have meant the most to you as a woman who loves women?  What made them special to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bradley Nowell of Sublime being alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
