<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also order it from the Google store.

https://store.google.com/product/pixel_phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fond a lot of things google image searching for "blush eggplant and gold wedding" and "blush plum and gold wedding" - almost all the wedding inspo I see has very specific fancy color names so try things along those lines. :) I'm sure many of these are not what you're looking for, but you might be able to find some gems, or send to your florist to say "like this, but with less purple and more blush". Or try adding in some additional search terms about your wedding like "elegant" or "rustic".

My sister's wedding colors are dusty blue and cranberry with pops of light pink and gold, for an outdoor garden wedding next September. She started off with a few colors in mind that felt very garden-y (blush, dusty blue, and sage) and then eliminated blush because we're too pale to look good in it and sage because the whole garden will be green and she wanted some contrast. It was mostly pinterest-ing that led to the cranberry combo.

Some of her pins that give a good sense: [1](http://o.aolcdn.com/smp/is/submissions/uploads/91176/54a6da5a404d0$!x900.jpg) [2](http://o.aolcdn.com/smp/is/submissions/uploads/104524/54f8a1e551d0e$!x900.jpg) [3](https://agneswrightdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/01/oct-22nd.jpg) [4](http://www.thebridelink.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Fall-wedding-colors.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do actually vote Naya! But you have to make sure you love it and feel comfortable in it.

For what it's worth, I went to a bunch of dress shopping appointments with my sister (she's the bride to be) and we're just definitely not the emotional crying types. I absolutely love the dress she chose, but no one in our family was going to cry about it. 

Also, I took tons of pictures each time we went dress shopping and she frequently would love dresses more/less after the fact based on the photos, which might be how you're feeling now. She thought she loved a particular dress, then didn't love the photos after the fact, but couldn't get over another dress she had tried on - she ended up going back for that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol Trump doesn't understand this question AT ALL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary is CRUSHING it with that response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here it comes... he's already getting ready to contest the elections results because "the media". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "wrong" returns... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ".... Thank you sir" Hahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably notes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No YOU ARE. 

Oh my god Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary is coming out strong and calm tonight, this is exactly what she needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds amazing! Honestly more casual BBQ and a live band basically describes my dream wedding. I've always kind of envisioned flipping burgers in a backyard in my wedding dress, hah! Make sure people know that you don't feel like you're compromising, you have no desire for a fancier wedding, and this is what will make you happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New last name is Decker. Best I could do was \#ToDeckerForever or \#HappilyDeckerAfter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vote #1! That fit is incredible on you! The second is beautiful and elegant but I feel like it swallows you a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is so helpful! I'm in the process of planning my sister's destination bachelorette for next summer so it really helps to hear feedback from the other side of things.

I'm definitely worried about the Airbnb situation - I won't want to wait too long to book it because we need a pretty big house and I want to make sure we get something nice. If I only factor in the "definite yeses" I might end up with a house that's too small, whereas factoring in too many people could lead to exactly what you described... the things that keep me up at night!

Also totally struggling with the communication. I lean towards being an over-communicator, as does my sister, but some of the girls have been pretty silent so far - I'd be more worried except my sister tells me some of them are ALWAYS like this and apparently there are people in the world who don't really check email all the time?!?

Glad to hear pole dancing class was fun - that's on our itinerary as well! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skogafoss Waterfall, Iceland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I think his feet probably hurt and he was shifting his weight trying to relieve that... but like, it's a chair. Just sit down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 05:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Normally I get a kick out of Hillary's amused smile during dumb answers, but when he said that she actually looked disturbed. Wish she had brought it up. There is a really good reason the best military minds in the US haven't decided that "sneak attacks" are the way to defeat ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curried sweet potato soup is one of my favorites! I actually just made a batch this week based on [this recipe](http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/food-network-kitchens/curried-sweet-potato-apple-soup-recipe.html) with a couple small changes - used regular apples with skin on instead of applesauce, added a can of white beans for protein, and added some dijon mustard for flavor (just trust me). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just cook everything ahead of time and microwave it quickly to reheat it? If you were my coworker I'd probably hate you for using the microwave for 10+ minutes at lunchtime too, to be honest.

If you're eating almost the same foods every day anyway, your life becomes much easier if you just prepare several days worth at a time (a la /r/mealprep), package them into individual tupperwares, and reheat when you get there. No need to cook chicken and broccoli every single night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, I fuck up math all the time! I was just hoping you found some secretly wonderful low cal coconut milk or something... TBH 510 filling calories for dinner is probably completely fine for a lot of people.

If I only used one can of coconut milk and maybe added some more curry paste and some chicken broth instead, do you think it would be terrible? Because that could maybe work for me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure about that calorie count? I really really want to re-create this because massaman curry is one of my favorite foods ever, but I'm pasting the ingredients into MFP and coming out much higher...

Unless I've gone completely mad, 2lbs of raw chicken breast is already just a bit under 1000 calories, which would be 200 each for 5 portions. And the nutrition info I've found for light coconut milk comes out to around 300 a can.. Am I missing something? I just got so excited for low cal curry, and then so sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curried squash soup! It's AMAZING. I've seen/made multiple versions, but [here's one example](http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/ellie-krieger/curried-butternut-squash-soup-recipe.html) that lists it as 295 calories per serving/4 servings total.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 18:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you put it on a credit card and pay it off/down once you start getting paid?

It's not ideal, but credit cards are great for emergencies and your dog really needs to go to the vet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catnap blep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm of the opinion that few people actually choose their careers (namely, people who go to medical/dental/law school, and then do that line of work forever) and most people just sort of accidentally fall into them - which isn't a bad thing. Choosing a job is not the same thing as choosing your career.

I was a psych major who had no idea what I wanted to do with my life. Through what I like to call "a series of fortunate events" I worked my way up from a temp IT employee to a software pre-sales consultant. I didn't even really know this was a career that existed, but I love it. I still don't necessarily consider it to be my "career" because I might decide to do something different 5 years from now.

My dad runs those inmate work programs (mostly overseeing them manufacturing furniture and such), and before that worked for a company that manufactured ingredients that go in things like salad dressing and dog food. I'm pretty positive he didn't grow up saying "I want to make salad dressing preservatives when I grow up", but he LOVED both of those jobs.

My advice is to talk to a doctor about getting your anxiety under control, and stop thinking about a job as your final destination. Instead think of it as a way to learn something, make some money, and be a stepping stone to another job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final two women are closet lesbians and choose each other instead of Nick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha that awkward stand up and wave... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jared's fake tan right now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which release are you in? You can disable state flows entirely under Configuration for the application, but I can't remember when that option was added...

https://docs.servicenow.com/bundle/helsinki-service-management-for-the-enterprise/page/product/planning-and-policy/concept/c_ImpDsblStFl.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely a rat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 15:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a documentary on Netflix that follows people taking the MS exam. Pretty interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the company. Some places set aggressive quotas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mutually beneficial, typically. You get a discount, they get closer to reaching their quota. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 01:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah having plenty of sunlight made it really easy to spend lots of time on the road. I'm not sure I'd want to do it in the dark!

The south coast has more to see and more places to stop right off the ring road. I spent the least amount of time in the northwest area. If I ever make it back I think I'd rent a camper and just do Snaefellsnes and the west fjords, but both take a lot of driving out of your way and are pretty middle-of-nowhere I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent a week in Iceland, but did the ring road the way everyone says not to (very quickly - only 3 real days of driving, but plenty of downtime before/during/after). No regrets, I loved it!

I stayed in hostels/guesthouses, no airb b because I traveled alone and it tends not to be worth it for one person. Sounds great if you're with a group, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 03:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only advice is to not go crazy overthinking the whole trip! There are so many beautiful places/things to see and do, and at some point you just have to accept that you can't see them all - make a general plan and don't look back, you'll have a great time no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of my favorite photos from my Ring Road trip earlier this month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 18:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 21:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to frame this and hang it in my kitchen, but I'm slightly worried it'll push me over into seriously crazy cat lady territory... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Partially undone loaf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 18:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ellipses are different! I only really use punctuation in text messages when necessary to set the tone. 

On a related, slightly geekier note, there was [an article in the NY Times](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/06/10/world/europe/period-full-stop-point-whatever-its-called-millennials-arent-using-it.html?_r=0) recently about how the period is "going out of style" largely due to punctuation-free texting/instant messaging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 18:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like it's not showing up in the additional comments, just showing up in the activity log, which tracks changes in general. If the issue is that users are looking at the assignment group to directly contact them, I would just role restrict the assignment group field to itil users only. That will also prevent end users from being able to see changes in the activity log. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I went through customs they seemed to base it off how much luggage you had. People in front of me with lots of luggage/luggage carts got waved down one hallway, I had a backpack and a purse and got waved directly outside. No one checked a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm... that's also how I text everyone in real life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The max speed limit in Iceland is approximately the same as many highway speed limits in the US (90kph is about 55mph) but you will definitely not have time to do the full ring road in 3 days. The things you mentioned wanting to see are honestly likely out of reach for a short trip. I'd recommend keeping to the south coast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 01:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reykjavik Roasters is great. I also recommend Kaffibrenslan if you're looking for a place to sit and hang out - it has a nice patio in a great location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
