<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul and other teachers were not considered "prophets" by either as far as I understand. I wasn't aware of "minor prophets" from Christianity which are not shared with Islam, are you able to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The circumstances of his death are still subject of debate. There's good evidence to show that he accidentally ingested the cyanide. I'm not saying he wasn't persecuted, but trying to get facts straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adam and Noah too...  
Actually, all of the Christian ones, with one more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single use </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But rain on a biblical scale still no reason not to go to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only dangerous because of the way people drive, it's not inherently dangerous by nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Brit, this confuses me. Not only because it rains 400 days a year there but because we're know to have a stiff upper lip!  
I'd get to work even in a blizzard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except driving in the snow is dangerous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You trying to take over the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the thumbnail I thought this was the Turin Shroud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use that quite a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You kids today are so cute!  
Have you not looked at a full keyboard before? It was used to scroll the whole window rather than moving the cursor up and down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KVM control. Yeah they just though "what button does nobody use?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's purple, it ain't floppy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was hardly "one shot" was it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buoy does this one drive me mad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying that everyone seems to be nervous, and you can see it in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a lovely state of affairs when people are scared when they see police, rather than reassured, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy they took 11 years to find, costing several trillions of dollars, and hundreds of thousands of civilian deaths, so he can be killed with "one shot"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were talking about the effect it'll have in the big picture. Just because it's insignificant, that doesn't make it ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the point. Killing a baby really won't have an effect the big scheme of the human race, doesn't make it ok. The reason because the banks failed is because of dishonesty. So by taking the $20 the. You are no better than them; except you were only given $20, not $20b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [twitch!!](https://youtu.be/om7O0MFkmpw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, searching is online. It just does the maps. It just means you use a lot less data. This doesn't really affect residents, but for people travelling here it's quite useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I didn't notice until now. They used to have it several years ago but then it stopped maybe 2 years ago? Seems they've brought it back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Google Maps now allows you to cache UAE maps offline! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this a "car hack"? This is just common sense/basic knowledge  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filling tyres with nitrogen is a complete scam, especially when you consider that the atmosphere is already 80% nitrogen).  
You will have literally 0 benefit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you left your car alone for 30 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not use a 4G network? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, just the majority, is that different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, was just curious if, despite his objections, the pros outweighed the cons. I too hate this, but still own a phone. I was curious if people actively protested this by not owning a phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not many call themselves the "land of the free" and are under false impression they have complete liberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the translation, maybe others will understand it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does economic nationalism mean?  
Your second paragraph doesn't make sense. You say he doen't blame groups based on ethnic identity. But then the next line doesn't say what he bases it on, only what he's blaming these ethnicities for.  
If you see all Mexicans as rapists, and Chinese as corrupt, and all Muslims as terrorists, then you are just like Hans my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spewed accusations against entire groups of people; Mexicans, Muslims for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you can be jailed indefinitely without triail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually probably more a demonstration of the tyres than the brakes. Brakes can easily lock wheels well before the tyres give up. This is why you have ABS, because the brakes are already way better than the tyres. If you want to stop faster, get better tyres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? If it's not their fault, why would they be punished? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't like the idea of a company having control over something I buy from them

Do you have a mobile phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Fuzz is NOT a 3 out of 5 star movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reminds me of this](https://youtu.be/1by0-nkKOTs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a backstory/history of the place at most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify: Blue is the easiest colour to make an alpha channel. However, green is  almost as good, but a lot less likely to be accidentally worn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if I've never cooked it before, how do I know what my taste is. The one writing the recipe should define it as it they were doing it. If it was to taste, I wouldn't be making this casserole, I'd order a pizza. The chef at a restaurant doesn't ask me how much salt to put in, he just does it, and that's what a recipe should do.  
I concede that weighing a pinch of salt might be difficult, but a fraction of a teaspoon might be good (although i have issues with the non standard sizes of spoons too).  
To someone who doesn't know how to cook, these recipes are useless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that would differ dramatically between people. Why not use a universally standard unit of measurement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's that ambiguity again "medium sized". What's the diameter or a "medium sized" tomato? When is it too big to be considered medium? And "two cups"? Which cup would you like? My espresso cup, or my MASSIVE one?  
Surely you must acknowledge that weight is an all round more useful unit in which to measure ingredients? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The vast majority of American home kitchens don't have a scale in them.

TIL! I can't get by without one. How would you measure non fluids? Like vegetables, or chocolate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A "pinch" is still a terrible measurement. Is that like just in the tips of the fingers, or a good squeeze picking up as much as one can in two fingers? The latter is a significant order of magnitude greater than the former!  
As for coming down to taste. That's down the the recipe writer to tell me. I don't know how it's meant to taste according to the writer, and I don't know what effect putting in 1gramme more or less of something will have.  
The recipient needs to be explicit. Once I've done exacrlybwhat they say, then NEXT time I can try deviating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a European that still doesn't clarify!  
Also, why not just give a weight. No measurement of volume or arbitrary "cup" sizes. Weight is very easily measured and quantified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, most Middle Eastern airlines provide a decent service, and proper cutlery. This threat seems to be based around Western airlines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the interior is designed after, and separately from the exterior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High speed? It's slow motion, not high speed.  
(The cemera recording had a high frame rate) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man... sleep is scary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, how do you think all those vehicles are built? Mining rare earth materials isn't easy. Electric cars are good replacements, but to actively replace for no reason uses more energy than just keeping your old petrol car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually you might be right, I think it's the crappy rate they give you that stings. Either way, they have consistently worked out significantly more expensive than other options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is only true for countries like India/Pakistan etc. They have massive fees for sending to U.K. And I think US too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UAEExchange is consistently cheaper, and if you do repeat businesses, you can usually haggle even better rates (even though they were already cheapest) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys are consistently much more expensive than UAEExchange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be right actually...  
I haven't seen many police cars outside DXB and AD, but the ones in AD are definitely 3 dimensional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flintstones, famous for their [fake cars without engines](http://68.media.tumblr.com/4f42e9388e9f529be9018e923c093e8d/tumblr_o5l9qwyc561r7rm1so4_500.gif), and also the saying ["Yabba dabba doo"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpGx4foRdPw).  
The "Yabba Dabba" sounds like "Abu Dhabi". There's an old joke "People in Dubai don't understand Flinstones jokes, but people in Abu Dhabi do" playing on the "yabba dabba doo".  
The first guy talked about it looking like a Flinstones car, the next guy pointed out the fact that it's not actually a Dubai police car, but one from Abu Dhabi, and incorporated the yabba dabba doo joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a Thin Blue Line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, yeah, I should get a cut! But yeah, I guess I'm just sharing my good experience with them (both product and service), just as OP was doing. We don't get enough good stuff here, so we should highlight the positives :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo, not only linking in the classic pun, but in context! (in that it's actually an AD police car, not Dubai) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all down to taste. The guys at RAW are actually good to recommend something for you. Tell them if you want a stronger taste (darker roast) or more light and mellow. I'm not gonna start spewing about hints of elder flower and berry here. Just give them a rough idea of what you like and they'll suggest one. They don't expect everyone to be a cupping expert so don't judge is you simply say "I like it strong".  
That said, my favourite is definitely the Yirgacheffe. It's been my bean of choice since living in the UK. But it's all down to personal preference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, the best coffee is the one that you enjoy. If you enjoy instant, then fine, ain't gonna judge you for that (I will... (na, just kidding))  
However, I would implore you to go to RAW and just get a latte. You will enjoy it, but won't necessarily see why it's so much nicer after one cup, and will think it tastes roughly the same. When you have it a few times, and then go BACK to drinking other stuff... THAT'S when you'll realise how bitter and harsh they taste, and you'll appreciate what it is to have good coffee :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, wasn't my taste. I prefer Arfican coffee. My favourite plantation is in Yirgacheffe, Ethopia. I was elated when I moved here and found RAW supplied this! :D  
If you're thinking of trying Kopi Luwak, make sure it's the real stuff, not the fake crap (no pun intended). The benefit of this coffee is two stage; the second only being the fact that it's been exposed to the gastric juices. The primary is the fact that the cats have the ability to seek out only the ripest berries, thus getting you the best stuff. The fake "Kopi Luwak" is where they just feed coffee to caged civet cats, and harvest the poop. Not only is this unethical, but it defeats the primary object of having your top quality coffee pickers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, there's forensics that need to be done on the video to actually prove it's not an elaborate setup. It'd be like arresting Keane Reeves because there's evidence of him shooting someone. Not saying it's not real, just saying that due process needs to be followed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As mentioned in another comment, I'm very fussy about my coffee. I've travelled the world discovering coffee, and some of my favourite places back home are Prufrock and Nude Espresso in London. I used to get coffee from Has Bean, Sq Mile, and Alchemy coffee in the UK. RAW coffee can compete at the highest international standard.  
They are more pricey than supermarket coffee, but supermarket coffee (yes, including Illy and the "posh" looking ones) is old and stale. You should consume within about 21 days of roasting. Compared to a bag of Starbucks coffee, yes, RAW is still a bit more pricey, but not by much.  
Since introducing my colleagues to RAW, they too have become subconsciously fussy about coffee!  
As much as I sound like I work for RAW, I can assure you, I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can also report their customer service is as fabulous as their coffee! I had an issue with grind size (my grinder was broken). I don't want to say "they gave me free stuff" because I don't want to set a precedent with their other customers (who could exploit it), but I can report that they endeavoured to ensure I was not short of my quality coffee fix. Their delivery guy is always friendly, always has change, always comes on time. I'm a self proclaimed coffee snob, and their coffee is top notch on an international scale. If you haven't visited, you should do so, their baristas are superb! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> deborted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What they're allowed to do and what they do aren't always the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [But not very well hanged...](http://files.explosm.net/comics/Kris/hotline.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Even better](http://files.explosm.net/comics/Kris/hotline.png)  
[Even even better](http://files.explosm.net/comics/Rob/note.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not realising "Future" was an artist really added to my confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was toying with whether it was grammar or not. Probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to check your own grammar before bitching about someone else's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you! I make an effort and still look shit. We hate people like you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does that graphic need to sit slap in the middle of the video, for the whole damn time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you look very unkempt, or have someone to do your ironing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aeropress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I'll simply remain curious :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, that's EXACTLY what the blue stuff is. It's mold. That's what gives it the flavour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your car...? Or Metro, or bus. I was curious as to why someone would get a taxi every day as it seemed a very uneconomical mode of transportation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then yes, you can carry a blade of up to 3" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even more curious as to why you would get a taxi every day. Isn't it a very expensive option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have honestly never heard "Patty". It seems it's an Americanism which may be why I've never heard it. Sorry, it wasn't me trying to be obnoxious (although I often am). I genuinely didn't know people mispronounced/misspelled it as Patty, as Paddy is what I've used and heard my entire life, and was curious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. Does seem very wasteful and environmentally unfriendly  to use AC to dehumidify the air, and then a humidifier to re-humidify it. Never used one though as I hate humidity, so can't comment on it's effectiveness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't... I'm not OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does a stick... or anything else that casts a shadow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the UK. Illegal to carry if your intenetion is self defence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got red on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Padraig is the Irish, and Patrick the English. I would guess that's where "Paddy" comes from.  
Now how does one get "Dick" from "Richard" (Etymologicaly speaking!!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Europe, roads are awesome: manual.  
Dubai, roads are straight and dull, and crazy drivers: auto.  
Source, have both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you need a humidifier in an already uncomfortably humid city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't trust knock off electrical items that take 230volts. Seen to many shitty designed products/circuits and seen too many in fail with potentially bad consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah! Didn't even notice OP's title! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Never follow a taxi, a minivan or a lexus. And never stay next or in front of any White SUV.  
  
Sooo, don't ride in Dubai? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riding in Dubai city is terrible. The roads are straight and boring. Speed cameras everywhere (it's easy to slip over the limit momentarily on a bike). If you are goi g abroad, where are you going? If it's Europe, definitely ride there!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wonder why people get taxis every day. Why don't you get a car? Serious question. Taxis must cost you a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
