<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3508</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely cetain what you ae talking about! Can you epeat that again fo me, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should US taxpayers care about Seoul?

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do understand that he has plenty of friends who would still "bigly" benefit and probably be willing to pay yuge sums under the table to see it happen, right?

The guy did business in Russia; he undersrtands wink-wink business deals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, two points to make:

1) She speaks in complete sentences!

2) She totally looks like E.T. in that video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutting of SWIFT transactions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But McCain will tell everyone what a bad idea it is, both before and after the vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if Sessions would resign in protest! Hahaha, very witty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give the books anyway please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe that's what he should actually be doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pros go to the bar a couple blocks down and wait

Because coming back to the DMV a little tipsy is a great idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One wonder when was the last time Trump was on the phone with Page...

And if Trump saw some conversation of his with Page, he'd jump to the conclusion he was wiretapped, not Page. Though I guess his name (Trump's) would be redacted, he might recognize the conversation.

Makes a lot of sense now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the redhats don't rinse, they just get dirtier and dirtier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> big-ly, you left off the "-ly"!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't it "the only one during the 2016 election campaign" which ended on 8 November? As in who knows who else got on it on say 17 November?

(17 Nov pulled out of the air, before anyone asks why it is significant. It's not, as far as I know) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that is the kind of thing 4-month-old accounts say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no fucking way Page is getting that 19%. He might be some commission, but the 19% belongs to Manafort and Trump. 

EDIT: And that's even part of why this is an even bigger story than it seems at first sight. Page is why too small time for the Russians to even look at *except* he had access to the Trump campaign. So, they hook him and he starts delivering. But it's not like he can say "If Trump wins, I want 19% in Rosneft." It has to be more "If Trump wins, this is what he wants and what he will do. As for me, I want to retire really, fucking rich". 

So, if the FBI was monitoring Page, then they get to listen to him talk to both the Russians and *Trump's* team and they are specifically looking for any kind of deal betweeen those two sides that Page might be communicating. 

Say there is another layer between Trump and Page. The FBI might suspect Trump /Tillerson / Flynn know, but while they cannot wiretap those guys - but they can sure as hell start here what those guys are telling Page. 

For example:

Page: "[Kellyanne - unmasked as directly relevant in this conversation], did my message get through? What is the response?"

Unmasked Kellyanne: ["Yes, I told Donald yesterday, but he's going to get back to me. You know him, he wants to run everythign by Ivanka and Jared first".]

In other words, everyone who has talked to Page since eaarly 2016 is nervously trying to recreate their conversations with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strangely, I would watch that movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence, I will not read it. Though OP's synopsis makes it sound interesting, I'll wait for someone else to report on it to read an actual article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the obvious take-away is that Manafort was getting paid by the Russians, right? Someone should be investigating his lines of income across 2016... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  88D chess

I'm going to presume you are being very sly by using "88" !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hah, good answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: you think we don't have war criminals of our own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reat others with basic decency. No personal attacks, shill accusations, hate-speech, flaming, baiting, trolling, witch-hunting, or unsubstantiated accusations. Threats of violence will result in a ban.

That goes against the rules:

...No personal attacks, shill accusations, hate-speech, flaming, baiting, trolling, witch-hunting, or unsubstantiated accusations. Threats of violence will result in a ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I guess it's okay when a Republican president snubs the Constitution, huh?

What rock do you live under? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we all now which speaks louder... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the main rocket place is Dnipropetrovsk

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yuzhmash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's stupid to say that. 

But let's back up - why don't you give us *your* definition of "ally". We may be speaking of different things.

In my world, an ally is someone who has your back, shares your world view and is trustworthy. Russia is none of those things.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Ukraine makes better rocket engines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, no. Profit is revenue less expenses. You can have a fuck ton of revenue and still be in the red. If you profit, it is due to spending less than you earn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to single me out. I doubt many people from there are reading this subreddit.

But this all reminded me of a comment I made a few weeks ago:

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/62cwx1/rural_trump_voters_embrace_the_sacrifices_that/dflk5hh/

I seriously think my commenting has far less to do with their supporting tyrrany than Fox News and Bill O'Reilly.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Garbage Soaked Flower Skunks"

Also good for chants Gee-Ess-Eff-Ess.

And I get free tickets to your 10-year anniversary greatest hits tour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> malinformation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mal is French for "bad". Think "mal"function. So, instead of "soft"ware, it's "bad"ware. Not necessarily destructive, but nothing good comes of it. As far as I understand it, it *is* a broad term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you know he's going to have a laid back lunch before or afterwards, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will or won't transit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who want the high security live in bumfuck Kansas, equidistant from both the Mexican AND Canadian borders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "now down"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honest question - how long does a round of golf take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bombing Syria?

^(j/k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but if your number crunchers show that a fairly stable percentge of people fail to show up for such-and-such specific flights, why would you not overbook and get even more -free- money?

It's a risk, of course. But those same number crunchers are telling you that over time you will make an extra $XXX and if the risk comes to fruition you're only out $X. So, you're going to profit from it.

And people are not going to just stop flying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me what year this went down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, there is beer in the afterlife??

I may need to rethink this atheism thing if that's the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Staying tuned... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> point is, no-one else knows what he is doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a bulldozer

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZXKAleVdp6s feature=youtu.be t=20s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't live in Kansas. I was just wanting to know when the "big news" would be coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me again when this vote is taking place? What's the date apart from any early voting?

Found it:

Thompson is facing Republican State Treasurer Ron Estes and Libertarian Chris Rockhold to replace Mike Pompeo, who is now President Donald Trumps CIA director. The election is April 11. - See more at: http://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/kansas-democratic-congressional-candidate-feuds-with-party#sthash.5YjzyhYe.dpuf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please send my pony *express* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What justification does a password manager app have for being subscription based?

I mean, I get that they are "improving" the app, but it's fucking fine the way it is. Have paid upgrades, fine, but subscription app for something like that is uncool.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not only being phased out, it's being pushed out. The used some sort of "cannot sync with mini 1Password or something". Then they say your free trial is over and they refuse to answer any e-mails. 

Seriously, fuck that company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I hope you're okay now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semantics. 

Deploy in fact mean "to move". Which is precisely why in your comment you write "have nukes on deployment" which I guess you mean as "already deployed" as in "in place".

If I asked "where does the US have nukes deployed?" I would expect a different list of places than if I asked "where is the US deploying nukes?"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It definitely meant liberals to his base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> catholic or mormon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  WaPo chooses to stylistically place the author's name before the title on their website when they have a guest writer.

There might be a good reason for that, y'know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told him. But he just laughed... :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted Cruz tells me to tell you he accepts your apology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when does revenue equal profit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, great insight. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm unaware of that. Can you give me a link to read?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm as anti-Trump as anyone. And I am convinced in my mind - given the reporting we've seen - that he was in fact in cahoots with Russia to win the election. I mean that honestly. 

That said, this line of conspiracy sounds weak to me. Someone is begging for more pepperoni. 

Anyhow, your Hillary parallel is empty, because Trump is in deep shit for his Russian ties. Hillary has not got *that particular* baggage, so no-one would be calling it a "Russian angle".

And besides, the same people saying Trump looks precedential for bombing Syria and the very same ones who would praise Hillary for it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do the Mercers need Bannon if they have Trump now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I predict](/s "She is going to join forces with what-his-face at Tyco station and end up leading the belters")  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **AND** that FB person of yours thinks "bombing Syria" has something to do with governing the United States. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Monte Verde

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monte_Verde

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***SHUT UP ALREADY!!!!***

Is this the only thing you know how to say???

EDIT: This is a bot. I feel had. Look at the account's comment history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit,m shut up already. Do you want people to take you seriously or not? Because copy/pasting the same thing over and over does *nothing* to boost your argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We heard you the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's name has binary in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Russian story has not gone anywhere.

The point is that Trump's campaign may have colluded with Russia to get Trump into the WH. 

That Trump does something against Russia's interests now, really doesn't mean anything.

I mean, I am not buying what some are flogging - that Trump and Russia set this bombing up to take away from the Russia story. But I think it quite plausible that Trump is not Russia's puppet in the literal sense. Russia's fool a lot of the time - yes. 

But I think the real story to the Russia-Trump scandal is that Russia is achieving its goal of destabilizing the United States. Has their backing Trump come back to bite them in the ass? OR are they and Trump still working together and this is all a set up to "prove" Russia and Trump are not connected?

**Who the fuck knows?**

^(*The FBI and CIA know*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently so.  For bad apples, I reckon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1311

165

117

75

3L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green car travelling Europe..? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now kiss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but if you are the one puttng the no-fly zone in place, then presumably you have the means to enforce it. Meaning, you de facto control the air space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erring, but then right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, but if it was required, a specialized cottage industry of "we'll check your hires' ID cards" would spring up and *BAM* - even more jobs!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone is probably drooling at the thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sorry, I was simply replying to the "Control the air, control the fight" part which sounds like it meshes well with a no-fly zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, like the no-fly zone Hillary was considering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddam, I wish this one had been true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of these days, the company should complete the interview with the mother present and hire the mother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, that is depressing. Shows Trump was right about his 5th Avenue shooting hypothetical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What people forget is that FAR from all boomers were hippies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, you brought up Le Pen in a thread about infighting: 

READ THIS (T_D): https://www.reddit.com/r/The_Donald/comments/63upop/rand_paul_urges_trump_not_to_take_military_action/

And make sure you get to this comment:

https://np.reddit.com/r/The_Donald/comments/63upop/rand_paul_urges_trump_not_to_take_military_action/dfxe6yg/

I mean, reading this is *joyful*

Comments like:

- Just when I think God Emperor knows what is going on and has everything going to plan, I read shit like this making me think otherwise.

- It's a 4D chess move. I don't see it.

- I will denounce my support for trump if he invades syria. This is some globalist shit FUCK OFF. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say IT IS a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's overall simply good because it will bring more opportunities. For example, the low coster airlines now trying to come in. 

RyanAir wants to start flying and that means cheaper tickets and more access to more cities. (Personally, I like that they are planning a Kyiv-Stockholm route!)

And not only will Ukrainian tourists win, many many more European tourists will also start considering a trip to Ukraine. "Hey honey, look, it's just 40 euros (or whatever) to fly to Kyiv from London. We ahven't been there, maybe we should try it?"

And that means money coming into Ukraine. Granted, it might not be much to begin with, and overall this might not really make a splash in the country's economic landscape. But I'll just be happy for the specific restaurants and other businesses that will see more cash flow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is certainly a hassle to have to go to the embassy in person and apply for a visa. Especially if you don't lieve anywhere near an embassy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, I don't believe you want to think about what could happen to her in a social setting bereft of normal human social mores. 

Unless, you mean to say, she is human so of course she'll be smarter than all the moneys in good time and become their ruler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, that was overdone. I mean, look at the title and then read "NSFW" ... and WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS ARTICLE ABOUT?

You really should not have put that there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Obama's fault for not being there to tell them it was a stupid idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liberals live in cities. Fuck them and make them cry!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is closer to "Cut off trains to cities? Sure, those cities are just full of liberals who won't vote for me anyway". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved this quote:

The greatest examples of libertarianism in action are the hundreds of men, women and children standing alongside the roads all over Honduras. The government wont fix the roads, so these desperate entrepreneurs fill in potholes with shovels of dirt or debris. They then stand next to the filled-in pothole soliciting tips from grateful motorists. That is the wet dream of libertarian private sector innovation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To recap his main points: 

 Jump back, scream like girl

 Continue whimpering in pain on the ground

 Get to ER

 Hyperventilate

 Sit on couch for 6 days and eat painkillers

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  praying my fucking grant gets funded.

So, you are religious and in favour of income distribution! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was posted 7 hours ago, so I guess we're up to at least 20? Or is he done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you. I think you are waaaay overgeneralizing. I mean, did you even read the article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You break past by not calling it that when you are campaigning. You just say "We are going to bring jobs to you". And then you say something about how handouts are bad, but people who are willing to put some effort into getting a job are going to get one. 

Then when they come in, it turns out the effort includes some education and training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am uneasy that your user name implies cats are dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, they want what Hillary was trying to offer them?

EDIT: Wow, thanks for the gold, good reddito. Did not expect that - it is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool story, bro. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unless you're a movie studio trying to control the narrative about your new releases

Umm, dare I say "bingo"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, if I understand him correctly, he is saying, "the document" did not change. There is simply *another* document describing an "agreement" and while the agreement (about the trust) did not change, the two documents describe it in different ways. 

I geuss related to Trump' trust - He was *always* able to take his money out whenever he wanted. Just we did not know this until the second document came out describing this aspect of it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe found Putin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Bannon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manafort is a big fish, maybe a whale. Page is a minnow comapred to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We want the story of how fucked they were when you left! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collecting, sure. But selling? Have their been any documented cases of ISPs *selling* this information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/uRF27rV.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, that seems eons ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NBC linky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I remind you this would not have worked except for the role played by guys like this: http://i.imgur.com/uRF27rV.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, a fuck ton of them are enablers, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  how does that reshape our understanding of the significance of the Flynn / Kislyak call

Man, I was already overloaded by this story, and I hadn't even got to making that connection yet. But yeah, DAAAYUMM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
