<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8830</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 08:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get into furry bondage porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously doubt these numbers. I have never had any of my family doctors, my wife's gynecologist, stat cares (which do a large part of care these days), etc that only see 5 people a day. That is a ridiculous number. And add in hospitals and the number goes WAY up. Maybe you don't live in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed and marching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, but, but...the carbs!!! That and I am sleeping at 2 and 4 pm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your first statistic, 19 patients was for average doctors and your second statistic was for cardiologists. Can you see where you have a problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung blames batteries for Galaxy Note 7 fires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure where you got your 1/10 statistics, but that flies in the face of the weeks and months long wait times for some soldiers as well as the reported shortage of doctors in the system. I am always looking for more information and if you could help me with any it would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone pays, everyone receives. The system would be modeled after the many countries that have great universal healthcare throughout the world, not the VA system. The VA system is not designed for huge populations. It wasn't even designed or set up for the amount of soldiers we had coming in after 2001. The system was not expanded quickly enough or even now, for the numbers who need(ed) it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "were meant..." So we're the 1967 boundaries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck health insurance. How about providing all humans with care? Seems like the decent thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we need universal healthcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of foolishness is why we need universal healthcare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are just throwing shit out there now. The Clinton Parameters were ONLY parameters needed to be "orally accepted for HIS continued support. Being as he hasn't been President in 16 years, they are irrelevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Building houses on land that is illegal by international law is wrong. If I put icing on a piece of shit, it isn't a cake. Israel doesn't even do much if anything about the settlements they themselves deem illegal. If Trump gave someone a permit to build in your back yard it doesn't mean it's right or legal. BUT, if the police never enforce the law and arrest said permit holder for trespassing and take the building down, then there isn't much reason for you to take matters into your own hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the kid is half theirs, so sounds logical. What is your problem with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your phone sucks. Mine gives me all cap words after 2 capitol letters in a row. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose you think I don't know what a straw man is? Or maybe you don't and so you can't avoid it. My argument was stealing land that is often in violation of Israeli law, not building houses. As for anyone firing rockets at Israel, that is wrong as well. Although, using horrible tactics, such as rockets, was used by Israel themselves to take the very land they now call Israel so it is interesting that they condemn such actions by those who they are stealing land from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you can, but I'm a normal human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See everyone naked to help with my social anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stamina. You cannot wank yourself into being a wise lover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or voted for Clinton. People not voting is what lead to this problem. Now they are all pissed off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like they want to go to war with their Arab neighbors again. They cannot believe that they can just occupy all of Palestine indefinitely. Then again, maybe they were just waiting for a president like Trump to get REAL crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I don't know much about computer altering of photos. Can you explain how one knows?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't look like it, but I really don't know. If not, I can see why from Trump's perspective that it looked yuge.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely doesn't answer the question. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With an HSA, having kids, like my two daughters (infant and toddler) would bankrupt me. I would not have money to pay for the regular Dr. visits, each year, within 6 months at most. Glad my union refused to let our employer change our healthcare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of a weird circular dislike pattern with me: I dislike people who dislike people. So people who dislike people are probably reinforced in disliking people because of sensing my dislike for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My water bottle, cap, and the package wrap are all different plastic recycling types. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mastubate before going to bed and when you wake up in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just watched this for the second time last night. It was a bit better than my first impression, which was not so enthusiastic. I can see what OP is saying in that it does open a door to a really good prequel: A romance that ends with him completing the "impossible task". It would have a happy ending that viewers would knows doesn't last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sadly even Obama couldn't get the FDA to be rational when it comes to marijuana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to know what your blood levels are. 200 mg a week is a lot. I doubt your Dr. will keep you on that dose unless your levels were near 0. Get your estrogen checked after a couple months and you will know if you need an AI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, cool. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trendsetter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Revolting mutants hunt human outcasts and underground fighters (Bruce Campbell, Marta Alicia) in a future world of mind control." 


Sounds interesting. I'll have to check it out if I can find it online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this is definitely it. Read it last year thanks to this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And gives everyone a job. "You're hired!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is already legendary in my eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my daughter's favorite shows. Now I'm a bit worried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who don't mind website ads, why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be exceptionally interested in any information you could point me to in regards to this. I have never heard such a theory in my study of their migration to, what is now called, North America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was too in my lipstick and nail polish days. Hope to see more of it...from everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG!!! I absolutely LOVE this. The multitude of colors, the metallicness, everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Democrats really screwed themselves with this rule change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just assumed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Mark Zuckerberg runs against Trump, as is being lightly speculated, I doubt Trump would have the support. Sadly, he might be a force against a Democratic challenger, whereas Trump will almost certainly not be (unless Trump and Republicans pass a Healthcare law that is not horrific). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck these guys in particular! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a respectable idea, but may be a bit far reaching. It might be better to just change it to indigenous people day (or something that sounds better). I feel, living in a VERY conservative part of the Mideast, that people might be opposed to a day honoring leaders of another culture more than honoring a culture we decimated and now live in place of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it means that anyone who voted never sways from voting democrat voted for her. She wasn't horrible in context of comparability to her opponent or experience, but in the sense of being out of touch with progressive values and being horrible scandal-ridden. In hindsight she would have been better. As I said recently, better a WallStreet puppet than a Putin puppet. Personally, I think many independents thought Trump might moderate his policies from that of his rhetoric and we are finding the opposite to be true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dig him up and put his skeletal remains on the bench!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed how this picture became famous. Can anyone enlighten me, please?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going through his photo, it is interesting to see him age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Discover". Well, at least they didn't massacre the indigenous population whose ancestors ACTUALLY discovered it tens of thousands of years before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delusional is not a diagnosis any of my therapists have stated to me directly, but perhaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, but unrelated to the great make up, I live the peace symbols in your eyes' reflection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? Look at the shape and slightly outward tilt of the top of the ear. Decades of age can't change that. But that's just me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will win by large margins. Low turnout and a horrible Democratic candidate are how he won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [William H. Pryor Jr.](http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/17/potential-supreme-court-nominee-who-wants-gays-jailed-denies-posing-nude-for-gay-adult-site/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's potential Supreme Court nominee, who wants gays jailed for consensual sex, posing nude in a gay porn magazine. [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 10:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Onomatopoeia. Thanks, been holding that in for years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a little help from their friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost 5 years on Reddit and I have not seen this before. Well done sir!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our husky had a problem with an old set if chairs when we had hard wood floors. The noise would send him either running or howling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then legally change it to Homer Simpson after they win the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read them years after seeing the movies and was blown away. Sadly the diminish in greatness as the series grows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered the whole NASA series of Baxter on a redditor's recommendation and was so fucking bored by his drawn out technology ramblings that I didn't make it 3/4 through the first. I am scared to try any of his others.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China urges U.S. to bar Taiwan delegation from Trump inauguration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explosion kills dozens in Malian military camp: witness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 06:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am doing it and am going in for my first visit since starting at home and I will be honest with them about it if they ask. I feel better on weekly and there is current medical research to back up injecting more frequently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 06:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw, and thought it was worth a chuckle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the engineering obstacles to build this floating city in the Pacific Ocean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 06:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 05:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. This whole thing is ridiculous though. No one has been killed or even hurt due to protesting on highways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me. I think it is foolhearted and would not do it personally. It seems to have done more to harm the recent movement more than help. I do not put much stock in the people planning the recent movement to spotlight racism in America today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, many people have been charged with manslaughter because they did not want to be inconvenienced. I am talking about law. I am not talking about protesters jumping in front of cars. Also, I have never, in any of the states I have lived in (CA, OK, KY, OH, TX) seen a minimum speed limit sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many Americans believe that their convenience (e.g. getting to their destination quickly) is more important than a stranger's life (meaning a highway protester's safety)? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jay walking maybe, but criminally negligent manslaughter (also called involuntary manslaughter) would apply if you see a group of protesters and do not take their safety into account when approaching them or navigating through them. I am absolutely stunned at how many Americans think their convenience is more important than a stranger's life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do wish you all the best. You sound like you deserve it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you are saying better now. Thanks for the explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump, The Mideast Conflict And The Fate Of A Two-State Solution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immunity for NEGLIGENCE! That is called manslaughter in the US and IS a crime. There is a huge difference between being negligent and not being negligent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest: Trump Adviser Tells Elite: Listen to the People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers Propose Bill To Allow Drivers To Run Over Highway Protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Dakota lawmaker's bill protects drivers who negligently hit someone obstructing traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely eentitled to feel that civil disobedience is a punishable crime, but does it justify murder? It is one thing to not see a random protestor, but another thing to allow your inconvenience to trump their, Supreme Court backed, right to free speech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant gravity wave spotted on Venus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 08:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers Propose Bill To Allow Drivers To Run Over Highway Protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term is Artificial Intelligence. I think these tech companies are just trying to convince people their invasive data gathering that lleds to hit or miss advertising is something it is not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you mention war? What does them investing in the US have to do with war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China sovereign wealth fund CIC plans more U.S. investments: chairman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 10:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump vows 'insurance for everybody' in replacing Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 10:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 08:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 08:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too much friend. A WallStreet puppet would be better than a Putin Puppet   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is much the fault of the media as the administration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE this idea!


Edit: sp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to yourself. The brain is an amazing thing. Listen to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks delicious. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was great. Although, I hadn't seen the first since it came out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show us on [This](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/cf/43/65/cf43656bce5b343a9ac6a009c60b14ac.jpg) diagram where they hurt you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once went a day without talking and another blindfolded. Today we are talking about not living with our cell phones for a day. Crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/19wi0k/the_stop_girl_almost_three_years_later/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on, I'll find it since you haven't heard of goodle. ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After waking from a coma and being told Donald Trump is about to be President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad teacher. No bone for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I always thought of AI as a consciousness growing up, but now all these tech companies are calling advanced predictive algorithms AI and it is diminishing the concept of what true AI could/should be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has it been shown to be demonstrably untrue? I have just briefly heard about it at all, but I can't imagine how it could be proven or unproven in any meaningful way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the pale lip look on you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be a day this is needed, but right now is not the time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain why this wasn't discovered sooner? I mean, that's how our body's cells communicate. I just assumed this was common within most biological matter at cellular sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my company's communications with my Union the months leading up to a contract negotiation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected Trump to destroy the USA for a while, but not start WWIII.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Did you get them?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I throw them away with almost every bag of trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it's not Iron Maiden.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that would freak me out every time I took LSD. Bathrooms are one of my favorite tripp spots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browse ALL of reddit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To get to the ova side.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ewwww! That's all I can think about too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 08:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damnit! Now you tell me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diarrhea - Burning Butthole Syndrome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could some well-known ailments be called to better represent their effects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill it away from people, hang it away from people is my new motto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born and raised in San Diego. Moved to Ohio 5 years ago. Never seen any hanging from trees anywhere, let alone the middle of town </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must not have been raised in San Diego. My fault for moving to Ohio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think it's fucked up that my stomach can handle spicier foods than my ass hole can. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is hilarious AND a tiny bit creepy too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think much differently of a parent of a toddler, in public, who is on their phone than one who is reading a book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was so funny. Definitely worth the watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WoW, getting anything in "about 7 days" is crazy fast. Thanks OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter is going to LOVE having her own tape measure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booooooooo! The probably don't want to have to pay her estate for said performance. Crappy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking-A!!! You're god damn Edison! Thanks for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be wrong, but I think that is his sister Valarie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned the majority of my knowledge, in college, from in class teaching. I should have read more, but the book often was reinforcement of class learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the LSD wears off he will realize the bathroom walls and tiles are just beige. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad thing is: We all are, but often  treat  each other poorly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it work? Can we see it in action? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to find out what religion this is and convert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a patch to cumbersome for me not to upvote. Cheers mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful color. A great tone for a "more natural" look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't necessarily find this about newbies, but I do notice that picture posts do better than question posts and that picture posts seem to do better if the poster is "attractive".  

Edit: that to than </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think you might find more scientists believing in the possibility of deism more than theism, but, overall, this number would probably be lower than the average of the population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't that "science" has any bias inherent in and of itself, for it is just the accumulation of data through the scientific method. I have never heard an argument against the scientific method, though I am sure reddit will finally enlighten me to any out there. That being said, every person who applies the scientific method has their own bias in trying to find answers to the hypothesis they are testing. As a psychologist there are means by which we try and avoid having these biases taint our data. We have others help set up our experiments so we can take into account things our biases may prevent us from thinking of, use random selection so we don't pick people who might conform to our biases, we do double blind studies, when possible, so the researchers nor the participants know who is getting what treatment, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO way! Trump would never let that happen to us. Right? I mean it's not like he has anything to gain from real estate ...... Oh, wait.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting fitted for a crown right now and could use the distraction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What fetishes and professions, ethically, go together? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pot at O. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now? Hasn't changed much recently. The poor suffer, the wealthy scoff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it is a delay of punishment or penalties, then the rich get over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IRS to delay tax refunds for millions of low-income families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which narrative is that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. property foreclosures at 10-year low in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *crosses his fingers and toes* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but except in very specific cases, robots only get smarter as humans get better at programming and setting them up in ingenious ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make one to heat my butter when my wife forgets to take it out of the fridge and I'll help cofound the company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you are golden. Fanuc ladder logic programming is where the good money is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which at this point we will probably become extinct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't started it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as I know how to control them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just took PLC and controls I last semester and am taking PLC and controls II starting next week. Unfortunately, my company just hired a controls engineer to do most of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love the PLC programming, but we have a, shitty, controls engineer who does that stuff now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must be in the book. Don't remember it in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ability to find/troubleshoot (visual inspection) is not yet viable, then retrieving parts and installation. It isn't that a system could not be made to do all this, but it is not cost effective yet. Not even close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but there is additional schooling you would need to do the electrical side. Not sure the pay would be worth. Your field of work will me needed far into the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you want a semi-sentient rooms? What a horrible life to give even semi-sentience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure some things can be diagnosed and fixed automatically, but diagnosis and repair still, more often than not, needs human attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, our robots are Fanuc. I like the programming (ladder logic) a lot more than changing joints and wrists, but even that is better than press maintenance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you not have to take college classes where you're atto be an HVAC tech?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I leave their greasy spilling for the operators to clean up, but I guess I have wiped a few robot broken butts (joints).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a maintenance electrician. I work in a semi-automated forging plant. I was hired as an operator and bbid into the job. They are sending me to school as an electrical technician (I will end up as a journeyman electrician) and I will top out, here, at around $22. Although, my cousin is a journeyman electrician in San Diego and makes around $50 an hour. But in this area of Ohio I probably won't make over $30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robot maintenance. In fact, my occupation is blossoming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been so worried about being left feeling like this that I haven't watched it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Prodding, Republicans Slowing Down Cabinet Confirmation Process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 12:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be surprised if Pence doesn't pardon him for whatever he gets kicked out of office for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 12:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be interested in knowing what compromising info they might have had on a Pope. Then again, we probably all know what it was.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA Will Be Home to New George Lucas Museum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 10:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin says it has no compromising dossier on Trump or Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 10:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HA! A real German could retake Paris on that weak shit.    
    

P.S. I just ate half a potato, so I have at least a few more hours to live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it's reefer. I was thinking you were on that harder shit. Hell, George Washington used to put that reefer stuff in his soup. It it was good enough for him... And I think you may be confusing reefer for tea. The British are the crazy land grabbing crazies. I'm of Irish, Scottish, and German descent. So hopefully not much murderous land grabbing in my bones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what y'all be smoking in Germany, but I would love some of that shit. Feel like sending me a care package? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This article, published the day after, explains better. it was a NASA scientist speaking at a conference. There was no NASA announcement.](https://www.theguardian.com/science/2016/dec/13/space-asteroid-comet-nasa-rocket) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. diplomat in Hong Kong describes Beijing's legal ruling as 'unfortunate' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but you lost me. What's this about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they land on skids, which, although thinner than tires, would compact the ground if not paved. Oh shit! We should probably warn people not to walk, run, or jump if we are really concerned about mother Earth. Damn hhumans always thinking of themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually sounds like a lot too, to me, because I know there are a lot of days in a month. hmmm Strange that $15 a week seems like a perfect middle ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that when the radiation is absorbed by something, that that is how the heat is transferred, but the heat must already be lost to that which is radiating it and even if it never gets absorbed it is transferred (or distributed) through the universe just through the act of radiation, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
