<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4083</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno.  I literally do this all the time when I get banh mi.  Ask for a cup of broth on the side and my sandwich choice is usually grilled/roasted pork or the sausage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appears I have over estimated the remaining number of XLB.  

Bad - No more XiaoLongBao.

Good - Means I get to have ShenJianBao soon.

Also Good - I forgot we had a bag of JiaoZi left.

This was breakfast this morning + freezer

http://imgur.com/a/R158O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  - Basket

 - Dragon

Notice the character for basket contains the character for Dragon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nunes' replacement will generate the exact same line of questions though.  He's no different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bing - Ice

Bing - Bread

Bing - Merge

Bing - Disease  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Ah.  I was without power much of that week due to storms.  So I guess it was good timing??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  would if you insulted my stapler.

That's because it's some garbage grey Walmart brand stapler and not a real red Swingline.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys like you and Nick Murray have some pretty pricey vehicles.  But not once have I ever felt that either of you were being assholes about it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

What happened to him going on vacation and not posting these for a while?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The proper way to eat them is that you nip the top of the bun with your teeth or, if they're made perfectly, there's a [little hole you stab your chopsticks into](http://kaleidoscope.cultural-china.com/chinaWH/upload/upfiles/2008-12/18/culturalchina74f4e54eedd2d406ba8e.jpg) which you suck the soup out of.

Though honestly myself and most people in China put them in your mouth and pop them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Soup dumplings is an American/English name for these.

Chinese name is "little basket buns".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Seems hard to do!

Cubes of collagen and broth.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My MiL lives with us and makes them all the time.  I promise, you do eventually get tired of them.  We have a 5 gallon bag full of them in the freezer though, when they're finally done she's gonna make shenjianbao. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider yourself lucky then?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they might add on the $200 license plate ticket but you are unlikely to get pulled over just for the plate.

TX you will be pulled over for sure if you lack the front plate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a little road rash, it's still good, it's still good!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt that "no side mirrors" thing actually pans out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're stuck with it here in TX too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  because NSC intel aide protected by bannon conducting unmasking review that WH counsel office ordered halted is deoperationalized **purple monkey dishwasher**.


Better?  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Doug-DeMuro

How do these independent car dealerships like this work with brand new cars?  Would you still get the same warranties/etc as if buying from a brand dealership?  Would you just take this M4 GTS to the local BMW shop for work?

Or are the people who buy these cars rich enough that non of that particularly matters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  good handling fun

The X5 isn't known for good handling though.  Did they fix it with the M?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'bout god damned time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every "near future" car, relatively speaking, has been "damn fast".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we plan on getting there around 5ish tomorrow/Thursday.  Maybe we can miss that rush.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I was under the impression that Google Hangouts was an analog to iMessage.  Can't think of a reason why Google wouldn't do that, honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the parking situation?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one I know uses anything outside of the default messengers on their phones.  :(   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.thrillist.com/drink/nation/supercooled-beer-slushies-thai-jelly-beer


Stuff is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been to their new restaurant?  They have brisket ramen there.  Looking forward to going but it's downtown and they have no reservations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'thumbsupemoji.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have an out.  My wife's iPhone 6 is acting up.  If she isn't turned off by the idea of my "hand me down", I might can get her to take my relatively new 6S+ and I can get one of these sweet bezel-less Androids that I keep seeing pop up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and Communist China

Orwell died before Communist China existed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I would miss iMessage though.....

This is what was keeping me on the iPhone.  iMessage and how it/facetime/calls integrate into my MacBook.

But then my MacBook broke, Apple half assed the latest version, and my current job requires some Windows only software (I requested Mac compatible alternative but they freaked out over security concerns and if I pressed my luck I'd get other people in trouble for buying it themselves and using it "without permission".  Didn't want to be that guy...).

However, from what I understand, Google Hangouts may do the same thing iMessage and all that jazz.  I'll have to look into it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the Fiata.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Oh yes, I will definitely be reinstalling Waze.

I use it on iOS.  They've made some updates recently that are funky.  It stopped announcing directions.  The feature was turned off some how after an update.  Fixed that.  Now the app talks *too* much.  Also for some reason whenever I pick up the phone to double check a direction, when I go to put it back down again it pops up some voice activation menu that I have to tap to get rid of.  Not safe and an annoyance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I might have to switch back to Android when this happens.

/r/Apple had a vid posted last week.  Shoot out between Android Auto and CarPlay.  CarPlay was hilariously bad compared to Android Auto in their tests.  Really making me consider jumping back to Android TBH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well there's the third option that they were spying on their political opponents.

The names were masked.  They had no idea who they were.  How can you spy on someone if you don't know who they are?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just take a look at Breitbart.

"The Mainstream media is watching their Russia election-meddling narrative teeter on the brink of collapse. Theyre holding their collective breath hoping it doesnt topple over, like the worlds highest stakes game of Jenga."


Lolwhelp.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually just watch the first 10 minutes of these vids.  Lets me know what he thinks from the get go.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  WTF is wrong with you?

Because him being a jerk off isn't a problem.  They wanted to stiff minorities and the queer community and are happy to sell out the country to Russia if that's what it takes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of phone is that?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something worse than the death penalty.

Just expropriate all of his and his family's holdings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most folks old enough to live through Nixon have expressed the idea that there's not much difference between the two.  Liberal policies with a blood lust to murder third worlders.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same way you know to change gears in every other car, Pinkie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tie rods.

My Dodge had the same problem.  Drove straight, steering wheel was turned to the left a bit.  Replaced tie rods and that fixed it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to me about a year ago when an undocumented worker rear ended me and totaled out my hemi.  He was able to fake insurance papers some how, some way, according to my insurance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife: "You know they can't hear you, right?"

Me: "Bull fucking shit they can't." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you're paying attention.  Guy on the right is 100% an asshole and at fault, but it's obvious dude on the left wasn't paying attention at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha.  I think I have a preference for the other guy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have different people doing the voice overs for these?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They gonna dig him up to verify whether or not he was really buried in that Neil Young shirt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpopular opinion here, but those $500 Cisco SMB switches aren't terrible.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what does this implicate?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything with gesture volume controls.

2009ish era MB S Class with air suspension.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I read "Binging with Babish" I think this is some Rick and Morty related video.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  that there seem to be issues with alcohol, but that he doesn't actually seem to be alcoholic.

They're wrong.  If you have a substance problem to the point where it causes problems on your life, then you have a substance abuse problem, full stop.

He's a functional alcoholic, but he's still an alcoholic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it in general, but personally I need my audio in my podcasts to be super crisp.  The last few WP I've listened to at random?  All of them on Skype and it sounded bad.  

I like Austin in genera as well, presentation and personality wise.  Not so much his associates.  Nothing wrong with them, just personal preference, but they don't have a well of a "radio personality" as Austin or the rest of the Giant* crew.  

Also, I don't like Vice from a political angle and don't like to support them so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like em myself but listening to their sub par audio for a few hours a week got on my nerves.  


ed

Also they could use some coaching on how to be a better "personality".  Some episodes I'll hear an "Aye yai yai!" about two dozen times.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't need to have this thread every week.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROCKETMAN!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You keep the revs at 3-4K all the time? Even when like cruising?

If I'm highway cruising?  No, but then if I'm highway cruising, I'd be in 7th in the Porsche anyway, so it's a wash.  Most of my driving is on city through-ways where the speed limit is around 50.  So hit it to 50 and keep the revs high for merging/etc.  

The C300's torque is something like 280 at 2500, the C43 is something like 380 at 2000.  Carrera S is 325 5600.  C43 beats it out there, but there's a 50hp difference in the Carrera's favor, so while I'd feel it to a degree between the C43 and the S, the 0-60 is pretty much the same on both.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  R35 GTR.

And because of that we get garbage Infiniti's.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they'd invest in better audio equipment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude bucks every stereotype imaginable for Lambo owners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most diesels now days come with turbos, not because it eliminates lag, but a torquey diesel eliminates the perception of it.

No real need for a turbo in an electric vehicle.  Turbo's require exhaust, which electric vehicles don't have.  They're fast and torquey as is as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should always keep 20k in your pocket if you don't have to otherwise.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair call.  I only hate Dan with a passion because I love him so much.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that this would definitely be true for men of color, but honestly, this is good advice for any man looking for a solid relationship.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan on going by tomorrow, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lemongrass is on the menu and I definitely see it in that pic.  Never gotten a very strong floral flavor from it though, so I didn't consider it.

Definitely not garlic, unless garlic is in that nam jim sauce.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pils are great with crawfish.  Or just on this side of frozen where they're basically a beer icee.  Or after mowing a yard on a hot day.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Dan, we know you're a garbage human being, you don't have to keep trying to convince us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mind helping me perfect a Thai style Grilled Shrimp Salad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooking for some friends this weekend and I want to try and make one of my favorite dishes from one of my favorite restaurants.  [Here's a pic of it I grabbed from Yelp](http://i.imgur.com/nrHrnTQ.jpg).  Menu lists: "Seafood" Nam Jim, mint, cherry tomato, cilantro, lemon grass, kafir lime.

So what stumps me a bit is that I think the menu listing is incomplete.  For one because they also serve it with watermelon radish, and for two there is a definite floral note on the dish that I can't place.

Also, I know that basic nam jim is more or less fish sauce + lime juice + sambal + sugar.  I wonder what makes this a "seafood" fish sauce.  I know they use ground dried shrimps in a few of the menu items but those usually add a very fishy/seafood flavor to those dishes, definitely not here.

[Here's the menu](http://i.imgur.com/jaLZbMF.jpg) for anyone interested.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you don't care about burning that extra 20k you should buy used.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best effort anyway, so probably don't need redundancy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll let the partner figure that end out.  Right now we're just trying to source reliable internet in general.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any ISP guys here able to recommend Business Class Service in Denver, CO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a partner trying to stand up a fairly large residential project in the Denver metro area.  They got some fairly aggressive pricing on a business class fiber drop but said something on the ISP's side financials keeps kicking it back for review every 90 days.  Now our partner is trying to source bandwidth else where.  

We've spoken with Level 3 and their pricing wasn't as aggressive.  We're trying to source as many options as possible.  If anyone could make recommendations, or if you have a contact eMail I can forward along, please PM it to me!  I would greatly appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own an "AMG".  Can only imagine what daily use of an AMG would be like.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the greatest god damned cars to ever exist and a bunch of people doing the speed limit or just below every time they see you int he rear view mirror.  Especially if you live in the South. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably for the best, the 9 speed in the C43  the 7 speed in the C450. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a C300 and a C43 Cab.  

The C43 is worth it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rag tops screw up the flow/lines of a car.  In general, at least.  The 991 generation got it right though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when they skimp out on the basil.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming in 2020 IIRC.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  switchport nonegotiate

This may have "fixed" the issue, but I don't think it actually fixed the issue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Macan which basically lords over the luxury C SUV segment and is imo absolutely a respectable enthusiast car

It's a hatchback and by god it's the best hatchback on the market.


The Panamera easily outdoes it's competition as well.  CLS and Audi A/S7 don't hold a candle.  640i/650i GC isn't even a consideration.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most old Hondas are also almost exclusively that garbage 80s silver metallic color. 

But this video!  Look at all these pristine and gorgeous colors!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think just the Lotus Evora for now

Evora and the Evora Cabriolet are headed here, possibly the SUV next.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a hell of a fun way to throw your back out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBRS/802.11ah/IoT controlled smart houses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should fix their interiors and engines first.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting to see what the first year looks like, then might see the chances of the Quadrifoglio.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three in my neighborhood suburb.  Two were on curb because the drive train went out on them around 60k miles.  2012/2013 models.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People actually want to drive the Giulia though.

Interior on the Giulia is also much nicer, even though the Giulia isn't the most nice in the segment.  No reason to buy a Ghibli at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cross shopped a ton of these in 2015.  Well, the 328i and not the Volvo or the Giulia.

I came away:

C300

328i

A4

ATS

Jag

Infiniti

Lexus



C300 had the more "spirited" engine and better or on par handling over the majority.  328i had an amazing transmission.  Infiniti won out over the Lexus simply because it had a slightly less jank interior. 

I also looked into a Ghibli and cross shopped the A6, S4, 528, and test drove a Quattroporte and Panamera, but I wanted to make sure I could end up with my current 3 car setup so passed on those.  


(Maserati is expensive, comparatively uncomfortable, and have not so great engines or transmissions.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be next gen though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  why though? I had an A4 before and one of the reasons I'm avoiding it is because I feel Audis are a bit boring.

People are smitten with the Virtual Cockpit.  The new TT/TTS has a really nice interior as well.

I prefer RWD and think Audi is too conservative in their styling though.  

I did the same with my C300.  Tested the A4, didn't particularly care for it.  The C300 will probably be replaced with a Giulia in another year.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For what reason would Prime be configuring these access points with such a low power level?

Set it to custom and to what you want then set it back to automatic.

They adjust power based on their ability to see each other.

If you have only 5 APs it may be easiest/prudent enough to just simply manage the power/channels yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But one of the reasons Tesla is investing so heavily in battery factories is so they can sell batteries to GM..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be just me.  I find a bunch of dudes getting snooty over an additional 2 doors to be cringey.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r///BMW corksniffers come out to let OP know that his sports car isn't a sports car but just a sporty car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GT is based on this, right?  It's "cheaper". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boss sold someone his M3 and the bearings failed on the trip home.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another gorgeous car we missed out on here in the States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google says 1000 were made, of which the US received 90.

So, I guess it's a moot point since it, in my mind, is a boutique car of which we got boutique amounts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We didn't get the recent one did we?  Outside of a few special orders IIRC.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That car will fool the people it's designed and rented out to fool.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bioware doesn't need EA or Gamestop.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  so why not preorder?

Because preordering is pointless and benefits the producer and storefront, not the developer.

And me, **personally**, I've felt everything they've done after the first Dragon Age was focus grouped to death and absolutely mediocre to above par, at best.  ME:A has still shown significant levels of jank up until *very recently* so I would tread water.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
