<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of mythologies are we talking? Greek, Roman, Viking? Or all of them wrapped up in one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cottonmouth was definitely the highlight, but that post-modern blaxploitation you're speaking of was layered on wayyyyy too thick IMO. There were multiple times I heard them say something and wonder why they had to sacrifice a basic back and forth, and replace it with something related to how great they are as black characters, and how much culture/power is behind them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With American Gods coming to TV some time this year, what are your thoughts on the book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It never gets anywhere close to the heights of the 4 other Marvel Netflix seasons

Luke Cage would like a word with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's in my original comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of em has a Reddit account with a top comment on a bikini shot of Brenda Song.  Lemme try find it .. [Got it] ( https://www.reddit.com/r/Celebs/comments/3dx5tl/brenda_song/ct9pirj) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here] (http://www.tolkienlibrary.com/press/1010-Famous-Tolkien-fans.php) is a list of fans, but giving it a browse, a lot of them appear to be loosely connected fans if that makes sense. The prince and whatnot going to the Hobbit premiere, along with the Manchester United player saying he wanted to meet Elijah Wood, I'd imagine hes a fan of the movies, but quite frankly aren't we all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Franco is a big fan it seems, given his appearance on Colbert's show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love almost all of his work, but I feel I'm also in the minority. I really don't like the way he draws actual characters. His landscapes and creatures are absolutely fantastic, but something about how he draws Morgoth, and Tuor... They just feel too old fashioned, and that's a shame IMO because I really wish I could appreciate them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, as much as I love keeping up with everything he does... Fuck, can we get anything other than some articles? Actual progress would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This confused me too. I can accept the show has quite a few flaws, but damn did I continue watching until I ran out of episodes. It's the first show I've done in a full sitting since DD season 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writing is definitely off at times, and it's not on par with DD, JJ, but it's easily as good as LC but nobody tore that shit about because it had it's eyes set on being a show about black power, and there's no other way to say it. 

I've groaned at dialogue in this show, but I had countless eye-rolls watching Luke Cage, seeing them sacrifice a normal back and forth with to emphasize how strong they are as black characters. 

This show really isn't the plague that most of Reddit seem to believe it is, so please give it a chance if you haven't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this funny?

Browsing Reddit most of the time I see the names, the same kinda attitudes, I forget sometimes there are people that generous with no real aim to gain from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn what a guy. Goodluck all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be, but shit was that Taylor joke the highlight of that talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely a different tone compared to the rest, and it's much more a noire-detective show than it is a DD or LC type show. On that.. I just love David Tennant. Everything with him and Jessica in the house was just wonderful IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine if you're a fan of the character you'll enjoy the show. I don't know much of him, but I reallllyy like the whole mystical, kungfu feel to it so I stuck around, and don't get me wrong, I notice the flaws, and sometimes they are VERY clear, but it's definitely not as bad as people made it out to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woody pointing back to him being on board with it before said it all did it not? The guy grew up and matured in some ways. Yeah he was that guy once, but it's clear now that at times he is very much a respectful guy with limits on certain matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit that Darth Vader bit was great. Also gotta say you killed it on the audio this week, thank you for acknowledging it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like to joke and whatnot, and sure, maybe it's a truly terrible attempt at a nuke... But I'd very much rather not find out. Especially considering the realistic target is the city of Seoul, a city of 10 million people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legitimately a great show so far. About 2 hours in and the conversation's have been great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... Enjoyed the show. I'm not going to say it's glorious, and anyone that dislikes it is wrong, and I'm not going to say it's without flaws, because there are some very clear ones.

But.. I really liked Finn Jones as Danny. Quite frankly the casting was fantastic, and even Claire's callback gave me a chuckle or two.

It's not on the level of DD or JJ, but IMO it's on par, if not better than LC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about that, given how insanely busy Ian McShane is these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ian Mcshane's the sexiest 74 year old man

I legit had to google this... How the fuck is he 74 years old? That's insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just absurdly reckless for nothing other than karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  just a stupid U.S. "holiday" used to perpetuate racist/nationalist stereotypes and encourage unhealthy drinking

That's just incredibly untrue. It's celebrated here, and yes, while it's definitely a day to have a pint, it's very much a part of our culture to celebrate today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't release shit games

The game isn't even fucking out yet though.. Yes, those animations look pretty terrible compared to what you'd expect from a Bioware game, but damn give it a chance. Wait for reviews to come out from people that have been through the full game, rather than what are basically the opening few hours to a game of this scope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you told me 15 episodes ago that I'd be enjoying Arrow more than Flash I would have called bullshit. 

The writing is just awful this season and it's so damn sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember this story, but the that's serious titlegame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering we have notes for almost all of his writing, do we have an idea of what his plan was for the fourth age? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked how many stars it had. 1. Netflix ratings are pretty fucked, but even then, you know it's genuinely shit if you get 1 star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wholesome Zelda advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because McKellen was up for nomination in Fellowship. He could have probably pushed for it in Two Towers, and I'm not sure about the 2004 movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess, but at the same time, at a certain angle almost everyone is ugly. [Here's  a simple shot from the paparazzi] (http://i1.mirror.co.uk/incoming/article7668829.ece/ALTERNATES/s615b/Kylie-Jenner.jpg)

Yeah, she has makeup, and sure she's not the drop dead stunner she shows herself to be doing her own pics, but realistically she's probably still hotter than the vast majority of women her age.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  involve rope and multiple people, none of the party seems exactly nimble

Good thing they were in a party of more than 2 people I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, using their money as a reason to deny their attractiveness doesn't actually lessen how attractive they are. Kylie Jenner for example. No matter how little talent she has, or how much she paid to fix each problem she found with her face through surgery.. That girl is straight up stunning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never at any point said anyone has to agree with me. I'm saying you're calling a pair of shoes shit, in a place where those shoes are highly praised. It's like walking into a church and talking shit about the bible. There's no point to it. 

I've often said Reddit is a place for discussion, but given that your first comment opened with "This looks like shit," I don't know what you expect me to say. Oh yeah dude, that's cool, I guess you're right, they're shit? I did legitimately say everyone has their own taste, but given where you are, saying they're shit is close to pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay? Then don't wear them. Nobody asked you to look them up or quite frankly give your thoughts on them. People like them, people wear them. They're an exceptionally popular brand so I really don't see the point in talking shit about them.

EDIT: Just realized the "give your thoughts" part.. My bad team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I get some people assume that because there is a cleaner it gives way to said person making a mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but that cleaner is the guy looking after the leftover wrappers from food in chairs, the guy who sweeps the floor in an empty carriage, the one making sure the bathrooms are always hygienic. He doesn't get paid to go out of his way and break out a bunch of extra cleaning supplies to clean what is quite frankly shitty graffiti.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen some brave acts in my lifetime, but calling Yeezys ugly in /r/blackpeopletwitter may be the bravest them all.

Or dumbest. Most likely dumbest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever feel shitty when asking your SO for cash or a lend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pay was late today and won't be here til the end of the week. Seeing as I have living expenses and whatnot this is really fucking me over. So I kinda feel like to make it I need to ask her for cash, and in reality, I have only did this once before, and considering she knows I'm good for it she was completely fine doing this. 

With that said, my mam was a real piece of shit when it came to lending money/ asking for money and whatnot, so the whole "I'll give it back in a few days" agreement among people is really dirty in my eyes. Not in the sense of it being a shitty idea, but I'm always afraid to ask because I know what she's like.

But yeah, I rambled for a bit, but also feel it's necessary for my side of the question. Thanks for any thoughts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man of Steel: $291,045,518

Batman vs Superman: $330,360,194

Suicide Squad: $325,100,054

*DC's opening 3: 946,505,766*

-

Captain America First Avenger: $176,654,505	

Iron Man: $318,412,101

Thor: $181,030,624

*Marvel's opening 3: 676,092,230*

They may not be critically acclaimed movies, but they are most definitely making money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is wanting to make a good movie called repair mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this is what Im looking for. I had no idea about the RTE one until about 2 years or so after.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 2 years into high school when that happened. I was legitimately one of the top students in my French class. 

The end of the year I was one of the worst. I know it's absurd, but that night changed my opinion on France as a whole. I was a kid, but even after visiting France and growing up a bit... Eh, my opinion is the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone getting paid to keep an area clean and respectable doesn't mean fucking assholes can make the place messy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I guess I'll be in seeing it then, god damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 5th goal gave me goosebumps. What a way to end it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skipping work and skipping class are completely different. Get your lazy ass in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching one of these is now on my bucketlist.

Same, but for some reason unknown to me, they refuse to come to Ireland..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything is cool when you're part of a team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "are you cold fella?"

The following 15-20 seconds were just pure gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No I haven't and why is that relevant?

Because if we're talking about spin-offs, World of Ice and Fire is the go to source for what the spin off will be. There's also no real reason to be an arrogant cunt when replying to a guy asking a simple question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the trailers, that's what it felt like. Can you explain why it's not going to be another version of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   two other Academy Award nominations?

Best actress in joy, and best supporting in American Hustle. Yeaaahh, I'm not gonna back away from my point off that. I will however admit I forgot about Silver Linings. That still makes 2 great movies out of... 14?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know in reality they don't look very similar, but I will forever mix up Adam Driver, Hozier, and Bob Morley on first glance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone calls him a great actor. The guy has an incredible passion, and given his down to earth personality, people absolutely love him. But nobody is saying he's an incredible actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by the end of the movie he'll be turning back to his family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but since that one performance, what in the world has she done to earn the praise she has?

I know this is Reddit, but I loved Lawrence once. Watched all her movies, but god damn is she wooden in almost every role she's in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   flashbacks,and foreshadowing

Some of those flashbacks in season 5 were the best parts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm genuinely not sure what scenes are extended-only scenes, considering I maybe saw the basic trilogy.... once? And that was when they were released in cinema.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it veryyyyy hard to believe that a series that ran for what, 50-60 hours or so, can be condensed into a 2 hours movie. Shit, Ozymandias alone is about 50 minutes right? How in the world can 2 hours do it justice?

Along with the over exaggerated title praising that he's sharing free content from a copyrighted show, and his editing is somehow re imagining the show by cutting out 50+ hours.

EDIT: The post now has 30k upvotes.. Jesus christ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dropped to 3fps last night during a 2v1. From 40, to 3fps for maybe 5 seconds. 

Then I tend to average out at 22-25 for minutes at a time, rather than the 50 or so I normally have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailer makes it look like a comedic version of Drive, but according to everyone in this thread, it's set to be amazing. Guess I'll see how it plays out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are getting mad that they sell in game money.

Other people paying for the cards in no way effects their end of the game. I really don't see why people are so fucking angry about it, when in reality all it gives the guy paying a new house, new car maybe, some clothes, whatever else is up for sale. 

It's not like when they buy 10 cards they get an exclusive area for the high payers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends entirely on your first feel of the game I'd imagine. It's pretty big as far as I remember, so you will get the hours worth for whatever you pick it up for these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  then Antman and Wasp

 standalone woman superhero film

Ummmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the thread is still hot, can I just ask something.

Everyone flipped out at the Doomsday release for BvS trailer, and there is no actual announcement to the villain in this trailer, but I've seen Ares' name probably a dozen times basically talking like he's 99% the villain of this movie.

So can someone help me figure out how it'd be so bad to show Ares in a trailer coming up, given that most people who know the character, believe he'll be the villain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadow of Mordor is a great game, it really is, but if you know the actual story of certain topics they cover, and have a grasp on lore beyond the movies, it may be hard to play or enjoy the story.

War in the North may be more enjoyable. It's a classic hack n' slash with a bit more depth that expected, but apparently it was pretty buggy back when it was big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellowship of the Ring. 

Return of the King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that, but you know what I mean. 

Man of Steel is one of my go-to movies, but it's not the greatest example of a Clark/Superman movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patty Jenkins really looks to have nailed the feel of WW in this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man of Steel didn't *feel* like a Superman movie. 

BvS didn't *feel* like a Batman movie. (not saying it was meant to)

But my oh my, does this *feel* like a Wonder Woman movie. Everything about this trailer screamed WW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a damn fine trailer. 

This movie may turn out to be many things, but I feel it's fair to say it's almost guaranteed to be beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see what you're seeing. When he talked about going on the trip and coming back to fill the guys in, I was excited. He seems like another Cumia. A guy who is pretty big in reality, but has a personality that really fits with the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The breathingis hard to listen to, but when he went on that coughing spree ending with "get an iron lung" joke.. 

Shit man, in reality, I bet Woody would fucking love to be in bed or relaxing with family instead of recording/hosting/organizing the show. 

Props should be given where it's deserved. Thanks for pushing through this week.

EDIT: Just got to the actual details of his struggle lately.. Jesus, what a rough time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was impressed the first time, I realized he had the typical shape for it the second time, but when he did it the third time, while Mike was on the floor, good lord was I like "daaaaaaaaaamn" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leicester City winning the Premier League.

Nothing will ever be as shocking as the day the lifted that cup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I don't care how poorly reviewed the show is. I've heard people complain about Jessica Jones, and Daredevil season 2 constantly, but here I am completely happy having watched them. I'll give the show a go, and sure, it may just be a genuinely bad show, and it may start the downward spiral for the Netflix/Marvelverse but I very much doubt it because of your reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realistically, how slow is Guardian compared to other classes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been bouncing around classes/races for a few days now trying to find one that fits my style, and one that may appeal to me is Guardian. I love the idea of Guardian Hobbit, especially because of the whole Sam Gamgee aspect. 

But on that, I asked in world chat once how slow it was compared to Warden, a class I briefly played, and they said it wasn't even comparable. The Guardian is simply the slowest class in the game by a large reach. 

But... This has to be hyperbolic right? I don't mind slow, but the way people make it seem... I should probably trust them, but given that I was tank Warden, hearing that a class is 100x, 1000x slower than the bleeds and playstyle of that class tree, I find it hard to accept.

Thanks for any opinions on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have people turned against the Force Awakens? This is the first I've heard of it. Also have to remember almost everyone agreed upon release that it was pretty similar to A New Hope. Still one of my favorite Star Wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a spoiler tag..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing will happen for Avatar 2.

Incredible hype, it'll break records, look truly spectacular, then a year or two will go by and everyone will agree it's a pretty average story that was blown out of proportion because of the visuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear it doesn't have my curiosity..*brb* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have clearly never been to the NSFW side of Reddit. The comments are nothing but nice 95% of the time, and when there's something negative about the girl posting, people kick him out of the circle.

Reddit is too big a site to say any post by a woman is filled with nasty replies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real talk.. These two comments have my eyes watering. Why did I ever have to get so attached to a world such as that of Middle Earth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, rhe directors cut of Kingdom of Heaven was pretty fucking fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> an underrated powerhouse

John Goodman is many things. But underrated is not one of them. I legitimately don't think I've ever heard a bad thing about him or his acting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd ask which one, but given that username... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hal and the GLC #12] I know I'm a bit late to the party, but my oh my did this shot give me goosebumps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, this guy literally wasn't alive when the show was airing, it may be a legit question. 

Answer: She was the lead actress in the show Buffy the Vampire Slayer, a show that aired in the early 2000s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently ranked Diamond+

Able to analyze and break down League of Legends at a very high level

Ability to state your points concisely and generate critical feedback

Understand, and communicate the root cause of a problem

You realize where you are right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He most likely couldn't hold up the candle like the current adcs, but god damn, even if it fucked TSM for a few games.. The meme's would be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then there are those that will simply enjoy the movie, while not being to the level of people in that sub, but will be pushed aside regardless because the majority will have voted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Marketing for all DCEU films thus far, whether it be posters or trailers have been great. WB almost always has great marketing.

Were you around for the Doomsday announcement? That may be what legitimately started the "BvS is terrible" circlejerk in this sub. People went fucking insane because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit they called it. 

Come back to the thread later and people will find a way to pick it apart. 

Do you really want her sinking into the sand? Is it genuinely that big a deal? 

Come on people. Yes it's a DC movie, yes there is a pretty big chance it'll flop, but good lord give it a chance first instead of tearing literally every piece of promotion for it apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone fill me in on Casey?

I heard Brie was giving him some looks during the oscars but I have no idea why. I remember his brother doing some shady shit way back when but I've come to forget what that was too.

EDIT: Well holy shit that's more than I expected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But.. He has been playing Prof X for nearly 2 decades now. He is as much Professor X as he is Picard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no, of course I can't, but after 2 months you return with 4 spam posts, that lead to a forum post created by you. You can say it's for the community all you want but if you were a man of the community you'd have more posts.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You seem to be mistaken as to what kind of person I am, don't be.

Given your account has 4 posts of the same self-post promotion, and before those posts, there is a 2 month gap of interaction, can you *really* blame me for this? 

Even if you're not the kinda spamming user I say you are, it's still breaking the subreddit's rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I've tried to post this on has deleted my posts due to some anti-robot measures.

Probably because all you're doing is spamming a link to a post you made on the forums. So yes, it's triggering an anti-robot measure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Users must make 9 non-personal submissions (both posts and discussion-focused comments) for every post containing content they own or from which they benefit in some way"

Not only are you breaking a submission rule, but your last 4 posts have been this link to different LoL related subs. Please stop trying to spam your self promotion, it never works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone skips in line. 

Someone is being a loud cunt in the cinema. 

Someone texting while driving. 

To top it off, I'd have to be an ass on occasion too and add: Someone is running up the stairs and trips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reply instantly after messaging mods. Well thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you crazy? 

Season 5 was a really good season, it just got held down by the shitty Sandsnake plot. Remove that and you have: 

Mance's infamous death scene. Arya found the house of black and white. Sansa started her journey with Ramsay. Tyrion got kidnapped by Jorah. Jorah then gets infected with greyscale. Aemon dies. Jon goes to Hardhome. Then the entire episode of Hardhome. Jon kills a fucking White Walker for gods sake.  Dany rides Drogon. Cersei does the walk of shame. The season then ends with Jon dying, Arya blind, a dead Stannis, a dead Myrcella, Dany is missing, and Sam is off to become a Maester. 

Season 6 was truly incredible, but don't let that, and the Sand Snakes, take away from all the Season 5 did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went there because I'm an idiot. I see all these genuine criticism's about mic problems, audio levels, patreon issues, but you better fucking believe I read one comment about how I'm a shitty person so let's talk about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea that people will start claiming the Stark's are too strong, and the show is shit now because they're not killing one Stark per season like the good ol' days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rickon literally died 2-3 episodes ago. I really hope a gripe people find with the show is the strength of the Starks. Seems idiotic imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it creepy? 

How many people browse Reddit a day? How many of them in the same subs? I'd imagine there is a redditor or two you pass a day depending on where you live. Just because this guy saw what could have been, and quite frankly was, a funny moment, he's creepy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam was not portrayed as gay in LotR. He wasn't a Boromir or Aragorn style character, but he was very clearly in love with Rose in Fellowship, then continued to marry Rose in RotK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if we take away recommending shows, we lose what I believe to be a significant part of the sub. Taking away posts that people don't like because they see it too often seems dumb. There is surely someone out there who hasn't. I also used the Legion posts from today to convince a friend to watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's wrong though. It's mid July. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Everything] Season 7 will begin airing on the 16th of July. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game Of Thrones Season 7 airs the 16th of July. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was different for 3 or so, then it was all by the one guy, to the point of him even directing Fantastic Beasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya'll better not be acting bitchy about teasers for trailers. 

I'd punch a small child for a teaser/trailer/clip of S7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who doesn't fully understand DirectX differences. If I'm on a low end pc, do I run the lower DX for performance, or the higher one? I've heard lower for performance and higher for graphics, but this is showing performance buffs when going higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How slow is guardian? I played Warden a while back, and that was a lot of bleeds and whatnot. Is it slower than Warden? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given I was 10 at the time, I'd love for this to get another release for a weeks even, just so I can see it on a big screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe me when I say this, I know these movies are absurd and pretty awful. 

But god fucking damnit will I be seeing this in theaters. The Rock just changed the direction of a torpedo that was racing beside him, as he hung out of his tank/jeep. If that isn't the perfect reason to turn your brain off for 2 hours I don't know what is.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, out of curiosity of course, but would that work on a computer that already has an OS on it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this is a really dumb question, but looking at the lowest "esports" pc there, would I be required to buy an OS outside of that and install upon setup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

You realize not all leaks are reliable, right? 

There have legitimately been 3-4 leaks that appeared from sources worthy of believing, then after a while you hear it's a failed idea. At this point I'm done believing I know the plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one little hit really wasn't satisfying enough for the 2 minutes before it. What a damn shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm aiming to spend between 500-600 euro on a gaming pc. Where do I start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd much prefer if we aimed at the 500, rather than the 6, and quite frankly, I don't need a machine that can run it all. I don't play the most advanced games (although that is in part with having an old laptop). I play LoL, Dota, WoW, CSGo, basically the front page of Twitch appeals to me. My aim is to run Overwatch I guess. 

Also, I'm not sure if it comes with the question, but I'd go for x64bit windows 10, if that is something you guys offer to add in when making the build.

Thanks!

EDIT: Also, PcPartPicker. Is that a site strictly aimed at the US? I've seen a few builds and they often find parts from stores that are simply US only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a joke, but Fingolfin leaving a mark on his foot may be one of the most extraordinary feats in middle earth history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta love how the sub is called soccer, but if you were to call the sport soccer at all outside of the sub name, you'd be burned at the stake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlefield has those 64 man servers though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I were to go Elf or Dwarf, is it a reasonable thought to consider moving on down to the Shire after the intro series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Shire, but I really don't feel good about any of the Hobbit classes just yet, and men are too play for me right now. So on that, I was planning on going Elf Runekeeper, then once I complete the intro quests to the game, I'd hitch a ride as far as I can, or simply run there. How crazy is this idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Explains why this one is dying and other ones are actually popular You guys are against views.

Nope. That would be the complete lack of interest in gaining any form of growth from the hosts themselves. 

Other podcast's are always given a shout out simply because the guest decides to. 

Most common guests on PKA always mention it. PhillyD, Tucker, Boogier, Kweblle, all of these guys are tweeting about the night of recording and whatnot. Hutch himself even said in a vid or a tweet once that he was on and people should go watch. 

Forcing someone to give the podcast a shout out is a terrible way of introducing them to the show's style. Nobody wants to be given a job to do after being invited to chill for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> recommendations for something as good as this.

That depends entirely on what you want. Harry Potter is 8 movies long and gives you a connection to the characters just as much. 

Star Wars may also do it for you.

Game of Thrones is the closest fantasy epic but that's both a TV show, and veryyyy different from Lotr. 

In reality, even with my suggestions, it all depends on taste. You could do all the marvel movies. The x-men movies. The fast and furious movies. Take a franchise and watch it. Odds are, one of them will hit the spot you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably cut the first 20-25 seconds of this clip and have the same effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He nails it as Starlord. 

Also, I'm not sure on Reddit's opinion of the movie, but I found him pretty entertaining in Magnificent Seven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That spiderbite scene makes me cringe every time I watch it. Nothing has made me as anxious as the thought of that happening to me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Watch for the kick. Best in .25 speed] (https://youtu.be/0sEJeWB3RA8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they do, but at the same time, it just looks like really poor fight choreography.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was streaming this as it aired, I legitimately thought I was in a bogey stream because the music playing over the episode was soooo different to the rest of the show, it must have been the host of the stream was fucking around.

Nope. It just happened to turn out as one of the most brilliantly crafted pieces of music on tv, and quite frankly it still is IMO.

And before any of you ask why I'm on dodgy streams for the show, HBOGo, and HBONow, whatever else they have, is not available in my country so I'm forced to watch shitty 480p streams until I can get a 1080p version to download. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Just found a really nice boxset for the trilogy in a local store and will begin reading within the next few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, real quick, why is Eleventh Metal to the side? Is that a spinoff of the first book in the trilogy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. Start with Mistorn Era 1. Read Elantris if in the mood. Then follow release order. Gonna save this comment, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I saved my comment to come back after work, which happens to be now, and looking into it a bit more, I found [this] (http://i.imgur.com/lJZazjo.png)

So in finding this, it seems like there are waaaaaay more books than I imagined, and when you suggest something like Mistborn, the following books are in the order listed about right? 

Or is Mistborn the name given for the overall series in the sense that A Song of Ice and Fire is the title given to the series with Game of Thrones, Clash of Kings etc. 

Also, looking at it from an outside perspective, it seems Elantris is the easiest place to start, although it may not be his best or most grand tale, and given the color scheme of suggested vs must read... The linear story setup seems to be out the window and I'm confused/overwhelmed by it. 

You may not be here to help, but hopefully someone will read my reply and help me figure this out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. Sometimes I wonder why I watch them, then I realize the reason is being a fan of the characters so I deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like I really need to pick up his books then. Where do I start? Epic anime/hero moments are probably my favorite events in whatever I read/watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which class would you recommend for a first time player with the intention of being a Hobbit? (Also being a solo/duo player) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm convincing a friend to play, and they want to go Hobbit, but have no idea what the classes are like. 

With that, they said they'll be playing simply for the world. None of the instances or epics. 

What would you recommend in this case? I considered burglar, but that seems very rng based for crit, while also needing to know the buffs/debuffs/cc and whatnot. I have no idea what Guardian/Minstrel/Warden is like so I'd love some input. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or when they got sponsored by Warcraft and most definitely never watched the movie. Advising their fans to go spend money to see a movie they have no relevant opinion on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's progress, so yes, you should be happy it's a poorly optimized system right now, instead of a shitshow like it once was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough I guess. Getting any further into this kind of discussion may just leave me in the same spot as we noticeably have a different speech pattern, but it is what it is. 

Fun talk though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen every episode of every season, and wholeheartedly agree with you. The writing is painful lately in most of the shows, and the filming style is classic network tv level, with the same kinda forced drama on occasion. 

But... Arrow is what got me into comics, and since then my reading has only excelled my stake in the tv shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This season's writing has reallyyyyyy fucked Barry over. It's getting hard to like him at this point god damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I skipped the poems/songs in LotR up until I read of the tale of Beren and Luthien I believe. It made me wonder what else I missed and found myself reading the previous songs/poems to see what was up. It slows down the read of course, and if you try sing them, it'll be a tough read, but oh my do I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really conflicted. The title seems hyperbolic, the top comments praise him, but the further you go, the most you see people point to the flaws in his writing. The simplicity, the relationships, the shitty jokes, and then those who allow the writer's world views to morph their opinion on his writings.

So can someone give me a TLDR of what to expect if I were to look into his books, and where to start? Also why him being a Mormon is a big deal to some folk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, after writing it, I realized emphasize was the wrong word. It splits them up. Sounds kinda silly to say, but if you read it out loud, it just didn't flow like a normal sentence to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate Legion. Not because of anything the show has done wrong, but as someone who has enjoyed Flash/Arrow/Supergirl/Legends for most of each shows respective airing (avoiding ArrowSeason4)... 

Fuck did Legion make it harder to enjoy these other shows. The quality of the writing, along with how fantastic it looks.. Watching Flash today was a "do I really wanna finish this ep" kinda moment, and damn is it sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely loved it. 

I know a lot of people hated Elektra but I really can't remember what was so awful about that season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, after Daredevil, I imagine a lot of people went in expecting another kinda superhero show with a dark take on it. Not a detective story that had a heavy emphasis on her past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really though? Applying a comma usually attaches an emphasis on the following word, even if it's a slight change. Emphasizing "players" leaves me wondering if I misread the sentence.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there a comma after forcing? 

Sorry this is unrelated to the textbox, but damn son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Can Kyle not flub up ad reads? Yeah, and he should. Can he or Taylor record a back up recording? Yeah, and one of them should. No excuse for it

So why don't you, someone with direct and constant communication with the guys, tell one of them to record it, or you yourself record it given that you're always in the chat anyway. 

people wonder why no one enjoys coming to this subreddit or engaging with people, the people always jump to conclusions.

It's not jumping to conclusions. The PKA Patreon has existed for nearly 3 years. Promises were made, ideas were given up, plans were thrown out to the fans. So far we've had 3 trips. Yes, PKN is consistent and I appreciate that, but where are the ringtones. Where are the meetups? The trips? Shit, even the hangouts are pretty inconsistent.

Don't get me wrong Chiz, I've always appreciated what you've done for the show in terms of sponsors and guests, but you can't act high and mighty on this one. You guys are in the wrong here, and treating the fans like a bunch of idiots who cry wolf constantly is not the way to go about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also once believed that he would never be sponsored by something he doesn't personally believe in. That hasn't been the case about 2 years or so. Some of the shit they sponsor he will never use, wear, or view, but they give him a check so.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also once believed that he would never be sponsored by something he doesn't personally believe in. That hasn't been the case about 2 years or so. Some of the shit they sponsor he will never use, wear, or view, but they give him a check so.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw the trailer openly showing a punch knock someone out, when it's very clear on camera that he didn't make actual contact with the guy.

What a shame too. It's continuing to spiral downward for the Netflix/Marvelverse.

EDIT: Here is the clip. [Watch in .25 speed] (https://youtu.be/0sEJeWB3RA8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treat PKA like a normal podcast and stop giving them money if you have a problem rather than fill the subreddit with butthurt crying.

Nobody is upset about the podcast. It's the lies and promises they made that have people in an uproar, along with the baffling ignorance Woody is applying on the matter. He clearly fucking browses the sub and does it at least once or twice a week, yet he calls himself an idiot for visiting the haters. 

The one place on the internet that is devoted to the podcast is simply a collection of haters in his mind and fans are tired of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phew, you took the correction the right way. I felt it was pretentious of me, but given that I love to see corrections when browsing, I'd hoped you appreciated the fix :')

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These low tier puns make me wanna bARF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh, okay I'm with you then. Some of the best movies, or at least my favorite movies in the recent years have been action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda confused by your statement. Are you saying action and quality are tied together in the sense that it would never reach 80% ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How significant is the information missed in the chapters leading up to it? 

I just finished reading about the creation of Ea and it was rather difficult, so if it's possible, I'd love to read CoH then come back one day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't expecting it, but I'm glad it's here. I loves me some learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How important is reading Silmarillion before Children of Hurin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm working my way through LOTR right now, and while it's wonderful, I'm been really drawn in by Children of Hurin. I've heard slight details of the story through my time here and r/lotr, but I've also heard the Silmarillion is pretty necessary for it given that it provides a significant amount of backstory and leadup to the events in CoH.

So, I thought I'd ask you guys. How much sense would CoH make without reading Sil before hand? Or is it possible to choose a few chapters among the Sil to read before CoH, without reading all of the Sil?

Thanks for any thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> optimizing*

But I'm also not trying to play victim. I'm just saying I've been playing him before the meta switch, during it, and I'll continue it after. My point being it's the classic fixup from riot of fucking the champ when it's the build that made it nerf worthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lethality was what made Varus that god tier of adc. 

Varus himself is only top tier now because people didn't realize lethality made him what he was. 

Those of us that played him before lethality are getting truly fucked here. Give us a build that makes us meta? Nerf it. Put us back to our old styles? Nerf him. 

From god tier to dumpster. The classic patch tradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying Superman appearing in two or so episodes of Supergirl was the only thing holding it together?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadow of Mordor is great on ps4. Fluid, great graphics, load times are wonderful.

Shadow of Mordor on ps3 however... Loading into menu takes 5-10 seconds. Loading into game/zone takes about 30. Sometimes you'd be running into an orc 'village' and some of the wooden textures wouldn't load, so instead of climbing the side of a shack that has planks along the sides to hold it up, and of course for you to cling to, it's just a brown/green mesh. I'll try find images.

EDIT: This isn't Shadow of Mordor, but this is the kind of texture bug I was talking about, and it happens every 20-30 minutes on older consoles. [Here] (http://i.imgur.com/IWfZ5bd.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I guess I'll see if I can pick it up, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How well does it play on the U?

Are we talking even gameplay/graphics or is it another Shadow of Mordor ps3/ps4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's just not your thing. Like I said, I brushed it off for months, but fell in love evntually. That may never happen for you, and that's just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bias towards the opener if I'm honest. It was the memorable flow of the lyrics that hooked me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... I knew after writing that it pretty much sums up most musicals, but I also haven't given many a listen through audio only.(I've seen a handful or so and it's always in person) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently fallen into it. 

I remember back when it was on everyone's mind I brushed it off as a musical, and a musical I would never see at that. 

Then I stumbled across the soundtrack a few days ago, listened to the first song about a dozen times and then realized there are 2 more hours to listen to. I'm baffled by how well it tells the story through music and music alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -5 points but he got gold. 

Sums up this sub in a post :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. He's 76 years old and they still have to get a makeup team in to make him look like an old man. What a lucky immortal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Danny Devito to play the full Squirtle evolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought was "was it really a mistake!?!? I wonder how it'd come to be..."

This off season is hitting harder than most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not clear to those outside the loop on viking history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the album] (http://imgur.com/a/j1BLI)

[Here is the image in question] (http://i.imgur.com/v8rfAAv.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is praising a director and cast circlejerk? 

I really don't get this sub sometimes. Wanting to put Villeneuve on a movie is circlejerk, but when it comes to talking shit about Snyder or an Adam Sandler movie, everyone in the comments is completely fine with it, and it's usually top comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I'm glad he got to talk to the guys after being a fan for so long, but I also feel I shouldn't keep his absurd thoughts out of the writing when giving my weekly opinion on the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is criticism on how he acts suddenly me being jealous? Believe me I'm not, I'm happy with what I have now. I just hate the way he talks about money and surgery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [yep, here you go] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q-JgG0ECp2U) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably some of the finest acting that came out of 2016. Also covers some topics I imagine almost everyone can deal with on some level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know sickness times vary among different people, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right? Defending a company that has put out some pretty stellar games last year.. Fuck them amiright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. 

The Dark Knight was a great movie, but Ledger elevated it to way more than it ever should have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diamond in the rough and underrated gem are completely different statements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  assume he's depressed

I never said he's depressed. He himself said in an AMA he has never been depressed, and would never claim to be. What I am pointing to is that he also said he started to have panic attacks on stage, and his Kanye bit in Make Happy was a real way to confront it and it helped him manage with his struggle a bit more. 

Don't get me wrong, I know his act is incredibly well thought out, and a lot of it is a mixture of irony and self inflection, but nonetheless, I've always seen him as a guy with a whole lot of conflicting thoughts in his head due to the life he leads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine left when I was 2 or so. He would have been early 20s at the time, so I imagine he caved to the thoughts every 20 year old Dad would have. 

I met him about 13 years later, and it turns out he has another family. The fun part is that they seems to be incredibly, incredibly happy and his two daughters were these incredibly popular school athletes. Turns out he did the whole "I'm raise you to be the best you can possibly be" thing.

Of course I'll always be slightly jealous that I was too soon, but considering a lot of people give runaways dad's shit, it was really entertaining to hear how he turned it all around at attempt 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
