<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reccomend supermega to, it's got a very similar feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been away from the game for a while </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I have no idea what's happened. Gnomes, unsolvable puzzles? Wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Assassins Creed Syndicate have an modern day story? x-post /r/xboxone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 10:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only played the AC games up until brotherhood so when I played Black Flag I was really confused by the out of the animus elements with it being a video game development company (?) or something? I always liked the modern day story but what I bought the AC games for was to run around history. Will I be confused by syndicate? It's actually reached a price I'm willing to pay on Xbox one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 10:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the story tie in to 4 and unity? Or is it kind of standalone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard not so stellar things about 3 so I didn't bother. I was getting bored of AC at that point. It's one of those thing that if it came to bc I'd probably get it now to see what I missed. And revelations. So do none of the newer games have modern stuff? Is it all set in past now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there's no out of the animus bit like in the originals with Desmond? It's all set in the past? If so I'm picking it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Assassins Creed Syndicate have an modern day story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only played the AC games up until brotherhood so when I played Black Flag I was really confused by the out of the animus elements with it being a video game development company (?) or something? I always liked the modern day story but what I bought the AC games for was to run around history. Will I be confused by syndicate? It's actually reached a price I'm willing to pay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the update I haven't been able to use my Xbox and have had to borrow my brothers who doesn't use his. I've been ignored my major Nelson, Xbox supports advice was to buy a new Xbox. I've been very disappointed in how I've been treated with this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally held my breath when Matt was going down the spiral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 12:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Children! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 12:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So all the way back in season 1? That's cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 11:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been away from this game for a while (BF1 beta what can I say?) but this all sounds like very good stuff. I was hoping community challengers would revitalise my love for the game guess I'll have to wait and see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 11:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What dont you like about the Wii U? I love mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movies were considered "timeless" when they came out but don't hold up today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last year I subbed to here around this time as September is the time I start to feel festive and I'm back again! Here's to the next 4 months! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting one. Do you think all men should act masculine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who yong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently picked up Battlefront so I am looking for someone to play that with. I also play regularly Plants vs Zombies GW 1 and 2, rocket league, worms wmd and I own battlefield 4 and will pick up battlefield 1 when that come out.

-subject1260nitt , UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It totally isn't by the way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 10:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's a return to form and reminds me very much of Jon Grumps editing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 09:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you didn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha basically this is what prompted the question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has sleepycabin ever offended you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're big enough to not let it get to you or complain about it. However no matter what you still got a little bit offended? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who draws the thumbnails? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the art style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 08:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I disagree. Pre ordering games just shows game companies you're willing to buy games before reviews come in and people play them which means most of the time they try and sell a broken product and get away with it. I mean they already have your money what is there to prove?  I've never preordered a game but if there's a game that I know I'm definitely going to get I never have a problem just going to the store and picking up a copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 08:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I compliment girlfriend without seeming lustful/perverty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has a lot of issues with self confidence and I call her beautiful and I believe she's beautiful but I want to tell her specifics to. For example the other day we went to a wedding and she has the most amazing legs I want to encourage her and love her by letting her know this but don't want to seem weird or a pervert. What's the best way to tackle these situations.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We didn't get a disco  the last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 13:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Primary schools do now. We got fish   chips on our last day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is! It's a mere four months away! ... Ass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's August. It's been a year and bit and it's nearly Christmas. You know what I want? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want and by want I mean need.. A complete Jake and Amir Blu Ray Set. I really do. I've been asking for this for years... Days even! And it's no where to be found. I want it in my wish list and in my pisslist! When will you make my peeality a reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care what this is. I'm not clicking this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children's UKTV character Mr Blobby. I'd link a picture but I'm still scarred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah sick strats at 8:32!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope that editing all these things while keeping on top of their own sketch comedy channel, let's play channel and podcast doesn't burn him out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is the Grumpoverse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to supermega. Having a hard time listening to podcasts and watching videos as both Matt and Ryan's voices sound the same </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This a problem for anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cinema Usher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After finishing life is strange I sobbed. I felt empty for about 3 days after when I thought about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's people who are constantly late. I find it just so rude, if you know you naturally are a laid back and often late person just set an alarm earlier or please the house earlier I just don't get it when people are constantly late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing you just can't empathise with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That it's not okay to ask questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 01:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suzy in all her goose glory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 01:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 15:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Bethesda want that $$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Without fail I will wake up at 4am every morning without an alarm, I don't mean to and I hate it. What are some stupid things your body does to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty I don't remember as it was a while a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty this year I've spent a lot of time on plants vs zombies garden warfare two. It's a fun game to play when I'm listening to podcasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience it's always been the other way around. I spent 110 on headphones once and they broke within a week. I got a replacement pair and they also broke within the same time frame. Last pair of headphones I bought were these 15 Sony ones and they've lasted me two years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take any Popcorn you don't eat home with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is only on YouTube right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I feel as if these are the highest quality videos the grumps have put out for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a general rule of thumb I don't preorder games and Recore is no exception even though I am planning on picking it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject1260nitt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your least favourite mechanic in video games at the moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 10:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should be over it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I loved Far Cry 3 but never got to play this. Always wanted to though! Will be picking it up!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow... That's hilarious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resident evil 4. I think it's one of the few games that changed up the gameplay of a series and it was well received. It's a fun survival shooter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some free time over the next few days. Add me subject1260nitt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I heard this episode had dolphin pussy I would just assume Chris would be the one to initiate it. Was pleasantly surprised it was Ross  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oney episodes are always my favourites.

"This is family friendly you dick!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 10:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This community is pretty bad but I literally rolled my eyes when I saw the 'Does Arin have a crush on Suzie' topic had over 400 upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon - Goof Troop
Danny - Disney Princesses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 15:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know it's just a bit annoying that my console isn't really working at the moment, getting some writing done though so that's a positive. I guess I saw it as a bit money grabbing telling me to buy a new console. I have tried the offline recovery tool and the problem still persists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 11:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Arin approach Chris first? Source?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 10:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was 2 days ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 10:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha way ahead of you! Already tweeted them but none of them have got back to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 09:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember the choice I made, I'd say I probably said remove everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 09:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept the games installed to an external so there was nothing on the internal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 09:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seriously been considering getting rid of the thing; I've said I'll give it a week but if I do I won't be trusting Microsoft as a brand again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 08:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, not even things on the internal will work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 08:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's ridiculous I wouldn't mind if my console actually worked but it doesn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 08:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I've factory reset the console and moved all games to an external and still nothing will open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My unsatisfying time with Microsoft support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 08:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the update the other day I haven't been able to use my console, no games, apps nothing will open. Right now my Xbox is a glorified paper weight. I've done everything moved games onto an external and hard reset, reset everything and it still won't work. I phone up support and they told me to do all these things when i told them I have they told me I mustn't have otherwise it would be working. I asked if I could send off my Xbox to repair or something and they told me to buy a new one. For a problem that Microsoft has made on my console I have found the support I got disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair Sony asked Microsoft last gen pretty much the same question and they said no, so it's no wonder Sony won't bite now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was the first thing I tried the other day, I was just wondering if anyone else had this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah, I've tweeted at major nelson but haven't heard anything yet. I had an evening off last night to play and none of my games loaded... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think the new update has bricked my console... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 10:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50% of the time I'm not able to sign in. When I actually can then none of my games load up, neither do any of the apps? Is there anything I can do?

Edit:it's been like this since the update dropped. I have turned on and off and hard rebooted the system and it still doesn't work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! UK and playing now. Thanks OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My [21,M] Girlfriend [23] of four months called be 'brother' I'm feeling very confused by the situation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 17:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context is massively important in this story. Me and my girlfriend have been really close friends for about 6 years, to the fact we used to call each other brother and sister. We stopped doing that a few months before we got together and well we got together. She said it again the other day when we were going somewhere. 'Shall we go bro?' however immeditedley said 'Oh that was weird' Ive been worrying about it ever since, maybe she doesn't see us as gf/bf anymore and has reverted back to thinking of me like a brother? What do I do?

[TL;DR] GF called me brother, and its confused me a little bit. Am I overreacting at a slip of the tounge or could there be more to it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 10:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GT: subject1260nitt

I'll be level 1 again but oh well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 12:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Force Awakens is a great game. The leap between TCS and the new one is truly next gen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 12:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah really? Shit... Think my hype has dropped now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that people actually play this online. The online for this helped develop the online for GTA:O. I remember having great times with friends online on this game and just hope we can breathe life into it once more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 09:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would i go about doing that? From the uk here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 01:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brought Liars and Cheats about 2 hours ago. Don't mind too much the game itself was reduced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are h3h3 remixes a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 11:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please Popcap expand the Backyard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HoW dU u KeIl en GAhDiN wArFaRe????????? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 09:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 01:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Hamill is in Kingsman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 00:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering is this vanquishes on all game modes? Or do you have to play team vanquish for them to count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh darn. I wasn't looking properly and assumed he was a new character. I'll edit now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to see when the game installs. I got it when I bought the game. On the recipes it says Xbox one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently the Lego Star Wars:The Force Awakens season pass is a 360 game... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 12:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Glad to see they won't abandon the single player content!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 12:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there more BB quests then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 11:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you hope from Zombtropolis Part 2 later today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 11:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems we knew exactly what we were getting with part 1. We knew two classes and a map. This one seems to be a bit more secretive other than we know about a new chomper customisation. What do you hope we get?

Honestly I hope they bring back Taco Bandits that was by far my favourite game mode in the first game.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 11:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plants vs Zombies Garden Warfare 2 is taking up my time! New dlc comes out today so that should be fun. Only stopping to play some bc games like halo wars and black ops.

Oh! I'll also be buying Lego Force Awakens today. So very busy atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 10:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was...  Underwhelming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 12:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd wish they'd just tell us when it gets delayed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 12:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Especially since she doesn't call or text beforehand to say "Honey because your feelings matter to me, I'm just calling to say that I'm getting breakfast with [friend's name] because [valid reason]". 

To be honest she wouldn't normally tell me what she's doing that day this way anyway. However I get your point, Ive felt for a while that she doesn't care. Maybe she doesn't. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 11:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Or at least I would make sure not to get emotionally invested, since she isn't.

Yeah I have thought this for a while, she tells me that she is but she never acts like it. Yesterday I sent her a text saying what I loved about her, like it was from a place of vulnerability and she just put a heart emoji back. Each day I feel more and more that a break up is coming. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 10:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just make sure she knows she's not doing anything wrong and that its not her fault.

Maybe it'd be good to talk about expectations in the relationship and whether or not she wants to talk to you everyday?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 13:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have anxiety and I know exactly what you're going through. In fact I feel that I. Could have written this about a month ago. I'd say it's always good to tell your girlfriend how you feel. I did and while she is still bad at texting back she makes me feel valued when I'm with her a lot more. Chin up and keep going buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 12:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll play this after doom then, always wondered about the new wolfenstein games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your exam in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you can be interested and not vote. I'll be following it until I sleep. Theres no real emotional element for me but watching everyone else here is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some ways I can get over my insecurities in my relationship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 23:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya guys. I've recently realised that I am very insecure in my relationship. Me and the gf have spoke about it and she's so loving and supportive but I just struggle to believe her. I struggle to believe it when she tells me she loves me. I think she's going to break up with me everyday. I think she can get someone better. If we don't talk one day I assume we are going to break up. I love this girl and I don't want to ruin that with my self esteem. I'm seeing a therapist but what are some other practical things I can do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 09:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game felt doomed from the start... And when they kept delaying it it didn't bode well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd appreciate some advice on how to play cactus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 09:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have over two days of game time on GW2 and have barley touched cactus. Every time I go to play as her I did pretty much instantly. Any tips and tricks for your standard every day cactus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 09:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I hoped so. The game went 'gold' like a month before release haha this shouldn't happen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the games been out for 7 months now... And it's still unplayable on my console. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 09:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously is this going to get sorted out? Whenever I load up the game it just lags a lot and eventually crashes. My game is unplayable, cmon Avalanche. You're better than this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better seasonings than salt and butter to flavour corn on the cob? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 22:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going on a corn on the cob streak but I don't really like how sweet it is. what are better ways to season and flavour it than butter and a sprinkle of salt?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 10:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back to /r/Jontron with you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 10:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... So what happens to the xp that you earn as mastered characters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 10:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol so random
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could do this in fallout 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [UK] Me and my girlfriend are ordering in Chinese on her request, Ive never had Chinese anything before any recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 13:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know I don't like sweet and sour anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 12:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She knows, it was her idea to get councelling.

Yeah I'm getting help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 11:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I've been going to councelling for a while now. It's helping; but for some reason weddings don't agree with me. The last wedding I went to I couldn't speak to anyone and cried a lot. I however hash e advantage of making them look like happy tears lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend (23, F) of 3 months sister is getting married this month. I (21,M) have been invited to the evening reception as I wasn't in the picture when wedding planning happened. I don't want to go as I have social anxiety. Am I justified In this? How can I convey this to my girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 11:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is taking her friend as a +1 to the whole day (this was arranged before we got together so I don't mind that she didn't ask me) but I've been invited to the evening do. I don't like dancing and I'm introverted with social anxiety. I will barley know anyone there and my girlfriend will be dancing with her friends for the majority of it. Due to that fact I don't really want to go. Heck I've only met her sister twice, am I justified in not going or should I suck it up?

TlDr : don't want to go to gfs sisters wedding reception due to mental/emotional reasons. Am I justified in this and if so how do I tell her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 10:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought superman vs goku was a stupid idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't they release the beats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 10:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I adore the beat used for Austin powers in the new battle and would love to listen to it without the rapping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 10:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft have said it's possible and they are open to it. I believe Sony is the side that isn't too thrilled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 18:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd disagree. Sony have crash and resi which are two massive names in gaming. Even people who are bored of zombies could probably get behind a new resident evil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's he unlisted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Damon's beard in the Martian. I watched a thing around the time of the oscars about cgi and it showed them making it. It's bizzare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 23:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they did it multiplayer I think there'd have to be a mode with them on and a mode with them off
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 23:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't laughed at a Jontron like this in a while. I thought 99% of the jokes were spot and it was just a great quality video. I'll be watching this again many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think people selling their Xbox's is what Phil had in mind this e3! Oops on his part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically I play my ps2, GameCube way more than my one. I'd kill to get some multiplat original Xbox games on the one and the old exclusive platformers to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's going down with the town hall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think we will get more single player content in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoy the backyard battlefield mode when just wanting to relax and I liked the campaigns. Do you think there's any chance we will get more single player stuff? Or should popcap soley focus on multiplayer now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't want this, I listen to sleepycast while doing stuff/driving. This would be badd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, seriously? Dudes determined I'll give him that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 13:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain what cortana even is? I know it's a voice recognition thing, do you need Kinect for it to work or can you just use your headset? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You talking about the 75k pack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds exactly like me and my girlfriend. My girlfriend hates texting so sometimes it could look like she's ignoring it but I know she isn't. Maybe texting just isn't his thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sick and tired of feeling shitty and insecure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought my girlfriend was ignoring my texts tonight but her phone was just on silent. She's so understanding but I fucking hate feeling like this. I hate feeling like no one likes me or people hate me. Fuck sake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banjo Kazooie is my favourite franchise, and I am super excited for this game.

However I was hoping this game wouldn't just be Banjo Three with different characters. I was hoping for its own charm, hopefully I'm wrong but we will see when it comes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I feel like I'm reading my own thoughts from a few months ago, me and my girlfriend barley text during the week if we want to talk at length it's always a phone call. If you looked at our texts you probably wouldn't think we were together but in person it's different. Some people (like us) just don't like texting, you have to adjust to that or if it's too much let her know how you feel about it. It may not change anything but at least she will know 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 10:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fallout 4 and witcher 3. I loved open world RPGs and fallout 3 is probably my favourite game of all time. Unfortunately witcher is hard for me to get into because I'm not a massive fan of fantasy settings and fallout just took too many features  out of fallout 3 for me to care about it: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 10:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GW1 and GW2, Xbox One - subject1260nitt

Down for anything!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 01:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plants vs Zombies Garden Warfare 2, is the first time in a very long time I have bought a triple A game and thought the price was worth it. The amount of content and support from the developers should be the norm and not the exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently asked my girlfriend what she expected from me... (Relationship question) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She said to lead her towards Jesus together. Which I think is a very good answer, albeit a little safe. She then went on to say that she never really was looking for much in a guy just someone who loves Jesus. This got me thinking is that enough to build a relationship on? I dunno it seems a little ... Vauge. Almost like there's nothing about me personally she finds special or likes apart from my faith. Maybe she didn't mean that or maybe I'm over thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well this got weird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I am a little too fragile. I don't know what I expected but I obviously didn't get it. Maybe it requires a little bit more thought from my side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll talk to her next time I see her. Thanks for the response  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I (21 M) felt ignored by my gf (23 F) at a wedding we both attended yesterday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 19:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been together for 3 months and this is the first wedding we attended together we were both invited to the whole day of festivities and overall it was good. I don't like weddings or big parties though, I struggle at them and she know that. Throughout the whole day she kept talking to her friends who are more social and didn't ask how I was holding up or anything. 1 or 2 of her friends asked if I was okay as I'm good friends with a few of them and I just said yes. Heck at one point during the night I got up to dance with her (trust me getting on a dance floor is a big deal for me) and she just turned away and continued dancing with her friends. I felt so lonely. At the end of the day before I left (we were going with different people) I told her I loved her and she just said 'aww' and scrunched up her face. I feel pissed that she didn't show me much attention. Am I being ridiculous or do I have a right to feel angry?

TL:DR gf talked to her friends all day at a wedding when she knows I struggle at big party environments. Am I right to be annoyed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take her to the moon for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 10:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, text her tommorow. It'll be alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 11:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently brought RDR for PS3 as I really fancied playing it, if they made it bc id buy it again for sure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avatar props are only available to people who don't touch themselves at night  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... People didn't like Pirates? I thought it was hilarious. However I may be biased as I think anything Arrdman touches is gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope there's times she has days off and at the end of the day I ask what she's done and she says not a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair the cable they gave me is quite small... Is there a way I can just buy the charger cables? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess, is it normal for someone to go days without speaking though? She's fine when we're together but if she really liked me I'd have thought she'd have wanted to talk to me a it more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Controllers not working, charge light on console flashing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently purchased a PS3 and the controllers aren't working, on boot up it tells me to plug a controller in and press the PlayStation button but neither of the controllers I bought have worked. I bought them from different places, I've tried resetting the controllers and leaving them plugged in but still no luck. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so it's just that she doesn't really make an  when we aren't together. Feels weird when I don't speak to her all day and she doesn't text me first. I always feel like I initiate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because she doesn't text me in the day, and it makes me feel she doesn't like me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girlfriend (23) texts me (21) as if we are not together but is really intimate when we are together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 13:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend texts me as if we aren't together. She will just put okay or yeah with no kisses. Before we went out this is how we used to text when we were just friends. It sometimes makes me feel like she doesn't want to be with me. Am I overreacting? 

TL:DR GF is awful at texting, what do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long do we think Sony will support the PS3 for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a lot of thought I have decided that tommorow will be the day I buy a PS3, catching up on the Sony exclusives from last generation will be a fun thing to do. I'm also intrigued in getting free games with ps+. Do you guys think they will still roll these out for a while and that sony will still support the console for a while yet? Or are we at the end of its lifespan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I (21 M) suffer from anxiety and every single day wake up thinking my girlfriend (23 F) hates me what do I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 11:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my gf have been going out for about two months now and all is on the outside going swimmingly. I have anxiety and we have worked together through some things but I generally seem to over react to things. We both attend a church and she seems to want to keep our relationship quiet. Not in a bad way we are just both that type of person. We haven't put anything on social media, because again we don't need to. But my head over reacts to all these things and thinks that she doesn't want to be with me. It's things like when she doesn't text back. For example yesterday she said she would text me before I went to work and she didn't. As I write this now I can see how I massively overreacted but I can't stop the thought that she doesn't want to be with me?

Reddit, how can I calm down? I'd like to talk to her about it but I'm worried it'd scare her off.

TL:DR - I have anxiety and keep thinking my girlfriend doesn't want to be with me because of little thing she does or doesn't do. How can I calm down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 16:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently been confirmed that you need the IW disc to play CoD 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 08:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thomas.unitt@gmail.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LF :Plump Princess account Have:Jae account, Kimberley marvel videos, big cutie Britt videos and big cutie gallery vids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 23:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 12:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add me specialunitt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I was on a double Decker bus and the person at the front on the top deck got off, causing the whole top deck to start a race to see who would sit at the front. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to know that I feel like this sometimes to, and it's okay to feel that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know how to talk about my depression with my girlfriend, any tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's known for a while I have depression but sometimes I want to tell her that today's been a particularly bad one but my depressed mind thinks id be bothering and or she'd get sick of my bs and break up with me. How can I ask if she's okay with me talking about it when I'm down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is buying a PS3 still justifiable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 11:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I owned a PS3 a few years ago and loved it, however it died and I never bothered replacing it. I own an Xbox one at the moment and will sell it in the next year to buy a ps4 however there are still loads of games from last gen I never got to play. Should I still buy a PS3? Are song still supporting ps+ free games for it? How is multiplayer generally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 00:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I would like them to go back to the street gangs where the series started. The gist I enjoyed most with IV were the bits where your powers were limited and just had to use guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 14:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just find every single character in LoTR uninteresting. I'm way more of a character driven guy. I can't stand Frodo, can't relate to him at all. I'd say the only character I don't find boring is probably Gandalf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 09:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got that from the downvotes, the worst part is I actually lost a few friends over this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not enjoy The Lord of the Rings trilogy and think that The Hobbit was alot better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see a series about the bald bespectacled chemistry teacher from Breaking  Bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 09:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe me, its not just America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My [21,M] girlfriend [23,F] struggles to show affection towards me and is scared of intimacy. What can I do to help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 12:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently got into a relationship with my friend of 6 years, we both thought there was more going on and decided to give it a go. I'm her first boyfriend so she's new to be whole thing. We've been going out for about 2 months now and it's going fine, however she really struggles to show affection towards me. I'm the one who always texts first, goes in for a hug or kiss, phones her. She does those things sometimes but it's very far and few between. I don't want to put her off by going in too thick but sometimes it makes me feel that she doesn't want to be with me if I'm the one whose putting the majority of the work in. I want to help her to understand I like affection to and would like her to do those things. What should I do Reddit?

TL;DR - GF struggles to show affection and makes me feel like she doesn't want to be with me. What do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 01:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when you drive me, people will think you're gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How cool would it have been though if the Spider-Man reveal wasn't in the trailer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's some must see television that no one is talking about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found chapter 2 so boring... Still need to finish it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I normally love silly humour such as monty Python and Deadpool but Sunset just felt a little try hardy most of the time. I cringed a lot while playing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its been nearly 6 months, why does the game still have framerate issues on consoles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 13:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in December Avalanche promised that the games issues would get fixed but they still haven't. My game on XB1 is pretty much unplayable at this point, is this game going to get fixed or do I have to sell it off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 20:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 14:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id say definately give it a go, it's mindless for the most part but I've had a lot of fun. Easy achievements to if you're into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played Lego Marvel Super Heroes in anticipation for civil war and you know what? Its a lot of fun, I haven't played a Lego game in quite a while but the fact you can explore new York is really cool. Will probably try and 100% this at some point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
