<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8542</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 05:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and let's be honest here, most of the people complaining will still begrudgingly watch it when it comes back on next year.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 05:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. In light of the explosives being set off in Manhattan earlier this week, I'm wondering if they decided to cut the episode short to play it safe... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 04:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dicks out for all the "Dicks Out For Tyrell" guys, if you will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 14:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao yes, I was making fun of that when I watched it last night. For how much sketchy shit she's done, you'd think she would have learned by now that * STARE SILENTLY WITH BUG-EYED-EXPRESSION * is, uh, not the best way of looking not-guilty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 14:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it cannot be passed on genetically, as it is almost always shaped by severe trauma. However, a predisposition to severe mental illness can and often *does* run in families.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something else bugging me: I'm realizing more and more how little we know about Darlene. At this point, she's too major of a character for us to have no idea where she lives, what she does aside from fsociety, if she has another job, how/why she learned to hack, etc.

Dunno if I'm necessarily sold on the idea that she isn't real, but I'm definitely starting to get suspicious about her character. 

edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I think is going on w/ the increasingly blurred distinction between Elliott and his dad: it's been obvious for awhile that Elliott has dissociative identity disorder, but for the most part, he has been aware of when Mr. Robot takes over and can, to some extent, control this. 

With DID, as its severity increases and the individual undergoes higher levels of stress, it isn't uncommon for these shifts between the person's "alters" to happen without warning. It's quite common for people who have experienced extreme trauma to go long periods of time with multiple alters before they ever realize that their "true" self wasn't always present.

This is also where phrases like "out of body experience" come into play, where people with DID legitimately feel that they separate from their physical form. Some people even report "watching themselves" act and think as a completely separate person, with no control whatsoever. 

I'm guessing that as Elliott adjusts to the shitshow outside of prison, his mind is kicking into Mr. Robot without him realizing it. He's gone from a rigid and constant routine to complete unpredictability and I'd bet that this instability is only going to get worse as the season progresses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angela   Dom 4ever 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of Reddit, what is the most ridiculous lie you've told your children in order to avoid a sensitive subject? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He(m) and I(f) were co-workers. Due to the nature of the job, we were forced to live, work, eat, sleep, shop, and relax together for 10 months with a small group of 5 other people. We figured that if we could date that entire time without getting sick of one another, we must have something good going. We celebrated 1 year together last week, and he just moved into his new place near me so that we can go to the same university together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
