<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't just say this shit and then not tell us what they are. You monster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daaaaaaaamn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, I'm not some kind of fucking casual when it comes to Swans. Duh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerky/troll farm collective, sweet. As the resident lush I'll bring champagne, pot brownies, and swans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc and I traditionally stay in, cook ourselves a decadent meal, I bake an apple pie, we drink too much wine, boom, done. 

He got on a plane this morning for a weeklong business trip after less than 24 hours notice. My massive anxiety is driving me insane because he hasn't landed yet. I went and blew the normal amount of our entire weekly grocery bill on five meals for some of the time that he's gone. And got a box of wine. (But like, the *classy* box.) I haven't been single for Valentine's Day since... high school? So this is weird for me. I am a dork about these holiday things, too, so I'm a sad panda. 

So I just made a massive ribeye for myself, am steadily working through the wine, and just opened a bag of those chocolate Dove hearts with the messages. Comfort food. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look a bit like Derek Waters, which is definitely a compliment because I totally have a dorky crush on him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My engagement was similar. I knew it was coming, down to what night. partially because we had a dating anniversary trip scheduled anyway, to the place I wanted to get engaged. That part was a coincidence actually, but the planning? Nah. We went together to pick out the ring, we had talked about marriage a TON, we knew we were ready. We'd been talking about marriage for years. Since very early on in our relationship. We knew when it would happen and people thought it was lacking romance. My fianc proposed in front of the castle at Disneyland, after fireworks and an amazing meal, on our four year dating anniversary, with a sweet hotel room, and a ring I loved, which included my heirloom diamond from my grandmother. How is that lacking romance? 

Good communication is romantic in its own way. Being mutually ready for engagement and marriage is better than any surprise proposal. Planning for the future is romantic as fuck. Don't let anyone tell you otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... that's a euphemism? Careful, Wendy's, this guy is just trying to get in your pants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I feel! Except my sister is my MOH and she and my mom get along just swell and they both annoy me to no end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get out of here Wendy's, nobody likes you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the actual behavior of a millennial: 

Yo, shut up and eat your nuggets, man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such an amazing feeling! My grandmother (also a best friend to me) beat breast cancer a few years ago. Since then she's been crocheting knit beanies and scarves for the chemo patients at the hospital she used to go to. She was recently diagnosed with uterine cancer but it's very early stages and easily removed, thank god. She's a tough old broad. I'm so happy for you guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk Makeup has their Sunshine Skin Tint in a rollerball format. I LOVE it. I struggle with pouring or pumping the correct amount all the time and the rollerball allows me to add just tiny bits more wherever it's needed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god this is gorgeous!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. And it's hard having those low points because your mood is up the days before... it's like double disappointing. But recovery is a process, it's slow going sometimes but if you are patient and honest and trust your docs you'll find what works for you! If you ever need to vent, I'm here :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the music started playing in my head the second I saw this. Awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen a proof pic where things weren't handwritten so that's cool (I'm also a little scatterbrained so maybe this HAS happened before but I forgot?) but I am also recently on antidepressants and it is the most bizarre thing in the whole world. I've been depressed for so long and I was so used to it I used to think it was the only thing in the whole world. But the last 30 days have... I mean I'm not 110% SAVED and I'm not not-depressed but there's an inkling of an idea that life might be worth living. 

I truly hope you find that soon, OP, because your swoopy hair is cool and you look like the kind of person that could appreciate the specific brand of dry humor that I love in a person. Have a virtual high five from me. I'm proud of you for pursuing treatment and I think you deserve the bestest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw you guys this makes my heart happy after a weird evening, thanks friendos, I'm gonna save this thread for later when I need cute owls to brighten my day. Thank you!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 07:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redbubble does prints and products fairly well, but I have taken some of my stuff to a chain print shop (not like an office place but a legit print shop) and gotten fairly cheap prints on good paper. From there it's Etsy and then taking over the world!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been in a Microsoft support chat trying to buy a stupid game for forty minutes. This person must type at 6 WPM. I want to bash my own stupid fucking head in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuuuuuuuuuuck youuuuuuuuu

Forty minutes of my life wasted trying stupid shit I've already tried while this fucking dipshit on the other end takes literally five minutes to respond to any little thing 

I am normally not someone who gets this frustrated but dear god lady, if I tell you I've already tried the console and two browsers, don't ask me if I'm using a console or a browser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a gif being posted around right now where a baseball coach finds out he's having a girl by hitting a hollow ball off a tee, that hollow ball is filled with pink powder. Gender reveal level: baseball coach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also buy prints of this! This is so cool!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I did this too. I have one on our fridge currently, straight out of the box. And then when I dropped them off at the post office this afternoon, I sent one to us too! FH thinks I'm a dork but he's marrying me anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh your start stats are my start stats, I've only lost 10lbs so far but holy shit this is some inspiration! You look amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I "acknowledge and counter" in a debate and "laugh" in anything else. If I get particularly stuck or a point is put across that I didn't see coming, I say "I see what you're saying, and I totally agree/disagree about _____, but lately I've been thinking______" 

In any other case, I'm a spaz and I just giggle about anything remotely funny to confuse the humans around me until I think of something to say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really about sides. Honestly, if I were in your position, the husband would be in the friggin doghouse ten times over. He turned his entire family against you, knowing they'd feel that way, because HE went against your very genuine concern without even asking. UGH. This makes me mad just thinking about it. 

It's this simple - is he okay with the possibility that she has a psychotic episode around your child and possibly harms him, intentionally or not? I would think that's not okay with him. And hurting his sisters feelings - when she clearly knows at this point that she's different - is a hell of a lot less important than the potential DEATH of your kid. 

Overall, this is your kid and you have the right to make decisions about who you trust to care for it. Don't trust her? That word is final. He has no room for debate. He's endangering your child. 

If you'd like to be conscious of his feelings, just remind him of how he'd feel if she had an episode and harmed him. If you want to really make him realize how bad this is, let him know that it was completely unreasonable for him to involve his family in decisions about YOUR child, and that if he continues to be dishonest and endanger your child this way, your kid isn't going to be able to see them at all. 

This is so scary. I had a friend in high school whose father developed a sort of mental illness after a traumatic brain injury. Someone she'd felt completely safe with for 16 years attacked her when he had an episode and broke sixteen of her bones, left her with internal bleeding. She needed stitches in four places. She's lucky she lived. You NEVER know when someone is going to have an episode. It's not worth it to say "it won't happen to ME!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have benetint/lollitint/sun beam/high beam, all BN no box, and benefit dandelion and Dallas, both used twice by me and sanitized. I would be willing to work out a discount if you purchased more than one!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm far from perfect but I am more dedicated than ever! 10 down, 60 to go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HW 206 | CW 196 | GW 135

I have yo-yo'd around for ten years. I'm 26 now. I was 135ish in 9th grade, which is when I stopped growing (vertically, anyway!) and I'm hoping to get back there (I'm 5'7ish and was a size 6 or 8) 

I slip up all the dang time. Have you tasted buffalo chicken dip?! Do you know about butter?! But I haven't seriously binged in a long time. I have started learning to just take small bites of "bad" stuff and to at least vaguely judge calorie content. 

But I'm not stressing myself out like I have before. I have been trusting my intuition a little more so that I can gradually work into a stricter regimen instead of going crazy on day one and killing my diet every few weeks. 

Today I was super proud because I did well even after a big party yesterday. Today's groceries were all super healthy and tasty. I made a smoothie that my fianc didn't want a second taste of but that I LOVED (banana, spinach, hemp milk, cacao, cashews, chia, mint, coconut oil). 

And I bought new running shoes! Instead of buying cheap shoes over and over that weren't comfortable, I snagged a pair of super comfy Nikes in a pretty color. I would go break them in if it weren't freezing outside and if I didn't have so much meal prep to do! 

I'm getting married in September, and even if I can't lose the whole amount, I want to get at least halfway through!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realized I sort of low-balled myself when I hired in 17 months ago. Haven't gotten a raise, never discussed it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My NF is pretty relaxed. I like them, they like me, the whole deal. I only work MWF, 7:30-5:30. There are three kids - 11F, 8F, and 2M - but for most of the day, the older two are in school and I just have the youngest. Still, I'm only making $15 - which is what I made at my last job, which was for much older kids (10M 12F and 14M) who I basically just did pickup and drop off, and helped the youngest with his homework. $15 made sense then and I was only working like 20 hours a week. 

This job is usually 30 hours. The parents are great about being home on time, and the mom will sometimes ask if I can come in on a Tuesday or Thursday if she needs to do work stuff. I think I signed a contract when I hired in but honestly we've all gotten so relaxed with each other that I don't remember. We've never had to use it, that's for sure. 

I have never had to ask for a raise in a nanny situation before. My last job was set in stone, a single year. The one before that was basically just babysitting. The family does pretty well for themselves, so I don't think it would be something they couldn't afford. But I am so nervous about making things weird! And I honestly don't know what to ask for. From what I read on here, $20 seems like what I should have initially asked for, but I think $15-20 is too high of a jump. 

How do I go about negotiating a raise? What should I ask for? I'm in California, for the record, and working in an affluent neighborhood. 

Also, how do you guys normally handle summer? In summer I'll have all three kids all day, like I did last year - much more work. She always covered activities but it was still a ton more work than it was during the school year. Should I get paid more for this? Should I just make sure we have plenty to do and that it's covered by NF? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoooooooop these two are my favorites, I'm supposed to be working right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hell yeah. We've had very minimal communication from our 100+ invitees because of it. We put plenty of links up to the available lodging in the area, explained how it worked on the site, and we've had zero problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 10:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi-related, I went on a trip for NYE. Camped two days then hotel and an event. Realized on the first hotel day that I forgot my makeup bag at home. I legit cried. My brush bag was in my suitcase but my makeup itself was not. 

Luckily there was a Sephora nearby. I figured I'd just spend what I needed to spend, try some new stuff, and return what I didn't need or want when I got home. (God bless that return policy!) Gave me a chance to try some new stuff. 

That said, my list was just over 350 and included: 

Too Faced Hangover Primer 32
Tarte Creaseless Maracuja Concealer 25
Este Lauder Double Wear 40
Laura Mercier Translucent powder travel size 28
ABH Dipbrow 18
Maybelline clear brow gel 4
Too Faced palette (don't remember, one of the chocolate ones. Wasn't a huge fan at all.) 49
Urban Decay Moondust in Midnight Cowboy 21
Buxom Mascara 20
Duo glue 4
Individual lashes (ardell I think.) 4
Tarteist Pro Glow Palette 45
Nars blush in Impassioned (normally I'd buy Goulue but didn't have time for shipping!) 30
Mac Fix+ travel size 10 
UD All Nighter travel size  15
elf tinted balm 2 

And that's a full face with a few options. Honestly it was so weird having to buy a full kit when I have an extensive collection as it is. About 75% of it went back. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just have to get this all out, it's so good, it's SO GOOD. 

Friendos, the last few years have been a wild time for me. I started this relationship at 20, the quintessential Party Girl who didn't want to settle down ever, drinking way too much even for a college kid and spending every cent that I could get my hands on. I was depressed but unable to confront it. I had terrible spending habits to the point of not being able to afford fifty cents bus fare, let alone lunch at work. I was irresponsible and on a course headed straight for disaster. My semi-abusive parents had recently divorced so my home life was a wreck. I basically didn't see myself making it to 25 at all. 

And then, you know, I don't want to say he SAVED me, especially since we met because I talked his ear off and wouldn't leave him the hell alone at a party, but man oh man did this guy help me. He never pressured me, but did everything he could to help me be a better person. I took it for granted for so long while I was still depressed, but I begrudgingly started taking steps to kick my spending habit about a year ago, four years into our relationship. This man has the patience of a saint. I'm lucky I'm too lazy to pay bills and that it's his job, because we would literally never have electricity on or running water if it wasn't for him taking care of my shit while I've been so depressed that I can't be bothered to keep up any friendships or paint or go outside. 

We've known we wanted to marry each other since very early on, but it took him four years to propose. We've been engaged a year now, taking our time so that we can do this the right way. I still struggled with my spending a little but not nearly as much as before, and I knew how to fix it now. I finally got the help my brain needed and now I'm all, like, emotional? And able to feel joy easily? And able to enjoy things? Bizarre, I know, I know. 

When we started this wedding planning thing, in Southern California where we reside, we knew it was going to be a chunk of change. But oh, man, we still underestimated it. We thought there was no way catering could cost several thousand dollars, or that a venue that allowed us more than a single day would be so far to find. Well, details aside, it's been crazy, and we've been purposefully avoiding talking too much about budget because it sends my stress through the roof and because we had some family things going on that affected how much we were going to receive. 

We finally bit the bullet today, after I have had a rollercoaster emotional day. Who knew that having feelings again would make me cry all the time, right? Like after sex, or in the shower, or in the kitchen when we're cooking dinner and I'm blasting Rihanna because music is good again? I was terrified that we were going to have to drastically cut something from the wedding or the honeymoon, or not honeymoon at all. I was afraid I'd screwed it up even though I'd been trying so hard. I was that little girl dreaming about my wedding day at age three. And I've let so many things in my life go by while I was depressed and have regretted missing out on so many things. I didn't want my wedding to be one of them. I wanted things to be perfect. I was feeling so hopeless about it all without even knowing exact details. The last few months have been wild. I started an anti-depressant that I wasn't sure worked at first, but WOW does it work! And the last week or two I've been antsy thinking about things and testing out how I feel on this medication, but I didn't even want to talk about budget because I felt like something was going to go horribly wrong. 

Anyway, we sat down, deep breath, and recalculated our budget versus expenditures amounts. Down to the single stems of silk flowers we're going to DIY. Down to how many yards of taffeta we're draping over the two big trees at the venue that make up the altar. Down to the exact number of LED tea lights. We had this crazy idea that we were going to do a two week honeymoon, and I'd been looking up ideas and plans all month.

And we're okay! We're more than okay. I cut my personal spending drastically enough that I still have a little spending cash, but we're putting a shit ton into wedding savings ($300 a week, which is a big chunk on our combined salary since I'm part time). We're going to be able to do it all! Our campy four day wedding weekend in the mountains in So Cal, my dream dress, a week on a Caribbean cruise, a week at Disney World, the whole shebang! And we've still got a bit of money for wiggle room/incidentals and a good chunk of spending cash, too. Also, since we've lived together for all of our five years of dating, we have everything we need for a house, so we're only registering for a few physical items and we're doing a honeymoon fund registry, so we'll have a little more cash down the line, too. 

I expressed my happiness to FH, and he patted me on the head and said he was proud of me. And I almost started crying again but then I had to stop dinner from burning, so there's that. 

Anyone else have any recent successes in wedding planning? Feel like celebrating? Ahh!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW I punched my major depression in the dick, kicked my spending addiction, and just realized I am now emotionally and financially capable of having my dream wedding and dream honeymoon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a crazy destination wedding setup too. We opted for a simple save the date magnet that showed the address for our wedding website - our website has all the pertinent information on travel and accommodations. You may think a website is a bit much for a small wedding, but it can be a good reference point for your guests so everyone isn't calling each other (or you) confused about anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't want to do cash, do something like a bottle of wine + a Date-in-a-Bag: Movie tickets, gift certificate to a nice restaurant, something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this! I just had the greatest rush of good memories. Anyone with a net is A+ in my book!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm reading. Didn't even plan it that way, but looks like we're going at basically the perfect time! (Wedding is 09/09, we're going either the next week or the week after that). Seems like this is the least busy week possible, so we're looking forward to that. We're DL APs, so we're used to our two tiny cramped parks and super long lines most of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The idea that someone wants you to run away with them sounds so romantic, but it isn't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running away won't fix anything. Running away won't make things magically work. 

I have been rewatching Gilmore Girls, I'm at the end of season 4. Jess comes to Rory's dorm room and says he needs to talk to her. She tells Dean to go home to his wife, and she lets Jess go off. He says he wants to be with her. That she can depend on him. He wants them to move to New York or anywhere she wants to go, to leave Yale and Stars Hollow and just GO. 

She basically just yells no at him over and over until he gets it. 

My guy didn't get it. I've been thinking about him a bit recently so I was surprised to see this scenario pop up this episode. 

Ryan was the older brother of a girl I had been friends with in elementary school. Ryan was cool, almost too cool, but not in your Football Team cookie cutter kind of way. Ryan had a huge ginger fro and was into Electronic music before it was cool. Ryan hung out with all the older cool kids, and I really mean all of them. Everybody liked Ryan. He was a counselor at the same camp as me and when we went to an amusement park, he smoked pot and got himself kicked out. He always seemed laid back. Fun. 

I don't know how things got to be that way. Different. 

I don't even remember when we started talking again. I don't know. Mild flirtation online. I remember we hung out at a party one night. We hooked up once when i was recently on a very angry break from my old boyfriend. It was all weird. So weird. It wasn't even a long time. That night and maybe one more. And a lot of texting and Facebook. But that was it. This whole thing happened over the course of a month or so. 

He got weirder and weirder. He wouldn't talk to me for a week then he'd call a bunch in one day. 

I got back together with the exboyfriend (stupid move). Ryan was furious, parroting back every complaint i had even briefly mentioned. Telling me this guy was trash. (He was, but I wasn't ready to hear it.) I told him to leave me alone. He told me he wanted to run away together. He wanted me to come with him to Santa Barbara, to leave my friends and family and my job and school. He wanted me to hop on a train and not look back. 

I told him to leave me alone. And I'm glad I did. I'm glad I didn't do the stupid thing. It doesn't work out. Never. Not even on TV. Any guy who has screwed up bad enough to have to propose running away together... he's not worth it. 

He told me he loved me. God, he was nuts. He showed up at my house one time. I pretended I wasn't home. He also called, over and over. I shut my phone off and when I turned it back on my mailbox was full, and he kept calling.  His voicemails and social media messages went something to the tune of "I'm going to tell your boyfriend you cheated on him" and "you basically forced me to sleep with you that night" (lies) and "I'm going to tell everyone you raped me."  A 22 year old guy with seven inches and sixty pounds on me, a 5'5 150lbs soaking wet college freshman with a bad back. Right. 

He kept threatening me, and calling. And leaving messages. 

I blocked him on every social media outlet, blocked his number. I hope he's doing better. He was a pretty nice guy before all of this. I asked a few of his friends that I grew up with how he was doing. Several years ago. He was fine. I'm glad. I hope he got his head in the right place. 

Rory obviously didn't have to deal with this guy. Jess left, after he asked her if she really meant NO. She said it again, fear making her shoulders rise, unable to even look at him, and he left. 

It's scary. Being confronted like that. The guy could be a saint otherwise, but I haven't seen it happen like that. A guy who is obviously feeling something very strong. A guy desperate enough to just show up and ask you to stop caring about everything else in your life so you can solely care about him. 

I have never told anyone the full story here. I was afraid of him. That day he showed up at my house? He stopped because there were no other cars in the driveway. I saw him looking. I barely got a glimpse of his car through the kitchen window. He didn't see me. I kept the doors locked and a thick tire iron in my room. I thought I had known him, but clearly I didn't. You hear so many horror stories. I genuinely feared for my life. 

And he made me feel that way. All because he thought he loved me. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woo! Our honeymoon is this September! We'll see the Halloween decorations up and spend a week in the parks before hopping off on a weeklong cruise. I've only been to WDW once before and didn't really get to do the things I wanted to do, so I'm excited to go back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *now kith*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly a story I'll tell my grandchildren. "There was this total fox working in my neurologist's office. Made a lot of BDSM jokes. It was a good time for both of us."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof. Reminds me of my one and only Hot Doc experience. I had an EMG done a few years ago. Basically, they stick these thick ass needles into a bunch of your muscles in a hundred different spots and make you flex those muscles - with the needle still in! - to see how the muscles respond. It is somehow even more painful than it sounds. But the doctor was like, this-guy-level cute and SO funny. He kept trying to make me laugh because I was obviously in pain. Once he realized I didn't have a stick up my butt and could take a joke, dude was relentless. 

A few gems were: 
"you know, some people like when their partner inflicts a little pain!" 

"That's why I took this job, actually, I get off on causing people pain over and over again. And I get paid for it! Really well." 

And, once we were done and he was finishing reading stuff, he just let out a big sigh and said "I hope it was as good for you as it was for me" 

I left that office still laughing so hard I had tears, and then afterwards I ran into him in the hall and he winked at me and I couldn't even be subtle, I just started cackling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Diva area. I use Mac Prep and Prime mixed with Maybelline Master Prime - the illuminating one. Even ratio or more Mac than Maybelline. Prep and Prime works perfectly fine under it alone but I try and put as many illuminating products into my routine as I can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the cutest thing I've seen all day and I browsed r/aww for half an hour this morning. 

Also you must have performed some kinda witchcraft to get your eyeliner/eyes looking so good! So pretty. And I'm super jealous of your ability to pull off a choker!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh I'm totally doing this once I deposit my check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does, actually. A little unfortunate but still hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'm just gonna leave this right here ](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=RS9LPPOIEZM)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently I'm using RCMA no color powder, and two sprays - Mac Fix+ then Skindinavia's Bridal spray. I'm kind of a diva about setting sprays but this will work just fine with any of the UD sprays! But the RCMA is honestly the best powder out there IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP but I am also raving about ELDW. I went through probably fifty different foundations trying to find something that would stay on my uber-pale, finicky, dehydrated-but-oily face. I tend to get oily on my nose but my skin is fairly dehydrated and can get uneven texture that lesser foundations settle into. ELDW comes in a zillion shades and STAYS ON. Plus, for me at least, when I press powder on to set and use a setting spray, I have the most gorgeous satin/natural finish. Ive never had a foundation like this. Magic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 3F thinks that for a few days out of every month I have to put medicine on my butt. I usually make her turn around when I need to use a tampon but she peeked once a year or so and thought I was reaching for my butt. She'd had diaper rash so she just thought I did too. Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 229! For our honeymoon. Fianc went before once as a kid, we went together with some of his family a few years ago (and got stuck following tiny kids around all week, which usually meant leaving around 4PM!) but I've been dying to go back just us so we can really get a better experience. We're Disneyland APs but the parks are night and day. I love DL for a day trip but I'm so so excited to go back to WDW for a whole week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of your boys has a face that looks a bit like Lee Pace. I'll let you guess which one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs at first I didn't understand all the FB group jerks, but I finally joined a group just to see what all the fuss was about and... wow. Just wow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Glad I could help out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greg McCullough! I am pretty sure that's the one you're talking about! [this one? ](http://www.yourwdwstore.net/Disney-Artist-Print--Greg-McCullough--Dream-It-Do-It_p_46068.html)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Sounds like they really meshed and had a good time. I'd say dinner or something casual is a fine next meeting. If you want to wait a week or so, feel free! But time between meetings won't change a ton except YOUR comfort level. If you need to wait, wait. If your sister and girlfriend want to see each other again, set it up. But don't take too long before meetings. I know you feel a lot of pressure to protect your sister, I totally get that. But if you sit down with her and explain what's going on, it'll make you feel better that she has a better understanding. 

I'd say a next step before another meeting is sitting down with your sister and making sure she knows what's going on - that you've been with your girlfriend a long time and wanted to reeeally make sure things were serious before the girlfriend got to meet her. Explain that you have been thinking about your future - and by that I mean yours and your sisters, mainly - and that you are an adult who might want to get married some day. It might be this girlfriend; it might not. But you've talked about it. Reassure her that she'll always come first. 7 is old enough for a girl to know how boyfriends and girlfriends work and what marriage is. If you better prepare her for either option - a breakup or a marriage - it'll be easier for her in the long run. Holding off and keeping them apart for periods of time could make a marriage difficult eventually. They need to get comfortable with each other! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?? Thank you so much! I threw it together last night with no real plans and almost didn't bring it. I only grabbed it last minute on my way out the door. I ended up bringing a bunch of daisies and handing them out too. I just loved the quote - I had to look it up because I couldn't remember  if I had the exact right words and I'm picky about that kind of thing lol 

Definitely victories. My whole body aches and likely will for several days but it was so so worth it to be a part of this. 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, in California you can provide care for any of your own children plus any number of children in one additional family. So right now I'm nannying for a family of three and don't need a license, but if I started working for a second family (technically this is true of nanny shares!) I would need a license. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm moderately disabled, I have a spinal cord condition that gives me a lot of nerve pain and weakness. Add anxiety at large events on top of that (the world is a scary place!) and an antidepressant that I just started and makes me feel a little overwhelmed... I don't know. I didn't know if I could handle it. I thought about going for days. I didn't want to ask anyone I knew if they were going. 

Finally last night I posted asking if anyone was interested in going. Within minutes I had two dear friends willing to carpool. I threw together this sign last night at like 2AM and almost didn't bring it because I've never done anything like this before and I was worried people would think my sign was silly. (Brains!) LA was a madhouse but it was beautiful. One friend had to leave early for work and my body was shutting down, so we left around 2 but still got some good time in since we'd gotten there At 9AM. 

People loved my sign (soooo many people took pictures of me/it) and since we were leaving early, I waited until we were near parking. A middle-aged couple was walking towards the biggest crowds past us and the woman said she loved my sign, so I gave it to her. Passed the torch. 

I struggled with identifying as a feminist for so long, but coming to terms with who I am as a person and as a woman made it impossible for me to hold off any longer. I'm a feminist. A bisexual, disabled, chronically ill, mentally ill feminist who had an amazing day surrounded by supportive, amazing people. 

Thank you, everyone who marched in person and in spirit. I love you. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sign for today's march in Los Angeles. So so glad I decided to go after all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! My first time doing anything like this. Bringing a buddy and meeting up with another. Currently designing my sign!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 09:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say don't get your hopes up, BUT you could get lucky. I went in 2013 a few months after it opened. We're Disneyland APs so didn't know how crazy WDW dining was and thus didn't make reservations. (Plus, we were with a group of 12/lots of small kids). Went one day just myself, boyfriend, and his sister. We walked up to see if anything was available for 3, but nope. They had a table for two, but we didn't want to ditch my fiance's sister and ended up turning it down. I still regret it. We got lucky but definitely have a backup plan!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 09:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, there's just nothing quite like clean data and the sweet reassurance that our mid-September 2017 honeymoon is a good time to go.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 20 when my parents split and my sister was 17 - she got to pick where to go. I luckily moved out right around the time of the divorce so I didn't have to worry about it. 

It's very common for the "left behind" parent to accuse the other one of turning kids against them. My sister chose to live with my mom because she was closer to her. My dad got upset about that. 

On the other hand, when they were first fighting and my mom moved out for a bit, I sided with my dad and stayed there. She accused him of turning me against her. It happened both ways and NEITHER of them were right. 

It was kind of shitty for your dad to let out why the divorce was going on, especially so soon when you're still dealing with everything. But what's done is done. You're staying with your dad and besides that, he seems to be trying to be as neutral as possible. That's good. 

Your mom is behaving badly. Regardless of WHY they divorced, she's not handling this the right way. Let her know that you love her and you don't want things to be like this, but her attitude about the situation and her accusations are making you uncomfortable. Let her know you're preferring to spend less time with her because it's putting a lot of unwanted stress on you and you don't like that she makes you feel that way. 

It's going to be tough for a while but it WILL get better. My parents are on fine terms a few years later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi it's me your other sister  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright there's no mistranslating calling me selfish, so let me remind you of two important things: 

1. I mentioned both here and to him that I was tired from errands. We had been out all day, on our feet, doing stuff. Walking aimlessly and tiring myself further was not something that sounded appealing. And HE first said "let's walk SOMEWHERE". But he had no ideas of his own, which is typical for him, so I listed stuff off. It's not about making it about myself. I wanted to take what he wanted to do and make it enjoyable for both of us. It wouldn't have been enjoyable to either of us if I was impatient and tired and my feet hurt while we just wandered around. Refused to go unless it was on my terms? I wanted to find a compromise. 

2. Is this not a support-ish sub? Call me crazy, but this set of subs is set up to vent about and get support for annoying and/or crazy shit our families and partners do. My partner did a slightly annoying thing that he has been known to do when I don't immediately agree to his ideas. I just needed to vent it out there, not be chastised on how I handle my relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's exactly like that. I was a little tired from errands so wandering aimlessly wasn't very appealing. But walking TO somewhere and actually doing something would have been fine. He just shot down every single one of my ideas and then decided we weren't going out once I found something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the Messenger blew me away. I borrowed it from my high school library (small school, no cards) read it in one sitting and never gave it back. So so good and the first book I had read that wasn't assigned and wasn't purely YA romance fluff. I only ever read it once or twice but now I'm going to need to read it again. Yay!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is! I also organized the drawers, top to bottom, by which ones I use most often. 

I too think that this was a nice compromise. So easy to see. Ah! I have to go look at it again now haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually [much simpler than I thought. ](https://imgur.com/gallery/d2gGL) and a little rudimentary but functional. I didn't realize how simple it was. I could probably have done this lol. 

The side with the existing shelf underneath, there are two pieces of metal already there. He bent two little brackets out flat to hold the wood on that side, and just used two more in the regular way on the other side. Didn't screw any of it down, just let it rest on the brackets. The shelving was not the exact depth of the desk so that's why those other brackets are laid flat - to hold it in. 

They do! Phillips Hue makes White Ambiance smart bulbs that have something like zillions of different shades of "white". I am still trying to decide if I want to splurge on the Ambiance bulbs or just stick with their neutral white dimmable bulbs. 

And yessss I know, it's weird how much I like them too. I think I have one in every finish now? Maybe? I don't know. I love the mattes and comfort mattes, but the sheers are so gorgeous. I have Sheer Ladyflower! I was OBSESSED with Cruel for the holidays (magic red with glitter that STAYED PUT!) But I'm looking forward to spring so I can break out Weirdo, which ends up like a bright-ish peachy neutral on me. 

And I just have an Echo Dot but I love it. Got it for Christmas because I have dreams of turning this 430 square foot apartment into a smart tech haven. One fixture at a time...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this should be the link ](https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01BCOFYF8/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_api_E0rFybR8KEX3T)  and they come in a bunch of different configurations and sizes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're very welcome! The brackets on the frame are kind of a pain in the butt but totally doable. Like I mentioned somewhere, I'm incredibly accident prone or I would have done this myself. And Home Depot or whatever will cut the shelving to size for you if you ask. I can send you a picture of how we bracketed the shelving on if you're interested! The floral mirror is my last piece of the puzzle, but I'm doing mine with smart bulbs so I can yell at my Echo/Alexa to turn it on. 

And yes, omg. I used to shy away from traditional bullet lipsticks but decided to give these a try. What. Magic. I've loved every formula I've put on. I tried other bullets after that but I just don't love them as much as the Vice ones! I only have 8 right now but I'm working on it. Ah!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! My brushes are all mixed and matched from a bunch of places. I don't even know where some of them came from. But the only amazon ones I have are a few cheapo wooden ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I had problems getting them to work at first (and they're SO shallow!) but I enjoy having it all out and easy to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? When we moved in I was like "what the heck are we going to do with this? Shelves? Closet?" Then when we started moving stuff in and there was no room in the bedroom for my vanity... I mean, it all fits perfectly. It's meant to be there. It's actually the space that's above the staircase that leads into our building, so I think it's the only apartment with a room like that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just keep going in and staring at it because this is def the most organized my makeup has ever been in my life. So soothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build her a vanity! Or help her find a small storage solution. But sometimes it's just easier to keep it messy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so so fun, but MAN does it get dirty quickly! But it is pretty neat being able to kind of display everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! 

The IKEA table pictured (Vittsjo) is a glass top, but the wood underneath was only in that square area towards the bottom/right - there was no shelving underneath the rest of it when we bought it. My fianc rigged it with a few brackets and a piece of dark colored shelving from Home Depot so that the wood went all the way across underneath, so that it could store things. (He did the work because I am prone to seriously injuring myself whenever hammers/saws are involved. ADD is cool.) 

We then bought stackable bamboo storage organizers from The Container Store - enough to cover the bottom shelf without spilling over the edge. I configure them so that the metal bar from the desk frame doesn't keep me from pulling them out. All my makeup down there is sorted and organized from left to right in the order that I use it. 

On top are acrylic drawers from Amazon (so cheap that way!) that came in a variety of shapes. The drawers have more eye palettes, my blushes/bronzes/highlighters, false lashes, tools (extra powder puffs, makeup removers, blotting sheets, etc) and anything else that didn't fit. 

I used to do my makeup on my bed all the time and surrounded myself with a pile of stuff, so I feel super fancy sitting down at my vanity now, even though I only sit down to do my makeup like once a week since I don't wear makeup to work!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fianc helped me customize an IKEA laptop table into a vanity a few years ago. My old mirror was a crappy four dollar Walmart mirror with some strip lights wired to it, my new one is a nicer IKEA glass mirror. I'm planning on adding a little more frame and flowers to make it look kind of like [this ](http://pin.it/BnCC0vh) but different. Maybe all white flowers? And smart bulbs, so I can yell at Alexa to turn my vanity lights on/make them dimmable. 

We used to live in a big four bedroom townhouse with roommates, and there was plenty of room. Now we live in a tiny apartment (but thankfully alone!), which has a weird 5 foot by 5 foot closet-ish space with a window. We've dubbed it "my room" and it houses my vanity and that shelf, which is also new. For the first six months or so that we lived here, it was just a pile of my stuff with the vanity barely usable. Now I can actually use the room! 

I recently added the acrylic drawers on top (amazon!), reorganized the wooden bins under the glass, and updated the aforementioned mirror. It's so clean and I can see everything! 

Edit: added something. 

[another view. ](https://imgur.com/gallery/NN82K)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So fresh, so clean! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the same one I'm thinking about getting! That or the brownish jacket with full sleeves. They're all so pretty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a sucker for a faux fur shrug/crop jacket of any kind, so keep that in mind, but given a mountainous wintery wedding, something like that in white or ivory would keep you warmer and also be really fun for pictures. I'm getting married on a mountaintop in September and while it's not going to be quite so cold, I am still getting something furry for pictures and once it gets cold at night. 

BHLDN has a great selection of bridal cover ups. I'm kind of obsessed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this dude on Reddit one time try and run a conversation in circles in a way that he was accusing me of being a rapist sympathizer. I'm a rape survivor and his argument was totally convoluted (HE brought up rape in an almost entirely disconnected conversation then tried to say I did?) then went on to harass me. 

The post was in TwoX taking about women appreciating when their men are extra careful in asking for consent/very respectful about it. I shared a story. Just a story. Nothing big. I don't even remember how this fucking guy worked this around to me encouraging rape culture but, ya know, fucktards on the internet. 

He didn't make it very hard to find him online. His reddit history was atrocious - misogyny, harassment, threats, all kinds of fun shit. I sat my ass down at a Starbucks over a pumpkin spice latte and went ham on this dude. 

I never could find his mom, but I DID find his little sister who apparently really looked up to him/was close with him. His little sister who, if memory serves me right, is a queer feminist. She got a message and links. And oh, his favorite small time band that he basically ran the fan club for? They got a link and screenshots too, with a note that "if I were you, I certainly wouldn't want my personal brand related to someone who talks to people like that". 

Welp. Iiiiiif you're going to be a tool on the internet and not hide who you are, don't be surprised when someone calls you out on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Queen will actually be officiating our ceremony, our vows are focused on my Brow Journey and how many vanities boyfie 3D printed me since we met. Only the best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same though, we're having like five different small cakes and paying out the ass for a bitchin' catering company. No shame. Our people will remember the food!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another vote for "dump her and take a friend." Or at the very least, don't reward her terrible behavior by taking her on this trip. If you do that, she's going to see that as acceptable behavior. 

You already sound like you know you want to dump her. This relationship is not making you happy. End things, enjoy your trip with a buddy, hit the gym, something something something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hero! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. Specifically says "do not reply to this email, any requests to cancel or reschedule appt will not be seen"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you still have it Friday (or if you'd be interested in holding it for me) I'll take it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you did the right thing in writing things down and deciding to come clean. It can take a lot of guts to admit to a professional that you haven't been completely honest, and even more to completely open up and let them know what's really going on. 

My anxiety used to make me make things up all the time - I don't even know why I was lying half of the time. It was a crappy reaction and I realized that it wasn't helping anyone but I did it anyway. I didn't see a therapist for five years because I was convinced that I couldn't make it work for me because I would freak out and make things seem more or less important than they actually were. 

I went back last week and was 98% honest with my new person. One or two times I said something dumb, but trivial things. I don't know if it's maturity or what but I knew I really needed help this time. 

I'm proud of you for taking steps to get real, honest help 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it a penis pop up card!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, that's too close to retail for me to want to buy used. Thanks though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, no thanks - that shade is much too warm for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the usage like? And how much are you asking? Super interested!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, that's more than retail - I'd rather just buy new. Thanks though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] ISO Kevyn Aucoin Sculpting Powder in Light, other cool-toned sculpt/bronzing powders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very pale (NW15 is sometimes too dark) lady looking for some sculpting/contouring/bronzing powders. I specifically am looking for the Kevyn Aucoin powder in light, if anyone has a well-loved one that they're not using that I could try out before committing to the full thing. If someone also has a new one they're willing to part with for less than retail, I would probably be into that too. 

Sephora Tranquil is a bit TOO gray and dark, even with a very light hand. 

Hoola looks very bronze on me and can look very orange depending on what foundation I'm using at the time/where I place Hoola. 

Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we're all 80 and trying really hard to make a point about Generation Gamma or whatever they end up calling those future whippersnappers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg. It's basically like "we normally don't give a shit, we still don't give a shit, why don't you go join a trashier page somewhere that gives a shit" 

Wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, this is some shit my fianc would do. He proposed at Disneyland because it's always been a dream of mine, but sometimes I wish I'd had a more private proposal. 

Also he and I are big B99 fans and we're getting married on 09/09/17. There were a few other dates available but we were like "we gotta do it, it's 99!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Directions unclear, now there's a hole in my junk and no beer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually /r/ToastMe ! It's a thing! On mobile and can't figure out links because I'm a doof  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake flowers - what's worth it? Who did you use? I just got screwed over by a SECOND diva florist. I'm done. Floral crisis. Send booze. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screwed over is maybe harsh, but I'm a little fed up with florists. 

First off, we're getting married in San Diego county. Shit is expensive, even though we're getting married up in the mountains and having a laid-back, mostly-family wedding weekend for four days. Florists don't seem to get this. I put in six inquiries at first, and four of them quoted me for some exorbitantly large arrangements and way more flowers than I asked for. The other two were booked. Okay. 

I waited a few more weeks and asked a few more - enter Florist One. Florist One worked with me for a full month and a half. When the quote finally looked perfect, I asked her how to pay - she asked us to pay the deposit before she'd even draw up an official contract. Before I could reply and say that made us uncomfortable, she sent a clipped email saying that someone else had booked her. What? She claims that someone just instantly paid the deposit through a paypal link on her page, without even talking to her. Whatever. She was majorly unprofessional in handling the fallout, so I left a negative review online. She then tried to get it taken down, claiming I was lying about her asking for the deposit before she wrote a contract. They asked me, I provided a screenshot that said she actually had done that. They left the review up but she had zero remorse for how she handled the situation until the review was already done and up. 

Florist Two comes in later - I found them on The Knot, a little desperate. Everyone else I had contacted was booked already. They could only meet certain weekdays, so I went down there with FH and we met for an hour or so. They were pretty helpful but their English wasn't great, so I think a few things were missed. There was a lot of attitude, too, almost very smug? Like we asked a few questions and they'd just look at each other and then give a very condescending "lesson" on what we actually meant. Most of the time, no, I meant what I said. They were just suggesting totally different things I didn't like. I felt a little uneasy but let them know I'd be sending a few pictures of centerpieces I liked to get a better feel for sizing. Two or so weeks later I email them and guess what? They're booked for my date now. 

So, now I'm several months into trying to book a florist. We've still got months to go but I'm overwhelmed and can barely be made to do any planning lately. Most florists in the area are VERY expensive. My mom has a friend who does events just for fun (including the greenery garlands I desperately want but are too expensive through a traditional florist) but I'm skeptical. Also, my mom is an asshole so she won't just give me the girl's number to talk to her myself, my mom wants all the credit for organizing this so she wants me to go through her. Not something I want. My mom is uncooperative at times and I feel bad asking this friend, even though she supposedly loves doing it. I don't even know how i would compensate her as she usually does this stuff for free or very cheap and I don't know that she's done a full wedding before, but my mom has shown me pictures of her dessert tables and florals and they're super pretty. 

Brides who have used alternative florals - HOW? Did you DIY? Los Angeles has a great floral market, we're just South of LA, I could always get them on the Thursday before we drive down to SD, even though the wedding is Saturday afternoon. Or I could have my mom's friend pick them up, since she goes often and does this, as my mom said she was willing to come up Fri/Sat/Sun to help. 

Clay? Paper? Wood? I have seen a ton of different ideas but I'm overwhelmed. I want something full of greenery and really lush and wild looking for my bouquet, but everything else is smaller and mossy, hopefully. I can DIY my own moss stuff, but how expensive are fake flowers? Too much to do a whole wedding? Centerpieces?? 

I am having a crisis over flowers. FLOWERS. Before wedding planning started, I was excited to plan our wedding. Now I'm a half step away from showing up in jeans and just getting plastered drunk on champagne while everyone eats hot dogs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you need to not go back, ever. If the stuff she pawned is her parent's stuff (which seems highly likely) and YOU removed it from the house, she could try to pin it on you. Take note of everything weird that has happened lately, what you saw. But don't go back and don't keep being an accessory to all of this. You might want to just send her a text letting her know she'll need to find someone else starting immediately, that you're majorly uncomfortable with the situation and that you won't be returning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't reply to him - he's just going to keep insulting you and pushing your buttons. You owe him nothing. You're incompatible. That's more than enough. 

If your friend asks how it goes, let her know that you're just not compatible people. And that when you told him it wasn't going to continue, he insulted you and made some very rude comments. 

Odds are she sees only the best in her brother. She's never dated him obviously so she probably doesn't know this side of him at all. It doesn't need to be "tattling" on him but maybe let her know her brother is not someone she should set her friends up with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 10:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 10:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs this made me laugh way harder than I should be laughing at 1AM, take your updoot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
