<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Matt, we were in a Network Technology class in High School together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen the movie. It was rich people tinsel town fascist ideological propaganda, its makers were fans and friends of Mussolini. That the movie is utterly disgusting and any one who would promote it as something redeeming is an enemy of democracy in my eyes.

It's a Divine inspired character becoming facist and removing the rights of individuals to "Free them from the burdens of free thought"

fuck you and fuck that movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too bad, go ruby ridge your self kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are talking about filibusters and not totalitarian facist spank bank bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Senator Wild Man Wyden doesn't care!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up truck driver frozen in cab, and hobby lobby, and also right to die stances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In comes Senator Wyden with a folding chair to the Heckler! Oh .. no.. they sent the hecker to the turnbuckle! Oh ... my ... god!!! It's a savage display of Legislator on heckerler destruction!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High court started out as 5 people. Check out Radio Labs' Podcast "More Perfect" about the history of the US Supreme Court 

http://www.npr.org/podcasts/481105292/more-perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm vindictive? really? I don't think r/all is saying i'm vindictive. It seems more people support this action than don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch "mr smith goes to Washington" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who runs it? Technically blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pupper is Ghira and she is 8 years old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can thank the tea party for destroying that idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ohnoes!", to "This is my life now." In two photos of puppuccino cup on face fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ohnoes!", to "This is my life now." In two photos of puppuccino cup on face fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From "Ohnoes!!!" to "This is my life now" in two photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oregon is only liberal in the Portland and technically Salem areas, the majority of Oregon is highly under populated and in those rural areas very red.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im fine with nafta.  The jobs "taken" by nafta would be blamed on the free movement of people part is entirely unfounded as we didn't lose jobs to Mexico, but to corporations moving to a weak china for manufacturing, and most American jobs still here in manufacturing were lost to automation. TPP would have been good for us accept for the copyright and trademark and patent sections that were written by the mpaa and riaa. The TPP was only bad because of that. The trade part would have regulated Chinese trade more and and made the quality level of goods meet safety standards internationally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make that money rain!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude i been like this since I was 7 and I'm 32 now. Ask my father, he worked in the federal government as a manager at the department of housing and urban development for 40 years and was a notre dame fighting irish trained lawyer. My mom was a theater professor and stage actress. I learned to be big mouthed and politically active from them. Hell my catholic family lived on political policy debates around the dinner table while watching The MacNeil/Lehrer NewsHour (now PBS Newshour) while I grew up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 states have found the gerrymandering illegal and violated the civil rights of minorities and have to be done and checked by the supreme courts before next year. It will be a good time for those states for the democrats then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emotional response meter is detecting mixed levels of sarcasm and exasperation captain ... it is as if he he wants to say something but feels he cant because to him "foolish liberals" just never listen to his conservative view point with the seriousness he thinks it should get based on his opinion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be hilarious if they do because they are going to have to reap what they sowed come 2018. The movement of scientists running for office has 1024 scientists so far to run for office and the women's march has organized over 4300 progressive women to run for office as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont forget concave earthers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch alex jones clips on sandy hook and prepare to be physically ill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get the tea party by the koch brothers co-opting ron paul's libertarian movement and moving the goal post to get fervent mouth foamers to extreme social and fiscal conservatism. Then topping it off with a good dash of xenophobia and racism against a black president for the sake of getting useful idiots to kick out moderate republicans for koch brother centric ideology supporting deomogues who wont even try to find middle ground policy. The last two congresses have been the least productive of any in history because of this dumb fuck extreme ideology that is all been to force disintrest in government as a whole, sell a narrative that government doesn't work, and to kill social safety nets to make workers scared and compliant and do things because they are told to (ie vote for this republican or loose your job), and in all honesty make more money for transnational corporations who have been sold as the innovators when in fact historically it has been publicly funded science that has created the most innovation. But hey private big Buissness doesn't want you to know that! Read "the master switch" by tim wu to learn about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This badass Oregon Senator has been holding a talking filibuster against the Gorsuch nomination for the past 14 hours! Jeff Merkley should be an example for the entire r/esistance. [ x-post /r/esist ] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They double roast all the beans they use since 1987 when there was a blight and they didn't want to worry about it. So they make sure the flavor is uniformly the same. The difference in flavor for espresso drinks is made uniform but their Pike's coffee is newer and isn't following the double roast policy they do on espresso coffee so that can be different. But I don't drink their regular coffee, only espresso drinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because 20 acres and mule makes up for 100 years of slavery and then 100 years of second class citizen status under law, and then 50 years of second class status by systemic off the books policies and also policies to break them as a political group ( google journalist gary webb and cia drug trafficking) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a people who have been under foot historically for 250+ years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope they are mad at her. They are pissed that she had the smarts and her skin color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> has anyone found any racist or r/T_D crap in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get how this works. I thought professional Athletes were not allowed to compete to the Olympics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We play by Brooklyn rules in here you Kentucky turtle bitch" - Chuck "BoneBreaker" Schumer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China, South Korea, Texas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Donald Trump is gonna send you back to your country" - this is the the litmus test to how racist a person is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to the irish who did everything they could to live during the blight who didn't come to the United States. The point is eating the rotten fruit by accident is the same thing. People will do anything to hold on to the life they had, fearing change, fearing the different and new. They would eat the poison fruit with glee as you can see with the election of trump if it gave them the sense that things might feel normal again and be happier times. But it's false hopes from a false prophet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same way with coffee and starbucks. No matter where you go it will be the same quality and same flavor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vice one completely throws me off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unless you are starving poor. Then you cut the 10% good out and savor what little you can eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't rack mount it easily and can't expand it with new cards easily to make it turn key stupid easy most pro go NO NO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from maryland, you just have the exact same username from Gaming / AIM as an old class friend of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apple has over $90 billion in liquid money in the bank still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhhhhhh he doesn't think that far ahead. He only plays 4d chess, not 5d chess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those are plugs from his back hair. The finest back hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like 60, You know MAGA and all that bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a path most students don't even think about because community college is looked down upon by most because the culture we have in america.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red hats are the new brownshirts more realistically  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always find stuff like this in extreme feat sports competitions amazing. Gymnastics, figure skating, skate boarding, surfing, and the like require a competetor to push the envelope to perform unimaginable feats like comparing olympic gymnastics from 1920 to the 1990s its like comparing watching a child walk for the first time to Usain Bolt running the fastest time. You have people who push it and force the performance feat sport on its head. I mean look at skateboarding from the 1980s in back yard pool carving to the insane foot tricks today. 

One person spawns an entire paradigm shift in in how people look at the tricks or techniques they can do like this unheard of backflip, now others are going to try and copy and expand this like a remix artist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to community college in town near school you want to go to save $40,000+ then go to school with college credits typically designed to transfer to that major school and have basic credit requirements done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yelling fire in a theater and directing a crowd to violence are the only two forms of speech that are illegal. And as we can see here he is dead to rights on at least 7 counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morals? Ethics? A Sith needs not these things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Current cheeto on Google](http://imgur.com/gallery/VgMdR)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im just gonna say it Andromeda is a shit 3rd rate scifi show and kevin sorbo can suck it. If i have to hear that man think he has any idea about politics again .... for frak sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was fired from that agency for making blanketly false reports to promote borderline genocidal level campaign against Muslims, sunni and shia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He grabbed him by the shaft and went on him like a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local government includes transportation panel which is an appointment position in government  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> behold the power of Star Trek, and the fact he has experience in local government as well as he ran for city council member and state assemblyman, losing though. But  he was appointed to the board of directors of the Southern California Rapid Transit District, making him part of the team that initiated and planned the Los Angeles subway system. Takei was called away from the set of Star Trek: The Motion Picture in 1978 to cast the tie-breaking vote for the creation of the Los Angeles subway system. He served on the board from 1973 to 1984. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snake oil salesman knows what's up, plug and run plug and run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In particular the republican party  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> APRIL FOOLS!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You treat this basic concept like a luxury you are asking to have people living in apartments 70s and split up houses and asking to pay 1500 to 1800 for a 1 bedroom. That just is not affordable. You can't have a service class who has to commute 2 hours by mass transit provide in the city services then. It is not possible to maintain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shared on my only political news facebook page of over 25,000 followers for shits and giggles because sometimes talking about the insanity of american politics right now needs a nice little musical interlude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just Small apartment Buildings, we need AFFORDABLE small apartment buildings. Like 500 Sqft with kitchen and bath for $650 a month with modern wiring for networking, bike storage, and parking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brace yourselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See West Virginia go blue in 4 years then if this is signed into law and coal miners become pot growers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between that and french onion in a bread bowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump nominates ex-AT T lobbyist Makan Delrahim as head of DoJ antitrust unit; Delrahim previously said AT T-Time Warner merger not a major antitrust problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump nominates ex-AT T lobbyist Makan Delrahim as head of DoJ antitrust unit; Delrahim previously said AT T-Time Warner merger not a major antitrust problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps new antitrust nominee has said he doesnt see major problems with the AT T-Time Warner merger: The president nominated Makan Delrahim as his leading antitrust enforcer today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps new antitrust nominee has said he doesnt see major problems with the AT T-Time Warner merger: The president nominated Makan Delrahim as his leading antitrust enforcer today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crime is a symptom of a much larger issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres the Data Republicans Just Allowed ISPs to Sell Without Your Consent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres the Data Republicans Just Allowed ISPs to Sell Without Your Consent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres the Data Republicans Just Allowed ISPs to Sell Without Your Consent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres the Data Republicans Just Allowed ISPs to Sell Without Your Consent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong the lead evil mogai was stripe. He then was replaced by brain in gremiln form as the leader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/shittylifeptotips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It runs in a plot line akin to Boys from Brazil and do you kill a kid because he is a clone of Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your leaders are dead and all you have are men who look to make money or power its hard to find proper direction for cases. Example being ACLU with Rosa Parks over Claudette Colvin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shall I go into the history and horrors of the black person's American Experience? From Slavery to Emancipation, from Sharecropping and Jim Crow to Emmit Till and [The whites Firebombing by Crop duster planes of Black Wallstreet](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tulsa_race_riot), from public lynchings and church bombings to civil rights that finally got rid of poll taxes and poll tests designed to disenfranchise poor and educated blacks alike, to the assassination of any common sense leaders who tried to help the community and unite it like Medgar Evers, Harry and Harriette Moore, Fred Hampton, and Martin Luther King. Lastly the fact there is evidence that the crack epidemic that mostly effected poor inner city black communities was done to fund gun running to south american anti communist rebels by the Reagan Administration and the CIA because no one would care about them and destroying their communities which stood opposed to the Republican Agenda which was mostly made up for anti black anti civil rights groups post the Southern Strategy by Nixon to convert the southern democrats. 

And lets talk about laws the then also criminalized crack cocaine vs powder cocaine twice as hard with mandatory minimums so even though powder cocaine is more expensive and higher grade and usually done by white people they are less likely to go to jail for it, [the fact that if have a "black sounding name" even if you have the exact same stats on resume it takes nearly 1/3 longer to get a call back for a job as a white applicant sound name.](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/black-sounding-names-study_us_561697a5e4b0dbb8000d687f)

African Americans make up 13% of the population yet have the highest poverty rate, 27.4 percent, followed by Hispanics at 26.6 percent and whites at 9.9 percent. 45.8 percent of young black children (under age 6) live in poverty, compared to 14.5 percent of white children. And poverty typical is generational and it can be traced back to the Reconstruction and those very Jim Crow Laws that put black men in prison for being black and out past a curfew.

If you want and understanding of the systemic issues blacks have faces i highly suggest watching the documentary [13th on netflix](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/13th_\(film\)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know its more than just that right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retarded pumpkin face confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 points more and he will match nixion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you hourly or salary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting for the nixon 25% level. Once he hits that and below then its really going to get good. I have a feeling we can do it in the first 100 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey i at least have articles with peer reviewed sources that's better than most people who post statements on reddit. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its one thing to notice here ... NOT A SINGLE DEMOCRAT ... ALL REPUBLICAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tis funny because creator of show is Russian! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read newspapers everyday and rarely are black scientists featured again accept for Neil degrasse tyson. A movie that is number one in the united states that shows a under told story about nasa and women who put us on the moon and into space puts dreams in children's heads. These become heroes for young girls who typically only see people as working parents, or entertainers or sports centric. The rise of black nerdom has changed dynamics greatly as well. Sadly female black nerds get people yelling at them from both sides about being black and being female. I see this in my engineering classes and in tech all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny fact, people who watch Daily show have shown to be more knowledgeable about the democratic process and politics of the USA as well as world politics than fox new watchers. Daily show viewers are also more likely to be NPR listeners as well who are the most informed overall of actual news broadcast listeners.

- http://www.thecarpetbaggerreport.com/archives/714.html

- http://www.alternet.org/media/science-fox-news-why-its-viewers-are-most-misinformed

- http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/tv-movies/fox-news-viewers-informed-current-events-don-watch-news-study-finds-article-1.981257

- https://www.poynter.org/2012/survey-nprs-listeners-best-informed-fox-news-viewers-worst-informed/174826/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In science there are very few public zeitgeist acknowledged modern day scientists who are black besides Dr. Neil Degrasse Tyson because he is the only one that gets on tv enough. Most kids when I have done afterschool  programs with don't even know who Dr. Mae Jemison is.

Typically the only names that kids can come up with are Eli Whitney, which hurts even thinking about that, or only george washington carver.

Having heros in science who look like you I knew from an early age was important. Hell I don't know why I knew it was important I just knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thissssssty snek! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OpenEMU equivalent for Windows? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i recently built a gaming pc having been on Mac / Linux for a long time. I'm wondering if there is anything akin to OpenEMU on the Windows platform. I have been using a raspberry pi with retropi for a home console setup but I want to play games on my pc as well now and I have no clue where to start for a Library collection system that shows my games like OpenEMU or RetroPi does for windows 10

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not going to end well on parts of the internet that are good with photoshop .... and like porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independence and joining the EU I bet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drive time to the centerline of the August 21, 2017 total solar eclipse (Salem is Ground Zero) [x-post /r/Mapporn] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See i love Penny, "Seriously Taylor Swift?!?!?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is not a ghostbusters joke here I will very disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant believe he didn't' give props to Jennifer Hale as well for FemShep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birdman rises! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gallop is 100 years old and it's statistical modeling which is kinda difficult to make bias since they are open about the questions they ask, the only bias you see is your bias because your asshats always lose, CNN uses them because they are 100 years old. They have proven to be good at calling presidential elections over that time. So please charlie go back up your horse somewhere else because seriously its only "liberal leaning" because you can't subtract your bias from your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it hits 23% we can actually say he is worse than Nixion. I look forward to this day greatly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um you don't understand how statistics work do you?

Trump's win is a statistical anomaly and the fact is based on people polls and the popular vote he lost. 

It is like saying oh hey an organization that has been around for 100 years and has pretty much gotten every election right based on polling and statistical modeling with 10,000 poll size for mathematical statistical reliability to match population and group make up of each area they poll got 1 wrong because of an unseen result except by a small group of people when every other statistical model agreed with them.



Yeah fuck them they called it wrong so they are wrong for life. The Math was there, Hillary won the popular vote, this is what gallop was polling on. Not electoral college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is his FIRST 100 days. This is historically low for that. Most presidents get a serious bump up in approval when entering he has been a stone in the lake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Approval Rating Drops to New Low of 36% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn met with Turkey at Donald Trumps hotel. Guess who else attended? Devin Nunes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn met with Turkey at Donald Trumps hotel. Guess who else attended? Devin Nunes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn met with Turkey at Donald Trumps hotel. Guess who else attended? Devin Nunes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though she has a masters in physics and PhD in quantum chemistry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew. He was a joke. No one respected him. He was the bloody secondary villain in Devil's Advocate for pete sake that rapes his daughter and the devil helps get away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. but the fact is most people don't know this and his face is on the book and they think he wrote it. So his name is bound to these words for life. There is no other way to deny them unless he were to recant in another book and explain his sins and misdeed to man kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter. because it is his name and he can't have another in his life since he has signed himself to lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Donnie's book. I guess he can always rewrite it ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Bannon wanted to use healthcare vote to make 'enemies list' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beware false prophets who are only in it for the profits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Lost Mr. Rogers Episodes Mysteriously ResurfaceAnd Might Be a Message to Trump: After Trump's budget called for ending public arts funding and hiking military spending, Cold War-era episodes about stripping public arts funding went live on YouTube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Lost Mr. Rogers Episodes Mysteriously ResurfaceAnd Might Be a Message to Trump: After Trump's budget called for ending public arts funding and hiking military spending, Cold War-era episodes about stripping public arts funding went live on YouTube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Lost Mr. Rogers Episodes Mysteriously ResurfaceAnd Might Be a Message to Trump After Trump's budget called for ending public arts funding and hiking military spending, Cold War-era episodes about stripping public arts funding went live on YouTube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Lost Mr. Rogers Episodes Mysteriously ResurfaceAnd Might Be a Message to Trump After Trump's budget called for ending public arts funding and hiking military spending, Cold War-era episodes about stripping public arts funding went live on YouTube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is fucking amazing. I saw this done with existing organs to make replacement transplant organs that become detergent cleaned and then seeded with the transplantee's stem cell / heart cells/ kidney cells / liver cells and makes it a exact match replacement organ . But this is an amazing lateral move of this same technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also Obama golfed on Airforce base golf courses that were secure and publicly funded and open to the public as well. Donnie has be dipping his hand in the pot by having tax players fund his private club he still owns and isn't divested from for 3 million a pop each weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The traffic for /r/the_donald is well know to be infested with bots and fake accounts to force the upvotes. Its just a ddos attack of a social media variety  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Donnie's book. I guess he can always rewrite it ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck did you get the idea I was blaming black people? shit I said southern states and Red states are the ones who are using the most foodstamps and federal funding handouts. shut up dumbass troll, blah you basic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's a bingo!](http://i.imgur.com/ltNd0EO.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> black people make up 13% of the US population. There are more white people on wellfare than there are black people. You never been to Appalachia or the rust belt have you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't happen to go to highschool In Annapolis, MD did you with Mr Grimes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then i say shit is hard. I was disabled for 10 years and have been on food stamps and medicaide as well for my medical issues. And I belive when I start making a salary in the 100,000 level with my computer engineering degree that i should pay more taxes

Make American Great Again? Well america was at it's Greatest in the 1950s by all accounts of the baby boomers and donald trump ... Guess what the tax rate was on the top 5%. during war it got up to 90 % and there was no capital gains tax there was just 1 tax rate on any income you made. And companies had no tax loopholes and paid 45% tax. We also had higher rates of small businesses then too. 45% of the united states worked for self owned shops. now that 15%

We funded sending every soldier to public universities and ONLY public universities. We created great network of schools in California for enlisted Naval Officers to have easy access to. We went to the moon several times and we did so many things to protect art and culture for the sake of history in public museums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. steel mills question Trumps Buy America talk as Russian competition revives N.J. community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. steel mills question Trumps Buy America talk as Russian competition revives N.J. community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. steel mills question Trumps Buy America talk as Russian competition revives N.J. community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a population relation map ... https://www.maps4office.com/population-map-usa-states-powerpoint

now here are the states that use the most federal money

The 10 states receiving the most in federal aid as a percentage of their general revenue, in order, were:

 Mississippi,  42.9% federal aid as percentage of general revenue
 Louisiana,  41.9%
 Tennessee, 39.5%
 South Dakota, 39.0%
 Missouri,  38.2%
 Montana, 37.4%
 Georgia, 37.3%
 New Mexico, 36.6%
 Alabama, 36.1%
 Maine, 35.3%

now foodstamps

 7 Louisiana
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: 868,192
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 18.67%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state): Around $107.4 million
 
  Cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $23.10
 
 6 Tennessee
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: Just over 1.28 million
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 19.58%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state?): Around $158.7 million
 
  Cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $24.23
 
 5 Oregon
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: 791,222
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 19.93%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state?): Around $98 million
 
  Cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $24.66 per person
 
 4 West Virginia
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: 369,249
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 19.96%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state?): Around $45.7 million
 
  Cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $24.69 per person
 
 3 New Mexico
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: 448,328
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 21.5%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state?): Around $55.5 million
 
  Cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $26.60 per person
 
 2 Mississippi
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: 650,911
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 21.74%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state?): Around $80.5 million
 
  Estimated cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $26.90 per person
 
 1 District of Columbia
 
  Number of food stamp recipients: 144,768
 
  Percentage of the state's population on food stamps: 21.97%
 
  Total cost of just these benefits alone (That is, how much do just the money on those EBT cards cost the state?): Around $18 million
 
  Estimated cost of benefits alone per capita in this state: $27.19 per person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is good quality shitpost! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it would go to consider that Blue states with more people would be using more welfare ... BUT THEY ARE NOT. 

But Texas is using their tax dollars to teach "Evolution is just a theory" they are the ones fucking over their next generation. Not the blue states. Also aren't you supposed to lift your shits up from the boot straps or something if you want to bitch about Blue states not giving a flying fuck about your fly over fucktard state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if he was a minor? he taking advantage then son? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide Squad reminded me of an 80s action film like Tango   Cash and knew how much of a joke it was.

BvS was just so fucking stick up it's butt grim dark serious that you couldn't take it serious at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remember to raise you kids knowing this. Never forget it. This country was founded with the goal of immigrants and those oppressed to be free and have a chance. It is a nation that wants you to succeed no matter how much the fear mongers and bigots say else-wise. We are a nation founded on the ideas of getting the world's tired, poor, and huddled masses yearning to to breath free. 

And be your brothers keeper and he will be yours. You pull that man, woman, or child out of the ocean of dispair, you be that savior in the night with every tax dollar we spend on services like education, after school programs, morning and after school meal programs, after school enrichment programs, elderly assistance programs and healthcare access. 

Thank you for making our country more diverse and making it a better tasting hot pot mix of amazingness. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh son, you better look at the federal spending maps and where welfare is used, medicare, medicaid, and foodstamps highest per capita usage is always in red states. the blue states use less federal dollars then they send in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The Farm Subs go mostly to agrochemical used produce like Dent corn which is inedible and makes high fructose corn syup. Check out this doc [King Corn](https://g.co/kgs/l8mzrU) to learn more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Mercer, is gunning for his lackey's failure on Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell that to the biggest users of social welfare, Red states </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lie Lie Land - In Political Theaters Everywhere! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about it I should have replied "[My sweet dear Brother Numsie!](https://youtu.be/eUeda7dRN0E)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vjUqUVrXclE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude russia is corrupt as fuck and gay people were not a scapegoat problem 10 years ago. The reason why they are banning gay people and information or support for them now is because its Putin's play to keep people distracted and finding enemies within and not looking at his dirty tricks.

You replace gays with jews its the same thing. 

Also I have visited Russia and have a bunch of Russian friends, trust me they are decadent and hedonistic as fuck. Nudity is on tv and so is hardcore porn on broadcast tv. Child poverty is rampant and you see kids huffing paint all over St Petersberg and Moscow. 

Their Culture is one of getting drunk and being bitter and and highly guarded all the time. They are western as fuck and enjoy all the crap we enjoy but Putin plays them like a fiddle and anyone who doesn't go his way falls out a hotel window, dies of radioactive tea, dies of explosion in their apartment on Putin's birthday, or some other what the fuck how the hell jesus christ grandiose assassination  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
