<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7498</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Animal Farm is a personal favorite of mine, I'd definitely recommend that to r/noturgrandmaw. It's one of those that engrosses you for a couple hours and then you finish and can't stop thinking about it. In Cold Blood is chilling. Really excited to read the rest of these. Hopefully I can bang them out in the next year or so, but I do have a lot more books to be read as well. I bring them in much faster than I can read them :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a list on Goodreads of books I come across that look interesting to me so I save them in a to-read shelf online. I will likely never get to all of these because it's in the hundreds now and growing, but it's a good source to pull ideas from. However, I also have a bunch of unread books on my personal, physical shelf that usually get priority since I own them. This is the list I was primarily referring to in the title and I plan on reading all of them. So I kind of just meant that my physical bookshelf is piling up and I should probably hold off on buying new books for awhile, but I simply can't resist when it comes to good deals. I think i'm over 100 books on my physical shelf now after today. If you're interested I do have both of these "lists" in two different online shelves on [my Goodreads page](https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/2829998-ian)

I'm always looking to share book ideas with people so feel free to add me if you have an account. The ones in this haul I picked up because I know the authors or titles. Many of them are highly regarded names in classic literature (Dostoyevsky, Faulkner, Capote, Marquez, Orwell) and some more modern (Smith, Dellilo, Foer). Then a few of the others are bestsellers I believe. I'm into a lot of literary fiction so you will find a lot more of that on my Goodreads lists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went out of town to a different Goodwill than i'm used to. Found out it's incredible. 50 cents a piece. **I have already read Animal Farm and In Cold Blood, but figured why not grab a copy.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $7 Goodwill haul. My reading list is getting out of hand! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually went into it not knowing anything about it other than that Camus was a psychological type of writer. So despite the size I expected this tedious, difficult book for no good reason. This made it that much better when I got hooked from the first sentence and became immersed in the story. He tricks you cause the writing is so simple and straightforward but suddenly certain sentences cut right to your core with depth and meaning. Now I know why it's talked about so much on here!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! I felt like during those last few pages it was just spewing with great qoutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished The Stranger and I loved it so much. I'm still trying to wrap my head around everything but nearing the end I was savoring every sentence. Can't wait to get to his other books now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was exactly my thought process. I saw the same video with the Karate Kid clips. Now it's driving me crazy as well! Seems like it would be a memorable qoute but it doesn't show up in any of the IMDB or Rotten Tomatoes qoutes for that movie, or other searches. It's very possible the fanmade video just used Karate Kid and the lyrics aren't even from that movie. My guess is that it's from an 80's movie of some sort. We may have to watch the movie to find out, its been years for me.

Edit: there are actually at least 2 videos using Karate Kid clips in the music video, so it's definitely the best lead we have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Karate Kid maybe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up. I do plan on getting to more of his works eventually. I will keep this in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing lol. It's a good thing you decided to go to one more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow that's awesome. All your hard work paid off! I like to think that was your 5th and final one where you hit the jackpot just to imagine how rewarding that would feel. They all look to be in solid shape as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What! Are you the only reader that goes to your Goodwill? I would be lucky just to find one of these books at my Goodwill. Amazing haul. 

Band of Brothers on HBO is one of my favorite TV series ever. I haven't read the book but definately watch the series after you read it if you haven't already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Stranger, by Albert Camus**

**Slaughterhouse-Five, by Kurt Vonnegut**

**The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time, by Mark Haddon** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - The Long Walk by Stephen King (pen name Richard Bachman) - Thriller/dystopian/horror

- The Road by Cormac McCarthy - Postapocalpytic, bleak but addictive

- The One Man by Andrew Gross - Historical fiction/thriller involving the holocaust 

- And Then There Were None by Agatha Christie - Mystery

- Flowers for Algernon by Daniel Keyes - heartfelt, emotional, psychological 

This is a very dark and/or emotional list so be careful. Don't do them all at once :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be just me but the minimalist type of writing style in The Road reminded me of Farewell to Arms by Hemingway. Both use spare diologue as well as use "and" multiple times per sentence. The Road is consistently bleak while Farewell to Arms offers some colorful moments, although both are very dark overall. Apart from the writing styles and emotional storylines the two novels are very different. 

Unfortunately, I haven't read anything else from these writers yet, so I can't comment on their other books. You may find more of that style in McCarthy's other works, however.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one hell of a list. Make your way through all of them :)

More specifically, East of Eden is a favorite of mine. Simple to read but so deep in meaning. Amazing characters. Beautiful, comforting writing. Vivid depiction of the setting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Psycho by Brett Easton Ellis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watership Down by Richard Adams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This excites me. Haven't read it yet but the family life theme really appeals to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Longest book i've read so far. But also the most satisfying partly because of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading Flowers for Algernon all in one day must make it all the more heartbreaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear about your relationship and reading struggles. Maybe you just need some time away from reading, or Harry Potter at least.

You could try another genre that you normally wouldn't go for, like non-fiction. Try reading in another setting than your used to, such as at the park or somewhere else outdoors. Maybe try audiobooks instead. Or take a break from reading books entirely for a little till your in a different emotional state. No need to force yourself to finish the series as soon as possible. We all go through reading slumps, it will pass eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I thought the movie adaptation was pretty damn good. Of course a film is never going to be able to capture the full experience of reading McCarthy, it did stick to the story pretty closely. I thought the final scene of the book was a little more ambiguous in my mind, whereas the film seemed to give the viewer a definite outcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The HBO adaptation of Band of Brothers has to be one of the greatest TV series i've ever watched. So powerful and incredibly well made. 

I love it so much I might still read the book, which I usually never do if i've already seen a screen adapation of it. But I figure theres gotta be some additional info on the relationships and experiences of E-Company in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading *The Long Walk* by Stephen King under alias Richard Bachman. It's a dystopian/thriller/horror. It's quite the page turner but very brutal. 

Some Dystopian Classics: 

- Animal Farm by George Orwell
- 1984 by George Orwell
- The Giver by Lois Lowry
- Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury
- Brave New World by Aldous Huxley 
- The Handmaid's Tale by Margaret Atwood

Also seconding u/cardinalsagain about *And Then There Were None* by Agatha Christie. That's a great mystery to start out with. Heard her other stuff is great too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited to read Dandelion Wine, looks up my alley from what i've heard. I own *Something Wicked This Way Comes* which also looks good. Do you know if these are stand alone novels or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Cannery Row* by John Steinbeck!

P.S...it's not about canning goods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Don't even wait any longer, pick up 11/22/63 right now OP. You won't regret it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to hear! It looked interesting to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> East of Eden does get crazy hype on here, but for me it lived up to that. But try not to be expecting something mindboggling every time you turn the page, let it come to you and enjoy the ride. I haven't read Infinite Jest, but it won't be like some groundbreaking style that blows your mind. If you have read Steinbeck before you can expect his same cozy style of writing. It's a wonderful story about two families finding their paths and teetering between good and evil. It is easy to read and understand, but so deep in every other aspect. It has not just one of the most memorable characters i've read, but about three of them at the very least. The scenery and people on the page are painted so vividly as well. Every page was just so pleasurable to read. 

That would be my vote. Just go into it like your there to read a nice long story and you will absolutely love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to have an emotional, very human experience and..

...want a shorter read: Flowers for Algernon

...want a longer read: East of Eden

Two of my favorites.

*I haven't read most of these though* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. I will give it a shot one day. I only paid 50 cents for it so I won't feel too bad if I have to abandon it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no. Painful in an emotional and violent way or painful as in hard to get through?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a reading challenge of mostly modern classics right now, but when I'm done I will be expanding. I try to write small reviews for most of what I read and am very active. I'm most interested in literary fiction, historical fiction, history non-fiction, classics, but I love discovering new books. Feel free to [add me](https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/2829998-ian) ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Catcher in the Rye* alone is worth more than $8 in just the reading experience alone in my eyes. 

Then you got *Man's Search for Meaning* and *Night*. That's one intense holocaust experience you're going to have with those two. 

You also got *Devil in the White City* which i've heard good things about.

You even got some more on top of that. Nice Haul!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Top 2** I got at Goodwill for $.50 a piece

**Bottom 3** were buy 2 get 1 free for $1.00 a piece at a library sale.

They looked interesting enough on Goodreads to give them a shot. 

**Also** The Dennis Lehane one is *Live by Night* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grabbed these for a total of $3.00 today. Anyone read them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked up *The Risk Pool* at a discount store a few weeks ago. Anyone read this one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love his storytelling and his writing. Everything he writes has this comfy type of feel to it that is hard to explain. I've still got a lot of his stuff to read too. Only read Of Mice and Men and Cannery Row in addition to EoE so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that makes sense. Glad it didn't ruin your experience. I personally picked it up on my own because It was recommended to me by people I knew, so I was under the impression they wouldn't have if it was a tough read. Plus I had experience with Steinbeck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you think Hitchhiker's Guide would be challenging if I might ask?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me about Lolita. I felt the same way. Maybe "tough" to read parts for some people because of the subject matter but the writing is wonderful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited to read Master and Margarita. Have it on my shelf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
