<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5027</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So fucking mad litt fucking fuck!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [no offense lady but what you don't know could fill a wharehouse] (https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=-59ezAQarKY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lunatic, raving psychopathic foh looking in at a chef at work. Avert yon eyes plebs! Magic is transpiring!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have free reign to enjoy anyone's misery. Cause that's how shit works now isn't it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I is rat, I are comfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a losing argument. 

I mean of course they were the only organization to preach poverty but accumulate vast wealth and power. 

The only one ever! 

It's not common place at all for groups and organizations to try to accumulate strength of self interest. Nope! Never happened before and certainly not normal, never happened again either! 

I mean that's why it's shady right, it behaved so different from every other organization at the time and since  right. Yep! Certainly not the most commonplace expectations at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rude to his water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The classic:
Post - "Doctors of Reddit..."

A thousand responses - "Not a doctor here but..."

Not a doctor but shut your fucking mouth you fuck. Not everyone wants to hear the bullshit spewing from your dick holder of a mouth, and you contribute to the white noise and growing inefficiency of this community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's happy ol'Russia trying to deflect interest in the Trump/Russia probe again. Pretty standard at this point I'd like to believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civility has nothing to do with cursing you insignificant little toasters. 
"Your mother tasted like twelve types of penis last night you loser, shame your daddy didn't raise you right or beat her proper."
See what I did there? Uncivil without cursing.

"Man I fukin love when some cun+ stands the fuk up for common sense and the right to freedom of speech, you'd be such a cool ba$tard if you did that"
See what I did there? Civil with cursing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry gang, you're all gay to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that and what a pussy Noctis is sometimes. Total bummer. But over all fucking very enjoyable game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct duck. Early morning, and 3pm during chapter six when the darkness begins to take over slowly. I just didn't have the patience to wait until 3pm with my clean clothes. Fightin to be done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different time of day. You don't see the dust though? I really don't have the idea of fucking bamboozling people over fucking dust on clothes. But I also wasn't gonna try to wait until the perfect time in day. Thought it was pretty clear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah not really. There's the one in the picture. It's end game shit though. It's the royal outfit you wear for the last bit, and the gang gets the claives outfit. There's also a chocobo outfit from the festival that was out you can keep. But the game doesn't focus on the actual outfits for stats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had freeze stutter today for the first time since day 1 release but having said that I closed application and restarted it. Running it on standby for two weeks. But up until that I haven't had a stutter, I wasn't even aware it was one of the issues until I just read your comment. Sheeeitt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like every other piece of the puzzle, I have my doubts. I want to believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I had a lot of little complaints at the beginning. But overall they've won me over. Who grinds to level 99 if they don't love the game ya know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a little dusty but only the finest Lucian gel hits this mop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before   after a restless week of fighting in FFXV. Dirty job saving the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "without problems" 
Righhht haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What could go wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some petty mother fuckers up in this thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noooiceee. One of these days, I'm going to cut you into little pieces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In light of the repeal of online privacy, this is a plan and a redditot spear heading it, to purchase the history of those who voted to repeal privacy rights. Please support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't think we should be greedy. Really just a few grand to everyone on this thread is cool, we cool, it's all good. I'll buy a sick gaming chair, guy can feed his kids, someone will definitely buy a goat to have sex with... Philanthropy in action!! Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut off the humans horn!! I am lrrr, ruler of omicron persei 8 and I demand the humans horn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this is such garbage. Go back to Wales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you deserve more upvotes than the person posting "for every upvote I'll go a day without smoking".
Remember. You're a far better example than that, keep up the good fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input sweetheart, I'll be sure to take a note on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is becoming dominated by non accidental images, and I guess whatever. Reddit needs to be a circle jerk to be true to itself but I had this thing going... See my friend is studying the Renaissance and we have some distance between us, so every day towards drinking time, I'll send him the top of Accidental Renaissance to spur conversation and debate. Unfortunately this is no longer the case these past few days. Just blatant images designed to be this way. Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta stick to the classics,
TROGDOR!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called a living wake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iPhone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no over qualified for hourly. Just forget that concept altogether. Numerous highly qualified industries charge exclusive by hourly (ie: lawyers, mechanics, technicians, etc). And at the same time shit loads of idiots get paid salaries in our industry. Forget the concept and move on with a decision on your own hourly rate, or your salary rate. Put either choice on the table moving forward with a new employer.

Use your skills and prove to be effective for $25-$30 (example) an hour and not a waste of money, they'll avoid working you too many hours then. Alternatively be sure to include a stipulation in your contact if you go salary, the stipulation being that the salary is for a forty four hour work week, and if you surpass that the hourly rate is x dollars for every hour. So many young people I've seen sign onto contracts without understanding it's very very very standard to outline the hours in a standard work week related to your salary.

I've never heard of over qualified for an hourly wage and perhaps it's a concept that's regional, but I can not stress enough that you must decide for yourself what your skills are worth hourly or on salary. You're allowed to waiver by small degrees and take a little less or a little more to compromise one thing or another, but try not to compromise yourself too much. It sounds like you're worth something and people will be lucky and happy to have you even if there's a struggle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah really. So annoying.


 Downvote and move on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the biggest circle jerk thread of the day!! Wooo wooo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You saw that post too did ya?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, much respect for the sentiment you're conveying, I too tend to feel minimums don't cover some situations we get ourselves in. Having said that this is professional and it is your life and career you are ultimately interested in, no one would expect less.

There are regional laws for notice and termination, I know mine but it doesn't always help. Personally, and I hope this helps without coming across as sentimental, I try to be as honest and direct as possible. I tell them point blank,

Ex: " I'm leaving, but I understand our situation... I'll be giving a guaranteed two weeks employment moving forward and I'll happily help in the search and training of a replacement. After the two weeks I'll also help out you guys anyway I can as long as my priority is given to my new job. I can work shifts when available until the replacement is trained, I'll always be in touch to help with vendors and recipes. You've been great and I want you to succeed as much as I want myself to succeed, so let's make this work, BREAK!!" haha

I've worked two jobs and extreme hours to help out a previous employer I've befriended, while on another instance they took my notice as an insecurity and they released me with a lay off (where I am located termination requires at least one prior written warning, and since they didn't have it they were forced into a lay off situation). It can go either way, but ultimately I was satisfied.

We're strong personalities, in small numbers, so we get attached. Just be honest, direct, and provide the limited options available to help those out who you deem fit. It's what makes us chefs. An unwavering direction and the strength to just make sure this fucking works.  

They hate to love us. Or love to hate us. 

Good luck 
From your fellow blood soaked savage forgotten by time and civil society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah in that case I apologize kind sir or sirette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My PC currents, some might appeal to you

Cities Skylines (city builder, like SimCity but good)

Fallout (all of em, cause I'm just more comfortable in the wastelands)

GTA V (can't go wrong, visually stunning with mods and a little of everything available for a gamer)

Hitman Absolution (the new one has six missions, Absolution has nineteen with great detail and an awesome involving story line)

Osiris New Dawn (early release stage, survival "horror" that has me addicted like crack. So fun. So gorgeous. Can not give these guys enough support, they're doing so well and involved with the community to avoid a no man's sky debacle)

Witcher 3 (it's a bigly game, huge hands, everybody knows it, China, period)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just mean man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cloud went full Malad!!! You thought Sepiroth was evil... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can hear a man walking from such a distance in that quiet. I'd hear someone in a vehicle coming for about twenty minutes it felt before you even saw hide or hair of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're getting downvoted to hell but the truth is a lot of people are enjoying the game. There is however truth to the..Uhh... Quality checking that went into the release. I don't like it myself but my buddy does and he's only half retarded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the teeth always get me man. Same with the Fallout. Witcher 3. Doing a playthrough again here now on Witcher and I'm like, please don't try to smile at me peasants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but you're wrong. And you're having an insanely hard time admitting it in the face of the consistent popular opinion that many more developers successfully managed facial features. Again you're allowed to have your taste in this world but it seems like you just popped off at the mouth and are sticking to your statement while being blatantly shot down...
Anyways. Good luck, umm, playing games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferret! Very social though needs friends in other animals. Super playful and loyal, lifelong style so only if serious because they live a long time. 

Sad but true, mine used to curl up every night with me, when I left for college he gained a bunch of weight, lost all his hair and died in a year. RIP Hobbes my little homie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the Andromeda talk, let's remember some good [RE7] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But.. But... Another settlement needs your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude as much as I want this it would cost a fortune to truck to the east coast. R/gamecollecting will definitely take it. 

My heart weeps at my distance right now :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I declare effing savage!!!
It counts, because I declared it.

Also can we take a minute for how Jim makes Dwight announce every guest at the formal party at Schrute Farm. My personal favorite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayyyooooo 
Now stuff it deep down inside like the rest of us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude this post fucking sucks. 
Your post is bad and you should feel bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, totally new to this subreddit. A lot of respect for a lot of reasons goes out to all of you who do this stuff and post with recipes. 
I have to ask and please keep the downvotes to a minimum haha but where does one get the take out style trays with compartments like seen in this post. Even their name would help the search </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super cool of you! Thanks for even doing this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like belongs in every subreddit except trashy, and a little bit on trashy too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great jerk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digby the rescue. Ridiculously photogenic jerk dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know what kind of madlad would have that font on their phone. It's truly insane how this exists and I hope he doesn't get Veronica pregnant at home coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are fucking kidding me, we look like schmucks to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn Scots ruined Scotland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you mean surprising things surprise you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cry less and be less of a little bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistics can prove anything, 4 in 5 people know that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll calf your elves to math blue bless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acktuallyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations ya fuck! Keep some of the handsome for the rest of us ya bastard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage. Full pic though come on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha nah brah. No originality left but you do what's right for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is insane to me that the top comment is about unwanted rebooting. Not that it happens to me, and nor do the ads, but because upon its release Windows 10 was a well documented privacy breacher, bandwidth stealer, and it just shocks me to see that even so much time later my Reddit brahzinskis are still suffering from it.

Here
https://windows.gadgethacks.com/how-to/everything-you-need-disable-windows-10-0163552/

And here
https://www.cnet.com/how-to/10-things-to-disable-in-windows-10/

And finally
http://lifehacker.com/how-to-configure-windows-10-to-protect-your-privacy-1716204024

Some of this will be repeated from a previous article, and some may be redundant for your system, but do yourself the favor and check into the level of connection and sharing you're involved with.

Disable auto updates immediately. Cut off the open peer to peer sharing they've forced on you. Disable advertising. Close the flood gates of personal information you're sharing as you see fit. But you can take it as far as you like, and these are friendly easy ways to get a more stable and private system. Upon my first install it took me two days with open eyes to disable the amount of spyware I found and even knowing it was an intrusive system I was genuinely shocked at how far it went. 

Anyways this article will be irrelevant for you as it was me if you just take a moment, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey lips look like they've been working out in prison ready to bust out that cage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah don't listen to that other guy. Print it out and shove it in his face. Then tell him, "You can run but you can't hide biiiiitttchhh" 
If he fails to get the reference slap him twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That forehead really frames that room nicely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of God ready for OP's anus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This magazine may just be you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Put a bushel of radishes in the picture brah" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely support this idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitch, you ain't fucking funny. You steal funny jokes and make them unfunny. Blame politics for your shitty reviews yeah that's totally gonna get the internet off your back. Fucking idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The people in my life lately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best crochet I've seen here it ages! Super cool, want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck these are getting annoying. So long bpt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she's the cutest damn hamster ever. Look at that satisfaction. :) :) Good for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stormtrooper here, more likely castrating Panama dairy lit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it works just fine... for a door stop, a small table perhaps, something to throw at raiders in a last ditch effort to save yourself! Reserve yours today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No. This is a fallout computer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God, I hadn't seen this reposted in almost two hours. Phew. Crises averted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Even without the plan. An apology needs to be at least the first three. My fucking ex was fucking horrific for this shit. She would apologise with an insincere "I'm sorry you're bothered by that," putting the blame onto me. 
I truly think some people are incapable of actually admitting blame, her wording was the level of a professional lawyer in order to avoid any consequence being on her. 
And in the end she would then say others can't get so upset at her when she repeated the same offenses over and over, because the distance she created was too much out of proportion. She infuriated everyone in her life frequently but of course, it was not her fault. Brutal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I love that woman. Gee golly whiz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gross by </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lithium is a pain and I don't want to ruin finding it for yourself but it can be a real challenge for sure. If you give up full stop just give it a quick google.
And yes you can craft a spaceship and leave the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not correct at all. Ramen is generally made with softer flours and has to be treated with alkaline water to achieve the chewy texture and prevent the releasing of all it's starches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I love chewing on a branch of rosemary. Add another few of them in there and I'm into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would give you gold if I could afford the five bucks or whatever steep dollar sign is attached to it haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting the receipt, you da real MVP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nexus mods is a modding community. Google Nexus mods. You can download or provide mods there, and often in the forum's you'll find people who are producing a mod that will provide new quests/characters/etc. 
When you see someone who is looking for voice actors you should apply, send them a message, a few clips and then hopefully get the part. 
Do this and similar to build a portfolio with a direction towards voice acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not from Philly here, but it's clearly because of... The implication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do not make a last of us movie.

I know ever videogame movie has worked out perfect up until now...But... Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please make this into a "deal with it" gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please make this into a "deal with it" gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude try black flag. I swore off assassin's Creed early but thankfully my friend was persistent in the fact I would love black flag and seig howdy was he right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> East coast. Brutal wind storm here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha fuck. Will correct and try again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And who starts a comment like that? That's right. Assholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My power is out. I was trying to find a way of describing it for y'all, but instead, fuck this kid in particular </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a highly personalized Android but thought hey let's give it a go, see if it knows something i haven't picked up yet... Literally the worst possible outcome. I'm no longer able to answer questions for myself, can somebody order my pizza for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. And he will. I want to be wrong. But from another country is easier to see version eventualities I believe. You will not have Trump impeached. Gentleman's bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it costs $30 000 plus. Some notable people who choose to ignore the idea include:

Al Pacino
Clint Eastwood
Denzel "don't call me Samuel" Washington
Diane Keaton
George Clooney
Robert "Big Bobby D" DeNiro
Julia Roberts

And more
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should get a little internet petition going, I've sent them an email they seem very curious and open as they've received a fuck ton more than just mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well lads and ladettes we should really take it PlayStation. Make sure they hear us because holy God awful yes this is a piss poor over sight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck I fucking hate to have to do this but I can't have hundreds of chefs spreading an error. 

* la carte* directly means 'of the menu', not off. More accurately in context when used it should read like, according to the menu. 

I'm sorry guys I'll accept the down vote party but it's my personal pet peeve when people use French terminology incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omar in The Wire. Shot by a five year old boy while picking up a pack of cigarettes. The cheese stand no mo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shower thoughts ? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sign game on point. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Men! Am I right?"
*Crowd goes wild*

Below a giant moon worm hears the thunderous applause and redirects itself. The announcer continues,

"They're just the worst!! Am I right?"
*Crowd intensifies screaming and applause*

The moon worm begins to salivate, increases his speed, and narrows down on the appetizing sounds location. His salivation only helps to speed him through the earth below the unwittingly tempting crowd of *"man haters"*. Blind as he is he knows he's getting closer all the while they're celebrating. Hunger is all he knows for certain.

"Don't be afraid to help around the house Jim! Heck maybe you should stay in the house this time around," the announcer triumphantly climaxes.

The crowd begin the claw at their own flesh in excitement while tearing out their hair to present to their goddess. This is their time, not to be shared, and it begins now. 

The thunderous applause grows so loud no one can hear it coming. He's close now. He can smell the blood above through the damp earth. 

The crowd, so loud now, can not differentiate between applause and the ominous low tone of the moon worm crushing the earth below their feet. And then, in an instant, it begins.

The earth cracks below their feet swallowing the stadium and creating a sink hole effect that sends sheer panic through the crowd. Their last instant sounds just as their first as they scream blood from their lungs while the moon worms jaws emerge, encircling all they can see. The walls of his jaws surround them, covered in jagged unkept teeth, as he raises victorious from the earth. The crowd is pounded against the earth, the collapsed stadium, one another, and the wall of teeth shredding their once energetic bodies without remorse. Those that are lucky enough die quick, while others witness the darkness of the moon worm around them and feel terror with their last breathes. How could they have known. Finally as the last are bludgeoned against the moon worms blunt killing instruments they are all once more silenced.

As the moon worm closes his jaws and darkness circles the scene, he retreats once more into his home.



He hears a low rumble... Another earth worm... In the distance..  it's communicating...

"Al," it starts.

"Come back to bed," it finishes.

"Uhh no Peg," he responds, flushing the toilet.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People cube eh. Soilent green cube? Interesting Freudian cock in the mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
