<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3642</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Words of an Explorer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Words of an Explorer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **September 9th, 2016**

This city is on no ones map. If it had ever been, those people have long since died. As have their children. And grandchildren. And great grandchildren. And great-great grandchildren. And so on.

Nonetheless, here the city stands. My source was right. My money was well spent. These ancient structures are black tombs. Weve set up our camp on the outskirts. The city is far too cold.

**September 10th, 2016**

Charles kept watch while I slept. He claimed to see no signs of life, but sounds kept him constantly alert. Soft sounds. Soft, wet, and unimposing. Sounds which drifted in and out at the limits of audibility, as if they were whispers, but windblown and damp - redolent of dying breaths and last words. 

I heard nothing. My sleep was as black as the structures ahead of us. No sounds penetrated the dreamless morass. For a brief moment upon waking, I believed to have been dead. 

Today, we tour the city.

**September 11th, 2016**

Before the chill had sapped our energy, we had explored the first couple hundred feet of the city. We stuck to the outsides, cataloging the sheer stone facades of the structures. Despite their immense age, the buildings stood unharmed. We found no indication of what had made the sounds Charles had heard.

Overnight, as Charles slept, I heard it myself. They were as hed described. However, I recognized structure in the sporadic haze of noise. If it wasnt a language, it was a natural phenomenon unlike any ever discovered. My mind wandered while I watched Charles chest rise and fall. 

The whispers suffused my auditory cortex and a synesthetic wave of hallucinatory strangeness swept through me. The sounds shimmered in my vision and danced on my tongue. They tasted like metal. Like blood. Rather than feeling disgusted, I felt a perverse sense of joy.

**September 12th, 2016**

I blinked and Charles was gone. How I could have fallen asleep is a mystery, as I was standing. But when my eyelids lifted, it was day. And my partner had disappeared. In his place were footsteps leading to the city.

The sounds are loud now. Im miles within the bowels of the cold, black city. Structures tower over me and block the sun; my breath freezes in front of my face on this late-summer day. The temperature only contributes to the feeling of wrongness.

When the wind blows, I think I hear Charles calling my name. Over and over and over and over, swept by gales of air and changing pressures and permeating the wet sounds which echo off every hut and dwelling, he calls. I will not sleep tonight.

**September 13th, 2016**

The first sign of life presented itself to me early this morning. It was a fleck of skin or gristle glinting in the sunlight. It was attached to the side of a small structure. When I went in close to investigate, I discovered it was growing from deep within a crack in the stone. I pressed my knife into it and it bled and retracted into the rock. If it werent for the gales of wind and what I now know to be Charles moans, I could have sworn I heard it make a noise. A tiny, wet noise.

**September 14th, 2016**

It is difficult to keep the fires from blowing out overnight. The expanse of this city is unlike what either of us had expected. I am beyond lost now; I am impelled ahead with the futile desire to help Charles and get us home.

The deeper I get, the worse shape the structures seem to be in. All the cracks and missing pieces are filled with the same, living tissue. Its density only increases as I follow the sounds. Always following the sounds. I know I should be running in the opposite direction. The flesh within the buildings ripples in directional peristalsis. I am following it. I have yet to see any entrance to any structure. 

**September 15th, 2016**

The city is more meat than stone now. The wet whispers assault my ears and work to infiltrate all my senses. I feel them coursing through my body. Onward, still, I trudge. The temperature is warmer. I can think of nothing other than forward movement.

**September 16th, 2016**

The cold has been replaced by heat and humidity. The stone has been subsumed by flesh; titanic structures of muscle and veins reach toward the gray sky. All is wet. All is moving.

**September 17th, 2016**

This morning, I discovered Charles. A Charles. Whether it was my partner or not is something I dont know. He was trapped within the meat of a structure. It appeared his body had been incorporated into the surrounding flesh; thick veins fed his legs and neck.

A few feet away, other Charleses were growing from different structures. All were in different forms of development. All twitched and moved with the all-encompassing fleshscape.

Theyve since noticed me. They began with simple staring, but now they are reaching. The hands of my partner - the man Ive loved - are extending toward my hands; hands which theyve held countless times in what feels like a distant past.

The wet whispers are seductive and intoxicating. I look back toward the sea of flesh and stone Ive crossed to reach this point. The thought of the cold on the outskirts of the city is hideous. To leave this warm womb where I am wanted and accepted seems abhorrent. And now, as veins extend from the hands of the Charleses, patiently waiting for my acceptance, I have a choice. Do I leave, cold and alone? Or do I enter this union of flesh?

Ive been cold and alone for so long. I need to believe Im ready for something new. Something warm. Something we can experience together. Pray for me. [Pray for us.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm definitely a fan of Tumblr. It's the main source of traffic to my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 21:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get between 250-400k per month. I'm a writer of short horror stories. The majority of my traffic comes from Tumblr but I also get some from Reddit. I've only monetized with Adsense but I'm still learning a lot. It's been a little over a year since I started.  

As far as three things, I don't really know. I think the most important thing was what I just did, which was move to a self hosted Wordpress site. Way more freedom. 

I have no idea what I'm doing. 

www.unsettlingstories.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Christmas everyone! :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magnificent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree. One of the best movies I've seen in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Takes off pants, covers self in bees.* Let's get bzzzzzz-y. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably fucked a table at one point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you not slip a muzzle on your woman, please, Mark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People downvote things almost instantaneously for pretty much no reason. Sometimes it happens multiple times within the first couple minutes. Some people are just dicks. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CAULIFLOWER *IS TRADITIONAL!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pore butt.

(Ew.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a really good idea but the author should've asked first just out of courtesy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/z83ffTWN21s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Thing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5ftmr17M-a4) (1982)

[Fire in the Sky](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ATmAc5CwJgI) (1993) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All mine are true but I don't think it's a requirement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Short Walk on the Beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Short Walk on the Beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recalling the sensation of my eyes bursting before they turned to ash is the only feeling of comfort I can extract from that moment last year.

I was walking my dog on the beach near my home. The beach had been closed for the season because of a toxic algae bloom. The woods in my backyard let out to the beach, though, and I knew enough to stay away from the water.

Parker and I were finishing up when I heard splashing near the shore. I glanced over and saw what appeared to be a school of fish trapped under the thick, algal sludge. I was surprised; the water was supposedly hypoxic from the algae. I assumed the fish would stay away.

The splashing persisted as we walked by. Parker growled. I was concerned, since he never showed any aggression of any sort since wed gotten him neutered. But as the splashing grew louder and the water grew increasingly turbid, Parkers growls became ferocious and he started to bark and pull at his leash.

I stopped and held the leash with both hands. The last thing I wanted was for him to jump in and get that algae all over him. I watched the water with Parker for a minute, then tugged the leash to get us back on track. The splashing stopped. Parker calmed down. We turned and began to move back toward the woods.

Right when we were about to step through the treeline, Parker pulled at my leash again. I tugged right back and moved on. Janice was making dinner and Id be damned if wed be late. Parker pulled again. Hard. At the same time, he whimpered. I glanced down while pulling back. My breath caught in my throat.

Something was grabbing Parkers hind leg. Something thick and tubular, almost like a heavily-veined tentacle. As the steady tug persisted and Parkers whimpering grew shrill and pained, I whirled around and saw the thick rope of veiny muscle stretching from the algae to my dog.

Without thinking, I stomped on the tentacle, feeling its boneless gristle deform under the heel of my boot. With a pull so powerful it tore the leash from my hand and caused a sickening, cracking sound to come from the area of Parkers leg and hip, the dog was launched through the air and splashed into the water. He struggled to stay afloat.

I ran across the beach and was about to jump in when a writhing mass of tentacles of all sizes began to emerge from the water. They were everywhere and stretched as far as I could see. Way in the distance, something else was starting to come to the surface. 

I was rooted to the ground with sheer, uncomprehending terror. I gazed at the shape as it rose from the surf. Parker had disappeared under the water. The tentacles slapped and writhed and twisted against one another as if they were dancing. My eyes remained riveted to the form emerging about 1000 feet offshore. I felt a hideous pressure forming in the back of my eyes accompanied by a blinding headache.

Seagulls swooped from the air to bite the fleshy masses, only to be pulled under by smaller, lightning-quick tendrils erupting from the larger tentacles. As more of the mass in the distance emerged, the blurrier it got. But as the pressure grew unbearable and my vision diminished, I still made out features: a hideous, gaping mouth. Clusters of holes with stalks emerging from them. Eyes attached to each stalk. And something else - something I can only describe as orbs of meat slowly orbiting its main bulk. I wept. 

It made one sound. Only one.

With a wet pop, my eyes burst. I felt the lachrymal fluid boiling as it ran down my cheeks. There was intense heat in my eye sockets and I was dimly aware of my hair beginning to burn. Before I lost consciousness, I was overwhelmed by a sensation of relief that I no longer had eyes to stare at the abomination in the water. I was ready to die.

Three months later, I woke up in my own bed. Id been in the hospital for 10 weeks. My wife had cared for me the entire time. No one knew what had happened to me. If it hadnt been for another passerby, I would have died on that beach.

In the days that followed, I did my best to relay to my wife what had happened. She just stroked the remains of my face and tried to console me. I could tell she believed none of it.

In my eyeless nightmare, I try to move on with my life. Its slow going. After what Id seen, I can think of almost nothing else. There are times when I think I can get by. Times, late at night, while Janice sleeps, and I lay on my back gathering the emotional strength Ill need to carry on.

But then, far off in the distance, I hear Parker barking. And theyre barks made by something other than him working his mouth and throat and lungs. 

Ill turn over in bed and imagine tears leaking out of my old eyes, knowing things will never be [good again](http://unsettlingstories.com).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hip hop artist who's good at Brazilian Jiu-jitsu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fill my ports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You motherfucker. That was gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roots of Change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roots of Change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **November 19th, 2016**

The lights in the sky were a diversion. We should have looked down.

**November 20th, 2016**

In a matter of days, the following terms will have meaning to everyone in the world:

That which grows through our heels.

That which tastes our skin.

That which fills our pores.

That which empties.

**November 21st, 2016**

Laura is dead. Gus is dead. Mohammad is dead. Nes is dead.

**November 22nd, 2016**

Where can one go when everywhere is a trap waiting to be sprung? I feel as if Im navigating an endless minefield, with every step having the potential to be my last. Everyone is staring at the sky with hope in their eyes. Everyone is going to die.

**November 23rd, 2016**

We shouldn't have gone looking for them.

**November 24th, 2016**

Roger is dead. He is standing right in front of me.

**November 25th, 2016**

That which grows through Rogers heels has reached his calves and thighs. His neck is still craned skyward and his beatific smile has yet to slip. His death mask is one of hope and astonishment. His body is being digested as he stands.

**November 26th, 2016**

The last of our group received a message from the other side of the base. Everyone is still to remain silent. I refuse. Even if Im dead by the time this is released, people can still say they had some warning. 

It may be too late.

**November 27th, 2016**

Dr. Franklin is dead. He was taken while in the shower. I was called to officially verify the cause of death, as if it were possible to have been anything other than what was already obvious. He was rooted to the ground and they continued to grow through the tile floor. As I watched, his achilles tendons snapped and rolled up into his calves. He did not fall. The growths seem to be moving faster now. Their tiny tongues flick over his skin.

**November 28th, 2016**

Laura, Gus, Mohammad, and Nes have started to undergo phase two. Their pores are stretching. The stalks are starting to push out. We can see the entities moving throughout their bodies. How such enormous pressure can be contained by skin is a mystery I hope to die before uncovering.

Mohammad has connected to Gus. Laura and Nes are growing away from the cluster. Seabirds are dying.

**November 29th, 2016**

Roger has connected to Dr. Franklin across a space of 250 yards. There appears to be no material strong enough to block the connections once theyve started. 

Both Roger and the doctor have gone into phase two faster than any of the others.

**November 30th, 2016**

The eruptions from the ground are reaching into the sky to capture birds. It began with a few in the vicinity of the Laura/Gus/Mohammad/Nes cluster, but it has spread island-wide. The highest burst point appears to be 1200 feet.

**December 1st, 2016**

One of our watercraft discovered a blue whale five feet below the surface. The animal had been rooted. Further investigation showed a 200 swath below the whale had also been rooted. Some of the affected had reached phase three.

**December 2nd, 2016**

All the dead on the island have entered phase three. The entities are emptying out of the pores and transforming the ground below. The birds which had been rooted mid flight are raining the substance onto the ground and water. The new biology is beginning to take hold. Its becoming harder to breathe.

**December 3rd, 2016**

The first report of rooting on the mainland came through overnight. There is nothing left to do but wait. If the lights give you any pleasure, just keep watching them. Just enjoy the moment for as long as you can. [Im sorry.](http://unsettlingstories.com)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still going! Was working on it today, in fact :)

The index is still there: http://unsettlingstories.com/index

Needs to be updated pretty badly, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SCREEN PASS TO L MILLS, SO FAST HE'S BLURABLE

ELUSIVE LIKE SHADY, BUT MUCH LESS DURABLE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he handsome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can neither confirm nor deny this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if the seal would get mad if you tried to put it in your mouth so you could feel it inflate on your tongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you want an email notification whenever I release a new story, just go to UnsettlingStories.com, enter your email, and click the "Subscribe" button on the right. I probably won't sell your email addresses to male enhancement companies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who saw that coming... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agonizing over him or AP :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 04:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike was the owner of the apartment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know :( 

Art is risky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monster-exclusionary radical furries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all-inclusive. No monster-exclusionary radical furry agenda will taint our fun. I hate MERFs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its hard to clean blood out of the crotch of a fur suit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its hard to clean blood out of the crotch of a fur suit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if the furs white. Sure, you might get the bulk of it off the individual fibers, but a stain will still be there. Its not easy to find someone who wants to blow a six-foot tall ferret with a blood stain on the business end.


Hi, Im Shane. Im 42 and Im a furry. And no, Im not one of those adorable ones who goes to conventions and acts like my favorite cartoon character and makes cute noises and then goes home. Im a degenerate. I like to be around other degenerates. Especially ones in fur suits. Take a moment to psychoanalyze me from your armchair. Ill wait.


Ready?


Ok.


My ilk dont have conventions. We get together, dont get me wrong, but conventions arent really our thing. Id say the closest thing we have is a gaping, semen-encrusted orgy of bodies sweating and panting inside hot suits trying to bring one another to orgasm. If that last sentence didnt give you an erection, then you probably wouldnt be interested. (If you are, send me a private message.)


Theres the background, now lets get to the root of the problem: the pizza-sized blood stain all over the cock slot of my suit.


Last Halloween, I got a text from my buddy about a meetup at the apartment of one of our regulars. I was excited - this guy was a freak. He was independently wealthy, always had the best drugs and booze, and since he owned the whole apartment building, we could be as loud and disgusting as we wanted. I am very loud. I am profoundly disgusting.


Anyway, I went and had an absolute blast. Nine guys and two women. Not that the sexes of the participants mattered, of course. Were all just furry plugs and outlets, my friends. Furry plugs and outlets.


After the initial debauchery, one of the guys didnt get up off the tarp. He was facedown with the rear flap of his fur suit open. That wasnt the odd part, since the flaps of all our suits were open, but unlike us, this guy wasnt moving. 


The owner of the apartment was extremely pissed off. The exposed skin peeking out from behind his Mike from Monsters Inc. costume was beet red. One of the main rules of his house was NO ONE was allowed to overdose. Aside from the complications of dealing with the police and ambulance, it made the whole party look bad. And he NOT want to look like a bad host.


We took turns trying to get the guy to his feet. He was breathing, which was a good sign, but he just wouldnt respond. Now, Ive been around ODs before. Shit happens. But something about this guy wasnt right. Id never seen him before. Turned out none of us had.


Id say the majority of us had a go at him at one point or another during the festivities, and Im fairly certain I remember his furry, green belly pushing against my forehead pretty early in the night. But now he was still facedown on the tarp preventing our collective liquids from soaking into the carpet. It was a really nice carpet.


As the host was looking for his phone to call an ambulance, the prostrate man started to get up. He looked around at us, blinked a few times, then smiled. We all breathed a sigh of relief, then asked the guy what had happened. He just apologized and told us he has narcoleptic episodes after intense physical exertion, and its nothing to worry about. Then he made us all laugh when he asked who was ready for another round of action.


All of us were, so we started up again. Then the power went out.


I was balls deep in our narcoleptic Oscar the Grouch when the room went dark. I didnt mind. Oscar certainly didnt, either. No one did. I heard the host yell, must be the ghost!, and we all laughed amidst moans and around mouthfuls of unimaginable depravity. Supposedly the hosts apartment was haunted by the original owner. But on we plowed, so to speak, making our way from partner to partner in the dark. 


A little while later, the room started to smell. Let me be more specific: the room started to smell worse. The regular background scent of 11 people fucking in rarely-washed suits and working up and good, frothy sweat in the process can be a bit off putting to those unaccustomed to our type of fun. But this smell was different. And it was powerful.


Being the troopers we were, we managed to go for another few minutes before one of us threw up. And that was the end of the orgy. People started to complain about the smell and the host went into the kitchen to grab a flashlight and a few candles while we mulled around and wiped off our various wipeables. 


A light flicked on and a candle was lit. We surveyed the area and a couple people left. Oscar the Grouch was on the tarp again, ass in the air. Something about the color of his skin, even in the dimness of the flashlight and candles, didnt look right.


Hey, Oscar, I called, and nudged him. He flopped over onto his side. I sighed as one of the women started to take off the head portion of his suit so he could get some air.


The portion came off and the most hideous smell Id ever encountered filled the air. The lights blinked back on and everyone shouted in despair and horror. We were all coated in blood and other incomprehensibly horrific fluids.


Fast forward a few hours.


We were all at the police station. Oscar was dead. Very, very dead. According to someone at the station, he looked like hed been dead for a long, long time. They were still trying to ID the body.


Fast forward to a week later.


All of us were charged with desecrating a corpse. In our state of collective disgust and confusion, none of us protested it. It looked like wed be facing some pretty serious fines and community service, but no jail. Thank God. 


They still hadnt IDd Oscar.


Yesterday, I was at home when my phone rang. It was my buddy whod invited me to the Halloween party. His friend, the wealthy party host, had been doing renovations on the apartment. Apparently the smell just wouldnt get out of the room wed occupied, so he was tearing down the whole thing. In the process, he came across a note, neatly carved into the wood on the underside of the floorboards.


If you ever find this, Im sorry for the trouble I may have caused. Ive been watching all the fun youve had over the years and wanted to try it for myself. I figured it wouldnt hurt to give corporeality one more shot. It was very, very worth it. Thanks!


I didnt really know how to respond to that. It didnt make much sense, but neither did the narcoleptic furry-turned-cadaver who showed up at the orgy. I asked my friend what we should do, and he replied pretty quickly, informing me wed be having another get-together to honor the dead mans memory this coming weekend. 


I cant fucking wait. Apparently therell be 25 people there.


But I just cannot get this damn stain out of my fur suit. I dont think it will make a good first-impression with the [new folks.](http://unsettlingstories.com)





















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds interesting! I love Crichton - I'll have to check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um how about you just drive your weird bus and not talk to me I'm only 13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends if they're done well. Some are, some aren't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this one out: [The Least Satisfying Explanation](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4413pt/the_least_satisfying_explanation/?st=iwp7f4ps sh=79938bcc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alzheimer's Ward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alzheimer's Ward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you work in an Alzheimers ward, its difficult to determine whether or not a patient is telling the truth. Obviously theres no malice intended if theyre lying; its likely they believe what theyre saying to be true. Its the unfortunate nature of the disease. 


A few nights ago, Madge Daniels started to complain about abdominal discomfort. We believed her. Thered been a nasty stomach virus going around for the last couple weeks. Madges overall lucidity was pretty good, too, so we did our best to make her comfortable and ensure she was getting a lot of fluids and adequate rest.


The next morning, Lou Franks, Ray Davis, Melinda Renz, and Veronica Auster-Coates were complaining about their own stomach pain. We gave them a once-over. They seemed fine. We figured theyd heard about Madges problem and believed they were experiencing it, too.


By noon, the whole ward was complaining about stomach problems. Some were obviously legitimate, since some of the residents had forgotten how to use the facilities and we had to change them, but with the others, we assumed it was phantom pain.


The following day, Madge Daniels was found dead in her bed. Her roommate, Elizabeth Fong, said Madge had been having terrible nightmares all night. The state of Madges bed seemed to verify that claim. The sheets and blankets were torn off and Madge was clutching the pillow in a death grip. An autopsy was scheduled for later in the week.


The reports of stomach pain began to dwindle. Only three residents were still complaining, and they were legitimately sick with that virus. Nightmares were the new thing. Everyone was having them.


If you were to walk into the Alzheimers ward at 3am last Friday, you wouldve thought youd entered a torture chamber. The agonized screams of the residents as they encountered whatever demons haunted their dreams were hideous and disconcerting. Some had torn out their fingernails as they clawed at the bedclothes while others had fallen while attempting to leave their beds. It was a terrible scene.


Two nights ago, Veronica Auster-Coates began to talk about stomach pain again. The nurse was about to shrug it off, but she could see distension in Veronicas abdomen, even under her nightclothes. An exam was ordered, and emergency surgery followed. A mass the size of a basketball was removed from Veronicas ovary. There had been no indication of this mass at her most recent physical examination two weeks ago.


The nightmares continued. Doctors and nurses began to grow concerned. The violence of the dreams was unlike anything theyd encountered in the past. While the disease can cause vivid nightmares, these were unusual both in their severity and frequency. 


Yesterday morning, Madge Daniels autopsy was conducted. Her life had been taken by a massive stroke. That was not the unusual discovery.


Madge, who had gone through her 74 years of life without even needing glasses, had developed severe, burn-like scars on her eyes the night of her death.


Yesterday afternoon, the dissection of Veronica Auster-Coates ovarian growth was completed. It was filed as a rapid growth of carcinogenic cells, but no explanation was given. No explanation existed.


Last night, the power at the hospital went out. The backup generators did not kick in. I was out having a cigarette with the janitor on the roof when it happened, and we both saw diffuse, orange lights darting back and forth above the clouds. The moment they disappeared, the power came back on.


This morning, the hospital is on lockdown and the Alzheimers ward is under quarantine. All the residents woke up with burns which had destroyed their eyes. All the residents have basketball-sized distension of their abdomens. Further, the growth which had been excised from Veronica Auster-Coates is missing from the laboratory. The final straw, which prompted the lockdown of the hospital, was the discovery of the corpse of the lab technician who had been [studying it.](http://unsettlingstories.com) 









 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha people always tell me I act old for my age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha are you Greek with big thumbs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha thank you! I was worried no one would get it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um when you say female like that it sounds, like, totes taxonomic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was able to do it in a way I didn't feel was exploitative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he keep his brain on the inside or outside? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You delightful motherfucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I did, then I realized I could write a story about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you sound like you work at a small family business lololol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say a great number of authors on NoSleep who've been writing long enough to have catalogs of stories will link to a site at the end of their posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um why would I do to a gross morgue? I am way too pretty to go into that part of town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right! Some people just have no concern for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, *EXCUSE ME*, but I respect him plenty as long as he likes me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom said I'll be a saint someday which I always thought was rude because it was like she thought I didn't already know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew that man is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no he'll be okay the baby in his head stopped moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right he's so handsome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want any more pictures of your thing like stop messaging me I'm 13 and I don't want you here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple?????? Like did you not read the part about my bedspread???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg isn't that a really really bad word in Spanish? I don't think monoxides would like being called that AT ALL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs why are you still here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh awesome. I was there so many years ago and I keep forgetting they're around. You just inspired me to try them again. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I'm not allowed to listen to that music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writing Madison is such a joy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there's exactly ZERO Geigers in my house. I don't need a fancy machine to count them when I'm smart enough to do it on my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um didn't the police tell you not to talk to me anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Omg guys why is it so hard to find a boyfriend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Omg guys why is it so hard to find a boyfriend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont want to sound racist but I think Kevin is gay lol. Like, my parents were gone haha it seems like they always are and I got Kevin to come over to help me with homework and he was SO not interested in my boobs. I mean, I didnt show them to him or anything yet but I pushed my shoulders together and made them all big and all he did was look at the homework and then his brain fell out.


I got mad because it was on my new bedspread and its now just like bedspread with brain and it doesnt match the lavender color AT ALL KEVIN.


But yeah he was all sitting there looking weird and bleeding from the eye his brain fell out of and now hes making weird sounds. So not sexy Kevin. Srs.


Like, I dont want to even [ask you guys for advice anymore](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4ho869/um_can_any_of_you_guys_tell_me_whats_wrong_with/?st=ivbamqdh sh=d65e3411) because youre so not helpful ([TOMMY IS FINE BY THE WAY](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5c2xzz/ok_now_my_brother_is_all_messed_up_and_gross_lol/?st=iwnnwacf sh=913f2fd7)) but okay yeah can someone tell me how to get a brain back into the boy I like?


Lol like sandwich. ^ ^


Before you get all Madison just pick it up and push it back in where it came out of Ill just say I already did that and I just made it worse. Brains are supposed to be one piece right? Yeah um well it plopped out in one piece but when I tried to push it back up his eye hole it, like, fell apart? Yeah.


Theres brain under my nails and I did them just so Kevin would think my fingers are sexy and I guess thats out of the realm of possibility lol. Unless hes into brainy fingers. People always tell me Im super smart.


So yeah. Kevins brain is all messed up. He doesnt seem happy because when I tried to unzip his pants to get a peek (Im not a perv I wanted to make sure he had enough air because hes breathing all weird) he grunted and pushed me. Omg if Dad saw him push me omg lol.


Im just gonna assume you wont have any good ideas about his brain. And you know what? I didnt expect any lol you guys are the worst. Jk jk jk youre not the worst like cancer is the worst. OH BTW


Kevins brain kinda came back together but it doesnt look like brain its more like a slug. Remember my cat? Yeah we got a new one. Mr. Flufferbottom was not fine after Tommy. Not fine at all. Anyway now we have a cat called Meowington and hes eating Kevin's brain slug thing. Kevin's walking around and bumping into stuff and stuff. His pants are still unzipped though. A girl can dream lolol no its okay he likes other guys I guess maybe Ill get a short haircut and he cant tell because he has no brain.


Ok, I guess Ill mention that one other thing.


You know my friend Danica I mentioned last time? Yeah, she was in my closet trying to record all the sex I was gonna have with Kevin before his brain got all clumsy. Anyway, I think it might have turned out Danica was pregs because she died or something and a baby ????????? like fell out of her.


You know how babies are supposed to be all cute and cuddly like stupid Tommy? Yeah, no. Danicas baby is like an octopus. But with people legs. With lots and lots of knees. And yeah its eating Danica. Which is so not baby food. Danica only ate junk food which is probably why she died Im gonna totally take her phone she has a 7 and I only have a 6s thanks Mom.


Im all trying to write this to you people and theres so much going on theyre interrupting the heck out of me. So Danica baby is done eating Danica and now it crawled in Kevins head and only one of the legs is sticking out his eye and Meowington finished eating the slug brain and is getting all hairbally and Kevin, bless his gay heart, is just sitting on the bed looking at me.


He looks so cute guys. I swear, if it wasnt for the weird baby leg flopping all over his face Id totally let him touch it. Jk Id still let him. Hang on.


No he didnt want to. Oh well. Guys Im so unlucky its really not fair. Im, like, really pretty. I know you pervs are gonna keep sending me pics of your things and I support your decision because you cant help yourselves but its not the same. I love Kevin. Kevin and his no brain and weird baby head. But its not meant to be.


You know what? Im gonna find Kevin a boyfriend. Then I bet hell love me back. [Bbl!!](http://unsettlingstories.com)







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which place in Norwalk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smol pupper bites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dot tumblr dot com. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw one eat a rocking chair once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long Fingers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long Fingers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saturday morning, there were long smudges on the glass of my front door. Three, thick, semi-parallel smudges from what looked like fingers. They trailed from the middle of the door down to its base, then disappeared. If they were from an animal, it wasnt any animal I knew about. If they were from a person, he was unfathomably deformed.


An hour later, I discovered nine dead deer behind my garage. Their eyes, sexual organs, and teeth were missing. I called animal control and was told there were mutilated animals being reported all over the county. They had no explanation, but I was assured the carcasses would be picked up before the weekend was over.


As I hung up, I heard something in the background on the phone line.


While I endeavored to shake the fear that had gripped me, I sat and tried to watch television. The picture was distorted. I flipped from channel to channel, only to encounter the same problem with the signal. For a moment, I thought I could make out something in the static interlacing the normal programming.


A shape.


Gooseflesh prickled my skin and my focus grew intense. I walked to the television and stared, trying to peer through the frames to whatever was on the other side. The distortion intensified and a form grew from the static. 


I realized the sound from the television had changed from the clipped, broken broadcast audio to waves of white noise. I heard nothing else. No birds, no insects, no hum of household electronics. Just the white noise and the pounding of my heartbeat in my ears. 


I was fixated on the shape. I couldnt determine what it was, but there was no doubt it was organic. It moved and undulated, getting closer to the screen before backing off. I was so close to the television I could see the pores in my skin reflected off the glossy surface. It distracted me momentarily. That was all it took; I saw something else reflected. Something behind me.


I whirled around and saw four of the dead deer propped up on the floor. They were arranged and stacked in an X shape; hooves to hooves. How they were able to hold that position was beyond me. The abyssal cavities of their empty eye sockets stared at nothing.


There was a sound in the kitchen and I jumped. As if startled as well, the deer toppled over in a sickening tangle of limbs. 


More noise from the adjacent room. Wet slapping. The breath caught in my throat and every old scar on my body, even the invisible ones, began to hurt. Pain radiated in waves, but never strongly enough to overtake the overwhelming terror and dread I felt.


Three long, fleshy objects poked around the corner. I knew immediately they were fingers. They waved in a sickening, serpentine pattern. Clusters of tiny, fungus-like eyestalks twitched at the end of each one. I wanted to run. I still dont know why I didnt.


The rest of its body came around the corner. It was a wide, quadrupedal creature. Its one arm remained outstretched with the long fingers extended, as if seeing and tasting the air. A cavernous hole opened at the center of its bulk. The ray of sunlight in which it stood clearly showed me countless moving parts within the hole, making me think of some sickening biological clockwork.


The fingers moved toward my face and I could smell their musty, rotten-mushroom aroma. I stared into the maw of the thing as the parts inside moved against each other, producing a terrifyingly-calming white noise. I opened my mouth to speak, but the three fingers slipped between my lips and pushed down my throat. I gagged and tried to escape, but I was being held in place. I could feel the eye-like protuberances growing down my esophagus. The creature walked toward me, the hole in its body opening wider.


From this new, closer view, I could see the inside was filled with what could only be described as pieces resembling the legs of crickets and grasshoppers, all moving together to produce the wash of white noise that had filled the room. But as I gagged and struggled to free myself, the sound changed. The movements in the hole shifted.


At first, it sounded like the white noise was growing harsher. But as the seconds passed, the timbre shifted toward something resembling speech. After another moment, that was exactly what it was.


Eight more of your days. Weve tasted your animals, and now we know them. Ive tasted your body, and now I know you.


I gasped as I felt tendrils squirming deeper inside me. A light outside began to glow dull red. I heard my next-door neighbor shriek from out in her yard.


You can be us soon. Can you taste me?


Pores in its fingers erupted and filled my mouth and esophagus and belly with thick, gray liquid. My eyes widened. The flavor was indescribable. The red light outside intensified.


Eight more days.


The fingers were pulled from my throat and I fell onto the hardwood floor. The light grew blinding, then it was gone. The creature was gone. Flies buzzed around the deer carcasses.


Fluid dripped down my chin and chest as I knelt and tried to right myself. The words, eight days remained in my head. 


My hands and fingers were numb. I glanced down and was positive the digits were longer than they had been. And now, almost two days later, its indisputable. This hospital is full of patients with unexplained deformities to their hands, as well as inexplicable growths in their mouths. Amidst the confusion and barely-managed hysteria, the sound of white noise is mixing in with the raised voices. 


Tiny sprouts are starting to lift the fingernails from their nail beds on my right hand. Even when my eyes are closed, Im beginning to see things from the perspective of that hand. See and taste. Six more days, if the creature was telling the truth. Six days. As the sound of white noise begins to overtake the normal speech, I find myself growing less concerned with every passing moment. Less concerned, and more [excited](http://unsettlingstories.com).



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/cmd102: How do you find the time and, more importantly, the patience to deal with not only all the stories, but all the authors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm a bit worried here. Good thing gameflow is to his advantage right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 03:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll get you again.](http://i.imgur.com/Uz5eHXm.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be super useful to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice! Making me hungry just looking at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://unsettlingstories.com/2016/12/07/that-good-dick/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask a favor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither! It was such a nice surprise. Tom's the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like them both. Same with writing them. If it's done well, I couldn't care less if it's "real" or supernatural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but we're strongly into monogamy for religious reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom does his magic before he brings them home. I never really asked. He's the smart one. I'm the pretty one. (Though I'm no slouch at calculus!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I got me a big, strong man to protect me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, anyone who's had the real thing knows there's no substitute ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh heavens, no. Sometimes the dick is, well, a little chilly. That's all! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? Tom's at work at the city morgue and I'm home doing my nails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so crass. We made love. We shared mutual pleasure. The way you say it, it sounds like a bad thing. Don't try to taint our beautiful moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than okay! Super happy I can share this little vignette about my husband and me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just call it lovemaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww don't worry sweetie, I'm sure you will be someday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a kind man. I'm a very lucky person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we love each other. () </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's so wonderful. Even when I'm feeling cold inside, he always warms me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Good Dick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Good Dick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Bizarre is memorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, frequency seems to be working for me. It's definitely not that easy, but it's not as difficult as grinding to a halt and trying to resume.

You should start posting again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I hope to do that someday, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reported for using two sentences in a title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/r3YggpY.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're in Boston now? No more AZ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus H. Christ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a great idea. I'll see what I can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so fuckin' cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad's ancestry basically fucked their way all the way across Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::eats self:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::gets a clear spot on the front of my pants that looks like the greasy side of a McDonald's bag:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::dons bridesmaid dress:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not. The bot seems to have made a mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brute force.

"If you don't write today everyone will forget you and you'll die alone."

That kind of thing. It works pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trees of Eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trees of Eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I bought these few pages at a local traders tent for the equivalent of $.25 USD. It was the only thing there written in English. I dont know what any of it means, but the fact it names the missing explorers and ruined village is troubling.*


**June 29th, 2016**


Let this be a journal of our last moments. I know we wont make it out.


**June 30th, 2016**


They took Jane last night. This morning, the trees have her eyes. All the trees; every knot hole, every space, every interstice, is stuffed with her eyes. Two eyes copied into thousands. I dont know how. Nothing makes sense. But theyre staring at us. Were being watched. They follow every one of our movements, as if they didnt already know what was going to happen. 


**July 1st, 2016**


The plants are choking us. Each step is harder and were stopping every 15 minutes to rest. Arts leg injury is worse. I wont even attempt to remove the fused plastic and metal of the phone from his hip and thigh. We can smell the wound putrefying. Theres no disputing hell die if we dont get him medical attention soon.


Thats a laughable fantasy at this point, though. Were countless miles away from anyone. No villages, no doctors, no anyone. Just unforgiving jungle. I can hear Art weeping as we walk.


**July 2nd, 2016**


I saw one of them in the river. It didnt notice us. It was gulping down thousands upon thousands of gallons of water. Where it kept it inside its skinny body was beyond me. All of this is beyond me.


Im covered in bites from mosquitos and spiders. I have a pressure wound beginning to form on my shoulder from propping up Art as we walk. Animals are starting to get his scent, and Ive shooed away carrion birds who land while he tries to sleep. I was lucky enough to kill one this morning. We can eat.


**July 3rd, 2016**


We cant go anywhere today. Art is immobile. I see something wriggling under the skin of his wound. I think it may be a botfly larva, but Im not sure. Its something. The remains of the phone are beginning to fall off as infected skin sloughs away. Its clear the burns are down to his hip and femur. He mutters as he sits there. I dont know if he can see me.


**July 4th, 2016**


I woke up to the sight of one of them near Art. I didnt move. I couldnt even if Id wanted to. As I watched, it traced its flaccid fingertips over Arts legs. They fell onto the leaves. I gasped, and it turned around to face me. We stared at each other for a little while, then it turned back to my friend. It picked the legs up and held them under its arm, near the leg stalks, and walked away.


Art was crying. There was no blood coming from the wounds. I could see the muscle and tendons and cross section of his femur, along with the pink marrow inside. The part with the melted phone was yellow and green with a reservoir of fluid beneath. Nothing dripped out. The wounds had been invisibly cauterized.


He is still dying.


**July 5th, 2016**


They took Art last night. His brown eyes have joined Janes blue ones in the trees. All the trees, now. They all watch.


**July 6th, 2016** 


There were six of them in the widest part of the river I passed, gorging themselves with water. The area of the river behind them had slowed to a trickle. Im not worried about them seeing me anymore. They know Im here. 


I saw the first village since the three of us departed. Its amazing to think just a week ago we were three. The village was transformed. Stone huts were covered in living, moving tissue. Muscle, from the look of it. Muscle and veins. The sound of something being inflated was filling the air as I went by. I didnt spend the time to look. From the remainder of the map I have, it looks like Im still a couple days from the nearest trading post.


**July 7th, 2016**


All eyes, no trees. Trunks of eyes, branches of eyes, leaves of eyes. Nothing but eyes. [Dry rivers.](http://unsettlingstories.com)







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shove that jizz back up there. Sorry dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not allowed. Score isn't negative most games, actually. It is if you have awful luck, like me, but the average is between 5 and 15.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write as frequently as you can. Learn from your mistakes, take the criticism you feel is valuable and shrug off the meanness and refine your style. Don't be afraid to use the same topic in different contexts. Sure, some people might notice and be annoyed, but you're doing this for you. This is your proving ground. Wring all you can from a topic, then move on to something else that interests you. 

I liked to write about bugs. I wrote a lot about them. Now I'm sick of bugs.

I liked to write a lot of body horror. Now I'm sick of body horror.

Now I'm into aliens and stuff. I still have quite a bit to do with that subject, so I'm gonna keep at it until I've gotten it all out of my system. It's fun.

IT SHOULD BE FUN.

Do what you want, do what you like. People will like it :)

DON'T BE AFRAID TO BE WEIRD AS FUCK. Seriously. Weirdness, when done well, is really fun. People love creative, out-there stuff. Embrace it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, though I beat him last time we matched up Week 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's our D/ST scoring rules. It's brutal: http://i.imgur.com/Gk6NynX.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks - it helped, but I'm still hurting: http://i.imgur.com/aXxd06i.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm soooooo fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (You can probably be a lot better.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the worst place for someone to try and eat your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robinson's gonna feast on a season-high 22 yards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death Looking into the Window of One Dying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death Looking into the Window of One Dying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As Andrew got sicker, hed point to perceived smudges on our bedroom window. Nothing discernible to him. Not at first. But the decline in my partners health brought with it a growing realization. Its a face, he told me. Its someones face.


I saw nothing.


I sat with Andrew through it all. Every sleepless night. Every shriek of terror as nightmares tore through him. Every sobbing declaration that he wasnt ready. In the mornings, the smudged face would be there, ever clearer to him. He was terrified of it. Still, I saw nothing.


Time went by while Andrew wasted away. Id started staring more at the blackness beyond the window than at my dying partner. A portion of me found comfort in avoiding Andrews gaze. His was a gaze of sorrow. Of regret. He knew Id be facing the same fate in the coming years. I begged him not to concern himself with such a thing, but deep down, in the vault of my soul, I resented him. His carelessness. 


My own.


Id grip his hand in my own throughout our last week together. He didnt have the strength to talk. He could only wheeze and stare. Stare at me. Stare at the window. Stare at everything.


Soon nothing.


On his last night, he did nothing but stare at the blackness beyond the window. The void. His void. But then he lifted his arm and pointed. He coughed and whispered, I see him. I see death. They were the first words hed uttered in days. He continued.


Michael, do you see him?


I squeezed his hand and told him I loved him.


The face, Michael. Please, go look at the face. He saw I was doing nothing, then raised his voice, bringing on a series of horrible, unproductive coughs. Look!


I obliged. I walked to the window and peered out. There was nothing but black, cold emptiness below a ceiling of unforgiving stars.


Look!, he wheezed again.


I pressed my face to the cold glass and saw nothing. Nothing but darkness.


I turned around and Andrew began to sob.


Look, he whimpered. Tears drooled from his bloodshot eyes. Look.


I looked. I saw smudges.


Michael, please help. Hes here.


I pitied him with such ferocity that I began to bawl. Everything, our passion, our experiences, our closeness, was nearing the end. And it was beyond our control. My promise to be with him through it all was being broken by the force taking him from this world. I couldnt bear it.


This had to happen on our terms.


Im not ready, Michael, he whispered. I held a pillow over his face. He struggled and moaned, no no no no no, through the pillow and used his last energy to thrash. Then he stopped. Everything stopped.


I collapsed on the bed, cradled my love to my chest, and cried for what felt like hours. The sun was coming up when I rose from his deathbed and looked toward the window.


I saw the greasy print of my face smudged against the glass, with my lips curled into a hideous, skeletal grin. Deaths grin. 


[I wept.](http://unsettlingstories.com)













 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the light go on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit that's better than my own writing. 

Kill it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am over Landry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So smol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found the Bees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found the Bees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I followed the sound of buzzing. The deeper into the woods I went, the louder the sound became. It was dark this far in; there were remnants of structures from industrial-era factories long neglected and choking with trees, vines, and countless other plants. Judging from the level of growth, no one had been here in a very, very long time.


The buzzing persisted. It became hard to walk through the underbrush. I spotted, or rather felt, a swarm of insects. They flew by my ear, paying me no attention, save for one. He flew into the back of my neck and instinctively stung me. I pulled his writhing body off my neck and studied him. It was a bumblebee, fat and covered with pollen. More streaked by. They were going in the direction of the sound.


I walked on, feeling a strange sensation of diminished weight as I progressed. The steps became easier. I could leap through the brush with increasing ease - so long as it was in the direction of the buzzing. My attempts to walk backward were met with more resistance than I would have considered normal. I realized the plants were pointing toward the source of the the buzzing, as if theyd grown that way.


When I reached a clearing, there was an old, dilapidated warehouse at the center. Despite the trees no longer blocking the sun, the light was dim. I stared up into the buzzing sky and realized clouds of bees were pouring toward the warehouse. Countless thousands. Countless millions. All flying toward the hole in metal roof. 


Snowflakes of clumped pollen, likely shed from the bees bodies, blew across the clearing and accumulated around the edges of the warehouse. There was a distinct pull on me now; an undeniable force tugging me toward the structure. I didnt fight it.


I reached the warehouse and looked around for an entrance. There were a few, but they were still locked from the inside. Near the back, I found a hole. It was small, but large enough for me to fit through. I was covered in pollen from head to toe; the cloying particulate matter forcing sneeze after sneeze out of me. Tears ran down my cheeks.


The buzzing was bordering on overwhelming. Id entered into a closet or maintenance area, so I still couldnt see what was happening. I opened the door and the force pulled the knob from my hand and the door slammed backward into the wall. But I didnt notice the slam. Nor would I have cared if I did.


At the center of the warehouse, there was a tiny, black dot. I felt disoriented looking at it and had to hold on to the door frame to keep my footing. The light around it shimmered. And bees poured into it. It was a ceaseless torrent of bees, all disappearing inside. 


It made no sense. None of it. I would have stayed longer, but I noticed something happening in the area around the dot. More light shimmered. Part of me thought it was a black hole, but I quickly dismissed such a ridiculous idea. But I couldnt figure it out. 


Until I did.


The light shimmered again, and a colossal, veiny eye opened above the dot. Then another one. A face came into view, showing the dots nature: a mouth. The eyes glared at me as it inhaled more and more bees and pollen. I turned and ran, fighting against the terrible suction until I was out of the clearing and far away. 


The bees never stopped flying toward the [warehouse](http://unsettlingstories.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 15:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like....mushrooms...but also jizz. We're living in a beautiful world, folks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smol round pupper belly is smol and round! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 02:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure! Feel free to visit /r/subject3642 for more quality smut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's so smol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you've read much of my work in the last year if you think that's all I write, but no worries. Can't please everyone! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how this person has a ton of friends who all grab a slice, whereas if I were to make it, I'd just roll the pizza up and fuck my mouth with it. Alone; crickets chirping outside. Mocking me.

Edit:

*Hot grease on my face;*

*salty tears soften the crust -*

*shoot cheese down my throat.*


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) Yeah, I've been on a roll lately. Trying to put out 15-20 per month just to keep in practice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the mention. Glad you enjoy the more recent stuff :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love playing with the commenters :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I have, no...but I better go check to make sure lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atta boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bits and Pieces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bits and Pieces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingernails were the first to go.


No pain accompanied the loss; the victims went to sleep one night and simply woke up without fingernails. The events occurred in Donglu village, located in China's Shandong Province. There are limited medical resources, so few sought treatment. The affected went about their lives. 


Teeth came next.


In Pinellas County, Florida, between November 3rd and 16th, 19 people checked themselves into local hospitals and reported they had woken up with jaw pain, bleeding gums, and missing teeth. They were all wisdom teeth. No one could explain what had happened.


On November 20th, 82 people in Lahore, Pakistan woke up without arms and legs. 


On November 22nd, four people in Ottawa, Canada, were found dead in their beds. Their hearts, lungs, and rib cages were missing. There was no sign of struggle at any of the scenes. Two of the victims were found by their spouses in the mornings. They claimed to have noticed nothing overnight.


On November 23rd, close to 15,000 people in South and Central America died. Autopsies revealed the entire digestive tracts had been removed. There were no cuts, incisions, or injuries that could explain the excisions. 


I work aboard a meteorological vessel for the United States Navy. Weve watched these reports trickle in over the last few weeks. Ordinarily, we wouldnt be privy to the details of the situations I described. Quite the contrary; authorities have gone through great pains to shield the public from the ongoing events. 


Theres a thread which unifies each event, however.


Our weather satellites have noticed an inordinate number of red sprites in the upper atmosphere. On the nights of the mutilations, above each affected region, the red sprite activity has been greater than anything wed seen in the past. Usually only associated with severe thunderstorms, these sprites are showing up over even the most modest cloud cover. 


On November 28th, a fishing village in Sardinia, Italy, notified authorities about a red tint in the seawater. Fearing an algae bloom, tests were run. Not algae. Blood. Countless millions of gallons from innumerable species of animals.


Later that night, red sprites danced above Sardinia lower than theyd ever been observed. We saw them in the distance. Our ship is in the Mediterranean. 


Yesterday, November 29th, three of our onboard scientists - the three working most directly with the sprite/mutilation connection - died at their posts. One second they were working, the next they were face down on their desks, bleeding. Immediate autopsies were ordered. All the brain matter inside their heads was gone.


Late last night, I was on deck smoking a cigarette. Sprites danced and darted overhead as a storm gathered. Its intensity grew faster than our models had anticipated. Lightning and thunder crashed, but no rain fell. 


Lightning illuminated the sea around us and a sailor noticed something in the distance. He called to the captain, who ordered the ship lights be trained on the object. They were. A hulking shape, perhaps a quarter mile away, floated in the choppy sea. Behind the sounds of roaring wind and thunder, we heard it bellowing. The sound was low and chilling. Inexplicable. Alien.


The water below us reddened and tubes of viscera floated to the surface. They flapped and writhed against the against the hull of the ship. Lungs and stomachs and bladders and hearts at the end of each intestinal tube throbbed and pulsated. More bellowing. More moaning. 


A flash from a red sprite and a clap of thunder made everyone jump. The floating object was gone. The storm was dissipating. The bloody water was diluting back to its normal shade.


I havent been able to sleep since then. All I can do is fill out my reports, write this account, and watch as tens of thousands of dead fish float to the surface. We havent been allowed to notify the families of our dead colleagues. Not while all this is still going on, we were told. And just a moment ago, we were alerted to sprite activity over [New York City](http://unsettlingstories.com).



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a complex man. 

Or a man with a complex. Not sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assembled raw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Prosciutto-wrapped chicken stuffed with red peppers, sage, and mozzarella. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np, I just tried out a new design, let me know if you think it's any better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still at [UnsettlingStories.com/index](http://unsettlingstories.com/index). I'm still working on the layout. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a GORGEOUS website. I'm jealous as fuck. Great work :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eavesdropping through an IP camera. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eavesdropping through an IP camera. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple years back, there was a software flaw in a few webcam brands. Whenever they were active, they could be accessed by scanning the Internet for a particular open port. Once the port was found, anyone could tune in without the user knowing they were being watched. And millions of people used these webcams.


The companies quickly released software hotfixes, but no one, aside from a few tech-savvy folks, updated their webcam software. So even today, they broadcast everything they do in front of their computer to anyone whos voyeuristic enough to watch. People like me.


Im not proud of my fascination, but I wont pretend it isnt there - and I wont lie and claim I didnt indulge it for a while. I watched thousands of people all over the world doing everything: laughing, sobbing, clipping toenails, masturbating, puking, doing homework, exercising, etc. It was all a thrill. None of them had any idea.


A few nights ago, I was snooping in on what looked like a greenhouse. The IP address was somewhere in North Carolina, but thats never completely accurate. Either way, it looked like the camera was being used for security, as it overlooked the whole area.


There were two people working; on what, I couldnt tell. But it became clear that one of them was in a bit of distress. Something on the table where they were working had latched onto his glove and they were both trying to brush it off.


The camera didnt have a zoom feature, but I was able to use my browser to enhance the size. It didnt do much; it just blurred and got even grainier. Still, I could make out what looked like a plant growing up the guys hand. Whatever I was seeing, it was infinitely more interesting than anything on any of the other cameras that night.


The two guys succeeded in getting the glove off. The wearer seemed fine, but he was pacing back and forth, as if he were excited or scared or anxious. Made sense to me; if a plant had latched onto my hand while I was working, Id be a combination of all those things.


One of them used a pair of tongs to pick up the glove and placed it into what looked like a fish bowl or terrarium. Then he did something I didnt expect: he turned around, reached into a cage I hadnt noticed, and pulled out a large, white rat. He dropped it into the tank with the glove.


Even though the resolution was terrible, I could see whatever was on the glove grab the rat. The animal jumped and rolled around before going still. The plantlife crept over its body. It didnt move.


The two guys were typing something on their respective computers. I couldnt see any of it. It looked like they were taking notes.


All that went on for about five minutes. I assumed the rat was dead. Then something happened. At first, I thought it was just a line of distorted video. But the harder I looked, I saw it wasnt. Something was growing out of the top of the rats head. And the rat was moving again.


One of the men picked up the cage and put it on a table much closer to the camera. Right then, I could see exactly what was happening. 


More of the plant grew from the rats head until it was sticking up about a foot and a half. Its eyes bulged, and the plant emerged from the sockets. The rat started to walk. It would back up, walk in a straight line, bump into the side of the tank, then try again; over and over and over as more of the plant emerged from its skull. Then it shook itself. A cloud of something spread throughout the tank before settling.


One of the guys appeared in the frame again. This time, he was wearing a full-body protective suit. He picked up the rat and placed it on the floor, then opened the door to the greenhouse. The animal hesitated for a second, then ran outside.


Nothing else of note really happened after that. I dont know what it was that I saw, but Ive been checking on the camera every so often over the last couple days. The same things would happen; a rat would get put in a tank with a portion of plant life, and the plant would grow from it. Once it shook that particulate matter from itself, it would be let outside.


This morning, when I checked the camera, the two guys were there again. One of them, the one who had his glove covered, didnt look particularly healthy. His skin was covered with blotches. The oversaturated color from the camera made them look bright red, almost like the skin was missing. Still, he did the same as hed done each time: plant sample - rat - rat shakes - release.


There was more light this morning, so I even got a chance to make out what was coming out of the rats head. Its weird to think about, but Im almost certain. Skinny, white mushrooms. 


I fucking hate [mushrooms](http://unsettlingstories.com).







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little bear pupper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shameless plug here, but I run [UnsettlingStories.com](http://unsettlingstories.com), a site for creepy, horrific, gross, and sometimes funny stories. There are over 200 up so far, and I've written them all. Check 'em out if you'd like. I hope you love them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fastest-loading website I've ever clicked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just CHALK it up to me just having fun by myself! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally pool, dude! :D

*Edit: :D* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOK AT THE PERFECT FLOOF OF A PUPPER

(And GB, I didn't even recognize you with your clothes on.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 22:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. Dong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally frozen on mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 02:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Reed had a good season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm not the person you were talking to, but I'll admit the most recent one wasn't exactly an example of great literature. When your goal is to get something written every day and you post it because, hell, people like that stuff for whatever reason, you're willing to share things you wouldn't submit to a publisher or put in a portfolio.

But anyway, if you want one I think is pretty good, check this out: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4zde6y/the_tomb_of_the_builders/?st=ivvie7l9 sh=bd20f739

If you don't enjoy it, no biggie :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/PnOBKTP.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::sluuuurp:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolling my fisted ass out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
