<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4988</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 09:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating stuff. It reminds me of a double pendulum, being a chaotic system and all. Actually, now that I think about it, the top and bottom faces are each parametrized by one variable--the twist angle (which determines how far they are from the center). But... I guess this cubic structure has more symmetry and a more complex set of interactions than the double pendulum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 09:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 07:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap some of these [comments](http://i.imgur.com/hcnqZRV.png) legitimately made me shudder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 07:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Astro)physically, this picture is very interesting! Usually, globular clusters have populations of old, red stars. Blue stars are generally more massive and short lived, and a globular cluster like M5, which is 10 billion years old, should not have many blue stars. However, the oldest stars in this group have evolved to the [horizontal branch](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Horizontal_branch) and are quite blue indeed!

Although it's not uncommon for blue horizontal branch stars to be found in globular clusters, I didn't know this ten minutes ago (even though I'm an astrophysicist) so I wanted to share! I had thought all stars in globular clusters to be fairly red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 07:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about the curly "L" for the Lagrangian density? That's my favorite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 07:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can try--however, I'm an astrophysicist, and not an instrumentalist, so I don't know exactly how the detectors work!

Our eyes are basically detectors. Very, very complex detectors. When we see stuff, we're just detecting intensities of light at different wavelengths. By comparing those intensities at different wavelengths, our brains can construct colors from them. So, if my eyes detect a lot of light at the blue wavelength, and detect less light at the red wavelength, I'll see blue. If my eyes detect a lot of light at the red wavelength but not at the blue wavelength, then I'll see the color red. If I see a lot of light at all wavelengths, I see white!

Okay, onto the ultraviolet (UV). Our eyes can only detect the [visible](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Visible_spectrum) part of the electromagnetic spectrum of light, but redder than red lies the infrared (IR), and more violet than violet is the UV. The Hubble Space Telescope has detectors that can measure the intensity of light in the UV, beyond what we see. In fact, it's just comparing the intensities of light at different UV wavelengths ([six different ones, in fact](http://hubblesite.org/newscenter/archive/releases/2003/23/fastfacts/)), to create a false-color image! Since what I've called "color" is effectively a difference in intensities of light at different wavelengths, the same can be done with UV light intensities, and that's what you're seeing here.

Since people seem to want to see the highest-resolution version of the image, [here it is](http://www.spacetelescope.org/static/archives/images/screen/opo0323b.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 00:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantum mechanics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 07:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! Dark matter is "dark" because it doesn't interact electromagnetically; in essence, dark matter has nothing to do with photons. Therefore it doesn't emit or absorb light! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 21:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the article is only saying that the cosmological constant accurately describes the effects of dark energy. For example, in equation 3.39 [here](http://ned.ipac.caltech.edu/level5/Peacock/Peacock3_2.html), we can see that as we approach z=0, the other density parameters have less and less of an effect (because they're inversely coupled to the scale factor). Therefore, dark energy dominates more and more, even though it is described as a constant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 20:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in Ellicott City! Man I miss that place. I moved right after we won Superbowl XXXV, and I've lived in Lousiana, New Jersey, and Pittsburgh (ugh), and I've never stopped missed good ole' Maryland. Congratulations on the pick up, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 19:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Shankar was the book I used for Quantum Mechanics this past semester. It's on the same level as Townsend and maybe a notch below Sakurai. Easiest A ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used Griffiths for the intro class? I only remember using Scherrer (and I thought it was okay). Frankly, I think [Shankar](http://www.amazon.com/Principles-Quantum-Mechanics-2nd-Edition/dp/0306447908) is an excellent intro textbook simply because it is so verbose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 21:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would personally say Hurricane Epsilon had the weirdest track. It consistently ignored forecast tracks and defied cold waters/wind shear and became a hurricane for five days (December 3-8th)!

Here's a picture of the actual [storm track](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Epsilon_2005_track.png), though it would look a lot more interesting if you could see the forecast cones superimposed on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 17:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I lost the black pencil. I only had the coloured ones." - Written in black pencil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 04:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went into graduate school, but I've heard that undergraduate astrophysics majors can venture into software engineering, if they've learned at least some formal CS and have proved themselves versatile with programming for research, schoolwork, etc. My friend's girlfriend who studied undergraduate astrophysics also recently got a job doing freelance web design, so that path could be viable. 

If she's more interested in hands-on stuff like instrumentation, perhaps she could try applying for engineering or technician jobs. However, there don't seem to be many observatories in Washington. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
