<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is now 'more than circumstantial evidence' Donald Trump's campaign colluded with Russia to disrupt election: There is evidence 'very much worth of investigation' says Adam Schiff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's largest school board is cancelling new school trips to the U.S. until further notice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe poised for total ban on bee-harming pesticides: Draft regulations seen by the Guardian reveal the European commission wants to prohibit the insecticides that cause acute risks to bees' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe poised for total ban on bee-harming pesticides: Draft regulations seen by the Guardian reveal the European commission wants to prohibit the insecticides that cause acute risks to bees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Emails From Former Exxon CEO Rex Tillersons Alias Account Have Disappeared: Tillerson, now secretary of state, used the email pseudonym Wayne Tracker to communicate with Exxon Mobil board members. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Formerly abused dog saves life of abused toddler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rex Tillerson: US forces will stay in Iraq after defeat of Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutors think they can extract data from phones seized during Inauguration Day protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University Puts 20,000 Lectures Behind A Registration Wall In Response To DOJ Pressure On Website Accessibility Compliance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany Schools President Donald Trump On What Security Really Means: Driving defense spending to insane heights is not the answer, German Foreign Minister Sigmar Gabriel said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  North Korea has conducted missile tests with increasing frequency and experts say this is likely to lead to advances in its missile technology.

One of these days they are going to get it right more by fluke rather than by design... scary thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany blocks arms sales to Turkey - report: The German government has refused approval for military exports to NATO partner country Turkey on a growing number of occasions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top NSA official says telephone surveillance should have been disclosed: 'U.S. government should have publicized the existence of a program that vacuumed up in bulk Americans' telephone call data before its existence was leaked by Edward Snowden, the NSA's deputy director said.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top NSA official says telephone surveillance should have been disclosed: 'U.S. government should have publicized the existence of a program that vacuumed up in bulk Americans' telephone call data before its existence was leaked by Edward Snowden, the NSA's deputy director said.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top NSA official says telephone surveillance should have been disclosed: 'U.S. government should have publicized the existence of a program that vacuumed up in bulk Americans' telephone call data before its existence was leaked by Edward Snowden, the NSA's deputy director said.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top NSA official says telephone surveillance should have been disclosed: 'U.S. government should have publicized the existence of a program that vacuumed up in bulk Americans' telephone call data before its existence was leaked by Edward Snowden, the NSA's deputy director said.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Creepy Things Your ISP Could Do if Congress Repeals the FCCs Privacy Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subway advertises for Apprentice Sandwich Artists to be paid just 3.50 per hour: Union slams fast food chain for 'exploiting' young workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Kids Demand Feds Turn Over 'Wayne Tracker' (aka Rex Tillerson) Emails: "When looking for evidence of a cover-up, emails from Rex Tillerson's pseudonym about climate change are just the kind of evidence the court needs to see." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigel Farage investigated by Ofcom for saying Sweden is rape capital of Europe: Ex-Ukip leader used his slot on LBC last month to suggest the Swedish city of Malmo saw the highest number of rapes carried out across the continent, and blamed it on EU migrant policies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI and NSA Chiefs Forced to Fact-Check Boss as Trump Live-Tweets Hearing: 'Either the White House is spreading falsehoods about this hearing on its Twitter account or the FBI director just perjured himself on TV,' remarks one journalist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is doing Russia's bidding by repeatedly pushing GCHQ wiretap claims, says former UK ambassador to US: 'Does he believe this stuff, or does he just trot it out because hes seen it on Fox News?' Sir Peter asked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia's billionaire king is on a lavish Asian adventure: ...and has arrived in every country on his itinerary  most recently China  on a golden escalator from his personal plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Intel Democrat: 'Circumstantial evidence of collusion' between Trump and Russia | "There is circumstantial evidence of collusion. There is direct evidence, I think, of deception and that's where we begin the investigation." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two big Brazilian meatpacking companies bribed inspectors to keep rotten meat on the market, police said as they issued dozens of arrest warrants, while a judge accused the Agriculture Ministry of betraying the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan becomes first country in the world to elect a transgender man to a public office: Tomoya Hosoda has taken part in various campaigns to raise the profile of LGBTQ in his country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 11:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Decriminalise personal drug use to free up prison space', say Lib Dems: Party believes criminalisation of low level users is behind jail overcrowding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 11:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Complain After Trump Spokesman Cites Wiretapping Report: British officials complained to the White House after Sean Spicer cited a Fox News commentators report claiming Obama had enlisted U.K. intelligence to spy on Trump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Call Out Pruitt's False View of Climate Change: "Just as there is no escaping gravity when one steps off a cliff, there is no escaping the warming that follows when we add extra carbon dioxide and other greenhouse gases to the atmosphere," the scientists wrote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Call Out Pruitt's False View of Climate Change: "Just as there is no escaping gravity when one steps off a cliff, there is no escaping the warming that follows when we add extra carbon dioxide and other greenhouse gases to the atmosphere," the scientists wrote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US reporters praise German journalists for questioning Trump: In her report, Dunz later wrote, "It is no longer a custom in the White House that hard, uncomfortable questions receive factual answers." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rex Tillerson, the US secretary of state has said he is uncertain of how America and China will continue to co-exist "for the next half century". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Climate Alarm Bells Ring, Trump Poised to Decimate Regulations: Trump is poised to unleash a sweeping anti-climate executive order to repeal major regulations enacted by the Obama administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rex Tillerson: Secretary of State used fake name Wayne Tracker to discuss climate change while Exxon Mobil CEO: Court filing comes in legal dispute in which Exxon seeks to derail probes into whether the company misled investors for years about the possible impact of global warming on its business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of Smart Meters May Over-Inflate Readings by up to 600% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese officials call for peoples war against Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MPs have voted to decriminalise abortion in England and Wales - 172 votes in favour, versus 142 against </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's largest sovereign wealth fund to blacklist firms that pollute too much: The fund may also exclude several companies in the defence, telecoms and arms industries this year over the risk of corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many foreign tourists say they're afraid to visit the US after Trump travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece calls for return of 'Elgin Marbles' to help fight rise of fascism in Europe: About half the sculptures from the 2,500-year-old Parthenon temple  stunning works of art created by the worlds first democracy after fighting off a Persian invasion  are in the British Museum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Community group: AT T 'digitally redlines' poor neighborhoods: The less wealthy the area, the slower the internet speeds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pesticide Residues Often Remain on Fruits and Vegetables Even After They Are Washed: '...strawberries topped the "Dirty Dozen" list of pesticide-contaminated produce that the Environmental Working Group complies every year. Spinach was a close second on the list of fruits and vegetables to avoid' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pesticide Residues Often Remain on Fruits and Vegetables Even After They Are Washed: '...strawberries topped the "Dirty Dozen" list of pesticide-contaminated produce that the Environmental Working Group complies every year. Spinach was a close second on the list of fruits and vegetables to avoid' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis may be backsliding on paedophile priest crackdown, senior Catholic official warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indias first lunar probe found orbiting moon eight years after losing radio contact: NASA finds the Chandrayaan spacecraft 200 kilometres above the lunar surface </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elephant poaching is losing Africa millions of tourist dollars: Around 20,000 elephants are killed in Africa every year for their tusks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full blown as in GE or just within the party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Park's action had "seriously impaired the spirit of... democracy and the rule of law," said constitutional court chief justice Lee Jung-Mi. "President Park Geun-Hye... has been dismissed."

Nice... what's the next official step following impeachment?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a first in the world for a president to be impeached by rule of law?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Trump adviser communicated with Russian hackers before election: Roger Stone appeared to know about documents the hackers had stolen before they were published. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis has warned in an interview with a German newspaper of the dangers of rising populism in western democracies: populism is evil and ends badly as the past century showed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Cuts Regulations as Oceanic Dead Zones Release Massive Amounts of Methane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland becomes first country in the world to make firms prove equal pay: The Nordic nation has pledged to eradicate the gender pay gap by 2022 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump renominates FCC Chair Ajit Pai for another five-year term: Cable lobby hails Pai for pushing "pro-consumer agenda" and "Internet freedom." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women and pro-choice campaigners in Ireland are going on strike to protest the countrys strict anti-abortion laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women and pro-choice campaigners in Ireland are going on strike to protest the countrys strict anti-abortion laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge blocks FBI from forcing fingerprints from targets to unlock iPhones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-British spy Christopher Steele breaks silence over Donald Trump Russia dossier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada sex assault acquittal signals 'open season on incapacitated women': Calls grow for provincial judge to be removed from bench after acquitting taxi driver of sexual assault on drunk passenger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive 4,000-year-old Galilee tombs force rethink of Bronze dark age: In northern Israel, archaeologists excavate largest dolmen in the Levant, with 50-ton stones to rival those of Stonehenge in size </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poachers kill one of Africa's last remaining 'big tusker' elephants: Satao II, about 50 years old, is believed to have been shot with a poisoned arrow in Tsavo national park, Kenya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pitbull that 'saved boy's life' will not be put down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope has urged having fewer children if you cannot bring them up properly, claims Vatican academy member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey's Erdogan makes Nazi jibe over Germany rally ban: "Your practices are not different from the Nazi practices of the past" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carter Page, Adviser Once Linked to Trump Campaign, Met With Russian Ambassador To US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The EPA has withdrawn an Obama-era request for methane emissions information from 15,000 oil and gas companies nationwide  a decision the Trump administration made after 11 states said the request amounted to harassment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study Shows Massive Global Permafrost Melt Underway While Trump Mentions Climate Not Once: Research shows immense expanses of permafrost rapidly disintegrating and releasing huge carbon stores in Canada, Alaska, Scandinavia, and Siberia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Ground-breaking' building material that 'reverses impact of pollution' launched in London: The award-winning material, called The Breath, can be used both indoors and outdoors and works buy absorbs harmful airborne molecules and dispersing "cleaner air" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TSA considers using scanners with CT technology for checkpoints </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's torture comments 'enough to make my blood run cold', says UN human rights expert: British lawyer Ben Emmerson says Trump's comments make him question 'whether anything at all has been achieved in the last 15 years' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EFF: Data Collected From Utility Smart Meters Should Be Protected By The Fourth Amendment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Federal Court rules patients should have access to life-ending drugs: For more than a decade a 74-year-old man fought for legal access to fatal drugs for his paralyzed, now-deceased, wife. A German court has now ruled that her extreme suffering should have been taken into account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Removal of Bumblebee From Endangered List Is Illegal, Advocates Say: "The science is clear -- this species is headed toward extinction, and soon. There is no legitimate reason to delay federal protections." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand Fishing Industry Accused of Driving Worlds Rarest Dolphin to Extinction: Study of industry that calls itself "world leader" finds that vessels illegally discard a third of their catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand Fishing Industry Accused of Driving Worlds Rarest Dolphin to Extinction: Study of industry that calls itself "world leader" finds that vessels illegally discard a third of their catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweden brings back military conscription in face of growing Russia threat: At least 4,000 18-year-olds could be called up each year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries pledge millions to plug hole left by US 'global gag rule': Brussels conference hopes to raise $600m for safe abortions worldwide after Trump administration reinstated US funding ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Boss Falsely Claims His Attacks On Net Neutrality Have Already Made The Wireless Sector More Competitive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finland Allows Same-Sex Marriages For The First Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burger King animal feed sourced from deforested lands in Brazil and Bolivia: Campaign group Mighty Earth says aerial drones, satellite imaging and field research show farmers carried out forest-burning for fast food giants soy suppliers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer Launches Witch Hunt Over The 'Secure' App He Just Said Was No Big Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK: New drivers who are caught using a phone at the wheel will lose their licence under new legislation that comes into force today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article:
 http://www.nwtgeoscience.ca/sites/www.nwtgeoscience.ca/files/resources/geology-2017-kokelj-g38626.1.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive Permafrost Thaw Documented in Canada, Portends Huge Carbon Release: Study shows 52,000 square miles in rapid decline, with sediment and carbon threatening the surrounding environment and potentially accelerating global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive Permafrost Thaw Documented in Canada, Portends Huge Carbon Release: Study shows 52,000 square miles in rapid decline, with sediment and carbon threatening the surrounding environment and potentially accelerating global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paedophiles who pose low risk 'should be given helplines instead of jail time': 'As a country, we have to turn around and look at alternatives [to prison time]', says UK's top child protection officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A UK outside the EU will become more reliant on the US and upon a president less predictable, less reliable and less attuned to our free market and socially liberal instincts than any of his predecessors, former British prime minister John Major said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC's Pai Moves to Kill Consumer Broadband Privacy Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents who let diabetic son starve to death found guilty of first-degree murder: Emil and Rodica Radita isolated and neglected their son Alexandru for years before his eventual death  at which point he was said to be so emaciated that he appeared mummified, court hears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deported gay Afghans told to pretend to be straight: New UK Home Office rules would send gay asylum seekers back to Afghanistan, where homosexuality is illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boris Nemtsov killing: Supporters to march in Moscow | Nemtsov, a reformer, democrat and a deputy prime minister under former President Boris Yeltsin, was a fierce critic of President Vladimir Putin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren Buffett praises 'ambitious immigrants' in optimistic annual letter: Buffett offered an optimistic look at America's financial future after reporting his company Berkshire Hathaway's net worth grew $27.5 billion, or 10.7%, to $172,108 per Class A equivalent share. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Rejects Warrant Seeking To Force Everyone At A Searched Location To Unlock Seized Electronic Devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Student-Built Website That Keeps Government Climate Data Safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Wyden: Border Searches of Digital Devices Should Require a Warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Exempts Some ISPs From Having to Disclose Caps, Fees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesco stops customers purchasing 200 worth of food for the homeless: The customers tried to purchase tinned food for the Saint Laurences Larder charity, which provides fresh food for those who struggle to make ends meet in the community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most wood energy schemes are a 'disaster' for climate change: new study says wood is not carbon neutral and emissions from pellets are higher than coal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CEOs of Goldman Sachs, JPMorgan are worth $261 million more since the election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women liberated from Isis in Syria take off face veils and burn them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women liberated from Isis in Syria take off face veils and burn them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Bill Introduced To Add A Warrant Requirement To Stingray Deployment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If New FCC Boss Ajit Pai Is So 'Pro Consumer,' Why Does The Telecom Industry Need To Pay People To Say So? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump state visit: MPs of all parties demand 'disgusting' US President's trip be cancelled | Debate in Westminster Hall triggered after a petition to block state visit reaches almost two million signatories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is a fascist, Labour MP Dennis Skinner says: Dennis Skinner accused Theresa May of walking 'hand-in-hand' with fascism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphin 'wrapped in clothing' sparks plea in Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asylum seekers in UK placed in rat-infested accommodation, Commons report finds: It is simply unacceptable in 21st century Britain that people fleeing war and persecution are being placed in such disgraceful conditions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nye: Trump Is Suffering From Cognitive Dissonance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First images of unique Brazilian coral reef at mouth of Amazon: The discovery of the 600 mile-long reef in 2016 stunned scientists but oil companies are planning to drill in the area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Orders Massive Rollback of Environmental Protections: In a major effort to dismantle environmental protections, Trump today signed an executive order requiring all federal agencies to repeal two regulations before implementing a new rule. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google recalls staff to US over Donald Trump immigration ban: Its painful to see the personal cost of this executive order on our colleagues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Has Done Enough for the Dow, for Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A British court blocked pollution claims against Anglo-Dutch energy giant Shell by more than 40,000 Niger Delta residents demanding action over decades of oil spills in the region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen forced to pee in bucket in school awarded $1.25 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did a damn good job:

 [Of the almost 200 current member states (and one observer state) of the United Nations, the British have, at some point in history, invaded and established a military presence in 171 of them](http://mentalfloss.com/article/13019/there-are-only-22-countries-world-british-havent-invaded) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northern Irish court allows judicial review into decision to prosecute woman under abortion ban: Women in Northern Ireland face up to life in prison for having an abortion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Donald Trump is bombing four of the seven countries from where he's restricting immigration: Plans for new executive orders are latest in string of the decrees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that was Mancow but I wasn't sure if Hannity honoured his bet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Sean Hannity finally get waterboarded for charity?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Donald Trump has said he believes waterboarding works, saying "we have to fight fire with fire". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Jong Un 'would nuke Los Angeles' if his rule was threatened, North Korea defector reveals: Claim comes after former deputy ambassador vowed to 'dismantle' the North's murderous regime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacker who stole nude photos of Jennifer Lawrence and other celebrities jailed for nine months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacker who stole nude photos of Jennifer Lawrence and other celebrities jailed for nine months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is facing a pre-emptive backlash over his reported plans for a ban on people from seven Muslim-majority countries entering the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposed CIA Chief Seems Happy To Spy On Americans, Even If Using Info Hacked By Russians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merkel advisors say Germany has 'given up' on Donald Trump acting like a President: 'The Americans, and the world, will get the Trump they elected' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activists have condemned as an assault on women's health, a decision by Donald Trump to block US funding for health clinics around the world that provide abortion services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany warns Donald Trump's presidency 'marks end of old world order': 'Today there is a great deal at stake. By choosing Donald Trump, the old world of the 20th century is over,' says Frank-Walter Steinmeier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women whose third child is born following a sexual assault will be forced to provide evidence of the rape or face losing tax credits, under controversial plans quietly rolled out by the UK Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women whose third child is born following a sexual assault will be forced to provide evidence of the rape or face losing tax credits, under controversial plans quietly rolled out by the UK Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kentuckys New Fetal Pain Law, Like Most Abortion Restrictions, Is Based on Junk Science: Specifically, Senate bill 5 would ban abortion after 20 weeks gestation, under the mistaken assumption that 20 weeks is the point at which a fetus feels pain, making abortion a cruel and unusual punishment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New online generation takes up Holocaust denial: Conspiracy theorists are flocking to outlandish websites, warns lecturer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia set to move closer to decriminalize domestic violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia set to move closer to decriminalize domestic violence: 'If the measure passes its second reading in the Duma on Wednesday, when the draft can be changed, approval in the third and final reading would be a foregone conclusion.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London university admits to monitoring student emails under pressure Government anti-terror programme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London university admits to monitoring student emails under pressure Government anti-terror programme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London university admits to monitoring student emails under pressure Government anti-terror programme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah...its not a flaw.

Its a pregnant pause - for effect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump confuses French translators with mixed-up speeches: 'Trumps vocabulary is limited, his syntax is broken; he repeats the same phrases over and over' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter investigating after users say they're being added as followers of Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps EPA Pick: Anti-Science Christian Extremist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of the blue - 'Trump' skywriting appears above Sydney protest: Skywriting Australia says it did the job at a cost of $4,000, and the clients wanted it to coincide with the Womens March </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vladimir Putin supporters hold all-night party and joke 'Washington will be ours' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 11:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denmark bans marriage for under-18s after report suggests dozens of asylum seeking teens arriving with spouses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 11:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lots of corpse flowers bloomed in 2016 and nobody knows why: The corpse flower takes ten years to build up enough energy to bloom, but mysteriously, dozens of them bloomed within weeks of each other in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lots of corpse flowers bloomed in 2016 and nobody knows why: The corpse flower takes ten years to build up enough energy to bloom, but mysteriously, dozens of them bloomed within weeks of each other in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish MP handcuffs herself in parliament protesting Erdogan getting more executive powers: Proposed bill which would abolish the position of prime minister and possibly let Erdogan stay in office until 2029 due to pass third vote in Turkeys parliament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a super surprise. Thanks for your votes everyone and the gold, mods! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
