<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 05:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 05:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, nope. The photo is untouched. Seriously. That's the original, untouched image.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 05:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't going to believe this. I took the pics with a Samsung Galaxy Note 3 using the fv-5 camera app. I tried with my Nexus 6 first, but was too close to focus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captured AMAZING close-up images of a fly. Wife swears that I Photoshopped sunglasses onto is face (2pics). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 04:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 15:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upvote for telling it like it is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because we're all conditioned to think this is the greatest country in the world and that we're the luckiest people in the world. You'll never see an uprising in america. We're all sheep and dont even know it. We will continue to get fucked more and more until one day we'll just take our paychecks and hand them directly over to the big corporations, more blatantly than we already do, while our rights are progressively stolen. And we'll never complain, because this is America! Land of the "we're lucky to be here!" Corporations run this country. Period.  They make the decisions, the laws, decide what rights we have. The politicians are nothing more than  the personal hand-puppets of whatever corporation is currently shoving fistfulls of hundred-dollar-bills directly up their assholes. 

Wow...did I just say that? Shit....dark man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're taking this way too literal and missing the point. The point is to make a statement, send a message. Drive it home with a sledge hammer (not a literal sledge hammer), but make it something the world will notice. Something other agencies/employers/employees/police/corrections etc will notice.  A hundred million may be bullshit, but so is half-a-million. Thats just my opinion. I'm just a guy in the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant seriously reduce this to just "a cavity search." That isnt what this is about. This goes far beyond a cavity search. Read the original article. The ORIGINAL article. The one that describes, in detail, what this woman was subjected through that night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? I thought that was low. For the humiliation this woman suffered. For how violated she must feel. For her trauma. For what has been taken from her that she will never get back. And to send a message so that the next time it happens it isnt you or your mother or your wife or your infant daughter. People, whether under color of law or not, just cant be allowed to do whatever they decide. If I'm allowed to violate your grandmother just because I'm a potato head with a badge then whats to stop me from determining that maybe a toddler is suit-casing an eightball of coke. Imagine if that dog had signaled on a small child. What would have happened then? Same night, same group of people working, same dog, except its a child thats suspected. Its a child thats strip-searched while people watch. Its a child handcuffed and taken to the hospital and violated even more, again, while people watch. Thats where I get a hundred million. To send a message. Probably wouldnt happen again if someone had to pay enormously. 

edit: removed smart-assery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean. How completely stupid does one have to be to think this is ok. And it wasnt even just one person. I could almost get it if it were just one person, but this was probably a dozen or more people. A few feds, a few supervisors, a couple of receptionists, a few nurses, and a few doctors. UNBELIEVABLE that none of them thought "ummm wait guys...is this really necessary? Is it really ok to do this?" Other than the victim, no one protested? And these are the people we have protecting our borders, carrying loaded guys? Really?  And the medical staff? Seriously? Sorry, I realize this isnt Craigslist Rants and Raves, but DAMN!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thinking about how many people made horrible choices that day. It just seems strange/odd to me that no one said "hey wait...commonsense says this woman is clean, lets let her go." How come that didnt happen? I can understand one person, poorly trained and dimwitted, but how about the others? A coworker, and then another coworker, and then others, and then ultimately doctors and nurses. That seems like a total breakdown of the system. No one gave a damn about this woman.  This is an embarrassment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That award is an embarrassment. It should be a hundred million with a hundred million more in punitive damages. Send a fucking message.  People need to lose their jobs over this...and not just the mindless sheep who were following orders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiding in plain sight....works every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your secure communications platform isnt being used by terrorists and pedophiles, youre probably doing it wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a much better title.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right? The only thing the malware has to do is make the user think something bad is happening. The popup provided a toll free number to call to remove malware from your computer and to stop the spread of your credit card number. I have seen it happen more times than I can count - a user panics and dials the number...and thats when the real trouble starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've spent a lot of time preaching to my users/clients to think before they click links in email, and it has worked! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once of my users received this email from a client of hers: http://imgur.com/a/IAFdB .  The "from" address is legit, but it's worded funny. She forwarded it to me and I checked it out. It definitely ISNT legit. I clicked the link in a virtual machine running W7 and it instantly redirected me, displayed a "windows-looking" ad, beeped, and informed me, in a woman's voice, that my credit card information was being sent to hackers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First encounter with a mirror (10 months old)..she stood this way for twenty minutes.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tons of porn, but easy to filter. Especially on KAT. Filter to TV, then by seeders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 02:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its on kickass and TPB. KAT has more seeders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 03:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Yes he did. Mounted that ass. This was in the eighties when he brought this thing home from the taxidermist. I was very young. He convinced my sister and I that it was a dangerous, wild animal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The year dad didn't kill a buck... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 02:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 02:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful dogs by-the-way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 02:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent seen it, but now I definitely will!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was afraid that would be the case when we got the new pup. Old dog has been our only one for a long time. She has a reputation for being an asshole, but for whatever reason she seems to really like the new dog. Big relief. Maybe yours will come around... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 21:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL..thats pretty much how she greets everyone.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats hilarious! They've got it figured out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...thats them. "Get the Fuck Back" and "Rub My Tummy".... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right about that. Its been very interesting watching them test one another. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats the TRUTH. They play well together and seem to have bonded, but old dog definitely makes it known who the boss is.  The older one is 12 years old. The new/young one is 11 months old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My old dog welcoming my new dog into the family pretty much sums up this subreddit.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I placed the broken hose into her car and took a pic. Sent her the pic. She immediately thought that I had gotten gas, had forgotten to replace the hose, and had driven off with it, breaking the pump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took out the wife's car to gas it up. Noticed a broken gas pump...and then magic happened... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 01:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I was in between houses/without internet for a few months in the last year. So I really maxed out my data use. I think the next year will look much better for me. I am more than happy with my phone and service (nexux 6). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 23:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine just did the same. I've been running on USCellular a lot lately, but always on 3G. I was on Sprint when I received the "Maximize your coverage" prompt. When it finished up I'm on T-Mobile. I'm in southwest Virginia (US).  I've noticed that T-mobile seems to be significantly faster in this area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 23:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my one-year. Not great, but better than my previous Sprint bill.  http://m.imgur.com/cm53dxj
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 12:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.imdb.com/title/tt4935334/?ref_=fn_al_tt_1
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 00:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called a spit roast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton disqualifies herself by her careless, reckless actions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mess with Texas! It's refreshing to see it done right. Why handle these assholes with "little kid gloves"...? This should be a message to anyone else considering violence against those who protect us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas TX - This is the first time I have ever heard of law enforcement using explosives to kill a suspect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 14:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dallas police chief just said that after negotiations failed, his officers placed an explosive device (a bomb) on a robot (remote control car), drove it to the suspect and detonated it, killing the suspect. This is after hours of negotiations and after numerous dead and wounded officers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 16:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. upvoted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 16:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well said. upvoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 15:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and if the FBI wont release it, maybe "someone else" will. You know what I mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 15:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..and if the FBI wont release it, maybe "someone else" will. You know what I mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her supporters are imbeciles, just like she is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree. What a mess! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant disagree with that. I look around and I just cant fathom why there are still people who cant see things the way I see them. People have their eyes and ears closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly, you are probably exactly right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well put.   I think she will be such a shitshow that people will wakeup....or at least thats my hope. This circus we have for a government needs to stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think of Hillary as "the tipping point"..not the change we need, but the blatant clusterfuck that is finally going to bring the change. She'll be president..but maybe she'll be such a disgrace that the sheep will wakeup next election and something good will happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 04:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cat PEE. I would never put cat shit on the counter.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 04:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her EXACT words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 04:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I told her I'd run it past reddit.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 04:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Cat piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife did NOT see the humor in this at all... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 04:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Article - The Born Soldier - Author discusses men who are at home in war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 04:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 02:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt want to carry 2 phones....some shit with my private email server...Benghazi....yadda yadda yadda I'm meeting with the FBI on Saturday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 13:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leno's chin changed the cars center-of-gravity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here....got this from Google Now. Disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am fascinated by North Korea and try to keep current on the news coming out of the DPRK. I cant seem to verify this. If its true its huge. Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6/17/2016 Any truth to the rumors Kim Jong-Un dead in apparant suicide bombing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was speaking of myself...hoping there were others like me out there somewhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you read.....up until a certain point. After that you just become a antisocial, paranoid recluse holed up in moms basement waiting for Amazon's next recommendations-email while Audible continues to deduct $14.95 from your credit card every month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife says that my cock is so handsome it looks like I was circumcised by Leonardo da Vinci.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this math...makes me wonder how long it might take me to jackoff every reddit user in this thread....if only someone would create a formula for this.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion many/most LPT's are common sense/common knowledge and are unworthy/not front-page material. However, this one is news to me. So, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 12:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cant argue with you there.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 19:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, I've noticed that soda in general, regardless of the container, loses its fizz/carbonation within a day or two max when opened and then resealed and stored. This wasn't the case 35 years ago. At least I think I'm right. 

I'll try this in askscience...thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am not into conspiracy theories, but I am almost positive that Coke and Pepsi have conspired together to alter their formulas so that soda loses its fizz much quicker than it used to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 18:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a big soda drinker, but I was as a kid, and I remember opening a two-liter and having it last for days. That was 30-35 years ago. I opened a two-liter of Dr Pepper and Mtn Dew last night for a kids birthday party, poured 2 cups from each, and resealed them immediately. Today they are worthless. Something similar happened a few weeks ago. So what gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..and then wait around for the curl... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 19:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> soooooo.....is he still Chinese?..AFTER the drugs and beatings I mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 02:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I remember thinking the exact same thing. Now I get to work 60-hour weeks! Yay!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We wanted to be adults SO bad... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 02:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cookout's 2-Piece Chicken Strip Meal.... Same Price as the 3-Piece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Loved You in Batman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well....when you put it like that.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dont shit in my burrito" ISNT ASKING A LOT!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and then spit it out...into the burrito </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..looks like they chewed it in half... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I was actually shocked...and pretty fucking angry. I felt like there was no way this wasnt done on purpose. What moron would pass this off as food?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely did. Thats a sausage breakfast burrito exactly as it was when I unwrapped it. It was so disgusting I couldnt eat it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try Burger King marketing team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nailed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AWESOME! I have never won anything in my life! This is GREAT! Wait...yuk...she's sweaty...Is she supposed to be sweaty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fryer, you say? Delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS is fucking AWESOME! You totally just won my vote, Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a good point, my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like Helen Kellers first day on the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I thought...I couldnt even eat it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE Taco Bell...but their menu is getting a bit TOO MANY CHOICES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice...but no Jack in the Box in my area...dammit man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burger King tacos? I do not remember this....stand by while I Google...HOLY SHIT ITS LEGIT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HORRIBLE way to begin a workday....especially a Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...me too....and I've SEEN my mom. You havent seen her, so you're taking your chances, but I've seen her. Love you, mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it does. I didnt even eat it. I also didnt return it because I picked it up on my way to work and didnt get to open it for about an hour. So not only did it look like one of the towers fell on it, it was also cold and slimy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured there would be some non-believers, but this is 100% exactly what it looked like when I opened it up. I bought it last year and immediately posted it to reddit and no one looked at it. Then when I saw the BK posts today it seemed relevant so I reported. Totally legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, I dont know if I would call it a burrito, but thats what Burger King calls it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, first world problem, but I really had my hopes up for that burrito.  Dammit man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
