<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2956</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I read the rules here, NSFW tag is for *visible* death, injury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=92b_1480654045). Not much info there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lions eat a buffalo alive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 13:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added it after reading the comments. Hadn't noticed the cyclist going down when I posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brakes failed on this truck in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=9c1_1480660425) The mug wasn't empty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=9c1_1480660425) The mug wasn't empty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grabbing a drink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB, while I finish the other mug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camel selfie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Risking life, Nganj gateman saves youth attempting suicide under train](http://www.thedailystar.net/country/risking-life-nganj-gateman-saves-youth-attempting-suicide-under-train-1323502) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alert railway gateman in Bangladesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Risking life, Nganj gateman saves youth attempting suicide under train](http://www.thedailystar.net/country/risking-life-nganj-gateman-saves-youth-attempting-suicide-under-train-1323502) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alert railway gateman in Bangladesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rainbow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 11:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress twitter account hacked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [1:30 min video, normal speed, chinese audio](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=2ed_1480442223) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trucking skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taiwanese truck takes a tight turn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://www.google.co.in/amp/elpais.com/elpais/2016/11/29/inenglish/1480410907_334156.amp.html)

Madrid29 NOV 2016 - 10:58CET

 A woman was rescued from the roof of her car on Monday after the vehicle came close to being fully submerged in a flooded underpass in the Spanish city of Sagunto, in the Mediterranean province of Valencia.

 The motorist had attempted to drive through even though access to the underpass had reportedly been fenced off because of high water levels.

 The driver allegedly ignored warning signs near the underpass

 As the car quickly began to sink, the driver was able to get out through the passenger seat window. She then climbed on the roof with her belongings to wait for help to arrive.

 A television crew captured her plight, and images of a woman standing atop a gently floating red hatchback quickly spread on social media.

 It was journalists who first alerted the local emergency services. Half an hour later, the stranded motorist was taken to safety on a firefighters shoulders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinking feeling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PM Modi asks BJP MPs, MLAs to submit bank transaction details between Nov 8 and Dec 31 to Amit Shah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/TH2Lt4snU-U) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mister Ohm tries to resist gravity on live TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sled ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 08:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sled ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 08:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The misinformation campaign to dis Modi's next mega project has already started </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bengaluru professionals spend extra hours at work; many hail note ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She didn't even change her pace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all relative, or rather cultural. 80% of my countrymen would think you are a psycho if you go to a party where they serve beef. 30% if you eat any meat. And yet there are parts of my country where they eat dog meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=354_1480339711) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are documented cases of wolf cannibalism (and human cannibalism). Maybe it just depends on how hungry one is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armed robbery in DC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leopard cannibalism has been observed many times before. They kill rivals and cubs of other males just like lions do. They probably eat them for the same reason other animals practice cannibalism, free meat. Here is [another instance of leopard cannibalism](http://i.imgur.com/yWoykVM.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=354_1480339711) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failed armed robbery in DC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/Q1t5N1wKeeM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Male leopard eats a female leopard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Qaeda terrorists planning to target PM Modi, wanted in string of bomb attacks held in Tamil Nadu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally different video/gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Towing a car stuck in the sand, sideways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baboon grabs a meal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 14:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 11:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://www.instagram.com/p/BK4KGl_hN1o/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pipe fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 11:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short ride to the fridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 09:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love smart, fit, older women (40+). If I have to drop one, I will drop 'smart'. My latest crush is [this 46 year-old](https://www.google.co.in/amp/www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-3952874/amp/Quality-time-Padma-Lakshmi-showcases-bikini-body-plays-sea-daughter-Krishna.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buharis has really gone down in quality, ever since they opened multiple branches. Used to be my favourite when I was a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Trichy special, I have heard. And totally different from the Kannappar in Chennai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They used to have a mushroom and panneer biriyani too if I remember right. Good stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Courtallama? Or the ones they have opened on ECR(Chennai) lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makkale, Tamil Nadoda bestu biriyani ethu?

1. Thalapakatti

2. Buhari

3. Ambur

4. Madurai (not sure what it is called)

5. Saravana Bhavan vegetarian biriyani

6. Kaakka biriyani

7. Poone biriyani

6. Biriyani patthi ethavuthu theriyumada unakku? (please enlighten me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been reading some of [her writings](https://www.project-syndicate.org/columnist/gita-gopinath) for a while now. Always had a very low opinion of her intelligence. Now that you have put a face(and body) to that name, I've changed my mind. She is 43, paging /u/thurki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 11:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is wakesurfing. Guess he could have continued for a while without the tow rope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 11:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A slightly [different edit](https://gfycat.com/ChiefGloriousAnemoneshrimp) of the [source video](https://youtu.be/G12eznbV3i4). Is this better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Hand me a beer" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 10:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Hand me a beer" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 10:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rajdeep Sardesai knows demonetisation has been a big win for Modi, and he is finding it difficult to swallow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=6a5_1480008225) says this is Pakistan. They are not sacred there, they eat them there. This video is also on Youtube without a location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Street bull-y </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO, this is really well made. 'Eye of the tiger' had me cracking, and then 'Chariots of fire' came along  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Think I'll watch it again, as soon as Planet Earth 2  is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The typical image of an ostrich is a male ostrich, which is black and white. The female ostrich(like in this gif) is grey/brown, like an emu. Hence the confusion, or he is just joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either mother and children, or siblings(usually brothers). Otherwise they rarely socialize or hunt together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/AozXE7p06-w)

The ostrich goes down in the end. Couldn't get that and the cheetah leaping on the ostrich at the beginning within the 15 sec limit.

I remember this was also in the first episode of one of the BBC Attenborough documentaries. (Which one?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ostriches are fast, but cheetahs are faster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 05:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't believe anything the Pak Army says. I would suspect the military casualties on the other side are much higher than they claim. Even our army can't know how many Pak soldiers they killed. There is also this curious lack of info on injured numbers from the other side.

After all we are talking about the same people who deny the surgical strikes, deny that any Pak soldiers were killed during the Kargil War, denied the very existence of Bangladesh till 1975 and claim they won the 65 war. The Pak Army rarely wins any confrontation, even the ones with their own terrorists, but amusingly claim they lost nothing after every confrontation.

The Pak Army is a joke, but what is more unbelievable is how stupid the Pakistani people are in trusting them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=f7c_1479870104)

 Was attending Beach Streets in Long Beach when this random drunk girl though she could jump this ramp. I told her she would fall but she insisted on how "badass" it would be so I had to record it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk girl jumps a 'ramp' on her bicycle, WCGW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just do it, you pussy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 12:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Indian media tried to link every issue in the world to Demonetisation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 13:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 13:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Indias shortage of banknotes spurs protests**

*A cruel cash crunch emboldens the opposition*

Nov 17th 2016|Asia

WHEN Narendra Modi, Indias prime minister, announced the shock recall of high-denomination banknotes on November 8th, economists hailed the move as strong but necessary medicine. The overnight scrapping of some $200bn-worth of cash would flush out forged rupees and corrupt earnings, dragging Indias vast underground economy into the bright modern world of electronic payments, bank accounts and taxes. Political pundits called it a masterstroke. Not only would citizens queuing to exchange old notes for new see for themselves how Mr Modi had kept a campaign promise to smoke out bad guys. With crucial state elections looming, the sting would also render worthless the vote-buying war chests of his political rivals.

The practice, however, has not lived up to the theory. The surprise scrapping of what amounted to 86% of the cash in circulation could, in fact, turn out to be the worst mistake of Mr Modis career. For hundreds of millions of Indians who cannot pay for essential goods with credit or debit cards, it has brought not satisfaction but the misery of waiting in angry queues outside overwhelmed banks, only to get limited quantities of new bills, or to find they have run out. For many among the estimated 80% of wage earners who are paid in cash, for the tens of thousands of villages with no banking facilities, and for the traders, drivers, farmers, prostitutes, beggars and others who work in the informal economy that accounts for anywhere between 25% and 70% of Indias GDP, it has brought anxiety and hardship. Well know later if Modi is right or wrong, a man outside a bank in Delhi told one television crew. All I know now is Im starving.

Rather than being cowed by the currency move, Indias hitherto divided and disparate opposition has been invigorated. At the stormy opening of the winter session of parliament on November 16th, Sitaram Yechury, a communist MP, ridiculed the prime minister as Modi Antoinette, echoing postings on social media that portray a regal Mr Modi above the caption, Let them use plastic. Leftist, rightist and regional party leaders later marched to demand that the currency change be abandoned. Even Indias supreme court chimed in. At a hearing over legal challenges to Mr Modis move, one judge joked that the governments claim of a surgical strike against black money looked more like carpet-bombing.

Mr Modi is unlikely to relent. Many citizens remain convinced that their hardship is in a good cause. Economists concur that in the longer term the currency swap will bring benefits, albeit not the ones that the government has touted loudest. According to a study by an academy attached to Indias finance ministry, cash makes up a negligible portion of illicit holdings: property, tradable goods and foreign bank accounts amount to much more. In any case the biggest hoarders of cash are probably the best-equipped to get rid of it. Within a day of Mr Modis announcement, first-class tickets on Indias longest train route, between Dibrugarh and Kanyakumari, were sold out for the next four months: they could still be bought with old money, then later refunded for new.

The people really caught out are likely to be ordinary citizens who failed to bank recent transactions such as property sales, which are commonly made in cash, or who were saving for some costly cash outlay. It does not help that this is Indias peak season for weddings, or that much of the country is seeing the end of harvest and beginning of new planting. Farmers have found themselves stranded, often far from banking facilities, with old money that they cannot spend on seeds and fertilisers. Wholesalers cannot pay suppliers and merchants cannot pay wholesalers. Informal financial networks, which by one estimate lend around 40% as much as banks do, are frozen.

Economists reckon that the currency squeeze will knock 0.5-1 percentage points off Indias growth rate in each of the next two quarters. When the money supply stabilises, important benefits should be felt. Indian banks, for one thing, will have received a huge injection of new deposits as clients rush to unload old bills before the deadline of 30th December but can only withdraw restricted volumes of new ones. Fresh deposits in the first week amounted to nearly $57bn, equal to almost half the increase in bank deposits over the whole preceding year. The boost to balance-sheets, particularly for state-owned banks burdened in recent years by non-performing loans, should lower interest rates and spur new lending.

The cash crunch has been an undreamed-of boon for the electronic-payments industry. Mobikwik, a mobile-wallet system, reports an 18-fold increase in use. Paytm, a rival, took out full front-page page advertisements featuring pictures of Mr Modi, congratulating him on The boldest decision in the financial history of independent India! Indias taxmen will also profit hugely from their enhanced power of scrutiny. That is a good thing in a country where only 1% of citizens pay income tax, and where government revenues amount to a puny 20% of GDP.

In the meantime, the difficulties of Mr Modis experiment are a lesson in humility. Despite much progress India remains poor, patchily administered and reliant on shaky infrastructure. On paper, for instance, its 1.3bn people wield a respectable-sounding 723m credit and debit cards, and under a government scheme some 255m bank accounts have been opened. But a closer look reveals that most of those cards and accounts are scarcely used, and only for small amounts.

Mr Modis shock therapy took the banking system by surprise. There were not enough new bills, in the wrong denominations, and Indias 220,000 cash machines were anyway not calibrated to handle them. Even now fewer than one in ten has been modified to do so and it will take weeks to adjust them all. In the meantime Indians will have to do something they are all too used to doing: wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let me pet this kitty, WCGW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 07:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sled ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Road rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 08:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/F9TfiLkOHqg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Must be a professional soccer player behind the wheel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 08:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Competition for what? We shouldn't be taking this sub thing too seriously. Should this sub be like randia which bans any mention of /r/indianews? I don't think the mods and users here are insecure as the mods in randia are.

There are thousands of subs on Reddit and subscribing to two more subs makes no difference, even though they have the same type of posts. For example, /r/interestingasfuck and /r/woahdude have the same kind of posts. Most people are  subscribed to both subs, and somebody posting to one sub would also xpost to the other sub. Competition and choice is a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 12:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/nbxjc-oNEIk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 12:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 12:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/nbxjc-oNEIk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instant ambulance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 11:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=bb3_1479474125) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And he just walks away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, this guy actually believes what he posted. A lot of effort went into that post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does tajurba mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any links to where this started </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mongoloid legs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran overtakes Saudi to becomes India's top crude oil supplier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were rumours of an Adreno 540 coming out with these 10nm chips a while back. Guess its not happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full video](https://youtu.be/yfa4mml0Fq4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lions fight over food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know much about him. But I remember he was one of the people who opposed the release of Kamal Haasan's movie that dealt with Islamic terror. He was supporting some Islamic/Jihadi TN group then. He hides behind the cloak of Tamil pride in attacking India to mask his religious beliefs. He was supposed to have been a successful director in the past, but hasn't made any movies recently. He and his kind get far more attention than they deserve by making shocking statements.

The so called Tamil nationalists are not like Khalistanis or Kashmiri separatists. They are more like AAPturds. They hate the country and hinduism for the same reasons AAPturds do. This is exploited by Jihadis and other anti-national elements just like they exploit AAP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope it isn't V.K Singh. His mouth is too big for diplomacy.

Modi could make a well performing minister like Piyush Goyal as Foreign Minister, but I don't think foreign affairs is as important as power. Maybe a non-performing senior minister like RS Prasad or even Smriti Irani? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is a Jihadi who claims he is a Tamil nationalist. Many so called Tamil nationalists come from a Maoist, Dalit, Jihadi or  Evangelical background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 09:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great gif, but I am a proud lungi. Can't be nice to you for ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shameless cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you post gifs on the larger subs (/r/gifs, /r/funny)? This is some top class shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build a wall in the north to keep the Wildlings out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demonetisation: Unaccounted cash triggers panic attacks in hoarders, say psychiatrists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/qT0jm5prdhQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car out of control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demonetisation: Narendra Modi did what Indira suggested was not for her to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 09:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just the beginning. Wait till Dec 30th. Loans would be paid, revenue/tax collections would shoot up, land prices would fall, bank deposits would go up. And for the currency that doesn't come out before that, 'I promise to pay the bearer a sum of x rupees' doesn't apply any more. The government can just write it away as paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did a Gujarat businessman surrender Rs 6,000 cr following Narendra Modi governments demonetisation drive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 08:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 14:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full article](http://mobile.nytimes.com/2016/11/14/opinion/the-incendiary-appeal-of-demagoguery-in-our-time.html)

The author is extremely butthurt like other people of his kind have been lately. I would be too, if I was a dumbass who had been fooling myself and others that I was an 'intellectual' by spewing intelligent sounding nothings for years, and suddenly realise people can see through my bullshit and know I am just an ass.

Remember to read the comments too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nehru's special security officer K.F. Rustamji gives us some insight into his personality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rustamji notes that Nehru was vain about his looks. He wore his Gandhi cap at a rakish angle and was never seen without it. He was bald as an egg. I noted that he insisted that every photograph taken by our photographers be shown to him before being released to the press. If one had caught him yawning, asleep or picking his nose, he tore it up with his own hands.

Rustamji has a lot to say about Nehrus unpredictable temper. If his breakfast was late, he stormed into the kitchen or the servants quarters to berate his cook. Once, on a visit to Sira (in Mysore), "he barged into the kitchen in a temper, like Jesus among the moneychangers, and almost chased out all the cooks from there," Rustamji notes in his journal. At almost every public meeting, he found something wrong about the police bandobast to control the crowds lining his route and the distance at which milling crowds surrounded the platform. And let everyone have it. Even before he became prime minister, he slapped the president of the Punjab Pradesh Congress Committee in full view of the crowd because the microphone went dead while he was speaking. Lashing out at unruly mobs became a habit. During a visit of the prime minister of Pakistan, Mohammed Ali, in 1953, Nehru was furious at the inadequate arrangements for containing the crowds: "JN got angrier and angrier. He flung aboutpushing people, running after cameramen, shouting, firing. I had never seen him so angry. Somebody opened the door of a car for him; he banged the door and beat people with a large, dishevelled bouquet," Rustamji noted. However, his vocabulary of abuse was limited and the worst he could yell wasbadtameezorbewakoof. I was at the receiving end on two occasions. Once he arrived in London past midnight. I asked him if he would like me to accompany him to his hotel. "Dont be silly; go home and sleep," he ordered. Instead of going to his hotel, he drove to Lady Mountbattens residence. The next morning one of the papers had his photograph with Lady Mountbatten in her negligee opening the door for him. He was furious. On another occasion he took Lady M out for a quiet dinner to a Greek restaurant. The proprietor recognised them and informed the press. Their photographs were in many papers. I was summoned to his presence. He gave me a withering look and said: "You have a strange notion of publicity." I thought it best not to say anything in my defence.

Like most Indians, Nehru treated whites with more courtesy than his countrymen: he spoke on the level to whites but tended to talk down to Indians. At times he could forget his manners. Once I had to host a lunch for the editors of leading British newspapers to meet him. Halfway through the meal he fell silent. When a couple of questions were put to him, he simply looked up at the ceiling and did not reply. The questions froze in the air. As if to lend the air some warmth, he lit a cigarette while others were still eating. To add to my discomfiture, Krishna Menon fell asleep. It was a disastrous attempt at public relations.

Rustamji noted that his idol was a tireless talker. He started talking to men and women in the car taking him to the venue of his meeting. His rambling speeches would at times go on and on for over an hour while many in his audience dozed. In England his audiences were limited. I noted that even during musical performances Nehru, sitting in the middle of the front row, kept talking to men and women sitting beside him. However, he did not indulge in gossip and small talk. When he met U Nu, prime minister of Burma, his host tried to show off how interested he was in India. "Panditji, I like your Vyjanthimala very much," he said. Panditji turned to his shadow and asked in Hindustani, "Kaun hai yeh Vyjanthimala?" U Nu also advised Nehru not to lose his temper at the conference. "I will try my best," Nehru replied. "But if I do, U Nu, you must kick me hard under the table."

While for the most part Rustamji bends over backwards to make allowances for his idol, he confesses that Nehru had his share of "littleness": "It would be difficult for a person who has not known JN from close to imagine what a petty, cantankerous man he could be at times. How rude and arrogant and full of prima donna tantrumshow irascible and selfish in small things! How childish and unbearably inconsiderate he was, not only to me but to those who were supposed to be his trusted advisers! And more than anything else, how impossibly sure he could be of himself and his dictums..."

[Source](http://www.outlookindia.com/magazine/story/like-a-storm-in-a-gandhi-cap/229482) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking every property owner in the country to come for verification with their aadhar and pan cards would be a beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now don't judge him, probably mistook her for a goat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gone in 60 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/Do5IpzrJnF4)

Non life-threatening injuries - [Source](http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/massive-ball-flames-fireworks-factory-9245876) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fireworks warehouse explodes as Russian firefighters try to douse the flames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/Do5IpzrJnF4)

Non life-threatening injuries - [Source](http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/massive-ball-flames-fireworks-factory-9245876) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fireworks warehouse explodes as Russian firefighters try to douse the flames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reliance Jios next big offering could hit DTH and broadband services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 06:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source says it's Chinese](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=c5c_1478880367).

No other info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese doll demo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Didn't mean to do that" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modiji solves black money problem, and partially solves bank NPA problem with one stroke. Maybe it will solve the cash for votes problem too, for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bengaluru rag-picker finds 1000 notes dumped in a plastic bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 11:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Businessman dies of heart-attack after ban on Rs 500, Rs 1000 notes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PBUT - Peace Be Upon Thalaivaa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did a thengai fall on your head today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just act cool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been subscribed here for years sirji, though I never posted. There used to be a lot of randia fags posting here before which kept me away. Not anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was hoping to trigger you. [Owned](https://gfycat.com/FrequentNeedyHyrax). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amits before the interbreeding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck democracy when it doesn't suit us. This is why the Brown Shirts got on German streets in the 1920s/30s, to battle Communist retards who have no sense of fairplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian police searching a suspect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB, I'm going home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [New York Times today morning](http://i.imgur.com/LloQ2Tt.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been following the results all morning. Nytimes was predicting a 75 Clinton win till 7:30. They were predicting a Trump win by 8:10. Was fascinating watching the mood change on /r/the_donald and the meltdown on the rest of Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good morning folks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parties have to start distributing money now. I think it is going to become difficult to exchange notes after Dec 30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nytimes is predicting a Trump win now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried it, tasted more like whisky than rum. Just not worth the 2000+ I paid for it. Don't think it was coconut based. Talking of coconut based alcohol (or rather distilled toddy), I like Sri Lankan coconut arrack, but never liked Goan coconut feni. Maybe I haven't tried the right brand yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adhu enna Old Monkka adhu? Paartthu rombha naalayiduchu Chennaiyile. Old Monk Premiumum rendu maasama out-of-stock Elite-la. Rendu varaama Bacardi Blackum out-of-stock. Dark rum ketta, etho Manila rum ethaiyo kaiya kattitu irunthanunga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also thinking of all the cash Amma's men have taken just for building permits in Chennai past 2-3 years, all in cash. And that is just a small part of the cash they have been hoarding for the next elections. Fucking billions of useless Gandhis now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Think of all the political parties who have hoarded 500/1000 notes for the UP elections and beyond. Then there are the builders and real estate developers, corrupt babus who had taken payment recently, the betting syndicates, retailers avoiding sales tax etc. The list goes on and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The curious case of Twitter accounts getting suspended soon after anti-AAP posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second time I'm seeing this posted here. Had made this meme and posted this on /r/kuttichevuru which is a tamil circle jerk sub (like bakchodi), not to be taken seriously.

Anyway TN has a higher per capita GDP than UP, Punjab, Bihar, MP, etc. Only 2 states have a higher per capita GDP, Maharashtra and Haryana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1080i TS was available on the net a few hours after the telecast. I'm waiting for the 4k blu ray though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is haram brother. Unsubscribe and run back to /r/islam. Allahu Akbar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't agree. This sub should never ban anything, people or sources, even as a joke. The open nature of this sub is what makes it unique. If anybody posts NDTV links here for the next week, just downvote it. And never watch that channel on your TV. If there is a way to unsubscribe from their channels on DTH or cable, do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full video](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=9a7_1478519176) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full video](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=9a7_1478519176) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hauling in the catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hauling in the catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like the Taliban, separatists in Kashmir dont want children to go to schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was wondering where all the regulars on this sub had disappeared for the past few weeks. Glad you are back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest of India probably emits as much pollutants as the North. But coastal areas like Chennai or Mumbai don't suffer as much because of the sea breeze. Also colder temperatures make a big difference, pollutants like automobile exhausts tend to stay much longer at the ground level.

I have suffered from allergy issues leading to respiratory issues all my life. I have lived in Chennai, Bangalore, Delhi and Mumbai. I have had very few issues staying in Chennai and Mumbai compared to Delhi and Bangalore. It also makes a big difference where I stay in Chennai, the closer to the sea the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wang Deshun, 80 year old Chinese model </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well, he died](https://www.stickboybangkok.com/news/sleepy-security-guard-dies-falling-drain/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Happened in Sao Paulo, Brazil](https://youtu.be/Wh2orAWf4Uw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truck appears out of nowhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleepy security guard falls into an open drain in Thailand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Careful what you grab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian Army wiped out Pakistans company headquarters; killed 20 Pakistani soldiers to avenge beheading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "ENGAMMA SINGAMLE" (Saw this on a wall painting/poster on ECR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 09:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Amit logic](http://i.imgur.com/elJ1mG5.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jayalalithaa likely to be moved out of CCU to private room in 3 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the end of Times Now. Hope they don't bring Sagarika into the channel. Would be interesting to see who Arnab teams up with to start a new channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the whole meaning changed there over time. Now I am wondering if 'Naalu kazhutha vayasachu' means what I think it means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes a lot more sense. I have heard this mostly when I failed at something, or was being lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the exact meaning of "Kazhuthai ketta kuttichevuru"? (Serious question) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my heard my paati say this enough times, but in different contexts. So I am still not sure what this means. The literal translation makes no sense. Did the mods name this sub after this adage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of us must learn and respect other Indian languages: PM Narendra Modis message at Sardar Patel exhibition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diwali at the Oval Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Scandal Too Far? Huma Abedin, Hillary Clinton, and a Test of Loyalty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I look at Deepavali, it is about having the maximum fun as possible on such an auspicious day. I had a swell time with the family and extended family, ate great breakfast, a very meaty and great lunch, started drinking with my crazy cousins in the afternoon, and drunk as fuck now. Hope everybody on this sub has a great Deepavali, since I recognize most of the regulars here cos I have been on Reddit right from the beginning(with a different account), when I was in school and Reddit didn't even have subs. Diwali is over for me now, and I hope all you dudes up north have as much fun tomorrow as I did today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy [ ](http://i.imgur.com/a7bpWJy.jpg) to you too.

Don't think we have to shorten Deepavali just because the chapati munchers do so. Anyways, the word (Deepavali) itself probably has a Sanskrit origin and is not from 'deepa oli'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottoman Turkey was were absorbent bath towels were first made and used. These were exactly the kind we call a turkey towel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the Tatas had no money to pay Pallonji family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/hWlNCzG5GaE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bear hug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pakistani Policeman Slaps Woman Reporter During Live Broadcast In Karachi](http://m.huffingtonpost.in/2016/10/21/watch-pakistani-policeman-slaps-female-karachi-reporter-during/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistani policeman vs TV reporter (watch till the end) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay, let's dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Okay, let's dance" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come closer.....closer... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squirrel plucks around with a peacock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delhi lawyers unaccounted Rs 125 crore income stuns taxmen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 07:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kerala man is key Islamic State 'recruiter' luring Indian volunteers to Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full video](https://youtu.be/X9p56wSzsPA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lion sneaks up on a leopard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is so full off Maoist bullshit, I thought I was reading The Hindu for a second. There are some disadvantages to banning Chinese imports, like cheaper industrial machinery, telecom equipment, solar panels, etc. But most of this cheaper prices is due to overproduction fueled by over investment there. These cheaper prices are not going to last forever, maybe 2-3 years max.

The bulk of the imports like cheap phones, tvs, other electronics, toys, fireworks, etc can be manufactured at a slightly higher cost here, but would give a fillip to 'Make in India', which is very desirable in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 09:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here you go](https://youtu.be/zAXz-33QQU8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Eastern brown snake](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_brown_snake) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Eastern brown snake](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_brown_snake) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Back off" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Back off" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shower time for kitty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spot the guilty one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hailing a bus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another comment below says they look like guy wires, not power lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A crane collapsed in Odessa, Ukraine. The driver wasn't hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Was put up in Surat](http://indianexpress.com/article/india/india-news-india/surat-rally-kejriwal-banner-osama-hafiz-saeed-burhan-wani-pakistan-hero-election-aap-bjp-3081630/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You shall not pass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB, while I open it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
