<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So?

The article also says

President Trump on Saturday called for NBC News to devote more attention to his unproven claims that President Obama spied on him and stop covering the investigations into Russias interference in the election

Either way Trump is asking or telling NBC News to do something because he's a little bitch about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it do?

@NBCNews...stop with the Fake Trump/Russia story

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not exclusive video of what Trump be like](http://i.imgur.com/sZbdwpO.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think i'll use that one next after i get the 20 headshot on the m18 optical for the ribeyesteakrolley. The slug version is 50 kills for another assault gun i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spent all day working on getting that cogwheel club. So i had to get creative with my melee  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   And the reality TV star he works for

Congress does not work for the President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet somehow Boris Johnson still looks to be the most out of place person there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Proof](http://i.imgur.com/uKlAens.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be a disappointing movie knowing that in real life he is like six foot eight and the actor that plays him isn't going to be anywhere close to that I imagine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going out clubbing in Fort Vaux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adam Schiff heads to his future house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since he came to washington work it at the DIA he's been a moron by all accounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously we all know the Republican's first swing at healthcare failed horrendously. Based off of comments from politicians they seem to be signalling they will be moving on to ~~impeachment~~ tax reform and infrastructure. Personally as somebody who lives and works in NY i think infrastructure in America, at least the north east corridor could use a pick-me up. Whether or not that gets done in a manner in which the work is done properly and the cash not pocketed by organizations or companies remains to be seen. As does President's Trump much talked about Trillion dollar infrastructure plan. So basically at the heart of the issue, moving from healthcare to tax reform and/or infrastructure do you find the fact that the GOP is effectively putting Healthcare on the back burner and moving on as their attempt to distract from the fact that in 1998 the Undertaker threw Mankind off Hell In A Cell and plummeted 16ft through an announcer's table. I feel as though healthcare oughta be a important issue given that fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dan Scvaino is also Trump social media director. He is the guy who gets dictated to and tweets for Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair there is nothing fake about this.

The headline clearly states (RUMORS)

The article references 3 tweets most notably this one

https://twitter.com/WestWingReport/status/847635937995612160

Which specfically mentions Michael Steele former RNC Chair.

https://twitter.com/MichaelSteele

Which is from the twitter page for this report Paul Brandus

http://westwingreports.com/about/

I mean the information this guy claims Steele told him is easily verifiable because Steele is a public figure, on CNN. This Brandus fellow is in the WH Press Corp.

It's outlandish yes, but nothing here is being presented as anything but rumor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the domain.

Shareblue is owned by David Brock I believe.

The Donald subreddit calls it Shariablue because they are morons.

Think of it as a website right wingers see as what liberals or anybody with a working brain sees Breitbart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Click A or Z to up/down vote when the arrows are hidden, i believe this works if you have RES, i'm not sure if it works otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never play as Assault but I decided to pick up the shotgun and found a reason to start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a simple explainer on the google US homepage and you've instantly put it in front tens of, if not hundreds of millions of Americans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WRONG.

Nunes answers to Paul Ryan and Nunes' consitutent.

He doesn't answer to the President. He doesn't serve at the pleasure of the President. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got double-down syndrome.

There is no cure :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are playing ping-pong with the corpse of Trump's presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be funny if they subpeona'd the children who mod that subreddit to come before the committee and talk about what they did and saw as leaders of the largest pro Trump site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the metric system!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it you little bitch.

I will be in the audience for that court hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What horrible color choices for that line chart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ronald Reagan

Old white man slowing losing his mind?

Somemight say Bernie Sanders come 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So just so i understand because i'm new to the game and well new to gaming in general again, i stopped for like 7 years after high school.

Attacker Howitzer,

Thats the cannon in the forest 1st sector the attackers use?

 Reduced Elite kits respawn time from 30 sek to 0 Verdun Heights

1. The elite kits respawn? lol

2. Those are the ones at the start of the 2nd sector for attackers? Right. 

3. This means if i die as trench raider it will automatically be back in it's box when i die, more or less but just for conequest not operations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thx bae </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?

Yes really. I didnt say Gorkov is or was a spy just that he went to the russian spy school.

I believe I missed typed in my previous comment that made it seem like i said there was no proof. I apologize.

Also you may want to take a peak at my link about the FSB. They do have schools which are claimed to be non-government focused.

Okay, fine. Personally I cannot find anything in that wikipage so if you can point out specfically where that would be nice.

How can I link to proof if even you agree there isn't any? but the proof that supports our educated guesses is classified.

But there is proof. His biography from Sberbank and VEB Bank both say


In 1994, he graduated from the Academy of the Federal Security Service of Russia with a specialization in Law.


Okay so what is Academy of the Federal Security Service of Russia. Well that is Russian spy school, that is The FSB Academy. The school the trains and schools people to work in the Federal Security Service of Russia as well as other Russian intel organizations.

Here they have a website

http://www.academy.fsb.ru/index.html

I mean for crying out loud it used to be called "The [Russian name] Higher School of the KGB" We all know what the KGB is most famous for being? Russian spies. 

The school Sergey Gorkov went to is the Russian Spy School. It can't be anymore clear. Whether he went on to work as a Russian spy in the financial world remains to be seen but let us not pretend he didn't just got to some run of the miller place of higher learning in Russia.

 Is there proof that the school was in fact a spy school 

Yes there is. Just look into the school itself, everything i've posted from the articles to the website for the dang school.

Gorkov was a spy

Nobody said he was a spy just that he went to school you go to to become one, to receive that type of training. 

Was there anything from stopping you from posting? Why are you, a random internet stranger, in a position to tell me, another random internet stranger, what to post? There are two people who can tell me what to do. You neither gave me birth nor do you let me fuck you doggy-style on Wednesday nights.Basically - don't tell me what to do. You're not my real dad.

Furthermore, all this bullshit. I don't know why you are acting like such a snowflake over it.

I was trying to help back up your claim Gorkov was FSB trained, showing proof that he was since he went to that school.

I was trying to explain it's far more useful to link to the proof he went to such school than linking to something that does not show the banker did what he did.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is no unclassified "proof" that Gorkov is a spy

I didn't say there was. I also never said he was a spy. In fact, nobody here said he was. Not I, not Rachel Maddow, not any of the articles i linked to state that i believe. Just you. 

So let me be very clear in restating, Sergey Gorkov went to the Russian spy school for schooling. Period, fact. Source? His biography of himself from the bank he was the deputy chairman at.

What I did say was this:

It makes more sense to link to proof that Gorkov went to FSB spy school or the Maddow segment when she discusses this instead of the FSB wikipage

What I also asked you to do is instead of linking to the wiki-page for the FSB is that it makes more sense to link to link to proof that somebody is FSB trained, proof that somebody went to the Russian spy school instead of just a link to the wikipedia page for the FSB as background information. Okay, background information is nice but that's literally burying the lead.

Making a claim that Kushner met with FSB trained banker and then choosing not to link to proof or a citation that said banker is "FSB trained" or "went to Russian spy school" is a poor thing to do.

The point is the proof is there. It was stupid of you to not include such proof in your "fixed" comment that really didn't fix anything but raise more questions to anybody who is not abreast to the situation or the nature of Sergey Gorkov/Jared Kushner situation
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon me but this will make you look rather silly.

If this information is so classified why does it literally say Sergey Gorkov graduated the Academy of the Federal Security Service of Russia aka Russian Spy School in his biography on the bank he was employed?

https://www.sberbank.ru/en/about/about_sberbank/sb_management/board_members/sgorkov

I've also included a number of news reports saying how Gorkov graduated Russian spy school. You should add them to your comment as proof instead of a useless like to the FSB wikipage.


http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/27/politics

http://foreignpolicy.com/2017/03/


http://www.businessinsider.com/jared-kushner-russia-vnesheconombank

 
So in closing I'd like to say I proved a Russian banker Jared Kushner met with with a direct Russian source and I don't even work for the intelligence community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes more sense to link to proof that Gorkov went to FSB spy school or the Maddow segment when she discusses this instead of the FSB wikipage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay maybe I just I don't understand now. You just said Source E was this Oleg guy and now you say it's not him.

What's going on here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if Source E is Oleg why are people saying is Boris Epsthyn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't Oleg be source E? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well one of the Sources, Oleg Erovinkin, was shot in the head.


People recently have been theorizing Epshteyn is Source E

The dead Russian with an E last name isn't "Source E" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've won and lost all sectors on Verdun multiple times on Xbox One. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kennedy Law
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suddenly i am in favor of this bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerrymandering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because voting for somebody because they should have federal funding is a pity vote.

Not voting for them on policy. Voting for that reason.

That is pity.

If no candidate represents you as well as you feel then just don't vote. I've done that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voting for a 3rd party for the reason that "they should have federal funding" is voting out of pity. Voting that you feel sorry for them not having the same opportunity as the 2 political parties who have supporters. 

I see that just existing as a 3rd party does not make them deserve federal funding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voting for the Green Party is always waste if they don't actually earn your vote.

Voting out of pity for a 3rd party is stupid.

Voting in the hopes of them getting federal funding is stupid.

I don't vote for parties that either 

A) Don't represent me

or 

B) The candidate hasn't earned my vote or I agree with him/her enough to vote for them.

It seemed like a lot of redditors, or a good number voted out of pity for the 3rd parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York:

Gary rhymes with Barry

Gary and Barry do not rhyme with Berry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada is talking about abolishing the Senate?

They cannot abolish me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sound of the G in Gary but the -rry from Berry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact Alert:

Gerrymander is named after Elbridge Gerry who last name is not Gerry like Jerry.

But Gerry like Berry, with a harder G sound instead of the Jerry sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottawa MP's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kek    -----this one

kek

kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats how the Senate vs House has always felt IMO.

You want a "prestigious" job in government as an elected official, you become a Senator not a Representative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the purpose of this feature? I'm not sure i understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Serious Seven

The Intelligent Seven

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Okay. Check my history. 

Why would anybody check your post history?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the OPM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DRILL BABY DRILL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A meeting between the Secretary of State and a Democratic Senator.

Seems pretty clear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even experts can be biased

There is no bias in the facts saying coal jobs aren't coming back. There is no reason to have to explain backstory for who is saying this when the facts and trends show they are not coming back.


Assuming the folks at IEEFA are experts, 

There is no assumption.

they have already declared their beliefs about this issue.

Because they are experts presumably know what is correct based off of their data, facts and interpretations of what is happening in the industry they are experts in.


You are making an issue where there is none just to cause a huff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you attempting to attack and remove credibility from the source instead of proving the data to be wrong?

Oh, that is because the data is correct. Coal isn't coming back and all that can be done is make it seem like those who are saying so are doing it out of a desire to put those people out of work out of spite or some bull.

They are "experts"

No, they are experts.

have every incentive to spin data to fit their pre-reached conclusions.

Having incentive and actually doing something are not the same.

Facts are facts. Coal jobs aren't coming back. That is not spin. That is fact.

This calls into questions any so-called "facts" that they deduce.

No it doesn't.

What is calls into question is your innate inability to see factual trends as just that facts and trends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woman drove her car past police and wouldn't stop.

I believe it was police that discharged their weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facts are facts regardless of agenda.

The "experts"

Also not sure why you keep putting that in quotes. They are experts, period.

It's not fake, they aren't so-called. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like that ship has passed the pointing of sinking and is already sunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nor do cows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it would go to the supreme court.

They are public officials and if its non-classified they can't hide it say through FOIA requests if done on their work computers.

As far as what they do on their private devices that should be under the same legislation as you or I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing a FOIA request doesn't fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

LOCK THEM UP

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many guys it take to nail him to the cross and roll a boulder in front of a cave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yall know this ain't ever gonna happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you keep changing the subject?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean shills?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Manafort? 

No we will have border Patrol man a wall but forts are not in the budget </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bookmark this website

https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/congress-trump-score/votes/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What blows my mind is rush hour in the morning.

Everybody is walking up the left and standing to the right.

Then somebody gets on the left and doesn't walk up. Like are you fucking oblivious or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sally Yates will be the Frost to Trump's Nixon and make him look like a complete and utter moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bigly if true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send a Fax to the House Speaker's Office and let him know otherwise

Website: https://faxzero.com/

Fax #:(202) 225-2012


http://www.speaker.gov/contact
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing weird about this WH claiming something negative about them is false.

I have no reason to believe the WH is telling the truth about this much like they claim to tell the truth about anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And of course the WH is saying it's totally fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deputy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a conservative and want your opinions reaffirmed you watch Fox News. 

If you are a young liberal and need your opinions reaffirmed you watch The Young Turks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. He's jealous. Clinton's have power, influence, impact on the world and history. 

Trump has 140 characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was born in this country

I haven't seen his birth certificate.

and is not a Muslim?

This doesn't look like a guy who is a church going Christian.

https://i.redd.it/z6gok0adydjx.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will also dictate tweets to his WH Director of Social Media Dan Scavino </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the same reason she got 3 million illegal voters to vote for her in states that didn't matter to the election.

She's playing 38DD Chess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antonin Scalia has more stamina than Rex Tillerson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so the meeting isn't cancelled.

Nunes just wasn't invited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you can explain why Trey Gowdy could be named chairman? Sure he's on the committee and chaired Benghazi but there are far more senior Republicans already on the committee, why him?

Pete King chaired Homeland Security and is far more senior than Gowdy, I think it would make more sense for it to be him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've already explain how what OP said comes across at sounding like it is definitive as if sourced from news report. OP seems to want to harp more on that, i've explained it multiple times.

I am still waiting to find out why do you [OP] comes to that conclusion Trey Gowdy could be named chairman? Sure he's on the committee and chaired Benghazi but there are far more senior Republicans already on the committee, why him?

Pete King chaired Homeland Security and is far more senior than Gowdy, I think it would make more sense for it to be him.

I will continue to ask this question until i get a goddamn straight answer. Sharing your opinion should not be fucking difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd that the people say Gordy would be chairmen but so far not a single definitive answer why from those folks. 

Smells like a load of bullishit. 

I never knew such a simple question was so hard for little to answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stiff For Schiff 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do you come to that conclusion that Trey Gowdy could be named chairman? Sure he's on the committee and chaired Benghazi but there are far more senior Republicans already on the committee, why him? 

Pete King chaired Homeland Security and is far more senior than Gowdy, I think it would make more sense for it to be him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the Producers that brought you *Band of Brothers* comes a thrilling new story...*Hellfighters*.

*"The harrowing tale of those African Americans soldiers whose heroic actions and sacrifices during the great war were nearly forgotten...until now"*

Starring Idris Elba, Donald Glover, Anthony Mackie, Mike Colter, Mahershala Ali, Erik LaRay Harvey, Michael K. Williams and Paul Giamatti.

Coming To Netflix 2018 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do you come to that conclusion that Trey Gowdy could be named chairman?

There are far more senior Republicans already on the committee, why him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the context in which you used "Gowdy would be put in charge" does that sound like speculation to me. It sounded like you  based your comment as a fact from a news report.


I don't understand why you are acting like such a a snowflake over the word "conclusion" so much so that you cannot answer what is a horribly simple question. It shouldn't be pulling fucking teeth for what is supposedly you god damn opinion.

For the third time now i will ask:

"how do you come to that conclusion?" that Trey Gowdy ~~would be~~ ~~could be~~ maybe be Chairman if House Intel?

Is that okay? I'm trying not to offend your horrible delicate sensitives over this query. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you claim you said

I said I would be 'concerned' if Gowdy was put in charge.

---

What you said

The one thing that concerns me is that even bigger POS Gowdy would be put in charge.

--------------

Do you not understand the difference between "WOULD BE" and "IF HE WAS" ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Curious how adamant you are on mischaracterizing what I said.

Because you don't get it, you aren't saying the same thing you did. You are the only person characterizing what you said.

I said I would be 'concerned' if Gowdy was put in charge.

Yes and no. You said you would be concerned but what you said is that

**Gowdy would be put in charge.**

Not if. But would be.

There is a difference between what you literally said and what you are now claiming you said, using the word "If". "If he was put in charge" and "Would be put in charge" are sentences with different implications for the reader.

"Would be put in charge" sounds like it's already a done deal some how. This is why i asked, why i continue to ask, how did you come to that conclusion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was on the Transition team so Gowdy is out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gowdy would be put in charge.

Saying Gowdy would be put in charge if Nunes is removed from the House Intel committee is a lot stronger than a speculation, you are claiming this to be a strong possibility.

I ask again on what grounds did you reach that conclusion that Gowdy would be named House Intel Chair over any other Republican currently on the committee?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it wouldn't generate any waves?

No i said it wouldn't have huge political implications.

 It would be one of the biggest news stories this year

No, it would not be one of the biggest news stories this year. The chairman of the house intel committee resigning because he acted inappropriately is no where near being the biggest story of the year.

We both know exactly how this will spin. He would understand his error, still claim that the information he discussed was unrelated but didn't want to appear partisan until proven otherwise.

We can talk about what we think he did but thats all unknown.

What we do know is he acted inappropriately as chairman and was on the transition. Given the outrage of his actions he would resign under the guise of not wanting to be partisan.

We dont know with what information did he act, with whom he discussed. We don't know a lot about what happened, it's just it looks really bad.

But lets not pretend like this would be some canary in the mine situation because it's not and would never be spun that way by the GOP.


Further, it would basically confirm theres real teeth to this investigation and that the GOP candidate won the presidency with Russian assistance totally delegitimizing him.

What? No it wouldn't lol how on earth do you come to that ridiculous conclusion, that sounds more like an anti-dream than logical reality.

It would just confirm the chairman acted like an idiot without thinking, even if the information he said he discussed was irrelevant. It doesn't confirm anything other than Nunes not having any foresight and being an utter moron.

I think it would be a part of the biggest story but Nunes alone being one of the biggest stories of the year is hyperbole.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the Winning Trump talked about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There would be huge political implications if he resigns

lol what?

No there isn't, there wouldn't be. The only implication is that he acted inappropriately as chairman.

Him resigning or being taken from his chairmanship wouldn't be some huge political revelation. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gowdy would be put in charge.

how do you come to that conclusion?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the Senate Minority Leader, that means a bit more than any other Democratic Senator.

I think Nunes will resign in the coming days or week or two. They just need a way to do it so he doesn't look like the biggest fucknut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the election was valid, at least the only part that matters in the validity of the election, the actual and physically voting. Votes were not changed or faked or anything like that.

The spread of misinformation to sway the minds of voters is one thing and i think a very different action and issue than the changing or faking of votes. But that action as taken by a foreign government doesn't invalidate the votes of the people IMO.

I think the best way to phrases it is Russia meddled in the presidential campaigns but not the physical election of Trump via vote meddling. 

This is not to say what Russia did by the spread of misinformation, false facts, fake news and such isn't a big issue or anything, it's just one i dont think constitutes an invalid election or constitutional crisis. Just a crisis of a different kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay and so what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There isn't really any example of how to proceed if an entire elected administration and cabinet is under suspicion

But thats not what is happening here now is it.

Only a select few are.

You remove Trump, Pence and Paul Ryan the President will be Sen Orrin Hatch.

He's not under suspicion of anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's sort of a constitutional gray area.

Its not.

There is a constitutional line of succession for when the President is taken out of office and so on down the line. 

You follow that through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or we don't coddle the President like a fucking dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I mean, is there any situation in where the election results would be voided/changed?

No, the constitution lays out an order of succession that needs to be followed.

Trump leaves and you get Pence, he goes and it's Paul Ryan and so on and so forth down the list until you get to somebody that is not guilty of an impeachable crime or is impeached.

You don't remove the President and immediately jump into making a constitutional crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   hates shaking hands etc.

Is that why he tries to rip peoples arms off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between Adam Schiff and Devin Nunes, only one of them grew up on a farm in California, studied agriculture business in college and is a climate change fact denier. 

The other is a former Prosecutor for the US Attorney's Office, Stanford and Harvard educated lawyer and political science degree holder and not a fucking moron.

I'm not saying that being a farm boy is a bad thing but between these to the level of intellect or at least the difference in ability in being a publicly elected policymaker and representative of the people is fucking massive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ex-obama speech writer and BEST FRIEND OF THE POD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Manhattan Billionaire doing battle with the Brooklyn Jew over taxes is like the financial political WrestleMania.

Can't fuck with Chuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were in Congress and you can't come up with a idea you fucking moron? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally i've used it to get on the defensive side in an Operations game to finish a task for a medal/unlock a weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jeez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on XBOX One

How do you folks make gifs or gifvs on Xbox One?

Really, i just dont know how to do it for any game. I only recently got an Xbox One after stopping playing XBOX 360 basically during college so i'm practically brand new to the xbox once again having fallen out of the loops for 4 to 6 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   assault tank

I believe that is the new St Chamond tank that is only available to spawn into if you have the DLC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody wanna tell him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> W I S E B O Y E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got mine last night defending the first sector on Verdun Heights Operation.

Probably suggest the same or Frontline. Gives you plenty of time and time and room to bang it out real quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike Trump aides, Clinton aides aren't fucking morons.

You don't offer up information for no reason. You don't volunteer to do things that could implicate you in later crimes or anything like that.

You don't speak until you are legally required to do so.

This is the difference between lawyers and moronic "businessmen" like Paul Manafort, Roger Stone and Carter Page. 

Even if you have nothing to hide, you don't give an open invitation to the people who will be deciding if you did something wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here i thought whydontyoutrythis.com would be reliable for news.

heh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When and where,

during the campaign and the transition.

It was big news when Woolsey abrutly quit.

He's a war hawk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you should try harder to repeal a law that an entire political party spent years working on, years trying to get it passed.

Fucking simpleton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrat Jon Ossoff and FRIEND OF THE POD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
