<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So empirialism

I think you mean *imperialism*.

I suppose that's exactly what I'm advocating. Only instead of Canadian colonies, it would be charters of a world constitution held by a world citizenry.

Old imperialism, and even 'new imperialsm' of the 20th century with foreign military bases all over the world were conducted prior to Little Brother and the capacity for people to record abuse of an oppressive powers and organize protest and resistance like the Arab Spring. The problem with these movements pulling down their oppressive governments, or getting rid of foreign military authorities is that it creates a power vacuum similar to what I discussed in my previous post when western powers try to pull out after 'Nation Building'.

However, if there was a world civilization charter and constitution with just laws, courts, and trade. Devised academically and crowdsourced to have wide input and shared interest rather than special interest. It would offer an alternative option for peoples of the world to demand and implement.

A franchised federation of fair government.

So yes, it's imperial, but it would largely be opt-in, self-implemented, and only executed by force in instances of extreme abuse of populations and corruption.

Any system will tend toward corruption, and traditional political models have only been accepted for their stability more than their effectiveness. However, the models for fair and equitable society and government are available to design and implement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 15:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All excellent examples of places where problems are acknowledged, but no outside action is taken because there's a feeling that either it's not worth it, or the consequences of action will just make the problem worse, like in Iraq right now. 

 Why Syria and Iran? Why is it a military problem?

Going to assume you meant Iraq, though there was plenty of sabre-rattling to invade Iran fairly recently too.

The problem as I see it is that the model of toppling a government through military invasion, followed by occupation, and then leaving a friendly government behind while pulling out doesn't work. It's failing now in both Afghanistan with the Taliban and Iraq with ISIS. You could make similar arguments for Hamas taking over in Gaza, though that was a democratic election.

Ultimately, these were/are expensive, drawn-out conflicts by western powers that are now blowing up in their faces.

I would propose that this is only going half way, and a permanent solution means a permanent occupation. However, this is impossibly expensive to achieve by a single country and also an injustice for one nation to take this action against another.

I would suggest it is not an injustice for the world to take such an action, however. I would like to see the formation of a world government, legal system, with police and courts, and an international military. Further, I would like see this international body gradually take over and remain a permanent fixture in small oppressive and/or corrupt states annexing them and introducing education, law, order, stable development of food, trade, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 02:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why do we have to do anything? 

With great power comes great responsibility. Allowing the world to descend into chaos because of the inconvenience of action is not a solution that will benefit us in the long run.

I don't mean to suggest that that action should be a prolonged conflict of half-measures. However, to do *nothing* could lead to a snowballing of conflicts that we will someday show up on our doorstep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 00:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a good review of some of the broader economic effects on [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Effects_of_the_April_2010_Eyjafjallaj%C3%B6kull_eruption#Economic_impacts) from the 2010 eruption. For the new eruption that might accompany all the recently reported seismic activity:

www.vox.com/2014/8/20/6049241/bardarbunga-volcano-iceland-air-travel

What are some predictable outcomes that might not have been corrected from last time?

Apparently New Zealand salmon did very well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the potential volcanic eruption in Iceland of Bardarbunga fast approaching, what were some interesting market trends after the 2010 eruption of Eyjafjallajkull that caused enormous disruption to air travel across western and northern Europe over an initial period of six days? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 23:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 11:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...this is the first government in our social media age.

First *Canadian* government. The Americans are much freer with the communications of their scientists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing the deleted comment would defeat the purpose of removing it. It's better to focus on the real content and arguments. The mods take freedom of opinion very seriously, but failure to communicate one's views in a constructive manner can't be tolerated if we want to keep this community as a safe place for real political discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada-EU trade deal text leaked ahead of fall summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama calls Stephen Harper to discuss Iraq crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 05:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 13:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The latest reports had it back below the safe level though.

I'd be curious whether any damage to the structure might have occurred while they were operating above prescribed limits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 00:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize BC had successfully dropped their income taxes, that's a nice little stat they can boast over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 17:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing Dion in real life, he quickly became one of my favorite Liberals. He's like Clark Kent most of the time, mild mannered, not grabbing attention. Then all of a sudden, he's superman passionately shouting into a mic you didn't even see him line up to use. I'm glad I got to see both sides and not just how he was smeared on TV. Politics is a bloodsport, but it's such a shame how things went down for him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 17:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peacekeeping (which I agree, should be our mandate) still requires a budget, well-trained personnel, equipment, etc. Keeping a well outfitted military has several advantages beyond jingoism and reckless international adventuring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 02:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Never has been...

Until the techno-autocratic reign of Dangerman the first, may he live until the heat death of the universe
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 02:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you support me, I'll make sure you get your own mechanized mobile-suit, and possibly a story arc involving a pop diva and conflict with ETs.

You might also be put in charge of trying to take me down after I become mad with power.

Aside from that, just devoting larger economic resources to science, research, development, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 19:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you got it right, I just checked the wikipedia article about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 18:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks fun, I think I'll give it a look.

I think my favourite body-switching was actually [Lord of Light](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lord_of_Light) by Roger Zelazny (classic hugo winner from '67).  Set in the future, a colony ship called the Star of India settles some random planet and the original settlers set themselves up as gods, taking the identities of the original Hindu pantheon over all their subsequent progeny.  Karma and reincarnation actually become literal plot devices.  Very bizarre and entertaining read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If by son, you mean the most intelligent and feared from amongst my hundreds of genetically enhanced clones raised in Canada's new space station in low-earth orbit (I convince Elon Musk to develop a space program in Canada in exchange for dominion over Mars), then no. I will remain Shogun until the heat death of the universe (re: immortality via anti-aging or some body-switching mechanism). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 18:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naturally a large portion of the GDP will then be devoted to scientific research and development, particularly biotechnology and anti-aging research such that I can achieve some measure of immortality, allowing for my scientist junta to rule in perpetuity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 18:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the whole of human history, democracy is admittedly a pretty great development. However, the fact that so many take it for granted and don't even bother to vote, or that large parts of the voting population are swayed by populist rhetoric makes me want to enslave humanity, name myself shogun and implement a semi-fascist technocratic oligarchy.

Keep pushing Toronto... See what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 15:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instant run-off ranked ballots would be a fairer and more realistic solution than suggesting some group of parties should collude together to the exclusion of another party to win ridings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 15:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys are definitely my favourite Calgary band.  Caught their show at Sled Island a few years back and was floored.  Really awesome live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 13:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dr. Hroux, thanks for being here.

I'm a PhD student working a lot with NMR. My spectroscope is shielded, but it's rated at 600MHz (14.1Tesla). Often I have to shove my head near the probe to make fine manual adjustments. 

Physiologically, what sort of effects might I be concerned about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 05:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm not convinced these numbers are statistically significant or not correlating with other trends. The fact that declined ballots increased across most ridings is significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 18:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... Gary Oldman... Spoilers, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 05:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why he didn't cast Ellar Coltrane (the boy in Boyhood) as Ethan Hawke's son in Before Midnight... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 23:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He uses the word twice, so it wasn't just offhand, but I've never heard the expression used before, in Calgary or elsewhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Park Lights (Ontario Canada) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 13:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Park Lights (Ontario, Canada) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 13:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 02:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be a good transition politically... Allows the ONDP to shuffle after the last election, plus the chance to make a big difference in her home community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 18:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of mention of Alberta in the comments so far, but if you're interested in job security, a good option is Saskatchewan; [unemployment rate of 3.6%](http://www.stats.gov.sk.ca/)

It's a little flat, but you can learn to appreciate the Roughriders.  Pretty good upward mobility. 

That being said, if there's one thing I've learned since finishing school (and I did the whole move out to Alberta, got a high-paying job gig for a while) it's that it's better not to rely on an arbitrary job for personal intellectual fulfillment or security.  It sounds like you want to start a family, so your priorities are probably different, but I'd encourage you to think about doing something new and different than the established pattern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researches in India have verified that barbecuing meat produces graphene oxide and other carbon nanoparticles, and concluded that, as man has been happily eating these nanomaterials since the discovery of fire, they are non-toxic to humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 22:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 01:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grey-matter back gotta perform us down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Replacing cadmium chloride with cheap magnesium chloride could reduce the cost and environmental impact of thin film solar cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 05:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 22:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be a clever way to encourage innovation within the bureaucracy, I like it.  Determination of savings might need to be made by an auditor external to the department, but that's already part of standard operation I believe.

Can I coin the term **'micro-bonuses'**?  

This would even be appropriate in larger private organizations.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 22:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 18:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think they're doing this one as a bit of a pilot project, but I wouldn't mind some analysis at the federal level to determine the best new format for these public institutions.

Case in point, [China is opening a hundred such institutions, apparently](http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702303722604579111253495145952).  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 04:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as an experiment, I'd like to sit down with you and get you to play DayZ for a while, and then revisit this scenario.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 04:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually really like these. Though I'm not certain I'd allow mayors to be a single voice in building a short-list of nominees (I live near Toronto after all). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 03:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pourquoi?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 02:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nearly did, but I couldn't quite figure out a good way to fit a semi-fascist technocratic oligarchy into the current model... Maybe replace the senate that way? :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 00:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CBC could televise it like a reality TV show.  The new MPs could start trying to form 'alliances' with each new season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 00:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, if any of them do a good job and want to continue on, they might be decide to run again for the next term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 00:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That parliamentary tradition could change

It's funny, because if Jean had said 'no' she effectively would have changed parliamentary tradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think it would be interesting if every session of parliament you randomly dropped 34 people of unknown political alignment or background into the house to shake things up a little.  One could argue that our system of government is unfairly biased towards the selection of politicians to government.

Also, you have to admit, if you got a visit from a representative of the RCMP one day who informed you that you had been selected to sit in the house of commons for a term, you'd be pretty stoked, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Firmly separate the Government of Canada from the Parliament.

Government of Canada *bureaucracy*, careful what you ask the genie, or we'll have to outsource the government back to England.  Though I totally support removing the capability to politicize the civil service and the RCMP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And is this a Canadian genie, or is it foreign owned? That matters to me.

Maybe instead of a genie it's a relic of a native tribe containing a trickster spirit and the system was never made to affect 30+ million people, but now the opportunity is here...

Second, we've gotta clean up these archives, there's dusty boxes and lamps on the floor, i'm tripping all over shit in here!

There was some talk of digitizing the genie and closing the archives, but there's not a lot of certainty about what's really happening there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Change the selection process of the governor general and lieutenant governor generals, such that they are selected from a body of representatives at the quasi-municipal level of government: mayors, rural reps, and first nations reps, etc. through a series of run-off ranked ballots.  Then allow them to exercise their veto power.

2. Create a special federal court beneath the Supreme Court of Canada of 5 justices to examine the constitutional legality of any new legislation. This court will examine challenges brought by the opposition (with controls in place so the opposition cannot simply challenge everything).  Similar courts of 3 justices at the provincial level.

3. Award 10% of the seats in both the commons and the senate, as well as provincial legislatures, on the basis of a lottery. ([Demarchy](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Demarchy))

Adding extra backup wishes in case I can wish for more wishes, or take the lamp to my grandma and get her to wish:

4. This one is just me being goofy, but still: Introduce a special technocratic shadow branch of government bureaucracy with a black budget in charge of Canada's espionage and merge it with the the National Research Council to fund a series of 'mad' science projects domestically, with the mandate of improving and safe-guarding Canadian quality of life and increasing our global influence.

5. Make the public school system run year-round, however take some of the added time and put it towards applied-learning programs where students visit national parks, science labs, public-infrastructure locations, governments, etc. to get a better perspective on roles/functions in society.  

6. Begin transitioning public libraries towards becoming technology spots and [hackerspaces](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hackerspace) to encourage invention and entrepreneurship.  It's crazy how much space opens up when you don't have to house tons of physical books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please share a change you would propose to Canada's political system that is not often mentioned on this sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding yourself in an obscure archives near parliament hill, you accidentally trip and collide with a stack of dusty boxes spilling what looks like a genie's magic lamp on the floor (or maybe a relic of a native tribe containing a trickster spirit; alignment chaotic neutral?). Picking up the lamp (relic) and going ahead and rubbing it for fun, out pops the genie (spirit) of Canadian political science.  The genie offers to fulfill any 3 wishes specifically pertaining to changing the governing political and legal mechanisms of Canada (all three branches).

What are three changes that you would propose?

Please share some novel ideas.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 16:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point I was more trying to make is that it's wrong to point the finger at Mackay, like he's some kind of symbol of gender discrimination in Canadian society, rather than the victim of a slow news week.

(While being sensitive to the fact that gender discrimination remains a real problem) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 16:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether or not this is true, I think it's important to acknowledge that our culture possesses gender biases, regardless of the gender of individuals, and that it's important as a progressive society to work together to overcome these.  However, I'd like to see more positive encouragement of gender equality, and less negative finger-pointing gotcha non-news-story nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter MacKay says controversial Mothers and Fathers Day emails written by female staffer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 16:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 23:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might not start out that way, but it could easily devolve into a circus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 10:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of starting a whole new political party, you might have more luck starting up a 'faction' or special interest within an existing party that's already somewhat compatible with your ideals.  

Also, it sounds like you have a lot of concern about fiscal transparency rather than 'futurism', so you might want to consider alternative branding.  Otherwise, you need something more novel than an expensive website that very few people are likely to want to look at to grab positive attention for 'futurism'.  

I always thought it would be interesting if a government programs could be run through a quasi-crowdsourcing model, where gov't programs/policy could be advertized like kickstarter campaigns, and adoption to an extent would be based on the popularity of their online support.  If you wanted to be really radical, you could let people direct a portion of their taxable incomes to the programs and goods that they want to support, so that people don't feel like their money is wasted, it goes exactly where they wanted it to (well, at least a portion, hard to get people excited about a new sewage treatment facility, however much a new one is needed...). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 04:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it first hand... You see a whole group built up over decades and then suddenly the ship's going down.  Researcher's already getting offered more money down in the states pick up and head to better labs... 

Some of the alternative funding programs that have been introduced like NSERC-Engage, I'm not sure if I fully support or not.  On one hand, it's a source of research funding, and helps build relationships with industry.  On another though, there's very little that can be completed in 6 months with that money, and I haven't seen any examples of companies putting in their own R D money afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 00:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea of decoupling pure research and applied R D in the form of targeted institutes and pilot facilities.  Canada has had this in the past (and continues to) through various NRC labs and institutes, but funding/mandates shift from one political administration to another and these institutes wax and wane in their ability and personnel to perform high value R D... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the pension board wholely independent? I had figured this program as being more of a means to provide an extra pool of money for the gov to tap in to for projects etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 19:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably misunderstanding how the program works. However, this new pension fund will mean a large new source of revenue for the Ontario government. Apart from paying out pensions, are the funds also available for them to make investments in the Ontario economy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 18:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is having a sizable pension fund for the Ontario gov to work with an asset at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 17:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be relatively easy to test, just give a sample of the population a holiday for election day and see if they vote... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 05:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Seat Count:**

* PC 42
* OLP 47
* NDP 18
* Green 0

**Percentage:**

* PC 37%
* OLP 39%
* NDP 19%
* Green 5% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 01:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be averse to awarding a portion of the seats in a legislature by lottery to accomplish this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C) Occasionally-violent disobedience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 08:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ruby Tuesday by the Rolling Stones](http://youtu.be/NW2eL8qWIvI) was incorporated into the [Royal Tenenbaums (2002)](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0265666/) pretty brilliantly by Wes Anderson.  In order to introduce the track, he first plays [She Smiles Sweetly](http://youtu.be/hlEatlyMv4Q), from the same album.  

Cameron Crowe picked it as his [#9 favourite music moments in film](http://www.empireonline.com/features/cameron-crowe-music-moments), saying: 

*"When "She Smiled Sweetly" flows into "Ruby Tuesday," even though Wes is re-sequencing the album, the result is an left-hook of deeper emotion. Now this already wonderful scene takes off into true greatness. Many a director has tried to use "Ruby Tuesday," the evocative Brian Jones/Stones classic, and failed. Wes solves the problem by letting you hear it the way the way you'd hear it in life... devastating and random in the way it pops up, innocently requiring you to remember the moment forever."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tempted to suggest that he's right to boycott the debate, and that live debates in general are an unnecessary anachronism.  He has very little to gain, and his greatest weakness is that he seems to lack some of the necessary charisma-factor that other politicians rely on.  

But how telling are live debates really?  It's usually just a demonstration of how well leaders can weave talking points at each other.  You have very little guarantee (especially with American live debates) whether the points being made are even factual.

The only part of televised debates that I appreciate is when candidates with little chance of winning take the opportunity to criticize and question the candidates that likely will win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 14:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep telling me to vote NDP... o_O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 17:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a one-time ranking? It's difficult to really draw conclusions unless our rankings in these areas are rising/falling over time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toll lanes best way to combat traffic congestion: Manning Centre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 22:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Law Deans worried about Government's statements regarding Chief Justice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 18:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Prime Ministers Office vs. The Chief Justice The Marc Nadon affair gets even messier still </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 18:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Were a number of experts surveyed, and only the friendliest ones hired?

I could see the administration suffering from a bit of a 'filter bubble' problem on this and other issues.  Their judgement on a number of issues has seemed a little out of touch with reality, particularly given their supreme court defeats.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In retrospect of all that's happened, ironically, Harper probably should have taken the call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 15:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more stories I read about Canada and foreign/diplomatic affairs, the more I start to think we're not especially popular anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 01:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really curious what this will mean for environmental/energy regulatory policy at the provincial level if Prentice comes into power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 00:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strategically he might not be voicing his interests on purpose though...  If he wasn't ambitious, he wouldn't have moved up through the ranks as he has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe from Oh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelly McParland: Reform Partys history shows how politics hates change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 21:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 16:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want my technocratic oligarchy! :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 04:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That video was Eisenhower advocating balanced investment by the state, not Keynes... 

That said, I loved the way he warned of the possible take over by a scientific and technological elite, how come that option couldn't have come to pass? sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 02:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada definitely needs to reevaluate its military. We've been neglecting it for the past several decades, but it's an essential expense and a public good, especially during domestic emergencies/disasters.

The longer we wait, the harder it will be to reestablish our former capabilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 00:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the fiasco of mental health information being shared with American Border Services and the FBI, I can't understand how digital privacy isn't a larger issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 05:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not. The monarchy is already symbolic in Canada, why not make the current representation of that symbol permanent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 03:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, made a visit, went along with all the ceremony. Im just saying it was a nice gesture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 02:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think she deserves it. She was the monarch that ~~let us~~ went along with repatriation in '82. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada should do away completely with succession. We should make Queen Elisabeth II the Queen of Canada in perpetuity, even after she is deceased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might not be interested, but his rise within the party shows he has some ambition. I think he'd be a good fit, especially since he's not out there tooting his horn seeking power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 22:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you say Baird isn't interested? His experience as whip would also make him a good pick for taking the helm at the PMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Akin: Winds of political change begin to stir across Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 22:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 22:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I really like Kenney, but I think he's been an MP too long in his career, he seems to lack something fundamental.

MacKay is too PC, and somewhat tarnished from defense. Moore just doesn't seem to stand out a lot.

I really like Baird, and I think he has the international affairs chops too at this point. He seems passionate, but also a really good person. Do you think he could still win over social conservatives after being such a vocal supporter of LGBT issues though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 21:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you think of Prentice coming back from the private sector? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 20:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   start freezing the extensive and questionably acquired assets of the Kremlin's cronies

It sounds like they're doing that as a general progression, more and more each week to keep up a steady pressure.  

Still, what are Putin's outs in this scenario where he can save face, or maintain power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 19:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has resulted that Germany via Merkel is the main go-between, but this entire crisis arose between the EU and Russia over Ukraine. Germany is part of this, not a broker.

Canada had an opportunity to be a mediator and I feel like we missed it. We have failed to build any relationships in the past several years that we can leverage to take on that role.

 We are very much at the table.

Do we have much of an active role in Geneva right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 04:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, domestic producers are riding high off the fracking boom. Canadian bitumen is much less of a critical investment than it was even 5 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supporting our allies is without question, we are a committed member of NATO. However, we abdicated having anyone's ear. We are a G7 nation, we could have helped facilitate communication and deal brokering. We're nowhere near the table now.

Supporting sanctions wouldn't have limited our access either. It was publicly vilifying the other side that's the mistake. I think we talked a big game when we should have been finding ears to whisper in.

Also, don't worry about being interrogative, I should better qualify my criticisms. I like talking to you Blue. ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea of a country and economy the size of Russia descending into civil unrest would mean pretty negative consequences for the global economy.

Is the current hope to sanction just enough that they will back down? I feel like Putin would prefer to drive his country over the edge before surrendering... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Should Canada have done nothing?

Canada effectively did nothing. Our actions and rhetoric only succeeded in marginalizing our influence and interests. 

Our actions should have been to affirm our commitment to our NATO partners, but to work towards a diplomatic solution. Not jingoism, especially when we're rattling nonexistent sabres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing morally, but I'd prefer to see Canada more diplomatically influential, and less simply part of the mob of angry rhetoric. Right now, we're just a drop in the bucket, irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 01:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you foresee Russia could become politically destabilized over this? Or is their military strong enough to sustainably quash dissent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 01:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if international condemnation provides any real discouragement. It seems to simply feed the 'Russia vs. the West' narrative that the Kremlin is using to garner support domestically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 01:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should be seeking to be different. We give up any opportunity to be truly influential by parroting everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 23:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have assumed with lighter weight requirements, no life support or ejection etc. they could reach faster speeds and greater altitudes depending on the design. Kind of like those F16s the American air force retrofitted as drones down in Florida. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 19:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you elaborate on the first point?  Do you mean piloted drones there or fully autonomous drones?

For the 2nd, you're referring to communications infrastructure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 19:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something that's been discussed here sporadically, but I'd really welcome getting some fresh opinions: 

**What is the real advantage to having piloted aircraft as opposed to remotely piloted drones?**

I feel like if Canada were to shift their investment away from conventional aircraft towards developing innovative drone technology now, we would possess a strategic advantage in future engagements.

I'm definitely interested in current limitations, but I also see them as opportunities for next gen drone tech.

It seems as though a lot of the current limitations to conventional aircraft are the human body itself, and reaction times of pilots.  Plus, from a PR standpoint, without the potential loss of pilots, the US have been able to run pretty dangerous missions with drones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 05:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were delightful in Grosse Point Blank. You and John Cusack have a pretty fun chemistry. Any chance you two have a co-project on the horizon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 19:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just heard he was a [vocal opponent](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/toronto/porter-seeks-runway-extension-in-move-to-reduce-noise/article14100462/) of the Porter runway extension for Toronto island.

Not particularly liking this potential candidate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Vaughan to run for Liberals in federal byelection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 18:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 02:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all the therapeutic opportunities for gene therapy that open up from using CRISPR, the conventional markets are the EU and North America first, where patents, at least in pharma, are still somewhat observed.  

Give it a couple years and someone will develop an alternative CRISPR protein suite, but in that time a few companies will be several years ahead in clinical trials for their new therapies.

Still, the genie is out of the bottle.  This is going to make the next 20 years look very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CRISPR Genome Editing Technology Patent - The Harvard-MIT genomic science institute trumpets its claims to an important genome editing technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 00:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 23:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I see the majority of people using the internet to further insulate themselves to ideas that confirm their views rather than to actively seek new information that counters it. I see politicians playing up these divisions between the good and the bad. I see scientists being placed on sides rather than simply presenters of fact. I quite frankly see our system getting worse.

The idea of filter bubbles freaks me out a little for whether my own positions are based on objectively weighing several arguments, or if they just fit conveniently into the adhoc moral model I've built for myself to interpret the world.

.....I need a beer

Absolutely.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 22:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you're being a little presumptuous thinking that this was ever intended as a good policy

I find it so demoralizing to acknowledge the likely accuracy of this.  I want to believe everyone is coming to table in good faith.  

There was that good post a while ago on [a piece by Ezra Klein](http://www.reddit.com/r/CanadaPolitics/comments/22fji5/does_politics_make_us_stupid/) about the fallacy of believing that the necessary antidote to political disagreement is more information.  I've always wanted to believe this, and I really need to be more skeptical about accepting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 21:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's one thing I'm still waiting to see in a political party, it's a willingness to acknowledge poor policy and adopt something effective.

I've always hated the expression 'waffling' that was adopted in political races in the US, because if anything we need to be more flexible with preparing legislation, not more intransigent.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 06:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is an interesting result, it's important to consider that losing the function of glucosidase has a major impact on countless protein-receptor regulations for countless glycoproteins in the body.  (Around 50% of all proteins are glycosylated^1, though that includes O-glycans which aren't affected by this mutation)

It's almost like if we lived in a world where circles didn't exist, that

Every N-glycan on every protein of every cell coming out of the endoplasmic reticulum is going to fail to have the correct post-translational modifications it should have leaving the Golgi.

It's miraculous these kids are actually still alive, but they'll actually suffer the side effects:
 Early in life, they each had a complex disorder characterized by dysmorphic facial features, generalized hypotonia, seizures, global developmental delay, cerebral atrophy, a small corpus callosum, optic-nerve atrophy, sensorineural hearing loss, hypoplastic genitalia, chronic constipation, and recurrent bone fractures; severe hypogammaglobulinemia was also diagnosed. 

 Really awesome free resource on glycobiology for anyone interested: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK1908/

^1: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10580125 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 04:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since there's discussion now of revising the appointments process for the Senate, that might actually be a good area to introduce such a policy to the legislative branch.  

It's a bit hard to mandate electing candidates from certain professions, but definitely not unheard of.  Appointments are easier to get away with though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 04:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An emphasis on appointments to the judiciary of technically literate individuals, sort of like affirmative action but for engineering and science to the bench might be an interesting policy direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laws and Ethics Cant Keep Pace with Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laws and Ethics Cant Keep Pace with Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 18:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you would fail a Turing test. :)

(I definitely mean this as a compliment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelly McParland: Senate offers Harper a route for Elections Act retreat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 18:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 16:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe /u/Majromax can chime in and describe what the process and consequences would likely be... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 16:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really had hoped more of his free trade agreements had materialized, I really was rooting for those. Particularly TPP.

The pipelines as well... Though I feel like Prentice has made some good arguments for why Keystone hasn't been approved yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 16:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the PM were to call a snap election, would it probably coincide with passage of this bill? (i.e. before parts of it could be overturned in courts?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 19:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Geist's [latest response](http://www.michaelgeist.ca/content/view/7107/) on this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New bill to crack down on illegal downloads has privacy experts worried </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 19:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadians' mental-health info routinely shared with FBI, U.S. customs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 14:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a newspaper's editorial board can make endorsements, I feel like a sub's moderator board could conceivably do the same, if they were inclined to do so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative who defeated Rob Anders says Jason Kenney had no business in controversial nomination race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 17:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 04:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be so cool to attend. I really need to spend some time diving into this research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 03:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true, motivating a vote from the centre-left through fear/anger tends to fail.  It's the emotionally optimistic narrative that tends to prevail. (I believe there's a statistical basis for this, but my google-fu is a little weak tonight...)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 23:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm super-excited for this, and a giant supporter of biotech. Reading some of these other comment about the FDA holding gene-therapy back, I just wanted to remind everyone about [Jesse Gelsinger](en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jesse_Gelsinger) a teenager who died in one of the early gene therapy clinical trials before we had things well figured out.

That's the event that's really held gene therapy back, not the FDA.

The FDA can definitely improve, like any bureaucracy, but there's a reason we proceed forward in medicine tentatively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open less than 24? :(

Amusingly, I actually feel disenfranchised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian dollar stronger following Quebec Liberal win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 17:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 02:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could hang out in a bar with all of you and watch these results.

Je tiens  regarder ces rsultats dans un pub avec vous tous.

(dsol, mon franais est terrible)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 00:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the ideas don't necessarily disappear.  Not unless it's all out genocide.  Especially today, where we have books, internet, etc., such that there are more vehicles for information and ideas than just the people who believe in them.  

For instance, fascism, communism, and liberal democracy with a mix of capitalism and socialism were all fairly popular in the mid 20th century.  However, by armed conflict (WWII) and a mix of armed/economic conflict (various cold war arenas, etc.) you could say that liberal democracy with a relatively free economy became the acceptable consensus for several countries.  Even China is gradually liberalizing their society and economy over time.  So a consensus on the societal model of government and economy is gradually being reached, even though in some cases armed conflicts have contributed to those developments.

An example of where an armed conflict lead to a weak consensus could be WWI, where the treaty at the end was completely one-sided, so an agreeable consensus was really impossible.  So a weak consensus, could be said to only be accepted as long as one side can force it on to another.

Edit:  A slightly more recent example would be countries that had dictators for several decades.  The populace was mostly willing to accept these arrangements, or at least uprisings could be put down fairly successfully, leading to a weak-consensus.  However, once one uprising succeeds, it can be very difficult to successfully achieve a new stable consensus that's acceptable for the majority of the population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 21:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say it's a "good" thing at all. However, historically speaking many conflicts have been settled with naked force. You could call it the simplest or weakest consensus when you simply destroy those who disagree with you.

The strongest consensus are those ideas that have run the full gauntlet of information and argument from both sides arriving finally at a normative resolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to accept the conclusion that more information doesn't by itself assist in the reaching of consensus. After all, the more nuanced the information, the more difficult to form informed opinions.

However, I'd argue that none of this indicates stupidity. Conflict of ideas ensures the absolutely strongest consensus is finally reached, sometimes violently. Look at slavery, now followed by gay rights, drug policy, etc.

Conflicts of ideas within society eventually leading to stable consensus on acceptable norms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 13:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think you'd feel the same way following a major outbreak of a preventable disease? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 23:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite sub apart from this one is probably /r/futurology

It's not as strictly sciencey as /r/science, but they like to discuss a lot of emerging technology and policy, like automation and basic minimum income with respect social impacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 15:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think instead of a sequel though, I'd rather see it done as a series for Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 01:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the zaps from a shield? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
