<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but salon folk are mean and grumpy, not like waiter folk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not cool to release our internet history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really buff guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't cuticle oil fix that for $6 or so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, why do you go to nail salons when you can get the same stuff in the comfort of your home for so much cheaper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hijo de la Luna in Spanish, it ACTUALLY tells a story. As in, the song is the plot about a woman wishing on the moon for a husband, and when the baby is born the baby is as light skinned as the moon. The husband then is convinced the baby isn't his and murders the woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to write journal entries on my Livejournal as a teen, my gamer friends told me I could write </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get raised by their own parents instead of the help, maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I didn't want to disturb my roommate last night, here it is much louder. My timbre changes much more drastically here:

http://vocaroo.com/i/s05i3MH517R2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's upsetting because you are walking around minding your own business and someone comes up to you and basically says "Hey I don't even know your name but I want to remind you that you are an outsider because you look like one even though the two of us grew up in the same neighborhoods and had the same teachers, now let me know what box of outsider to put you in. Oh, that box? Now let me talk about random crap related to that box that has nothing to do with you but I will assume you find it interesting!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents are mainland Chinese city folk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Born in Scotland, raised in the US, have Asian parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a question since you mentioned timbre.

My timbre changes drastically between the bottom and tops of my range. My voice teacher classifies me as a soprano but at the lower end of my voice I can mimic an alto sound.

Here is an example: http://vocaroo.com/i/s1J4teEx4eCg

You can hear as I go up I shift back into a soprano sound. Do my low notes therefore not count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a guild where guys would regularly rage-quit and then rejoin the next day all calm and apologetic. It was routine enough where you just expect them back every time they did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are loudly talking about a party that all of them went to the night before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trying to guess what kind of Asian I am and then talking about said Asian country like I am its spokesperson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeling like your parents care more about money than your health or wellbeing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had sex when I was 25 with a guy I wasn't even attracted to, just because I didn't want to be a virgin anymore. It wasn't that no one wanted me, I'd had a couple boyfriends before that, but it went from "my first time has to be so special" to "oh fuck just get this over with" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh this reminds me I had ice cream in the fridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apollo because he is damn entertaining. Plays the lyre, god of the sun, strong, beautiful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an occupation most likely occupied by someone who is an asshole? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I was the soprano whose recordings you commented on just yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all it was my first time saying anything like this to you (each time it is actually a different person telling you that you don't know what you are doing - you have a LOT of people telling you that you have no idea what you are doing), second of all you no one has anything to be jealous of, and third of all you have 3 posts on the front page so as a regular on this subreddit of course I am bound to comment on one of your posts because you spew so much bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the girl in the video was maybe 14 so you aren't much older than her. 

Well I am still fairly new to singing (3 years of choir and 4 months of voice lessons) so you'd have to take what I say with a grain of salt, but I could (and still can) go down a loud, rumbling low E when I was 17 to make people laugh. Then when I joined my first college choir I squeaked my way up to a G and got placed under soprano. I was dying in the soprano section and asked the choir director if I could move to alto, he said no and that I just needed practice to hit those notes. I meanwhile took some free voice lessons with the university and explained my dilemma to the voice teacher, she frowned and said that I sounded like a soprano to her. I then tried joining another choir, got turned down but the choir director once again said I was a soprano.

Joined another choir years later, got placed under soprano again. Took voice lessons, voice teacher says I am a soprano. I guess they cant ALL be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do some 3 day cliche to pretend you don't care, just meet her whenever.

Pay attention to hygiene (no shirts with holes or ones that ride up and show your gut) but don't go overboard and end up reeking of cologne. A nice fresh shirt is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually the case for me too but I keep getting classified as a soprano by voice teachers and choir directors lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only count the notes you can SING and sing comfortably and consistently. Don't count just any note you can make noises at. Do scales like C-D-E-F-G-F-E-D-C going up one note at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're 30? You honestly act like you are 15. In every post I see you spouting delusions. Look, you clearly go flat when you go high and insist you aren't after everyone points it out, you tell professional musicians that they don't know what off-key means, you assume you know your voice type based on range when you are an untrained singer who clearly does not have the vocal ability to access their full range (plus timbre and tessitura matter more anyway), you post clips of yourself wailing in pain and expect compliments without realizing that the first rule of singing is that people are supposed to not wince in pain from hearing it, and whenever anyone offers something constructive you argue because you are so convinced you know so much more than even professionals.

Look, your singing is terrible and you don't sound any better than any other shower singer. You honest to god suck and on top of that you seem to have a narcissistic personality disorder that makes you assume you know what you are talking about when you clearly don't. I have never seen a user get consistently downvoted as much as you have. You make an ass out of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a girl's voice, you remind me of the girl who plays Little Red Riding Hood in the Into the Woods movie. https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=dQ-f6C3sCf0

I don't think you are a low mezzo, mezzos have a darker, older-sounding color to their voices. You might be an untrained soprano with some good low notes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought this was a troll post. Very interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My meat pie baking skills, I keep eating it all before I can share it with other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have a very pretty voice!

I think you are a soprano - your voice is light like mine and my voice teacher says I am a soprano. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it harder for some voice types to learn to sing than others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, would a musical theater soprano have a harder time than an alto because she would have to learn to sing classical AND belt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the number her actual number or is it a fake? If it is a fake she isn't into you from the start. Sorry, that's happened to me once when a guy was practicing his flirting and got my number but never called. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because "how are you" isn't real question. It's a greeting. "Fine" is the only acceptable answer when you don't know someone.

"How old are you" "20" is a genuine lie. You are attempting to mislead someone. If you genuinely lie to someone to date them, whether it be lying about your age, pretending to want kids when you don't, or pretending you are single when you're not, you are actually building a relationship on false pretenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lying about how old you are is completely different from saying "I'm fine" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People lie to each other every day, multiple times a day. 

I don't, and I have the same standards for a partner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The age thing is whatever to me, the problem is that she chose to lie. I wouldn't be with a relationship with someone who feels it's okay to casually lie, it reflects the state of their conscience. My mom is someone who can toss a lie casually off her tongue, and she also does stuff like intercepting money my dad gives me and pocketing it for herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about that, it's the fact she has no qualms about lying to people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my lessons are 30 minutes each, once a week, and about $160 a month so that's about $40 every 30 minute lesson. Maybe my teacher isn't being critical enough? She doesn't stop me every so often to correct me, she just listens to me sing a song all the way through and and then comments on it at the end.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw man :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your input,

There are two voice teachers in my area, one isn't very musical (she uses just karaoke CDs and we warm up a cappella) but she is good at explaining things, and the other is very musical (can play any sheet music on the piano) but terrible at explaining things other than saying "like this". I am taking lessons with the one who is better at explaining things because with the more muscial teacher I learned absolutely nothing technique-wise. I do worry I don't have the best teacher, last lesson I asked if she had a good 2nd soprano audition song for a choir and most of my 30 minutes was her rummaging through her cabinets to find her Fiddler on the Roof book instead of us actually singing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah my voice teacher says I should first focus on getting the technique right and add the theater later so I was just focused on "is my voice resonating in my forehead right now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I also recorded it with a different device so I hope most of the improvement isn't just the quality of the recording itself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Originally I would strain since this song is right in my break area and so to keep from cracking I would hold my voice back when I sang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the feedback! Singing high notes does feel easier for me now than before, I just wasn't sure if it made me sound better or not to a listener. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taken voice lessons for 4 months, recording myself singing the same song 3 months apart. Do you hear a difference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I started taking lessons in December. I am 28, female, 
have sung regularly for 11 years, done 2 years of choir, and started taking voice lessons for the first time in December 2016.

I recorded this song in December after I got my very first song assignment, and I sang it again today now that I have had lessons for 3 months. I learned to do some things differently, mainly to resonate through the mask and how to stay relaxed. It is $500+ in lessons already so I would hope there is SOME improvement. I feel like it improved when I sing, but after I hear it recorded back I don't know if I can tell a difference.

Part of Your World December 27, 2016: 
http://vocaroo.com/i/s0s8WxKhH6iz

Part of Your World today (April 8th 2017):
http://vocaroo.com/i/s0bgdb0RaL29
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate the sound of a piano being played by a little kid because it reminds me of getting hit and locked out of the house for messing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone who understands music theory explain the logic behind this choir music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i64.tinypic.com/24h1e.jpg

The first clef is soprano (splits), second is alto, third is tenor, 4th is bass. Why would the altos have a higher note than the second sopranos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom doesn't have feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one lies assholes in general. Just because someone isn't an asshole doesn't mean they are a doormat.

If the waiter gets your order wrong at a restaurant and you throw a yelling fit, you are an asshole. If you politely point out the order was wrong, you are normal. If you don't say anything and quietly eat the wrong order, you are a doormat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For guys it often comes down to the right grooming and hitting the gym </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are always the one initiating contact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, a lot of guys THINK girls like assholes because they see a girl dating a guy who is one. It is the equivalent of a fat, ugly woman thinking men love bitches because she knows some women she doesn't like and they are in relationships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means they think you are ugly. Being an asshole would just make you an ugly asshole.

Seriously though, I and other girls have turned guys down if we just aren't attracted to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! I am on Match but so far I haven't had much luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those who dated someone they met through a dating site, what have your experiences been like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a miscarriage, not a period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a religious friend who made a very long post about how she traveled with a violin and how God was looking out for her that day because the violin was "only" in a violin case. When the violin wasn't scratched after she got home, she realized God was looking out for her blah blah blah she is so thankful. I chose not to comment but I judge her silently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One guy kissed with his eyes open, it creeped me out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally more social people do seem to be more attractive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not understand your English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting a job offer after a long unemployment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a published novella for my first long publication, mine is about the same word count. I looked up a couple indie publishers on Google and queried them the sameway I would query an agent. They have very little marketing power though, the cover art was so bad (I think the artist must have been a high school student) that people tell me it turned them off from buying the book. There is also little promotion, all they did was put the book on their webpage that people don't visit. I got only 17 sales in 6 months and they were mainly people I knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> running to your corpse on World of Warcraft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hard mandarin Chinese trying to mimic British RP. Horror of horrors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played an online game. Much higher level guy farmed me, which is against server etiquette. I sent him a friendly email asking him to please not farm me because I am active, and in response he farms me twice in one day and then sends me a reply with just a smiley face.

It was on. For weeks I grew my army until it was so massive I had to wake up in the middle of the night to feed it so it wouldn't starve. Finally it was ready. The guy showed up to farm my account and I whipped out my massive army on my low level account and decimated him. Since I was several levels lower than him he lost an epic amount of points.

He then grew his army again and tried again a week or so later, and I beat him again. He quit after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get famous just for existing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever broken someone's heart? What happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking to strangers over the internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would do someone who is a master at SQL and salesforce development because I need to be better at both for work purposes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camping in a desert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarah Jessica Parker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy hitting on me was Asian, I thought "Ooo". When I realized he was south-east Asian and got a little disappointed, but then I caught myself doing that and wondered why I thought northeast Asians were better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buying ripped ugly clothes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact a lot of us still believe in religions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing big, stuff like not being sure if something was sarcastic or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had dress codes at our school, they werent uniforms but you still had to dress a certain way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theme from Forrest Gump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game related, found out my guild leader was using bots, he denied it and called me crazy and kicked me out of the guild. I was a long time member of the guild (a year) and I was pissed for days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I approve, less kids getting sent home for wearing the wrong shoes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever read a book where the author came across as so pretentious you had to toss the book aside? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck to ya! I've been on a full request for almost 3 months now and I am dying lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who got represented by agents, how did they let you know they would represent you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they call you or do you only correspond by email? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the issues you butt heads with other Mormons on?

I am a non-Mormon working for a company based near Salt Lake City, from what I have seen it is 50% non-Mormon. Are you in a rural area?

Edit: nevermind I looked up the location of Utah State. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me, whatever you do do NOT move back in, they are still the same people. They just see you less so they go into guest-greeting mode. Speaking from experience if you move back in after college it will be prison again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You saw the post after it was edited, the original post said she "could be a 7" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and what is your own rating, exactly? Why do you think you deserve a 7? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah even if you stayed with her, you can't marry someone that temperamental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my mom used to beat me until I cried, told me to get the hell out of the living room and into my bedroom, and then she would come in acting all sweet and telling me that she beat me for my own sake (over grades/piano) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that is unfortunately normal for people like us. Tell her that undiagnosed issues don't mean that the issues don't exist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my managers have all been very positive, none of them were nearly the nightmare that my mom was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there is an extra dine-in tax, but not much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand the sound of what sounds like childish piano-playing, 6 years of slaps and getting locked out of the house for that shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is typing as fast as she can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are only going to hurt yourself by continuing to go back to them and hearing them pelt you with all these insults :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not ask her to show you the email? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a movie sequel that is just as good as the original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Las Vegas. I kept winning. And then I lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Tython? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah above the human hearing range so no one notices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What happened before C-sections if a woman couldn't give birth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she die of a heart attack? Does the birthing stop and she just stays pregnant forever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very clear warm voice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The brainwashing. Suddenly everything is offensive and you can't handle any ounce of hardship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuff like that makes me wonder if I am transgender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question only made me think of how good I had it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A8? I can hit a Bb14. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also need to be furnished and you have to pay the electric bill and water bill and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your most epic workplace screw up and did you get fired for it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can always go on Craigslist and find a shared room scenario where someone is already living in an apartment and needs a roommate, the hard part is to be wary of scams and make sure you are compatible with someone before moving in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Itchy   Scratchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Executioners of dangerous criminals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pillow, sleeping without a pillow feels weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most butch lesbian thing I've ever done was play a tank on World of Warcraft back when that game was fun.

I dress like a super femme girly-girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
