<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5867</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 20:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got to play the original, but my sister and I used to play House of the Dead 3 in an old local arcade. I remember it being a lot of fun, even though we never got past the third level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 02:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite book of his is definitely Insomnia, favourite film is either Shawshank Redemption or The Mist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 02:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the first two issues of this series and I really enjoyed them, but I found the last two issues to be way too stupid to be even remotely fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 17:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. I still doubt that they'll be able to do anything, but I'll stop by the police after class finishes.

EDIT: Went to the police station, they filed it away as an incident and told me that they would call me if anything turned up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 08:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a bit confused before I clicked the link, because I was trying to figure out what Mindless Self Indulgence had to do with PCs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 05:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as your computer has Windows 7 or 8.1, you should be able to upgrade it to 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saved by Sirens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 04:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to go outside tonight, typically I dont go out at night, but I just had an argument with my mother, which ended with me leaving, slamming the door shut. I decided to walk over to the local coffee shop and enjoy the free wifi there as well as cool down. But after awhile of scrolling through Reddit, I decided that I would just continue going for a walk as I drank my iced coffee.

I left the shop and began walking down the street, still thinking about the argument. As I reached the corner of the street and I waited for the walking signal to appear to tell me to cross the street, I saw a man with his face covered in shadows, so I couldnt see his face, all that I could see of him was his yellow Hawaiian shirt. Originally, I thought it was weird that someone else would be out at a time like this, but I just shrugged it off.

But as soon as I crossed the street, he began to run towards me. I swiftly turned around and ran back across the street, not even caring to see if any cars were coming. I crossed the street and for a brief moment, I felt relieved since I figured that he wouldnt follow me across the street. Unfortunately, I was proven wrong when I turned to look over my shoulder and saw him still coming towards me.

I began to run as fast as I can, I didnt know what he wanted, but 
I didnt want to find out. I ran as fast as I could, but when I looked over my shoulder, he was right behind me, getting extremely closer. The adrenaline in my body began to run though my body even faster, making me run even faster than I thought I could.

Suddenly, I heard the sound of sirens and I looked behind me to see the guy running back away from me, he must have figured that the sirens were coming from a police car. I continued running just in case, later finding the source of the sirens coming from an ambulance that drove by. I ran all the way back home, just in case that he saw the ambulance and decided to chase after me again.

When I got home, I slammed on the front door, not wanting to waste the time to find my keys in my pocket. My mom opened the door and I rushed in, closing the door and collapsed onto the couch. I explained what happened, she recommended that I go tell the police what happened, but since I didnt exactly get a good look at his face, there probably wouldnt be anything for them to do.

But I am never going to go outside at night ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 08:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who neomail me trying to get me to sell stuff that I have in my gallery. If I wanted to sell something, I wouldn't put in my gallery, it would go in my shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 21:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look closely at the sakura trees in the last panel, you'll notice that the leaves aren't leaves. They are bloody handprints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> End of a Tunnel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might have already figured out how to watch it, but if not, you can watch it right [here](http://zeldathon.net). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else remember reading Commander Toad as a kid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
