<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8135</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Speed, What's Your Highest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I hit 155.7 yesterday in my Nero (not custom) during the "High Speed Challenge". The map rendering was pretty laggy at that speed. 

[Proof](http://i.imgur.com/5Gex1F3.jpg)

How fast have you gone? (No mods plz) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sucky sucky makes me lucky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucky sucky makes me lucky
My producer has the best cummies and makes me feel sillyHe begs me to be squishyand sloppy just for him he's my daddyI get special candy to make me sleepy because I'm his sweet babyprincess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a new day and your boss has a new boner, time to get down and slurpity slurp slurp  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a new day and your boss has a new boner, time to get down and slurpity slurp slurp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghost Rider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus wtf are these actual problems that y'all have to deal with on a date?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never expected it to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, never really expected to go anywhere with it lol. I sent her a link to the Get Schwifty episode shortly after and she un-matched.

Plus my mom's name is Tammy so it would've been weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet that thing is a total riot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess she didn't want to get schwifty with me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just posted over there, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Expedition finally looking right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stop caring so much about what other people do!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this guy who tries to fit in with our family. Let's call him Charles. He's bludgeoned his way into our holiday gatherings by trying to play the pity card and generally acting like a little bitch. You sound a lot like him. Maybe you are him? He does have the tendency to be a little "playful" with the younger kids in the family. 

When and if I see him at Christmas this year I'm going to calmly explain to him why he isn't welcome in the family and how nobody likes his presence. Thank you for reminding me how much I hate people like you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need to see your side mate, you want to fuck a kid and that's all




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank God I didn't know it was banned. I heard about it a couple weeks ago and lurked a bit with my jaw on the ground. What a place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
