<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The economy these days, am I right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My proudest haul yet. Over $200 in makeup, a romper from Old Navy, and a Jessica Jones pop vinyl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have mad respect for you. You seem very reasonable and like a stand-up, decent human being. The few AP I've encountered (especially at Target) are so fucking rude and act like lifters are animals, even those (like myself) who lift out of necessity.

My question is, what would an announcement over the intercom for LP sound like? Do they do that at Target?

Also, what would you consider the best method for lifting at Target? Using the reusable shopping bags? I've done a few push-outs with food and groceries but I feel like this is a dangerous method since every once in a while I see an APS at the door checking receipts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's haul! Heading back to Ulta later to get some treats for myself along with things to resell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, I just ended up doing a good old-fashioned push out. My tried and true favorite method at this particular store. It's worked for me so far, so I can't complain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to do the cereal box trick without looking suspicious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know, go to a blind spot. But I'm still worried I'll look sketchy as fuck shoving stuff into a cereal box.

Are you guys sure self checkout will deactivate security tags? I'm probably just being stupid, but I'm paranoid since I've never lifted like this before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talk to myself too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weirdest or funniest shit you've ever done/said while high? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few nights ago, I was high off my ass and started taking  closeup pictures of my left eye with the flash on, which for some reason was making me laugh really hard. I doubled over and grabbed my stomach and was panicking to my boyfriend that I couldn't stop laughing and asked if I would ever stop before my stomach exploded.

I also asked my boyfriend "Was Justin Timberlake in blink-182? ...fuck, I meant N*SYNC. I want garlic bread."

I've also started laughing, then once I forget why I stop laughing and then immediately start back up again after realizing that I looked so silly. A never ending cycle. Lmao. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one I go to is small and has one camera...there are 3 employees who are usually busy helping customers and don't address me. I grab items quickly, hold them under my arm and take them to a fitting room near the mall exit. Fitting rooms aren't monitored so I take my items in with some clothes to "try on", take the RFID tags off the makeup, stick them to the back of the mirror so no one can see, and put the makeup in my bag, then hang the clothes up. I left once with two Modern Renaissance palettes (one for me and one to resell), a NARS foundation and concealer, 3 beauty blenders, and the Sweet Peach Palette.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any of you guys have partners who don't lift/don't know you lift? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend has no idea I lift. He's super against it and would freak if he found out. I wish I could tell him, but he'd be so upset and he'd think I'm crazy. We can't afford groceries and clothes and medicine and shit so I lift for the two of us. I want us both to live comfortably and be taken care of.

Do you guys have a partner who doesn't lift? Or does your partner not know you lift at all? How do you explain all the new stuff to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
