<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6283</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 09:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your posts and content are just great. Espeicially love the gif of you sucking your man's grool covered dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually pretty sad, but also happy at the same time that you're not actually a bunch of alcoholics getting wildly drunk and messing with paint and canvasses. Imagine being completely pissed and thinking you painted this awesome portrait of your instructor and really it was just a. Big round circle with glasses. 
Btw, nice painting bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commonly front callipers are essentially all the same. Wind back/screw in callipers, electric and cable brakes are commonly only used for a parking brake/hand brake. Some bikes do use cable, but that's old school stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that as "assmosphere" the first time..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 16:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Human Centipede original.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 03:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need more of this! A man needs a name.. For science... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tooth gap. Georgia May Jagger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Describes Fifty Shades of Grey* *Copies and pastes wikipedia plot into comment section.* *Recieves multiple upvotes and downvotes, no gold however.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until about 5 years ago, when I was 16, I use to think the expression "Going to see a man about a dog." Meant that they were actually going to get a dog. A friend of my dad said the expression once to me and I asked him what dog he was going to get and why another dog, he had 4 or so already. I remember him sniggering as he walked away while shaking his head..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would still bang. 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 06:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic. You got aa boyfriend, husband or male friend? I'd love you see you in action, that would be so damn awesome. Some videos would be just ridiculously fantastic. Keep it up, I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf, that's disgusting, sick and wrong, source please? For science..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fucker. You got me zooming in and shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
