<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7982</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I saw a Funhaus logo in Northern Idaho on a car, but then I realized it was a different symbol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firehouse Subs coming to Spokane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harrison Ford's Taxiway Landing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Thanksgiving Dinner? Especially a roasted turkey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Park did it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderland maybe? Like Chuck E Cheese, but is a bit roomier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That may be true. I just realized I had the premium version. Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be out ~~Sunday~~ Saturday (if you're a First Member)

Edit: Thanks /u/kris_random   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both Planefinder and Flight Radar 24 do this, although I recommend the second one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He posted it within 40 seconds of this post going up. I'm impressed more than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thick and salty

Heh heh.

But that makes sense, I really want to try it now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can somebody describe the taste of Vegemite to me? Why are they so disgusted trying it straight, but it's okay on the bread thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] What happened to Puff, The Magic Dragon after the events of the song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be completely honest, that would be difficult, at least in the winter. Snow closes 195 all the time, whether it's wrecks or just blowing snow. So you take a 1.5 hour drive and make it 3 hours or so if it snows.

Spokane does have a satellite WSU campus, however, so maybe you can look into that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. You guys get better, they get smarter. Kind of a back and forth. Yeah the only other thing I can think of is sort of like the system Reddit has. One of the subs I moderate had a problem with new accounts posting spam, so we put in a minimum amount of karma needed to post in the sub. Spam dropped dramatically, and we approve non-spam (but still low karma) manually.

I don't know if it would be possible, but maybe a way of verifying an account is a "good" account before letting the post appear in the community feed? Or something like that, I don't really know. I just like troubleshooting stuff like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool! I didn't expect to have an actual worker respond so that's awesome. If they are still getting in would that mean they are just using cheap labor? In any case, I'm happy to see it's in capable hands! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florio has a hate boner for the Hawks and I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Roosterteeth not have a captcha on account creation? Maybe they should, along with captcha on first ten posts, or something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough! I guess that's a good idea, since the sub is still growing so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The companies picking the winners see RT as an entity that can do something for them

Hell, other companies like MVMT and Shari's Berries probably wish RT talked about them as much as they mentioned Tinder on the podcast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said, however I think you're missing the third part of the puzzle. There are those that liked the joke, then hated it for a while, but then thought it was funny again. It dies for a while, but they help bring it back to life. 

As an example, Rickroll as a search term is just as popular, if not more popular, than 2014.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] A mailman that modifies letters before delivering them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if you could prove that you were being throttle at 5GB, and not at 22GB, you would have a case against them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The original dancing baby would have been old enough to drink by now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. From what I've seen on Youtube, Chance has one of the most creative "mainstream" concerts out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Upvote and Downvote icons in the Sub should be a cow and a Cleaver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How cool would that be? Plus they should shoot our fireworks when you upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tinder just agreed to send Barb on a romantic getaway to Hawaii </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they probably will, especially with the veteran's rest days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hotfix

The Checkpoint
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, in terms of traffic stops I have a anecdotal evidence, no real numbers though. So you may be right.

That's a dangerous fucking direction for us to be moving in.

Agreed there, Maybe I should have meant more-so for this sub itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're making a lot of assumptions about a sheriff you know nothing about. At least here in Spokane the Sheriff still does active patrol, and before he was elected sheriff he led the SWAT team, so I still trust him. But obviously I erred in posting this, as people seem to disagree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, of all people, I would want a Sheriff armed in a public place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried Heroes and Halfwits out yet? There's some downsides, but overall it works pretty well as a Podcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Hey Bert, we're a bit low, aren't we?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for responding! That makes a lot of sense!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] When Charlie was a young ant, his entire family was wiped out by a child holding a magnifying glass. Himself injured, but not dead, he sets out to get revenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good catch, but I tried to include names only of the most notable. In fact Kearse probably isn't even the best example. I mean hell, Seahawks had 24/53 players that were UDFA. that's crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI OP, to skip a line you need two line breaks. So instead of:

    Joe: Lawful Good
    Ashur: Neutral Good

You should actually do:

    Joe: Lawful Good
    
    Ashur: Neutral Good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody asked this on /r/CowChop, and it's a good question: Why does Gavin's shirt not have the Cow Chop logo in the thumbnail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever seen pepper spray hitting an eyeball at 100,000 frames a second? I know I want to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current Seahawks UDFA:

 - Doug Baldwin

 - Jermaine Kearse
 
 - Thomas Rawls

 - Michael Bennett

Not to mention their later drafts picks:

 - Russell Wilson - Third Round

 - KJ Wright - Fourth Round

 - Kam Chancellor - Fifth Round

 - Richard Sherman - Fifth Round </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about working with online content creators?

Specifically, Colton Dunn worked a bunch with [Roosterteeth](http://roosterteeth.com), and it would be awesome if you did some shorts with them too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family member found this rock in Arizona. They said it was heavy for it's size, and a magnet would not stick to it, but beyond that not much info </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I watched this video last night and when she saw this shirt she immediately wanted it. So thanks Gavin, my wallet is so happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA. But I guess the Carnival experience is worldwide! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's crazy! I mean, not that I don't trust carnies, but I definitely think I was too small for the ride at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh I like this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space Jam!

I remember it because right before the movie I went to a carnival across the street, and my brother had to grab me to stop me from falling out of my seat on the octopus ride when we were upside down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I did as well for a while. If you're curious, I think George Wright was camped out just southwest of the Four Lakes Exit. In-between what is now Granite lake and the small lake to the East </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brett in a Behind the Cow Chop video did at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man reading up on these battles is crazy. Especially the [Battle of Spokane Plains](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Spokane_Plains). I don't really like George Wright, but he was one hell of a commander. 

If I get some time today I might try to annotate on Google Maps where the battle took place and how it went down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe they are purposely delaying it a bit. They don't really want to do weekly like GTA or Minecraft, but still have semi-regular episodes. Your patience will be rewarded! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the house was called the Slaughterhouse, what should their impeding location be called? Assuming it's a warehouse I'm sure we can come up with something good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's a good idea. Funhaus and their fans could potentially contribute too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. But I do think there is some wiggle room, especially with scenery. 

*Props needed: Large tavern, old ship, sewers*

Something like that wouldn't give anything really away, but fans could still create cool stuff for the scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! Then yeah I totally hope they get an old Winnebago to drive in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish fans could create props for Heroes and Halfwits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like how cool would it be if they put out vague descriptions of characters and scenes, and the fans could send in what their interpretation looks like and possibly be used in the show. Not only would fans enjoy sending stuff in, but it would save the team some work too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Church of Chop! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Cow Chop: Roadtrip to L.A**

Yes please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, a new computer will make you happy while you're using it. But a new bed improves your quality of life overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're ever on the Northside try Taqueria Fiesta Brava. It's right by Francis and Nevada and it's great, and the people that work there are awesome! I love their fajita burrito.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever think how often Cow Chop's neighbors thought they were filming gay porn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 06:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean:

 - A bunch of young fit guys coming and going constantly 

 -  A ton of filming equipment

 - They went into the back yard and lit up a tent and filmed it

 - Lube pool

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was exposed to Agent Orange, and still suffers side-effects because of it. I bought him some of this and he absolutely loved it. He even posted it on his old vet buddies group Facebook page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Long and Thanks for All the Fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because something looks simple does not mean it was easy to design.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the Xbox One app daily. It is buggy in some aspects, but I like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You raise a good point, although I think you may have responded to the wrong comment of mine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a while he was working on his Visa, so I know that was part of it. Combine that with RTX Australia and him being a busy person overall and he just can't be in office as much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how Reddit works. I try to mention it a lot in this sub because I think this sub downvotes stuff too much, and I'm on a personal crusade to fix it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really good point. If that's the case they should definitely tell us that though, so people at least know it might take a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. And I'm sure that they help tons of people. It's more-so that these posts are becoming more common than ever before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I remember that too, which is why I'm surprised so many of there are showing up. An alternative idea is that RT is growing so fast that they literally can't get to everything.

But at a minimum, give people a time-frame. I run Tech Support at a company that has about 10 different customers ask for help a day. Even if I'm slammed, I will email back the customer and let them know I'll help as soon as I have a chance, and when that might be. This helps keep the customer happy, even if it takes a long time for me to help them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Roosterteeth have an issue with it's support team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I know it's a bit taboo to criticize RT, and as a result this might get downvoted. But I think it's an important point. 

If you have paid attention to posts lately in this Sub, there's a reoccurring theme that pops up.  A lot of people seem to be having issues, either with the Store, their First Membership, or similar. And many of them say the same thing, that they email RT support and they don't get a response back, or the response doesn't help much.

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5srd92/need_help_with_first_membership_dont_upvote/

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5sl0qt/so_if_anyone_could_help_me_fix_my_first_membership/

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5rok0y/problem_ordering_a_squiggly_cup/

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5rj6i8/extremely_unhelpful_support/ (there is a comment complaining about not getting emails back too)

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5qkci1/unable_to_get_a_response_from_customer_support/

Now to their credit, they sometimes do a great job responding in the Reddit threads, which is great. But what about the customers that don't come on here as much? If they aren't getting responses to their emails then they are probably just being let out to dry.

I'm not trying to start an argument or even really chastise somebody. I just know that if people are paying decent money to RT for a subscription or merchandise that good support is usually expected. And I know I wouldn't want it to be an issue if it ever happens to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so fun to read your comments in your voice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I can only answer the 1.5 question. Here is the Fire District map:

http://www.interceptradio.com/wiki/index.php/Spokane_County,_WA

Note that it's a bit outdated. Specifically I believe that Spokane City Fire now covers what on the map is marked District 10 - Station 2, and they are also airport backup. 

Edit: Correction. Here is the updated map:

https://www.spokanecounty.org/DocumentCenter/View/113

Looks like I was a bit wrong, as District 10 station 2 is still there, and SFD has a different station (6) near the airport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Gordon. What should I make for dinner tonight on a budget to really impress my girlfriend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks to me like it may be trademarked, so they may not be able to use it on apparel.

http://tmsearch.uspto.gov/bin/showfield?f=doc state=4801:6gtveq.2.3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of when Kanye launched his last album on Tidal. I really wish they used a different platform for this show, because otherwise it seems great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a semi-conservative (Like some stuff Trump does, hate most stuff), I do think if you're getting offended enough by RT's political positions to quit watching then you have really thin-skin. As an example, I don't always agree with Jack, but he makes me laugh and is a great person overall, so I'm still going to watch him. It would be stupid otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi OP, If you are looking for survey respondents your best bet is /r/SampleSize. Try it out and it might help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was not as funny as I was hoping James.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~8am breakfast beer and caffeine

Add Fireball to cold coffee and you take care of both at once - And it's delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! The only reason I knew is because the kicker for my favorite team said it a few years ago and I remembered that! It is a funny resemblance though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an FYI, "Kickers are People too" came around before RT did their short.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mind me. I love reading semantics debates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly can't enjoy the videos where they inhale plastic smoke and other noxious fumes. I don't know, I smoke beforehand and it makes me incredibly anxious and I just can't watch.

My other complaint is that they should put out two BTS videos a week. But that's a very selfish complaint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So up in my neck of the woods it's icy and snowy right now. When I was driving into work this morning I watched a deer go full stupid. I seen them on the side of the road, kinda antsy and definitely wanting to cross the road so I sped up a bit and got past them.

But after I passed them, they decided they then wanted to cross, and started running. Somehow they didn't see the van on the other side of the road. The one made it across the road cleanly, but the other deer went full speed into the side of the van. I mean fast enough that there is probably a dent in the shape of a deer's head on that van now.

At this point I slowed down to make sure everything was okay, and I was just watching out my back window. The deer that hit the van tried to get up, but it really was icy outside. He promptly slid underneath the van he had just ran into full speed. So now the van was sitting there, and the deer was trying to kick himself out from underneath, while I'm sitting there crying because I'm laughing so hard.

Finally the deer gets himself out and bounds off into the woods. I really hope the other deer made fun of him, because it sure started my day off right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you see yourself in ten years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and some parts of this image were absolutely devastated by the Depression. Specifically, Trent Alley or "Japantown" at the time, which is the block at the bottom of the image to the right of Washington St. Our Asian population dropped dramatically because of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Flight Radar 24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! I missed it on my first go-through too! I didn't notice it until my second good look. And thanks, I'll let you know! For now Google Newspaper Archive tides me over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, there is a date in the bottom center.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay looks like it was a large wildfire up near what is now the Wandermere Golf Course.

https://news.google.com/newspapers?nid=ddB7do2jUx8C dat=19290726 printsec=frontpage hl=en

See the article about the fire at Glen Tana on the front page. 

Edit: Coincidentally, the grain silos in the top right part of the picture (to the left of St. Aloysius/Gonzaga) had a massive fire a few days after this photo was taken. It took the entire fire brigade to bring it under control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy studying the history of Spokane, so I did a bit of research. First, I think the Hillyard yard (and township) is a bit to the right of the fire in this picture. This was also before the Kaiser plant was up. I did find a newspaper from December 1929, which mentioned how bad the wildfires were that year. So a wildfire would be my best guess. If I get a chance later I'll try to find some news stories about wildfires near Hillyard in 1929. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to what the other poster said, there is another issue with them not counting it towards data usage. In a way, it makes it much harder for potential competitors to establish themselves. 

Think of it this way: You have two streaming services (A and B) that are somewhat equal in what they offer for the user. However streaming service A doesn't count against your data usage, while streaming service B does count. So service B is at a disadvantage, and most people in that situation will choose service A moving forward. That's why people have an issue with it, as it makes it harder for new start-ups to gain an advantage.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel bad! I have a feeling the money they make off of you watching on Youtube pales in comparison to a First membership, and they will gladly take less Youtube subscribers if their number of First subscribers go up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How small would a planet/asteroid need to be for an NFL quarterback to throw a football into orbit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he meant the band? Like the landlord is okay with them breaking shit, but playing psychedelic rock is where he draws the line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, I'm at work, so is this an okay show to put in the background and just listen to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God Aleks would have been perfect in the KGB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Write from the perspective of Waldo, trying to avoid being found by assassins searching for him in large crowds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Far into the future, long after humans as we currently know them have disappeared, you are a Digital Archaeologist. You are tasked with analyzing an old robot's code to find out as much as possible about humanity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it.

It also made me think they could try ipecac, maybe in a food challenge? Last one to puke wins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you like to see as "The Last Hurrah" for the current house? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they probably have to keep it in good shape for the landlord, but let's be unrealistic and idealistic. 

Obviously, burning the house down would probably be the ultimate send-off, but what else can they do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically it's a crowdsourced writing project...

This explains it better:

https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/4nxjc5/what_is_the_scp_foundation_about/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was a Rage Quit joke. I think? The SCP Foundation Wiki is weird man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it is Tetris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be Starcraft? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll wait for the other clues, but I feel like it will be KGB killing MI6. Great Britain and USA both got more medals than Russia in Rio, so it could be either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. :( hopefully it comes back up. But thanks for the clarification! I'll check out that video later too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've considered this before, and looked into it a bit. My guess is that they won't have the manpower/demand to do it, unless there is an open-source (or premium) implementation they could adopt and add easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I really wish they would team up with Amazon. I know it would take up a bit of revenue, but I feel as though I would buy much more merch if it was stocked in the Amazon Warehouse and had Prime shipping. Hell, I wouldn't be surprised if the extra revenue from changing to Amazon covered Amazon's share of the revenue completely. 

Plus how awesome would it be if small stuff was listed as an add-on item. Like $5 keychains and stuff like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so, but can't remember completely.

In any case, they should do it again with more people and more liquor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason golf seems to be one of my favorite sports games for them to play, in all forms. Can we get a big live-action Mini-Golf with all six soon? That would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked this before but didn't get an answer... Does anybody know if this shirt is available?

https://i.redd.it/9a3gj7ohhg5y.png
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! Made it easier to follow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so Jackbox itself has no delay, because everybody is connecting to the same server, and it's serving everybody at once.

At some point during the stream, Jack mentioned the stream was 20 seconds behind (or something like that). What this means is that the audience was getting the questions 20 seconds before they saw the questions start on the stream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so to explain more fully than the other comment, it started with Steve Hutchinson. He was on the Seahawks, and the Seahawks gave him a transition tag. What this means is that basically other teams could offer a contract to him, but the Seahawks had the right to match any contract and keep him.

So the Vikings, in order to "poison pill" the contract, wrote in that if Steve wasn't the highest paid lineman on the team, then his entire contract salary became guaranteed. The issue the Seahawks had with this is that at the time Walter Jones was still on the team, and just signed a massive contract. So the Seahawks literally couldn't pay for Hutch. 

In return, the Seahawks offered a contract to Nate Burleson, who at the time was tagged on the Vikings roster. In their contract, they offered to make his entire contract guaranteed if he played more than five games in a season in Minnesota, or if he made more than all the RBs on the team combined. Obviously Minnesota couldn't match this Both parts at the time), and this is where the feud came from.

The next time the CBA came up the poison pill was elimated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> outdated

I wish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll probably get downvoted for this, knowing this sub, but I enjoyed this joke. 

Maybe he got the munchies from his avatar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Gavin has adopted the Cow Chop style of editing now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest people in this sub really hate speculation about personal lives of RT employees. Mostly because while what you said is pretty innocent, there's a small group of people that will delve way too deep into the personal lives. "I know she's not pregnant because I followed her around at the mall and she never went into a baby store!" That sort of creepyness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/mrscain for posting this originally. It was found on Rockly Bay. I'm not sure which satellite it could be as I thought the ones that failed to make it to orbit crashed in the Indian Ocean, and I didn't think the currents would take any pieces to the Caribbean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A user in /r/airplanes found what looks to be a piece of one of India's GSAT satellites on a beach in Tobago. Can you identify which specific satellite? [x-post /r/airplanes] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that /u/obersttseu is right, it's part of the GSAT satellites. What's weird is where you found it. As far as I know all of the GSAT crashes were near India in the Indian Ocean. If you don't mind, I may crosspost to /r/Space or /r/whatisthisthing to try and get it more visibility, because it's really interesting. If you would prefer you cross-post, let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I renewed, my CC details page was HTTPS, so I'm not sure why they changed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Pro-Tip: Bring a credit card, even if you don't plan on using it. You never know when shit might hit the fan, so it's good to have it just in case. 

Second tip: Budget more than you think you will actually need. Stuff comes up.

Now for how much to actually budget, /u/beckymegan hit it on the head. Beyond the fixed costs, if you have $100 a day to spend you should be absolutely golden. (Depending on how much merch you want)

Just a note, I've never actually been to RTX. This is just from my business travel, but they should be pretty similar. $50 a day for food is how much most companies budget for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest the reason I like the Xbox Minecraft is the Coop over anything else, but yeah I will definitely get the PC version soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I'm on Xbox One. Maybe I'll pick it up soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aah okay I see. /u/Xikar_Wyhart what platform are you on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you join builds like these for the community?

Specifically I would like to build some of the stuff I suggested in this thread:

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5ns346/some_minecraft_lets_plays_ive_thought_of_both/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to help! It's always mind-blowing how close to honest annihilation we came.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your pick:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vasili_Arkhipov

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1983_Soviet_nuclear_false_alarm_incident

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_nuclear_close_calls

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, but the it was well known at the time that it could all go wrong at any second. Hell, the clock was at 7 minutes to midnight in 1962, and that was when the Cuban Missile Crisis happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they are saying that right now the world is closer to Doomsday than almost any point during the Cold War, except 1953. Yeah that's just stupid. We are in bad shape now with nuclear weapons and climate change, but there were multiple points during the Cold War in which literally one guy stopped the world from being destroyed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Badminton. Could you imagine a 300lb linemen going up and lightly tapping the birdie?

Well that and synchronized swimming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh, there is a good chance it was a Sonic Boom

https://twitter.com/usaircraftspots/status/824096731902054400 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the issue overall. He keeps saying crazy shit, but it distracts from his actual actions. The stuff about inauguration crowds or voter fraud all just seems like a distraction. I mean all the news stations are running with his voter fraud claims as their lead story (at the time of this comment), meanwhile he is doing stuff in the background nobody is covering well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good eye, but Italy is definitely taking out France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
