<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8455</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 19:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, about women's hips, but I'm telling you, you could never tell! It was dark, there was just one solitary street lamp nearby, it was impossible to distinguish a sex... anyway, meybe they thought they'd attack still, if it's a guy - rob him, if it's a girl - rape her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 19:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, thank you for saving my post! ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, guys, I wanna format it, it irritates me like this, too, I just don't know how :D help?:} And ya, I know, those guys were something else.... usually such a thing would never happen in a town like ours, but that's what all smalltown people think... until it happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 08:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thank you for the ideas, in fact it never occured to me they might have been thinking of robbing a guy. But even when I came face to face with one of them he still wouldn't let go, and the way the other bastard deliberately lifted his finger and shushed... Man, I knew, I just KNEW what was going to follow if I didn't do something, anything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost Got Raped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 05:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a few years ago I was at a club with my best friend, but for some reason my mood was really bad and I wanted to go home. All went over the edge when a guy who was dancing crazily accidentally burned my hand with his cigarette. Even though he apologized, I decided that was that, and I was heading home.

I left my best friend with some people we both knew. It was winter, was really cold, and 2 in the morning. 
Now, my home town is pretty small; the club is located at the very centre, and there are always cabs waiting for clients nearby.

I thought I was gonna grab a cab, since I lived in a neighbourhood away from the centre; it was a good half an hour walk home. 

But there were no cars present at the spot. I figured it was because of the cold, but my phone was down and I couldn't call for one. Given my already pissed off state, I just waved the whole thing off and decided to walk home anyway.

Biggest mistake of my life so far.

Now bear in mind, again, it was winter. I was wearing beggy jeans, a huuuge jacket with even huger hood covering my entire face, and sneakers - from the looks of me one could never tell if I was a boy or a girl.
So I'm walking down the street, and soon I reach a point where it connects to two other streets from left and right, and the whole thing forms something like a roundabout.

Suddenly from the street on the left two guys emerge. I immediately get a sick sensation in my stomach, like I KNOW something is about to go wrong in an instant, oh, the famous female instinct. The next second my fears get confirmed when one of them starts crossing the street and coming my way. I still keep walking, we're about to pass each other by, when suddenly this motherf**** grabs me by the jacket and slams me onto the wall with my back against it. All of this happens in the spam of few seconds, and I'm so shocked I cannot believe it. He looked drunk, all I could muster to say to him was, "Get off of me!" 

Then my glance falls onto the other guy (who was much much bigger by the way), and he puts his finger on his lips, making a shushing gesture.

There and then I knew I was done. There was not a single car driving by, not a single living human being around. You can't imagine the pounding of my heart, but it was adrenaline that saved me. 

Wearing puffy winter gloves, I lift my weak hand formed into a pathetic fist, and hit the guy directly in the nose so hard I hear a cracking sound. Next split of a second I realize I gotta run, because if he grabs me again, there will be no letting go this time. 

So while he was holding his nose I sprinted away, and in my panic I crossed the road and ran by the bigger guy, who just stood and watched me in awe. 

I ran and I ran, not slipping on the icy road even a bit, I felt like my feet weren't touching the ground.. I was horrified.

Almost half the way though I stopped to catch my breath and suddenly got SO pissed at these two that I almost made a turn back to crack their heads.

NO ONE has the right to attack people!!! You can't just think you can go out and find someone you can assault! 
At this moment I thought that even if there were like 10 big guys surrounding me I could beat them all, that's how pissed I was. 

I walked the rest of the way, no one ever chased me. I wondered if I should tell my Mom this... I did, and she almost got a heart attack:} 

To this day I believe it was a combination of luck and adrenaline that saved me that night; luck, because it was the thinner of them who attacked me, and adrenaline, because without it I wouldn't be able to make such an accurate and strong punch on that idiot's face (I'm not a fighter and if need ever came to defend myself I'd be dead probably).

I hope they remember me and think twice before trying anything stupid with other girls. It still baffles me though, how they decided I was in fact a girl. Something must have given me away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
