<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject893</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timothy McVeigh was pulled over for missing plates barely an hour after the bombing. Rookie mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just sprinkle some glitter on him and let's get out of here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shh bby is ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 08:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No women ever invented an atomic bomb    

But they made a shitload of [other bombs along with guns, bullets, and other weapons.](http://www.history.com/topics/world-war-ii/world-war-ii-history/pictures/women-factory-workers-of-world-war-ii/munitions-work-world-war-ii-war-industries)
     

And Rosie the Riveter is a feminist icon. This is the sort of irony that makes me feel warm inside.    

Edit: I'm a woman, btw. I'm just as capable of horrible things as men; I simply don't have Lex Luthor money to execute them. You're all very lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, white people don't count because of TEH PRIVILEGE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 12:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to peel it so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 11:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, it makes it look like Tyra's entire face can be peeled off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 09:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in the early seasons, when the show had celebrity guests play themselves, it had the good sense to adapt the guest for the show so that it maintained its integrity. "Homer at the Bat" works so well because the writers made them fit into the usual show hijinks. Now the show builds the episode around the celebrity. Prime example: that fucking Lady Gaga episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you eat yourself if you were a hot dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show them [this.](https://comicnewbies.files.wordpress.com/2016/09/aquaman-and-mera-vs-superman-rebirth-1.png?w=620) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 11:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From *It* by Stephen King:    

"Maybe there aren't any such things as good friends or bad friends - maybe there are just friends, people who stand by you when you're hurt and who help you feel not so lonely. Maybe they're always worth being scared for, and hoping for, and living for. Maybe worth dying for too, if that's what has to be. No good friends. No bad friends. Only people you want, need to be with; people who build their houses in your heart." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muh oppression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
