<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8234</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 01:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really awesome. Lets you keep track of the beers you have and you can rate them, add pics, and check in places so you can keep track of what you like and don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 22:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 23:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hops are the bitter taste, while malt is the sweeter taste that counteracts that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 17:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all IPAs are as strong as each other, but they are mainly citrusy because of the hops. Do you like hoppy beers or malty better? Because honestly there's so many out there it's hard to narrow down..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 06:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my favorite at first but after I started tasting more and figured out that I love hops, i branched out and found stuff that makes that Amber pale in comparison. Bells has some killer brews, like Best Brown, but I've found that I really like Founders nowadays. Their Big Luscious and Black Rye are some of the best brews I've ever had. I also really love Shorts and their Wowee Zowee. There's this brewery near me called Tapistry Brewing that has a delicious double IPA called the Heart Full of Napalm, which is probably my favorite right now. 

TL;DR- get out there and try some more Michigan brews!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 06:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't had that one, but I too experienced a beergasm after tasting Founder's Big Luscious. Sweet lord..   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 06:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Horse's Scotty Karate scotch ale is in my top 5 favorite beers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the Red's Rye and I loved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone tried the Founders Black Rye yet? I had it a few weeks ago at my local pub and loved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 14:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like blues check out St. Paul and the Broken Bones. They're great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 06:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi OP,

Junior year psychology undergrad here. Considering going into cognitive neuropsychology or a similar field. Any advice on applying to graduate programs? I've already got a lot of research in (presenting at 3+ conferences this year, paper submitted for peer review), so I'm hoping that will help my chances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 08:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just started my beer journey last year. My advice is to try as much as you can- you'll get an idea of whether or not you like IPAs, Amber or Pale Ales, hoppy vs malty.. Once you figure that out, do some research and find the best of those categories. Here's my favorites so far:

Founders Black Rye
Founders All Day IPA
Founders Big Luscious 
Bells Amber Ale
Bells Christmas Ale
Frankenmuth Christmas town
Tapistry Brewing's Heart Full of Napalm
Dark Horse Scotty Karate
Shorts Wowee Zowee
New Belgium Fat Tire

Hope this helps! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 07:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Filthy McNasty and Blowin the Blues Away by Horace Silver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 07:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I think something like Romanza would be great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 07:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Blue in Green for the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 18:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn man as a fellow Chicagoan that is one hell of a walk. The water is really gorgeous at night though, I can definitely see the appeal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 03:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and rightie have a lot of intimate moments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 03:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked a girl out to a dance once by heating up a fortune cookie, opening it and putting my own note inside and sealing it back up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 21, junior psychology major working for my professors doing research. I love what I do, but I can't wait to go to grad school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beer in the Joe Louis is SO overpriced. IIRC they were offering 20oz cans of Molson for 10$.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 07:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you're pulling the intrinsic/extrinsic motivation definitions from Allport and Ross. If that's the case, I don't really agree. Allport and Ross basically assumed that intrinsic and extrinsic motivations determined human behavior without taking into account any other extraneous variables. Human motivation is so much more complex than this theory allows. Imo, it pretty much limits motivations to intrinsic or extrinsic causes. I just cannot see how that's all there is to it. 

I recently did a study on the relationship between religiosity and perceived levels of stress. I used an intrinsic/extrinsic religiosity scale but none of the subscales explained any of the variance for the stress scores. I used an internalization scale instead, which predicted somewhere around 30-40% of the variance. Internalization basically means that you move a belief or view from the external, to the internal, where you truly believe it. It's like comparing following Christ because you believe in him to following him out of peer pressure or guilt. 

Anyway, I just think that internalization of beliefs are waay more important than extrinsic/intrinsic values when discussing human motivation. As far as the purposes of serotonin and dopamine go, I don't really know the answer to that- it would be really interesting to see if there were any correlations. Have you done a literature search? That might hold some answers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 02:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psychology major here. If you want any ideas/advice, feel free to PM me. I'm just finishing up my junior year of undergrad and about to start applying for grad school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 22:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried scotch for the first time a few weeks ago and made the mistake of having good scotch (Glenvilet 15 year, damn good in my opinion). All other alcohol is ruined for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 09:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan is the best for beer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 04:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Petitioning was more of a joke. I was more or less interested in the idea of Netflix picking it up and making a spinoff. I really enjoyed your analysis though! I hadn't thought it through that far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 01:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a Forbes article about how they thought that LoK should be picked up as a Netflix series. I think we should start a petition. A Netflix version of LoK would be amazing. It could finally be a serious, gritty show instead of something geared toward kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 13:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up telling her exactly how I felt about her and that I thought that even if she was scared our friendship would change I thought that we could get through it and be fine but she played it off and acted like I misinterpreted the whole thing. I ended up telling her that I would respect whatever decision she made and I wouldn't push it.. Kinda regretting saying that now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 05:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube! They have most if not all of the episodes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 05:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just started my craft beer journey. My favorites so far are Dark Horse's Scotty Karate Scotch Ale, Bell's Best Brown, Founder's Big Luscious, and Seventh Son's Wildermann Autumn Farmhouse Ale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 07:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a free speech issue. Free speech means you can't be censored by the government. This is Sony making a business decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 06:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homeland. I downloaded the first season and I'm absolutely loving it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is so fucking cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever been over to piece pizza in wicker park? I swear that place is a gift from heaven  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 05:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a tour of JHU this summer and their cognitive science program is pretty much all Linguistics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 18:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I just had a Bell's Christmas ale for the first time and I was really impressed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 21:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native Louisianaian here. 
Let's be honest- Cafe Du Monde coffee comes in pre-packaged cans. I've been places that served it, but nothing even comes close to the original. 

My Etouffee usually comes out in a darker brown color. I've never had anything really pink.. maybe with a pink hue, but not really overtly pink. The only place I've ever been to outside of Louisiana that did Cajun food well was this place called Yatz in Indianapolis, and the owners there were from New Orleans. The etouffee I like is usually really bold flavor-wise- heavy on seasonings, and more like a thick sauce than a curry or soup. I've had etouffee that had the consistency of gumbo, and was extremely disappointed.. My best advice? Keep your expectations low for quality of food when you're looking at Cajun outside of Louisiana- I currently live in Michigan, and anything labelled Cajun here usually only has some sort of seasoning akin to Tony's (although not nearly as good). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 06:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a Founder's Big Luscious and a Bell's Christmas ale in your honor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved it! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 00:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 year old college student, Male, psychology major, from Louisiana  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 16:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, since RS went down the drain its a way for me to keep the nostalgia around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 16:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Devon Street! The culture there is just really an amazing thing to experience. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 07:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my old runescape username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 16:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/eyebleach  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 05:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend buying some American DJ PAR24s or PAR56's with gel and just plugging them into static power. Dmx is going to be too much of a hassle if you don't know how to control it and if you don't have a guy to run it for you. Buy some of those pars and do uplights/washes with them. You'll have to buy gel frames and gels but it shouldn't set you back too much. Look for a tech dealer/rental company in your area to determine what gels you want. I'd recommend Rosco or Apollo. 

You could also go LED- Monoprice has LEDs for around 100$ a fixture. I've used them a lot, they're surprisingly good! You could use them as uplights or something but you'd have to set them to standalone mode. LEDs don't have a bulb to burn out or gels to ruin so that might be a better option for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 22:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know if you can get mega glalie and mega steelix? I've got glalie but I really wanted to find steelix too..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 05:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to go but I don't know if I can afford to drive two and a half hours.. Anyone think it'll be worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 16:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminded me a bit of the Bells Amber Ale. It was a solid amber ale, with a perfect mix of malt and hops, with a great nutty note at the end. Less hoppy than the bells amber ale, with a bit more malt. I haven't had anything from Founders that really reminded me of it. More of a Bells/Dark Horse drinker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 20:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't tell you. I'm from Michigan, visiting Columbus on a job. I'm well versed in Michigan brews but this is my first time having an Ohio one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 05:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're planning on English I honestly see no reason to take the class in the first place. Any English program looking at your transcript won't care about a dropped statistics class, or even one with a C.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of a statistics nut- I took two semesters of psychology stats and loved it. I'm currently an undergraduate psychology major. 

I would recommend roughing it out. Sure, your GPA will look better- but colleges want you to take hard classes. The thing I regret most about high school is not challenging myself. I'm not saying you aren't, but by dropping out I think you're underestimating yourself. Statistics is more about logic than math. Get a tutor. Go to a local university and get some help. Google homework problems and do them. Look up YouTube videos and try to understand the overall picture. Don't give up just because it's hard- buckle down and finish it! Don't sell yourself short- if you really tried you could probably pull off a C+ or a B- by the end of the semester. 

Also, what field are you interested in? If it's anything science related, especially psych, you'll need statistics anyway. 

If you'd like any more advice, feel free to pm me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 06:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite episode was the butter shave, where Newman gets hungry because he smells the butter on Kramer.. I just die laughing every time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 01:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. I'm 21 and still haven't had a relationship or even a first kiss  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 01:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind me asking, when did you start having sex? Also, how often? 58 is the highest number in here so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 21:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it better than Oberon. One of my favorite restaurants had a Bells tap takeover so I had a lot of fun trying some different brews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 19:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not. Look on the official website. You can fly across hoenn and land wherever you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 05:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infusco Coffee Roasters in Sawyer, Mi and Gaslight Coffee Roasters in Chicago, Il </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 07:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you mentally orgasm? Is there a process you go through?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 16:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it OP. If your heart is there, go. Don't regret not taking the chance later on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 07:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one about 7 years ago for 45$. Little expensive but this thing has never let me down! It's amazing. Still works as great as the day I got it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 16:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Striped* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're a proctologist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 06:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in your situation. the absolute best advice I can give you is walk away. you need time for yourself. You need time away from her to heal and get over her. Do whatever you need to- delete her number, Facebook, all social media- whatever it is you feel like you need to do, do it. Your happiness and comfort comes first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 04:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sign me up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 01:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northern MI is fantastic. Check out Petoskey and Traverse City while you're up there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 22:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha since I'm just getting into beer I had no idea Michigan had this much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 19:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually heard that Founders quality has gone down in the past few years. Any idea if that's true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 19:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea. Haven't seen it around but that doesn't mean much. I'm gonna try and make it to Kzoo and visit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I should've mentioned that before. 

I'll check those out. The only Michigan beers I've had so far have come from Round Barn Winery, so I really want to try the good Michigan brews while I'm still here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about 20 minutes away from Greenbush. I've heard great things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 08:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee is casual. Bring her somewhere nice. as you start to get to know her more, it'll be easier to figure out whether she's interested or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 16:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 16:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live near Chicago.. Where would you recommend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 06:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a quick lit review, looks like there's some interesting research going on in the field. 

This suggests language affects the way people perceive color: http://cdp.sagepub.com/content/13/3/95.short

This is more of a neuroscience based article on brain activation in an MRI while people are looking at colors in their right and left visual fields: http://www.pnas.org/content/106/20/8140.full

This looks at language-specific terminology and color perception: http://www.pnas.org/content/106/11/4567.full

Pretty interesting stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 01:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mobile

http://m.cliphunter.com/w/1256187/Lena_Nicole_Evening_Pleasure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 00:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about a nice guitar pedal? Maybe a custom guitar case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambridge University Jazz Orchestra - Count Bubba, Ischia, 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 01:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide is not the answer. Things WILL get better. 

I was suicidal for a few years. Then, my grandpa killed himself in my driveway. Blew his brain all over the pavement. after going through that.. Enduring that pain, constantly replaying that day in my mind, wishing I could've changed things.. I could never put my loved ones in that situation. 

Life is a bitch. It sucks. There's going to be bad days. But OP, I promise it will get better. It took me a long time to get better.. But now I've found a girl I love and I'm now in a place where I'm happy. It'll happen for you too. 


If you're really suicidal, try /r/offmychest or /r/suicidewatch. There are people out there willing to help. You just have to reach out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 15:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about two hours from Ann Arbor and GR. Just north of South bend, IN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 15:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm located in southwest Michigan. I've tried most of the local stuff though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Where do you get your favorite beans from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 01:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my friends is having a birthday coming up and he's a fanatic about coffee. He's tried a lot of different companies (Intelligentsia, Whiskey Barrel, ect.) so I'm looking for something good that he hasn't tried yet. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 08:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undergrad psych major here. Going to grad school in two years. 

Here's how I look at it: sure, phd is more school, but I don't want to look back 20 years from now and wish I would've done it. I'm a huge advocate of continuing education- PhD programs are worth it simply because a lot of them will give you a masters along the way if you enroll straight from undergrad. In addition to the financial benefits, she'll be much better equipped to be competitive in research as well. Plus she'll be taken more seriously by juries with a phd than a MA in court settings 

The GRE is a glorified ACT. just get some study guides, like the one that has the 500 most commonly used words on the GRE, and study for it. Most psych majors make a 300 on it, and grad schools like 310-320 I believe, so after retaking it a few times she'll be fine

Speaking from experience here, find a grad school that does research she's interested in. I just looked at the Johns Hopkins cog sci department and realized it wasn't for me merely because all of their research is in linguistics and I'm just not interested in that. Chances are once she enrolls in a program she'll be doing the same project for the length of the program, so she needs to find a school with professors that do research she's interested in. Once she does, have her email them and find out more.. Ask for their articles, ask questions.. Eventually when she applies they'll want her because of that interest she has. IMO most of what grad schools look for are 1). Research experience 2). Letters of recommendation. If she has either of those, she'll be able to find a school that fits her 

Sorry for the lengthy post. If you have any questions feel free to PM me or have her PM me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 00:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not a masterpiece, but Hot Club of Detroit is great. I've tried posting about them on this sub before but haven't ever gotten anywhere.. They sound like classic Django Reinhardt and have consistently been putting out good stuff in the past few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 05:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I hated math until I took stats. Now I'm using it at my research job in the department every day. Never thought one of my favorite parts of being a psych major would be the data analysis.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 05:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own a '97 TJ currently so I know a bit about older vehicles. 

From those pics, looks like he babied the hell out of it. Definitely looks promising. Word of advice: drop 100$ or so and get it checked out by a good mechanic just to be sure that he's not trying gyp you. 

As far as owning an older jeep: jeep ownership is amazing. I love the freedom- taking the doors and top off is fantastic in my area during the summer. Also, I love being able to do my own mechanic work. Because there's hardly any electronics, besides the obvious, it's super simple to work on. I just replaced all four of my brake lines in an afternoon. That kind of freedom IMO isn't found too often with newer cars. Mine tends to have problems now and again but all of it is so simple that I don't mind. Plus, I'm in love with mine- might be a bit of a rust bucket but I love the thing. 

Look for rust on the under carriage and frame. Also, pay attention to the age of the wiring under the hood- it'll be a good indicator of whether you'll have issues in the future. Check out all the hoses and lines (brake, fuel, ect) to make sure that they're not too rusted out. Even if they are, I'd still invest in it and try and get the price down due to the rust. Check the differentials, brakes, and engine bay for wetness or moist areas. Might be an indicator of a bad gasket, radiator, hose, ect. start it up first before checking. 

Above all, test drive it. Get a feel for the transmission, how it shifts, how the brakes are (spongy, solid, ect), how acceleration is, any weird noises. Driving it will give you more information than anything else will. 

Owning an older vehicle is definitely a bit different but it's rewarding nonetheless. I wouldn't pass this one up just for it's age- from the pictures and price, if everything checks out, it's a steal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 04:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be new here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 03:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a dumbass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 23:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you drive an older car without a USB or Aux port, a FM transmitter. Most have a USB charger as well. I got mine from monoprice and it's worked great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 17:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quality headphones/sound gear. It'll completely change the way you listen to music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 16:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a tad late here, but I know the people who started this. They tried, and failed, to succeed on kickstarter. A big group of people from the university goes to Chicago, or some other big city, hold these signs, and talk to people. They're all gung-ho about it, and act like they're implementing a culture change. It's pretty funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
