<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3775</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For nearby stars, the distance can be determined through parallax measurements. The position of the star is measured against the background of distant stars, or preferably galaxies, at opposite sides of the Earth's orbit around the sun. The star will show a shifted position from these two readings. From these two position readings, you can compute an angle between the two observations Knowing the distance from opposite sides the Earth's orbit, or actually just the Earth's distance from the Sun, because you take half the angle between the positions. So you now have a right triangle from which you know the base (the distance from earth to the sun), and the angle at the apex (the line direct from the sun to the star, and the line from the earth to the star). Albeit, it is a very tall and narrow triangle, but using trigonometry you can compute the length of the sides of the triangle with the angle and base length. It's a little more complicated than that because you also have to look at the offset angle of the star from plane of the Earth's orbit, and compute a correction to the length of the base; but using this method you can get pretty accurate out to about 100 parsecs or 326 light years.   

The other method that is used is to look at the star's brightness in the sky compare the measured brightness to a model of how bright a star of that size   type should be --i.e. compare it's actual/relative brightness to a model of the absolute brightness for a star of its size and type. The difference between these can be used to compute the distance due to light attenuating over distance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very much like the assertions that Islam requires women to be shrouded, segregated from non relative males, etc. despite never appearing to be codified in any sacred religious texts. The ban on women in the preisthood may very well be dogma, but it is a reflection of "culture" rather than having any basis in the religion itself. Claiming it is part of the core religious belief is simply a power argument where an entrenched group seeks to maintain their monopoly by claiming a historical practice is equivalent to adhering to the religion itself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point was the poor, and not so poor too, are angry about the direct economic impact of reduced coal production. They don't care about the long term health costs to themselves as miners  or to themselves as having to live on the land and breathe the air polluted by coal and the resultant coal ash. They also don't care about co2 warming the planet. Hard to care about that when you've lost your job  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [link](https://www.math.hmc.edu/funfacts/ffiles/20010.5.shtml) is for the "Nth" and following  digits of pi in base 16 with a very compact and linear time expansion without first computing the prior N digits. I recall when this was published and there being discussion about it being a boon to cryptology because you could easily use it for cryptographic keys. In any event, wondered why you couldn't use this to compute a sequence in Hex, approximating about where the Nth base 10 digit would be, then convert the Hex digit answer to base 10. Is your question concerned with getting to exactly the Nth base 10 digit, or being able to quickly get to some randomly chosen position in the sequence of pi, and representing it in base 10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to burst your bubble, but that looks very much like a rock with recent barnacle and other mollusk "footprints" left on it after the shells got worn off in the surf. The rock does not appear polished enough to be seeing these actually embedded in the matrix of stone
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does "a great deal of influence" mean? Is it implied they're lesbians, which would be a kind of puritanical / moral backlash. Consider if president park had a long time male lover, would there be such angst about someone personnally close to the president advising her? Another analogy might very well be Nancy Reagan's astrologist. Supposedly Nancy's influence of Ron, and the astrologists influence over Nancy lead to cases where the Astrologist's advice was used in US presidential decision making. One can see how this would also be very negative, implying a lack of serious and professional judgement in the person one expects to have a level, serious mind controlling the direction of the country. Everything else I can see as simply hyperbole that Korea's equivalent of Foxnews, Brietbart have spun their own cult like disciples into a frenzy over, having scented blood in the water.  

--EDIT---  
It is a valid question I think. It seems there is a lot of passion in the controversy that from a distance, people outside of Korea don't understand. It would be helpful if you could make explicit what is behind some of the euphemisms or innuendo that are behind this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you look at the political anger in West Virginia and Kentucky, there are, or were, a lot of poor people mining coal in these states. There were also a lot of people making big bucks out of those coal mines. They're also slicing the tops of mountains off to get to the coal and filling up green valleys with tailings from those sliced off mountains. Poor people are impacted by the pollution, by the permanent destruction of green space, etc; but what they remember is when they lose their job. When the power plant down the river converts the boilers to gas, or installs gas turbines, they stop buying coal and the coal mine drops shifts, or closes entirely. They don't care their health is being ruined, their kids are sick, their land is being polluted. They care that they can't buy hot dogs and budweiser because they're not working shifts anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, it never was. A lot more land was exposed than it is today, but at a minimum, they would have had to cross about 100 miles of open water. They must have had boats or rafts of some kind to get to Australia
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, birth is going to be just like that too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 1980's I worked on sonar systems for the US Navy that were designed for operations under the polar ice cap. The descriptions of the underside of the cap were of a giant upside down forest and jumbled upside down mountain ranges formed from multi-year ice piling up and getting pushed down in a jagged icescape.  This was in contrast to the single year sea ice that forms a monotoniic flat ice ceiling. With the arctic moving toward a ice free summers, that high surface area/lots of hiding places under ice environment is disappearing. It calls into question what ecological niches are disappearing with that undersea icescape? What species depend on it for development and survival?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snakes on a plane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worry when I feel it pulling from 3 inches up inside my nose that a chunk of brain is going to come out on the end of the hair. Nothing like that snap when the deep follicle lets go though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL - Disney cartoon men shave their armpits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't bogart that tank my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had astronomy buffs talk about the Andromeda galaxy being as wide as 6 full moons if you have dark enough sky to see it. When I've looked at it through the telescope though, what I've seen looks a lot like this picture and is a small tight core much smaller than a full moon. For a three hour exposure, it seem like you ought to be seeming the width of the galaxy in the sky. Can you talk about the size of this field of view? Is it the larger, 6 full moons wide view we're seeing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to theory, Neanderthals left Africa about 300,000 years ago, settling in Europe and parts of western Asia.  

I've never seen it stated that Neanderthals migrated out of Africa. Instead it has been implied in diagrams that Neanderthals evolved from homo heidelbergus from a population that dispersed out of Africa 800-600 k years ago. --i.e. Neanderthals evolved in place on the Eurasian land mass. It make no sense for Africans to have no Neanderthal genes if Neanderthal came out of Africa  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, I thought Perigrine Falcons held the record as the fastest flyers, with speeds of +200 mph in a dive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was his name Andy Capp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 15:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a kid going to school in New Mexico, there was a small tongue of Texas about 1/2 mile wide and about 2 miles long that stuck out of Texas across the longitude ~~130~~ 101 degree west meridian into New Mexico (NM eastern side)on large scale state maps they had in the classroom. It still showed up on maps when Mapquest first started doing online mapping, but no longer appears in Google maps or Bing. I figured there had to be an interesting story around that but have never seen it explained, or its disappearance in modern days  
----- EDIT ----   
Actually, the more I think about it, the tongue might have been the opposite direction - a bit of New Mexico intruding into Texas. Either way it's missing from maps now. Anybody that knows, would be interested to the story.  

----EDIT 2 --- 
Yah, typo/dyslexia reading the longitude off google maps mouse pointer URL: 101st meridian. The tongue shaped protrusion was near Clovis NM/Cannon AFB (south of there). Often wondered if it was some kind of federal thing associated with the military </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ask women if they want to see your scars from a vicious animal bite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the archeological record, it is clear they were making [ceremonial robes](http://www.northernearth.co.uk/img/freres3.jpg) and not rugs! The drapes did not match the carpet!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm hemlock mmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 13:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide drones have a more common name: cruise missiles. Promoting the terminology "suicide" shows what sick values pervade the Irananian regime, where the idea of a suicide bomber is considered something other than a perverted, diseased mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any theory predicting the half-lives of the heavier atomic nuclei that has been verified with practical measurements? In the wiki page they say the half lives predicted for the island of stability range from mintues/days to millions of years? What effect are these different predictions using and is there any way to validate or calibrate any of them without actually making the element? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she just liked having birds around the house without them being hunted. Stray cats are officially feral animals and are considered vermin in many areas. Recent studies have demonstrated the degree to which both stray and pet cats hunt and kill small birds is creating a trend toward extinction. Won't say I understand the circumstances of your wife's "hobby" but suggest you'd probably think nothing of getting out the ole .22 to shoot rats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broad is always the preferred term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow on - how does the IRB approval differ for pet animal vs human vs lab animal clinical trials? Are you projecting some of the factors that would normally apply to human trials but not lab animal trials onto the trial with pets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a recent nature magazine podcast discussed some of the issues around a recent trend to start using house pets in clinical drug trials. The lack of strict environmental controls, dosing and genetic diversity of pets vs standard laboratory animals was cited for both positive and negative factors. How have you modified your trial protocols for these factors (as compared to how you would run a trial with lab mice or ferrets for example)? Motivation was another topic discussed. Pet trials are seen as more realistic than lab animal studies when trying a drug with potential as a human drug. However there is downside of not being able to ask the drug subject how they feel, e.g. Quality of life and adverse side effect issues that can be captured in a human trial. Will you be utilizing the pet owners assessment of these type of factors in your trial methodology / data collection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you're under a huge pile of spiders. God, hope they don't all wake up at once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the DoJ has told banks they will be charged with laundering drug proceeds if they provide banking services to legal marijuana dispensaries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is really disturbing is how many republicans think this fair play and consistent with the civil government ideals of our country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I need you to validate this with my friend's pictures from the dead sea. Their tour guide apparently told them the black salty mud of the dead sea bottom has skin conditioning qualities. He came home with pictures of them floating in the dense water, completely covered in dark black mud. I mean completely covered with only a tiny tiny ring of white flesh around the eyes. You're saying there's some alternative to sticking your head in the water to wash this off? Do tour buses usually have a fresh water shower for such cleanup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it would make a difference if the heard sound rather than the flag was the start. At the beginning of the race you're trying to hit the starting line at full speed. If you're early you need to slow down and turn aside so you don't cross the line before the start. Often there are other boats along the line to the race committee, so you can't see the signal. In that case you need the audio to know you're not over early </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember. I'm pretty sure it was novella in a collected of "year's best", but probably from sometime back in the 80's or 90's when the mandelbrot set was all the rage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lunar excursion module (LEM) lander legs [had spikes on the ends of the pads](http://www.astronautix.com/graphics/1/10075054.jpg), intended to help stabilize the position of the lander when it came down. There was some thought the Moon's surface might be covered in deep dust that the pads wouldn't stably rest on. For Apollo 11, they took the spike off the LEM leg with the ladder on it, fearing it might bend back up from rock underneath. The concern was amstrong walking down the ladder would impale himself on it and die while billions watched on TV  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's less than a second difference, but if you're 1/4 mile or more away, you definitely hear the end of the sound on the radio and then the through the air sound start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radio waves do move at the speed of light through the medium in which they are passing. The speed of light in a vacuum is c. But the speed of radio (and light)in air, although slower than c, is still "the speed of light" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once read a science fiction/fantasy story that was based on the idea that hell was a julia set that traversed the entire world (the mandelbrot set is a specific instance of the julia set class of sets). Demons could only travel through hell to get to any location on the world --ie along the filament of the julia set that is hell. In the world of magic/fantasy, these are called Ley Lines. The thing that your question reminded me of was multiple references in the story to the fact that the total area of hell was exactly 1/2 acre; hence the expression "Hell's Half Acre" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The race is actually started with a flag raised at the same time. The visual signal is the one you use, but if you're  relying on sound, the radio is more accurate The race starts when the sound is emitted, not when you hear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody recently asked a question on askscience about being able to hear the time difference between the actual sound path and the sound being picked up by radio/walkietalkie transmitted at speed of light, and re-issued as sound by the receiver. It so happens I have direct experience with this in yacht/sailboat racing. The committee boat uses a horn or shotgun to signal various time points in the starting sequence: Basically a "ready","set","1 minute" and "go" set of sound signals. These can either be 3 minutes or 5 minutes apart (except for the 1 minute before the "go" signal). The starting line is usually about 1/4 mile long. Boats of multiple classes waiting for their start are sailing and milling about an area of about 1/2 mile radius from the race committee. The race committee keeps an open radio channel calling out which of multiple different starts they're doing, and giving a 5-4-3-2-1 count down for some signals. (This helps people setting their watch). Point is, the sound of the horn or shotgun used for the signal goes through the radio channel, and yes you can hear a very definitely difference in the sound arrival time from the radio vs. direct path to your ear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you like it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idaho National Lab is mainly known for nuclear technology (correct me if wrong, but isn't a big reason it exists to train US Navy nuclear reactor officers?). You state you're looking at low carbon solutions, nuclear and renewable. While I believe nuclear needs to play a role in our future energy needs, I'm wondering at the juxtaposition of both nuclear and renewables in your statement. How much of your research efforts goes into each category? Are there any energy solutions that nuclear/renewable hybrid technology?  What would a hybrid nuclear/renewable system look like or produce as output? Are there any paths to use nuclear energy to produce high energy density portable chemical fuels?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW - on my only visit to iceland, the rental car company gave us a couple bottles of water in the car. It was the best tasting water I'd ever had. The tap water all over the country was absolutely delicious and pure tasting. Back here in the USA, have started seeing icelandic bottled water on the shelves. It's good, but not quite to par with the water in iceland. Don't know why any of you would put ice from tap water from other countries when you have such an incredible resource locally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like 85% total is renewable, 15% fossil. Of the 85%, 64% hydro, 21% geo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is especially crazy in terms of carbon footprint because most power in Iceland is generated renewably with zero carbon footprint. Almost certainly any ice from the USA ice plants is going to fossil fuel generated. So why then is Icelandic ice so expensive? One possibility is cost of labor involved in Iceland (no help there Ivarson); but there's a distinct possibility it is due to the higher cost of electrical power in iceland. Geothermal is clean but it took a lot of custom engineering to make it work. You can think of it as already paying carbon tax (since none of those carbon tax dollars helped fund that capital investment). The answer to this conundrum is those imported ice cubes should be taxed for their carbon footprint, and that money used to subsidize the geothermal industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will Ireland throw off the last vestiges of British domination, join the civilized world and start driving on the right side of the road? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judge already threw out the charges against democracy now reporter. Seems like a special prosecutor is needed to investigate the prosecutor bringing these charges. There appears to be undue influence and conspiracy behind these charges </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps they should look in the [hollows of any oak trees](http://colonialwarsct.org/1687.htm) near the parliment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientists have described several different orca populations in the areas off the Washington State and British Columbian coasts. The ones usually seen in the whale watching boats are known as "Resident" populations, are highly social and tend to interact with humans. They feed primarily on a limited species of Salmon. Two other groups are less social, one of which has been observed hunting sea lions as well as stealing salmon from fishermen's nets. They're less social and some fishermen have reportedly indicated they felt threatened or like they were being stalked. When spotted, these orca tend to move away, as if they know the  consequences of getting caught. It suggests that yes, they leave no survivors; but also they are careful not be witnessed either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact, Duterte is EXACTLY what a Trump presidency in the US would look like: an asshole shooting off his mouth about things and announcing changes to policies that the legal process of government does not permit without acts of law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the gulf coast of Florida's panhandle, starting in about November and continuing into December, sometimes January, you see a lot of robins gathering along the coastline. It's weird because you don't think of robins in flocks, but that's what you see. Hundreds and hundreds of them lined up on park benches and dunes, looking out at the gulf. It's like they're waiting for a good northerly breeze or trying to get their nerve up. When the cold fronts start clocking across the country in the winter, they get that north wind. After the first big one hits, they're mostly gone but a few who have arrived late or didn't have the nerve hang around, sometimes all winter. They tend to disappear when spring comes around, I think catching a ride with first ones flying back up from their winter in ~~Costa Rica~~ Central America and the Caribbean   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woooohoo! Hook'em Longhorns!
What fraternity are y'all in dudes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abortion was legalized in 1973. Most street crime is committed by people 15-25 year old (40% of all arrests). In 1985, a good percentage of the 15 year olds who would have been entering into their crime careers to replace those who were aging out, simply didn't exist. They had been aborted. The trend really kicked into gear in the early 90's as more than half of the street criminal prime ages had been subjected to being legally aborted. By 1998, an entire cohort of 15-25 year olds who would have been raised unwanted children simply didn't exist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a quote from an online [Thorium Reactor page:](https://whatisnuclear.com/articles/thorium_myths.html)  
Thorium reactors work by breeding Th-232 through Protactinium-233 (27.4 day half life) and into Uranium-233, which is fissile. Pa-233 is a pretty strong neutron absorber, so the MSBR (basically the LFTR) has to extract it from the core once it is produced and let it decay to U-233 away from the neutrons. Once the U-233 is created, it gets fed back into the reactor. Well, if you went rogue, you could build up a little excess reactivity (maybe add some low-enriched U235?) and then divert the freshly-bred U-233 into a weapons stream to make U-233 nuclear bombs. It may be difficult to do this several times without going subcritical, but it certainly could be done. A U-233-filled bomb has been tested before, and it worked just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say Uranium and Plutonium, you're actually talking about specific isotopes, Uranium 235 (as opposed to the more abundant U-238) and Plutonium-239.  There are other isotopes of Uranium which could potentially be used to make bombs but typically have not been. U-233 is sometime cited as a bomb candidate material. It is produced as a by product of the supposedly safe "Thorium Fuel" reactor and undercuts the thorium reactor proponents argument that the technology is not a nuclear proliferation risk. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, given the breadth of your experience and the specific militaries you've had contact with, are you at all concerned about being able to be identified and having blowback from your frank comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter, apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teabagging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the implications of the extinct palaeomerycids  being giraffomorphs rather than Cervids? Does this mean that other giraffomorph species could potentially have populated wider ranges of the Eurasian continent? Are there any evolutionary theories to explain the predominance of two antlered ruminant species over three and four antlers? Is there evidence of a sort of "antler Pre-Cambrian explosion" before evolution decided the two antler pattern was the most biologically efficient antler pattern?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused on several levels. The DA didn't want to indict the cop at all, yet the headline says he was convicted of involuntary manslaughter. Yet again, the man he shot apparently lived, although his wife died as a result of the accident. Was the cop charged in the wife's death? How did that work? Does the cop continue to face further charges from having shot the man who was driving the car? Is the person who was convicted of manslaughter actually the man driving the car (whose wife was killed), meaning the reddit article title is totally misleading? If this is the case, has the cop actually walked away scott free? What does that mean? Who was Scott, and what was he accused of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've got my my scent on you!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the ABV for an OG chicken?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In his book guns, germs and steel, Jared Diamond discussed the characteristics that made a species a good candidate for domestication. In most of the world, megafauna that didn't meet these criteria have been mostly wiped out. Africa retains the most diverse sets of undomesticatable species, with numerous antelope and giraffe populations. Is there anything in phylogenetically to suggest why so many mega fauna species persist in Africa when they don't in other parts of the world  
--EDIT---  
? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A recent paper that received news focus indicated giraffes, formerly considered a single species, were in fact four separate species. It seems the definition of what is and is not a species has blurred in recent years due to examination of genetic evidence. As an example there was recent move to delist the American red wolf as a species. This gives the impression species definition has become somewhat subjective. What are the objective criteria phylogenetics uses to declare a population as a separate species, or in the case of the red wolf, retract a species designation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Footage of Architeuthis aka the giant squid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 22:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Is this some kind of joke](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5HvV-rB-ltc)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good concept but think it would be improved with a striding chicken and player in an active hitting stance/mallet swing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eyeball staring from the ceiling is a nice touch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 02:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny. That's how rule of law works, something Trump specifically and the GOP more generally doesn't believe in. Guess it's like the Geneva convention, you need to not torture prisoners, bomb hospitals or arrest diplomats even when your opponents don't adhere to those principles, because otherwise nobody will follow them. Oh wait  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How will the Cubs winning the World Series precipitate the apocalypse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, that's a union fireman's workweek: 2 days on, 5 days off. 2 days on is 48 hours straight on duty. On duty means ready, waiting for a call. No fire? There's a weight room to work out. Some training too. Tired? There's bunks to sleep in. You're getting paid while you sleep. The important thing is that you're there ready to depart for a fire. Your 48 hours are up? Long as you're not fighting a fire, 5 blissful days of weekend in front of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to hear a dramatic reading of this work by Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A strong case could be made for the [hippo](http://forgifs.com/gallery/d/186445-2/Hippo_poop_sprinkler.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The inside of my beer cap looks like a butthole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 14:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cherry flavored dried cranberries? What foul thing is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Period of Cardinals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, what I'm looking for is charging prosecutors with conspiracy and accessory after the fact when they refuse to file charges against murdering cops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 13:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, will the tax be levied on the CO2 produced from processing the tar sands bitumen into crude oil? What about the refineries emissions in cracking crude into gasoline? Or, will all of those cumulative emissions simply be tacked on to the price of gas at the pump? Who will be the ultimate payers of this tax? The corporations or the end consumers? From an economic standpoint, doesn't matter? I say it does. If the corporations have to pay for the emissions in the processing pipeline, they'll be more inclined to develop cleaner, more efficient production methods. If the end consumer has to pay, then they just continue. Usiness as usual while the common man bears the burden  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 02:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The federal government build a huge plant to get rid of the hydrocarbon pollution in lake mead by bubbling ozone through it. My uncle supervised the installation of the largest stainless steel Venturi tube ever built for returning the cleaned water to the lower lake levels. If they'd dumped the clean water back into the lake surface it would have gradually diluted the pollution, making it take longer to complete. Thus, the huge tube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This stuff was not grainy in texture. I was like a blob of epoxy with the consistency of axle grease.  I was sawing with the hacksaw and he had his face close watching the cut. He had just cranked up the pressure on the vise, trying to split the shell, when this blob shot out. It  hit in the corner of his eye, we were able to wipe most of it away, with it leaving a grey smear stuck to his skin next to the eye and some of still in his eye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> science class </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure one of my flights landing in Austin TX was struck by lightning and yes, it was loud as fuck. The smell of ozone also filled the plane: sharp metallic smell that often accompanies a electric motor burning up. Thankfully there was no smoke and the smell rapidly cleared. Only thing I can think of was ozone was generated by the lightning strike and was sucked into the cabin air intake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 14:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are we looking at for the foliage next to the lake? These look like the trees are in bloom, but that is unlikely this late in the season? Is that frost crystals off the ends of the leaves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The incident in question happened about 1971, so that was possibly one of said old balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 15:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid we used to collect balls from the margin of a golf course to take home and do the same. We'd put them in my friend's father's vise and use a hacksaw to cut the shell. This was tricky as the shells tended to be slick and required multiple cuts until you could peel the shell off. We'd peer closely at the cut looking for the start of the dark colored rubber bands starting to show. On one occasion we discovered some balls are instead filled with a liquid goo when a jet of the sticky grey stuff shot out and went into my friend's eye. He screamed in pain. We had a panicked few minutes rinsing his eye, him swearing it was acid burning his eye out. He was ok but it gave a view that not all golf balls have the same construction  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ATownStomp, you're a snotty little shit; but since you're also apparent an intense scholar,  here you go:

After Martin Cahill  the Irish gangster known as the General  stole 18 paintings from the Beit Collection at Russborough House in County Wicklow in 1986, the artworks led an extraordinary life. One painting was sent to Istanbul, where it was used as part of a payment for a heroin deal. Four other paintings  including a Gainsborough, a Goya and a Vermeer  were taken to Antwerp, where a diamond dealer accepted them as collateral and advanced Cahill a large sum of money, with which he tried to start an offshore bank in the Bahamas.   

From
https://priceonomics.com/how-do-you-make-money-off-stolen-art/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not laundering the art. The art is transferred from one criminal organization to another as a "front payment" before a several ton shipment of cocaine or heroin is moved from the 2nd to the first. A drug lord might actually display the art for themself but considered unlikely - same as you would never get your gold bullion bricks out of the vault to just play and feel them. Because they're so small, they're easily and unobtrusively transferred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spate of thefts of very valuable, very well know paintings by masters in recent years has been speculated to be driven by organized crime needing collateral for high value financial transactions. The anti money laundering regulation and surveillance/reporting of large financial transfers has driven organized crime into barter transactions. Works of art like these are used in the same way that nations previously would transfer gold bullion. Gram for gram, they're thousands of times more valuable and more compact than gold  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK, the dipper is called "The Plow". The ancient  Britons said it  looked like a big dick with massive balls getting ready to do the missus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wells Fargo said in a statement that it apologizes for not living up to its commitment of ensuring that *all service members "receive the appropriate benefits and protections." *  

Wait, so was this illegal only because the victims were service members? Meaning, the actions they took were perfectly valid against ordinary citizens ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you beating a dead camel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like symbol for a devil woman with dicks for horns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be higher up - you have to go through training and be decent at it, but it's not college. You work and get paid for your work while you're learning. Once you're certified, you can be your own boss or work for a shop. People complain about having to pay though the nose for plumbers, electrician, HVAC install/repair, etc. The truth is few want to do these jobs because they're not "college degree job". You want to know where all the illegal aliens are working? They aren't taking factory jobs or office jobs, they're doing these manual skills jobs because there is more demand than there are laborers to do this work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rocket exhaust leaves an ionized gas trail that can "seed" a lightning strike if there is already a decent electric potential field present when it is launched </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why just racism? Studies have already demonstrated a number of different biases in Science against a variety of different groups and situations --e.g. biases against women advancing to tenure and bias against NIH and NSF grant proposals that are reviewed just prior to the review board lunch.  Wouldn't it be better to look for all types of biases and develop a generalized model for bias, and its triggering conditions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 01:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do oceanic turtle crabs meet their soul mates? Does normal crab partner selection only occur when turtles mate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dictators don't commit genocide, minions kill millions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exploding aquanet makes a wonderful potato cannon propellant
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The patient can also be spun on an axis with the tumor at the center of rotation. The idea here is that radiation exposure and damage is a cumulative process. The more radiation a volume of tissue is exposed to, the more the tissue inside that volume dies. By rotating the patient within the beam, in theory the tissues that have the beam scanning across their surface off and on absorb a sub-lethal dose while the tumor sits continuously in the beam absorb a lethal dose, killing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a copy of the British Indian [Great Trigonometric Survey map](https://alpinedrome.files.wordpress.com/2012/11/1st-everest-map.jpg)  showing the sight lines used to determine the heights of major peaks in the Himalayas, including Everest. Kind of turns it around. Rather than how far can you see, it shows how far way Everest was seen.  
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in the florida panhandle. People used to look at our beach pictures from the winter time and think it was snow. It is very fine and very white - think confectioners sugar and table sugar mixed together. Spent a lot of time TDY in Houston after moving to the Mid-Atlantic. Decided one trip to go look at the beach in Galveston. Man what disappointment. Water looked like concrete slurry. I pity the people who had that for their beach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now, some human music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aht! you touched my boobs! this isn't a massage, it's a fucking grope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding to this, isn't long term usage of NSAIDs associated with damage the cardiovascular system in general, and the heart specifically?  If you save their mind but end up causing an increased death rate from cardiac issues, is that still considered beneficial from a quality of life perspective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we can talk about the speed of light and the time it takes for the light showing an event occurring until that light reaches the earth and our eyes. Your question could just as easily be applied to the sun. It takes light 8 minutes to get from the sun to the earth. So how do you know the sun didn't explode something less than 8 minutes ago and the light just hasn't reached us? The short answer is we don't. However a longer answer is that our studies of the sun and stars like our sun say they don't just all of a sudden explode. Most events of that scale don't happen, just all of a sudden, without producing precursor events or signs that they're going to happen. A couple people have cited Betelgeuse as a star that could have blown up and we don't know it yet. Betelgeuse is 642 light years away, and yes it could have blown up already and we don't know. It is producing some of those precursor signs that our studies say indicate an imminent supernove.  However, science also says it could also live as long as another several hundred thousand years, so the likelihood that it has happened in the past 641 is pretty low compared to the possible wait time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meanders of the gulf stream loop current pass through the area of the deep water horizon wellhead. The fishing productivity of the Florida panhandle coast has long been associated with upwellings from the Desoto underwater canyon in the area as well. Are these two associated? Does the loop current flow deep enough in the ocean to hit the walls the the Desoto canyon? Is this same process bringing toxic emulsified oil and oil dispersants to the surface waters when it would normally remain in the depths? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait til he tries to find the tit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You Brits deserve this for having a royal palace or official castle or whatever it is named Blenheim. What the fuck did you expect when you give it name that sounds like it came right out a Prussian Barony  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 20:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the movie where the kid goes back in time in a cocaine dealer's custom car and has to score with his mom if he wants to return to his own time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 20:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the data so sparse over northwest Spain? From the flight lines north and south of there, it is clear flights pass over the area. At a sample rate of once per minute, there is no way all the traffic manages to miss getting sampled. It suggests flight track information in this region is being suppressed. Why might that be? Are there simply no tracking radars covering that area? Highly doubtful. I note this is partially over the Basque regions. Is it possible the data is being suppressed so it cannot be used for targeting planes for terrorism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it might be a [spider conch](http://www.stromboidea.de/bilder/Lambis_crocata_Colour_1_Philippines_Coll_Poppe.jpg)  dug out of its shell. I still wouldn't eat it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earthquakes are largely the consequence of plate tectonics on Earth. Mars doesn't have plate tectonics. I remember from the Apollo project the astronauts left seismographs on the moon and for months afterwards there were reports of the Moonquakes; so I guess quakes without tectonics are possible. However, it prompts the question, what is the mechanism postulated for these hydrogen generating marsquakes to occur?   

The scientists examined special types of rocks that are created when rocks grind against each other during earthquakes. The samples the researchers analyzed from Scotland, Canada, South Africa, the Isles of Scilly off the coast of England and the Outer Hebrides of Scotland were up to hundreds of times richer in trapped hydrogen gas than surrounding rocks that were not generated from such grinding.  

Just because rocks exposed to Earthquakes are enhanced in hydrogen, it doesn't mean a similar process would occur on Mars because Mars wouldn't necessarily have the quakes, due to the lack of plate tectonics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was in an elevator in hotel with 50 floors, room in 44th floor. Woman with two kids about 11 or 12 got on with me. They were going to 19th floor. As the door opened, one of the kids started punching buttons, just running his hand over the array. I stood there slack jawed for a second. The woman looked at me, shrugged and stepped off as the kid kept punch buttons. I drew back my leg and kicked him in the ass so hard I thought my ankle was broken. He flew out the elevator door and landed about 6 feet outside, already screaming before he hit the floor. The woman turned, looked and started striding back toward the elevator. I shrugged and smiled as the door closed before she could stick her hand in. Foot hurt all the way the remaining floors. Never felt pain so fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never watched Orange is the New Black, but from the clips I've seen, it appears to be pretty low humor, and it seems to be the most popular show in pretty much every country. This would seem to suggest any claim to high or low browism in the humor of different countries is really just discussing fine degradations of lowness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there was a click bait link to a picture or story about you, what would the teaser link say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is actually a museum to the wack job who made up all that shit about washington. He was a pastor in virginia in the 1820s with the memorable name "Weems-Botts" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no historical record, excepting religious texts which many would agree have a biased/conflict of interest in the matter, that Jesus ever existed as a real person. Putting him in this list is the equivalent of naming Sherlock Holmes or Hamlet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
