<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's hinted alot and also it says they COULD have a familial relationship, but still it doesn't matter when the author has passed away :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly the author passed away, this series had ALOT ALOT I MEAN ALOT of potential to become really big. Sadly not everything in life happens the way you want it. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It even says in the wiki they could have a familial relationship (saeko and rei) and also the episode (i think 11) saeko said "can you stop referring me as senpai" and after that "in reality we are". There's 2 things she could've said there, 1: "we are the same age" or 2: "we are sisters, so call me by my name" rei said don't speak about that, also in the manga it's the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question, always been on my mind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARE saeko and Rei sisters?(half sisters?) On chapter 12 en episode 11 saeko said a line that they could maybe be sisters, she said something like "in reality we are" then rei said "i don't want to hear it" or something like that, people are saying it was about that they are/should've been in the same ear but they had been hold a year by that problem. BUT STILL in wiki (saeko's wiki page) it says rei and saeko could have a professional or familial relationship.

This question has been on my mind for so mang god damn years. But i never knew this subreddit existed. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, okay i see the volume's title was **The Lizard Man Heroes Arc**  lol

I'm so blind lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://overlordmaruyama.wikia.com/wiki/Story_Arcs
Is this the right order? It says "chapter 15-18 is volume 4" but the manga is made upto chapter 24, which volume(s) are chapter 19-24? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about stuff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know volume 3 is covered by chapter 10-14 and anime 10-13 and volume 4 by chapter 15-18 

BUT the question was does after that the chapters adapt the following volumes (volumes 5-6-etc)

Also is season 2 going to adapt the LN exactly the same or are they gonna screw up and change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But on the wiki it says rank ss on level 1/2/3 stats. I think it's only possible because of the fast growth skill he has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leveling system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read about the leveling system because i still don't understand it 100%  
But still my question was, if bell got everything to rank s at level 1 and then leveled up to level 2. Did it make him equal to a level 3 (because of the all s of level 1?) 
AND do you get to be equal to someone higher of a level if you got everything to ranks S OR rank SS? (Same question as the first one only is it applied to rank S or SS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already seen it -.- i mean like a chapter 108 timeskip, maybe kids? Both of them as parents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about buying manga and light novels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Questions.**
1:how do i see the difference between manga and light novels when buying, i mean like, wtf the description doesn't even say "manga" or "light  novel" (book depository)
2: WHICH site is the best for buying manga and light novels, i want it to be international shipping (i live in the Netherlands). (i heard book depository is good) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it ends like white album 2.. lol rip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah fuk, BUT he could be a son of someone from the zeus familia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i know that it's translated upto vol 7, never got the chance to read it, bein busy with school. Also i hope he actually is the grandson of zeus and he unlocks his hidden divine powers ^_^ i hope his divine powers are like a lighting aura and he becomes super fast, atleast like lighting fast xd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Info about bell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhm, i read somewhere that Bell is the grandson (in the anime they said it too) of zeus. Does bell have hidden divine powers aswell then? I mean he inherited powers (maybe) from his grandfather, if he would, wouldn't he have some kind oflighting powers? (Isn't zeus like a lighting type???) and also wouldn't he be calles a demi-god then?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i think the knife's status is bell's status, they said "while bell is growing the knife does too" i think the knife is connected to bell energy force/power level. That's such a awesome weapon, i would REALLY REALLY want the knife to become a sword ONLY when bell touches it, like when the knife's writing lights up (only if bell touches it) then it becomes a sword, when he puts it away or lets go of the knife the power goes away and it becomes a knife (like what everyone is saying, only the hestia family/bell can use the knife, if someone else does it becomes useless, that same effect but then with transforming from a knife to a sword would be epic).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is season 2 coming out soon? 

I would love if they would have enough of money to make danmachi a weekly series, like danmachi could get even more populair than sao and those other animes, Danmachi had that super unique feel, imo it's my fav anime. Put that aside, SEASON 2??? (Also hope if they have a budget, please be 24/26 episodes long s2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But "full potential" like bell's power right? So anyone in the family can use bell's potential in the knife? (In the hestia family).

Or does the knife uses everyone's power apart (like everyone apart in the family)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks alot! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks! Is it translated up to volume 7? Or did the author make it up to volume 7 and he needs to continue the story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can i read the light novel? Or do i need to buy it somewhere?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
