<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2372</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Speaker has only said that he won't invite Trump to address Westminster Hall because that's the venue he has power over. 

The only people in recent memory that have addressed Westminster hall are the Queen, Nelson Mandela, Pope Benedict, Obama and Aung San Suu Kyi. It's considered a great honour and isn't offered lightly. I don't think many people would say Trump belongs on that list. If the speaker says he's not inviting him then it's not happening. 

He could still possibly be invited to address a different venue in parliament but it's unlikely with the way things are going at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaker Standing Up To Trump Is "A Thing Of Absolute Beauty" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Corbyn says Speaker John Bercow is 'absolutely right' to ban Donald Trump from Parliament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unfortunately being an Oxbridge graduate doesn't guarantee intellectual honesty. A disturbing number of our MP's are climate deniers too:

https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2014/sep/10/climate-scepticism-still-rife-among-tory-mps-poll

My favourite troll in the house of commons at the moment is a guy called Jacob Rees Mogg, a relic from an aristocratic dynasty of coal mine owners who used to run one of our biggest newspapers. Here he is advocating for slashing our environmental standards to Indian levels now that were no longer held back by troublesome EU regulations:

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-safety-standards-workers-rights-jacob-rees-mogg-a7459336.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans hit back at Commons Speaker John Bercow for blocking Donald Trump's address to Parliament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is why taking a "wait and see" approach with Donald Trump is no longer good enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Left Must Condemn Political Violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
