<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7451</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand father and daughter found in Australia after month at sea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  Revisit this in 5 years and this may turn out to have been the best Cowboys' draft since at least [1975](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dirty_Dozen_(American_football\)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my thought: *little late*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really sad is that the only way Trump will accomplish his goals is with a complicit Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kent Garrison, Digital Producer and Webmaster for the Cowboys and producer of the very popular FinishThisFight video series, will be doing an AMA in /r/cowboys this Saturday at noon central! Don't miss it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kent's a good guy, long-time member of Reddit and contributor to /r/cowboys.  It's about time he gets some love for the great work he does for the Cowboys and us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His character really does seem remarkable.  And apparently he's got mad charisma.  I personally *love* being able to root for guys I think I'd like if I knew them in person.  It's not as common as it should be.

Additionally, the team has changed a lot since Jones hired Garrett, all for the better.  Its character (speaking of character) is nothing like it used to be.  Which very much is a good thing.

Welcome to the sub, bud.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're actually in the process of arranging an ama with the producer of that terrific video series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me a lot of the first time the Cowboys played the Packers.  At the time the Packers' defense was supposed to be so good.  I told a Packers fan who came to the sub that the Packers' defense was not going to win the game.  He laughed.

The Packers' offense will not win this game.  Whether the Cowboys win will depend on whether the Cowboys' offense can perform.  If it does, the Cowboys go to the championship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you.  I don't think how the Packers have been playing will have anything to do with the outcome of this game.  People have been saying all year the Cowboys are going to lose, and so far they've met every challenge.  I'm looking forward to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy tries to rob gun store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GG you are so awesome!  Have we told you you're awesome?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Garrett's approach to life also helping Cowboys win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More or less.  Courts would try to interpret/apply the new laws, and whether they could rely on existing law depends on the circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that one's belief as to what the law is has nothing to do with what the law actually is.  Similarly, one's belief as to the nature of national security doesn't mean one is authorized to define national security.  Get what I'm saying?

As for recording others, each state has its own laws on what can be recorded and what can't.  [Here's a place](https://www.rcfp.org/reporters-recording-guide/state-state-guide) to check that.

If you're talking about recording a communication that is protected by federal secrecy laws--perhaps for disclosure, you're into the area of whistleblower laws.  [Here's some info](http://www.whistleblowers.org/resources/faq-page/know-your-rights-faq) about those. 

In short, it's dangerous.  Whether you're vindicated often may depend on whether you're prosecuted and in which court.  And if you're not you'll be subject to punishment--typically incarceration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest problem was epitomized so effectively by that cartoon--on the internet no one knows you're a dog.  As a whole we have trouble distinguishing knowledgeable informants from crackpots.  Social cues are nonexistent--and we've seen clearly on reddit that groupthink or group evaluation is a terrible substitute for experience and education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the thing: in 2 years you'll be 2 years older.  So you might as well be 2 years older and a nurse!  Go get it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Film student's Adidas ad refused twice by sports clothing company goes viral </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They work for me in firefox and chrome.  I suspect there's something going on in the browsers you use, but I'm no expert.

GG's the one to check on this.

Hey /u/ggitaliano!  You know any reason why the "My Subreddits +" button in the top left corner might have links that don't work if they're above the bottom of the blue line that cuts the star in half?

GG is *the man* when it comes to coding.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't he awesome?  What a great player.  I used to love Jay Novacek, but Witt is on a whole other level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.  Witten *did* play with a lacerated spleen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you can hope for him to recover soon--*just not by next week*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm with you.  It looked to me like he ducked his head and intentionally led with the crown of the helmet.  Of course only he knows what he *intended*.  But my guess is the NFL will fine him for it.  Not that that proves intent.

Certainly it wasn't a situation where Hall had no choice but to hit that way. 

In any event, it's a shame, because Nelson's important to the Packers, and it's no good when anyone's hurt that way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I can say: when winning streaks hit playoffs, anything can happen.

So I'm not worried about the winning streak.

I *am* concerned that Rodgers is looking like his old self--because early in the year he was misfiring.  However, if Montgomery and Nelson are out, that will help.

Still, it'll be the Cowboys offense that decides the game.  One way or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have bad memories from all kinds of games.  This is why I dislike every team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same for him, you know?  He's such a good player.  *But not by next week!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Packers it'll be.  I hope Montgomery's okay--but that he misses next week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottom line is every game from here on is against a good team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concur.  A red-hot Packers' team is worrisome.  But I just don't like the Giants.  Truthfully I don't like either one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boot. : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Wild Card Discussion Day 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **JAN 8, 2017**

Miami 12 Pittsburgh 30  
NYG @ GB 3:30 PM CT FOX



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI we have gotten *zero* response from the Dallas Cowboys whenever we've reached out to them.  Same for several more high-profile media members.

Every now and then an intern from the team will contact us--but will lose interest when we make it clear we're not surrendering control of the sub to them.

It's weird.  Other NFL teams seem to be much more interested in working with subs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've linked this to mod mail--which is the best way to ask for things like this (for next time).  If the guys agree, sure, it'd be fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  Limited to 2 at a time unfortunately.  Stickied again until we take it down for the day 2 wildcard discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to pick all of them for play of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 21:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a ridiculously bright suggestion.  Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an article, gosh, some 15 years ago now, comparing the advent of the internet to the early days of radio.  It talked about how, when radio first started, it was described as such a democratically-liberating technology, as everyone could talk to each other independent of the government.  It also talked about how monied interests came in and started limiting regular persons' access to it by lobbying government to pass strict licensing rules, raising fees, and so on.

I haven't seen anything in the intervening years suggesting that the article was anything other than prescient and straight-on accurate.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 14:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really it's just about lack of equipment, materials, and experience. But I love telling the anecdote anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Our girls weren't raised like this?*

Yes they were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to disable rumble in PS Now for pc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 06:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to play The Last of Us in PS Now for pc, and for the first time I've connected a DS 4 controller to my pc.  I've downloaded DS4Windows and set rumbleboost to 0, but it doesn't seem that DS4Windows is necessary to use a DS4 controller, and that setting doesn't seem to be having an effect in the game, as I'm still getting rumble.

Maybe there's an order in which I'm supposed to activate DS4Windows and plug in the controller or something?

I'd appreciate any feedback on how to turn it off.

Edit: I've just figured this out!  And I'm going to leave this post up as evidence of my ignorance in the unlikely chance that anyone else gets so easily stumped.

The solution is to press the PS button in the game screen, and there's an obvious selection for it called (wait for it): Vibration Settings!

So if anyone else misses the obvious there you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 06:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is that the NFL allegedly isn't abiding by the CBA--at least, according to the article: 

*"Although the 2015 Policy on Performance Enhancing Substances ("2015 Policy") required a minimum of three arbitrators -- there were only two," Zashin wrote. "In addition, the 2015 Policy required that any arbitrator assigned to hear appeals was not otherwise affiliated with the NFL and NFLPA.  That requirement was not followed.*

*"The 2015 Policy entitles a player to information upon which he can contest discipline.  Lane was denied even the most basic information, including information about his treatment under the 2015 Policy."*

Of course these are just allegations in a complaint.  But I must admit I haven't seen much suggesting that the NFL knows how to professionalize its disciplinary proceedings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember once in Houston just the *threat* of half an inch of snow shut the city down.

In contrast, I spent several winters in Maine, and within hours of the end of blizzards those roads were *clear*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah sure--he's exhausted administrative options.  Great point!

I just wish the NFL were run more professionally.  I mean, geez, it's a multi-billion dollar industry and so often it seems little more than ad hoc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah only reason I did was because you and I came to initially superficial opposite views.  I trust you JC!  Lord help me I trust you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically maybe if the NFL actually did anything (which I agree with you seems unlikely) there might be some chance it would lessen the length of Gregory's punishment.  

While that wouldn't help the Cowboys now, at least it might help Gregory later.  Assuming he can get his act together at last.  

It can't be helping him that in NFL terms he's basically unemployed for the next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a good book.  Nice recommendation.

Thing about Jerry, though, is that he just says stuff; whether it has anything to do with reality is beside the point.  How, for instance, exactly is Jerry going to keep this case "active" when the NFL already has announced the punishment?

Gregory appealed; the appeal was denied.  Exactly what can be done short of a lawsuit?

So just like with all his pronouncements about personnel issues, unfortunately too I have to take this one with a grain of salt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah who cares about groupthink--it's more fun just talking about stuff!  Interesting perspective.  Speaking of lazy, if I weren't so lazy I'd try to track down what the NFL's policies actually are.  Would be nice to have an actually informed opinion for a change.  :)

As an aside, the above numbers don't actually *show* that the NFL is more strict on domestic violence, but it's a limited sample and may be missing a lot of background info.

And Gregory, well, I've said it before.  I understand having a hard life and facing emotional/psychological issues and needing help.  But at some point you're responsible for who you are.  And until the law/rules change, you have to realize what you're risking when you even approach violating them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely concur!  This season was incredible.  Magical in so many ways.  It reminded me of what it was like to love the team when I was a kid.

Regardless of the Cowboys' past, and whatever I might think of Jerry Jones, it has been a long time since the Cowboys were relevant in the NFL.  

But over time Garrett has been transforming the team into something I actually could appreciate, which doesn't create intellectual dissonance when I root for it: he's created a team that doesn't quit, that's starting to accrue dynamic players who love to hustle, who actually seem to enjoy being good people.  

Best epitomized in a quotation I read just this week: *"We really just try to emphasize to our players to be the best versions of themselves in everything they do."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To tell the truth, do any all-star games matter anymore?  In the old days, I understand, it was the one chance fans had to see all the best players.  But now, with the net, we're inundated with histories, lives, interests.  We don't need to see them all together because we see them all the time.

MLB's tried to fix it with the homefield advantage gimmick.  But that's not particularly fair, and I doubt many fans--or players for that matter--care who wins because of its effect on some future event.

For the players--well, who pays for the trip to Hawaii?  The NFL?  That at least might be a perk for them.  And after a long season it's understandable, with how sore and banged up their bodies must be, that they don't want to play particularly hard.  But that just makes the game for fans even less relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After you said this, JC, I actually looked at the figures above.  Granted it's a limited sample, as it's only based on the past few months.  And I am no apologist for Gregory, as I've said elsewhere that at some point he has to take responsibility for his life.  But of the names with multiple punishment on this list, the punishments look like this:

Mike Pennel was banned 4 games, then 4 games  
Rolando McClain was banned 10 games, then 16 games  
Armonty Bryant was banned 4 games, then 3 games      
Karlos Williams was banned 4 games, then 10 games      
Sammie Lee Hill was banned 4 games, then indefinitely   
Seantrel Henderson was banned 4 games, then 10 games    
Gregory was banned 4 games, then 10 games, then indefinitely    

Maybe there are other circumstances, and I am no expert on the CBA.  But that is not consistent punishment, which is one of the first factors courts consider when it comes to issues like *arbitrary and capricious*.  

Also, I think a point of the post was the ridiculous disparity between the NFL's punishments involving violent crimes and what some would say are victimless crimes.

Without apologizing for Gregory, pretty sure we both would agree *that's* messed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope he was trying to be helpful.

[Here you go](https://www.cnet.com/how-to/how-to-enable-reader-mode-in-chrome/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What We Learned About The 2016 Cowboys: The Role Of Coaching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Packers and Giants in the mix, the Dallas Cowboys can't be caught playing favorites in NFL playoffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing thing about that game is that they didn't panic at all.  In fact, composure has been something this team has had in spades for almost the entire length of Garrett's tenure.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be marvelous if for once the NFL would get in front of a social issue like this, recognize that attitudes are changing, and fix its unduly punitive system.

Failing that, I don't understand why some of these guys haven't sued the league.  Sure, CBA.  But at some point, sheesh, it's time to get a court to look at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DeMarcus Lawrence won't be a FA until [after the 2017 season](http://www.spotrac.com/nfl/dallas-cowboys/demarcus-lawrence-14443/).

It's probably safe to say, though, at this point that for whatever reasons Lawrence and Gregory have been disappointments.  

I love Boat for many reasons, including that he's so upbeat.  But I'm not such a big fan of potential.  As Dandy Don Meredith used to say, *If ifs and buts were candy and nuts we'd all have a merry Christmas*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but we're not going to block the Dallas Morning News, which is one of the primary sources of news about the Cowboys, because a user doesn't want to use incognito mode.

What we *will* do is try our best to comply with any applicable laws.  If you have an issue with that, I suggest you simply not click on the links or use Reddit's "hide" feature.  

Otherwise, as far as I'm aware, the use of incognito mode to circumvent a paywall is not illegal in any way.  If you happen to know that it is, you may want to notify Google and Mozilla.

As for your *suspicions*, words fail.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's ugly, incoherent, and pointless like every other political argument ever

This is so accurate.

It's such a waste of time.

What's the worst is that so many are so willing to believe that the rich--i.e., the political class--give one rat's butt about their interests.  It's as though they intentionally delude themselves merely because the politicians appeal to their biases.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We really just try to emphasize to our players to be the best versions of themselves in everything they do," Garrett said.

This right here is a great philosophy for *everyone*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys' Prescott: No playoff bye trips planned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NFL's disciplinary system is crying out for a class action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judicial system won't do squat; this punishment was imposed pursuant to the CBA, and courts almost never rewrite bargaining agreements.  

That said, he might be able to argue that the punishment was arbitrary and capricious, but generally to succeed at that he'd have to show that the punishment was out of line with punishments imposed for similar offenses (and inconsistent with the provisions of the CBA).  Not sure whether he'd be able to do that.  Offhand I don't remember that the NFL has imposed that many 1-year suspensions. 

There is at least a chance though that he'd succeed in a lawsuit; from outside the NFL's disciplinary structure seems so ad hoc as to be laughable if it weren't so imbalanced and unfair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we're not going to risk issues with the admins, and because there are gray areas as to whether we would violate the DMCA otherwise.  It's simply not worth facing a potential legal action because users don't want to use incognito mode.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has the quickest release I've ever seen--quicker than Tarkenton or Montana.  His signature play has to be [this one](http://profootballzone.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/wattnomatch4romo.0.gif).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still using the f/0.7 lenses though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Composite photo of [the dark side of the moon](http://news.psu.edu/sites/default/files/styles/threshold-992/public/DSOTM%20farside%20NASA.jpg?itok=4d87eZzD).

No not the Pink Floyd album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can say is [this](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/f8/Internet_dog.jpg).  No way to tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, Danny White held numerous Cowboys' QB records when he retired.  At the time it was pretty generally acknowledged that if he'd managed to break through to one Super Bowl championship (for instance, during those 3 straight years in which the Cowboys appeared in the NFC championship game), he'd be in the Hall of Fame.

White was a terrific QB.  Just didn't quite get there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah copyright is somewhat different from plagiarism--and here it has to do with lost advertising revenue, as users who can read the article here w/o going to the web site don't count as page views (or whatever metric DMN uses).  So it's really just an issue of taking away visitors from its site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really we just need to wait and see.  So far Dak's played great, and there's no dispute that he led the team to a great season.  No one can read the future, and what a player did in the past doesn't mean he'll be able to do it in the future, either.

Just a shame that anything would detract from Romo's brilliant career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi.  Thanks for trying to be friendly, but as I explain elsewhere in this thread, we can't allow copies of the text because we did actually receive an official complaint about it.  The last thing we need is to have to deal with the DMCA.

So it was nice of you to do, but we had to remove it.  

Other subs may allow copy/pastes--and we actually did too until we received the complaint.  But since we're the ones who received the complaint we're the ones who have to comply.

Maybe our mobile users could contact the devs of the mobile app to see if there's a way to allow for incognito mode through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and probably the reddit app huh?  No way in it to go incognito?  

Wondering if maybe we should add a note in the sidebar about this.  

But the main reason we don't allow reprints of the articles for mobile users is because in the past we actually received a complaint from the Dallas Morning News, and last thing we need is to deal with a DMCA issue or inquiries from the admins.  So I worry that explaining how to circumvent the soft paywall "officially" could present us with the same problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the name of the award: the Nominate Whoever for Whatever Award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works in Firefox too.  And if it ever stops, it's really easy to delete the cookies pointing to the site.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to point out: any QB struggles against a team with a good defensive line.  That's what a good defensive line causes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Dak Prescott's mother once shut down Nick Saban on the recruiting trail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhat regularly I see ideas that originated here show up in the media.  We've got a great group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool.  We have the most knowledgeable Cowboys fans on the net.  BD you're definitely one of them.  Cheers bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say that.  Instead, I've [said the opposite](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5lubnl/president_obamas_supreme_court_nomination_of/dbzm3zq/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very friendly FYI: Dez Bryan**t** 718 12%

But Brer this took a lot of work.  Thank you for coming up with the idea and implementing it all year.  You've made the sub a better place.  Bravo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but I'm not *blaming* anyone.  If anything, the machine the GOP's been able to create and operate over the past 30 some-odd years is impressive.  It's been a long-term play all the way.

As I've said repeatedly, this is not a L/R thing at all.  It is an us/them thing, where *them* represents the powered interests.  You're right, though.  If the Dems had managed to create this type of machine, we'd be facing the same issue: the imperilment of our political system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is that if everyone adopts the why bother approach, we'll morph into a one-party system.  And in the absence of choice, even if it is as weak a choice as the Dems sometimes present, we're no longer a republic.  In other words, there is a valid argument that a republic needs political competition simply to survive.  So the people who *bother* do it because they love the idea of what the U.S.'s political system represents.  As should we all, because, left or right, we all are Americans.  And we need a competitive electoral cycle or we all lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure the issue is as much about the Dems' platform as it is about the GOP's abilities to: (1) gerrymander state and federal legislative districts to take control of governorships, state legislatures, and Congress; (2) develop a consistent think-tank system and propaganda machine to spread its message, based generally on sloganeering at the expense of people's true interests; (3) display solidarity of principle and conduct in response to perceived pressures; and (4) attack long-held structural beliefs about how the system should operate.

Years ago the GOP rethought its entire process after Goldwater and morphed its goals toward a long-term strategy.  Unquestionably it's run circles around the Dems since at least 1980, as over time it's taken control at the grassroots level.

It does not seem to have any interest in limiting its advances, even if they do ultimately seem bad for the U.S.  And why should it?  It's furthering its own goals while advancing its platform, and as there's no consistent message from the other side, there's nothing to stop it from shouting down moderates within its own party.

But these are all procedural issues and have nothing to do with the actual underlying value of message.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not going to be able to convince him.  Poor guy's caught up in the L/R thing; he can't see it's really an us/them thing (where *them* refers to the people who would use our own values against us).  If the Dems had done what the GOP's doing, it would have been just as bad.  But the simple fact is that they never did and the GOP is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a book about monsters...Trying to remember what it was called.  Unusual monsters.  Maybe made-up monsters?  Not sure.  Not Where the Wild Things Are.  

But check [this list](http://www.goodreads.com/list/show/20016.Picture_Books_with_Monsters).

Or, maybe better, [check here](http://www.oldchildrensbooks.com/looking-for-a-book?page=7).  Or [here](http://w1.loganberrybooks.com/stumpthebookseller/?cat=11). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additionally, the GOP seems to be very interested in the U.S. turning into a one-party system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah wasn't questioning.  Sounds like you have a form of deuteranomaly.

Have you tried [Enchromas](http://enchroma.com/)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are only 4; I first thought I couldn't see them either.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be really cool to see these for every QB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that article twice.  There's no *explanation*.  Only description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Davis would be a 2d-round pick is my guess.  Late 2d.  Exactly where the Cowboys will be drafting.

I agree with you though.  Defense is what they need.  Though a burner who could catch would be useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can say at this point is that I hope, all evidence to the contrary, that most Americans are wrong, because *he's who we've got*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or pizza.  Because no one can eat pizza in any sort of dignified way.  Plus it's quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing to be ashamed of.  Her fault for not being kind, joking about it, and making you feel better.  She'll never meet another person who would do that for her.  Her loss.

Listen: being socially awkward isn't the same as being worthless.  

Keep your head up, thank God she blew you off because she's no match for you, and try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice answer!  Thank you.  But that seems to explain only why they rotate in the same direction, not why they do it on generally the same plain.  Could you advise as to that?

Maybe because in the sun's case the *denser regions* happened to be generally on the same plain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There'd be a lot of award winners from reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French tourist bitten while posing for selfie with croc in Thai national park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A repost from /r/nfl.  But it came up in a recent conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actual scouting report of Troy Aikman on display at new practice facility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a different age, for sure.  Today's NFL is much more suited for inflated stats; comparing the 2 eras is misleading.  

The difference between Romo and Aikman might be like the difference between Rodgers and Peyton Manning.  Aikman was 100% blue chip.  Romo's a junkyard dog.  

Legend has it that after Landry first saw Aikman in a scouting practice, he canceled all other scouting appointments.  Jimmy Johnson said that if the Hurricanes had Aikman, they would've gone 24-0, winning every game by 50 points.

Here's Aikman's [scouting report](https://twitter.com/RickGosselinDMN/status/767384043071508480/photo/1).  1s or 1.5s in every category.

There is no question--none--that any GM comparing the 2 would've wanted Aikman.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact, before the winning began, circa 1964, the clamor got so loud for Murchison to fire Landry that Murchison solved the problem the only way he could: he gave Landry a [10 year contract](http://dfw.cbslocal.com/2015/12/29/moment-40-landry-10-year-extension-29-years-as-head-coach/).  That made it clear to fans and the media that Landry was there to stay.

Of course, [Jerry did the same for Johnson](http://articles.latimes.com/1989-04-07/sports/sp-1196_1_10-year-contract), but the ego clash was so bad neither could stick with it.

This is the thing about Garrett: he doesn't care who gets the credit.  I.e., he's the only one who could put up with Jerry.  So for better or worse Garrett's the best chance for the Cowboys to become relevant again in ~~our~~ Jerry's lifetime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny; you watch the NFL long enough and you can see why some teams don't succeed.  Their expectations are unrealistic and they're impatient.

The Cowboys from the 60s-80s, the Patriots (yuck) over the past 15 years, the Giants and Steelers, hopefully the Cowboys now going forward--they hire people and give them time to do their jobs.  

We used to have this discussion a lot back when Garrett was new.  Consistency of management seems to be really important when it comes to sustained success.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a ghost in the trees! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah I have no clue; I can't read the future.  Someone said yesterday that the difference between the Cowboys keeping Romo and releasing him is $8M.  Not a small amount at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aikman was the most skilled, perfect passer I've ever seen.  Not a scrambler, not a game-changer, not even a marshal of the game, but a perfect reader with tremendous strength, form, and accuracy.  He knew exactly where to throw always.  While we'll never know, I'll guess that the majority of his interceptions occurred because his receivers were out of position, not because he threw to the wrong spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  I sure hope you're right about their dumping Sanchez and keeping Tony as a backup.  I guess we'll see.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fans do it too!  It's like a failure to appreciate the present.  I liked this article, though, because it tries to address a question I had: why did they only keep him in for the one series?  Especially when it seems clear that if they'd kept him in longer they may have won?

Caution, sure, but.

Maybe they played him because they wanted to see if he still could?  And upon seeing how sharp he was, they didn't want to risk him?  

But like the article says, the question about Tony has nothing to do with his skills.

Only sure answer: we saw that Sanchez can't.  I mean, he looked *awful.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no dog in this fight, and I only want the Cowboys to win.  I see both sides of the issue, for sure.

That said, Tony did look really good.  Problems though are 3: durability, the amount of time Tony lost to injuries, and that Dak took control of the team.  (Maybe that's 2?  I couldn't decide.) These are not insurmountable problems, but they are significant enough that we have to acknowledge, if we're going to be reasonable, that is, that the Cowboys did not resolve this irrationally.

Arguments that Tony gives them the best chance to win are not particularly persuasive, as Dak led them, in his first year, to as good a record as Tony ever did.  Arguments that Tony gives them the best chance to win in the playoffs aren't, either, as his playoffs record hasn't been so great.  Further, both of the arguments are speculative and unprovable.

It's true that Tony has some skills that Dak doesn't, and of course lots of experience.  But Dak also has some skills that Tony doesn't, including a surprising ability not to risk the ball.  As turnovers famously correlate with losses, this should not be overlooked.  

The experience issue is offset to a significant extent by the fact that Tony's skills are not the question.  The past 2 games he's played, stretching back over 2 years, he's sustained serious injuries.  The question is durability.  Tony's not 28 anymore.  Heck he's not even 34.  His body has shown that it no longer can take the pounding.  And there's no answer to that, as time makes a mockery of us all.

Sure, the past is not evidence of the future, but in every line of work it is persuasive.  And while any given team can handle disruption caused by switching QBs, that doesn't mean the team would go looking for it.

So I dunno.

Another thing I guess I should add is that most of the great QBs' careers have ended because of injury--concussions and the body breaking down.  For example, Staubach and Aikman, when they retired, both still could play, and their skills hadn't eroded particularly.  Their bodies, though, had begun to go.  This is what I'm seeing more than anything in Tony.

Finally, we shouldn't overlook Tony's relationship wih Garrett and Jerry.  Clearly they're friends, so there's something going on in those dynamics to which none of us are privy.  But we shouldn't overlook whatever that is.  Whatever it is.  But friends wouldn't respond the way these 3 have unless some sort of recognition, a shared value, understanding, or something, was there.  We just don't know what.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> x Tony Romo's limited playing time failed to enhance his trade value for Cowboys, so what was the point? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 08:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Cowboys QB who looked bad the whole day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 01:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm rooting for the Packers tonight.  If they win the Giants go to Lambeau. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like and as.  Dang you're right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expensive no matter what, right?  But boy didn't he look sharp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HA!  Great metaphor.  I wonder if a giraffe even could fit on a plane.  I picture one with its neck sticking out, wearing goggles, scarf flapping in the slipstream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dream (as unlikely as it may be): if they have to trade him, Romo and our #1 to the Browns for the chance to draft Myles Garrett. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that phantom call when Wentz went out of bounds.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  It's not that he showed nothing.  He did show something: he's not a viable backup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize there are pros/cons to both sides, but I don't like seeing teams do this.  As much as I don't like Belichick, I much prefer his method: put your guys out there and let them play.  Here, though, with 2 backup OL, I at least understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.  Looked like he was trying to give it to them.

Shows really how remarkable Dak is: Sanchez is a veteran, and he still looked like he didn't know how to read a defense or make a throw.  In contrast, we have the guy who should be either MVP/ROY, or share both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that sucked. And it makes it really clear that Sanchez is not a functional backup.  Sure, 2 backup OL.  But that's no excuse.

As problematic as it may be, I'd like to see the Cowboys keep Romo.

On the bright side, the defense looked really good again until it got exhausted at the end.

Sanchez (sigh). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This and ninite may be the most useful 2 util sites on the web.  It was a great idea, you ran with it, and you deserve success.  Bravo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who could determine something like that?  I wouldn't even know where to begin.

But I'd guess Carter, who was swept into office based almost entirely on the impressions of him as an honest and decent man--important virtues after Watergate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding?  Have you noticed who he's been appointing to his [cabinet](http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/us/politics/donald-trump-administration.html?_r=0)?  Generals, CEOs, GOP retreads, and people from Goldman.  Trump's just as beholden to money as all the others.  But I edited my post to try to avoid L/R issues.  So i'm sure not going to get into it with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was obvious and disheartening from early in his Presidency.  It's just that people weren't ready to hear it yet.  And they're so caught in their labels.

But I couldn't care less about L/R.  Those are names used to divide us.  But don't get me started again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardly standard, as L/R is the only argument most people know.  But you're right--it's mostly digression.  Just sad is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VI is six, not XI.  And the NFL's blocked it from reddit, apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  First off this would just apply to broadcast channels 

This doesn't mean we don't need a return of the Fairness Doctrine.  We do--it's just not all we need.  But  I remember when it was revoked--Murdoch pushed for it so he could bring FOX to the U.S.  We see the result now: confirmation bias throughout the media and a divided populace.

We won't get any new laws which protect print media or whistleblowers, though, until somehow we can break the stranglehold money has on politics.  I think maybe money's always had a huge influence; it's just that now the civic limitations on power have been weakened to the point that there are no more checks to it.

I hate to think I'm as pessimistic as you suggest elsewhere, but absolutely it's true that the U.S. is not immune to historical forces, and a people who don't fight for freedoms lose them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Criticism of Mr. Obamas stance on press freedom, government transparency and secrecy is hotly disputed by the White House, but many journalism groups say the record is clear.

What's really amazing to me is that Obama came into office claiming that he'd run the most transparent Presidency in history and promising protections for whistleblowers.  Instead he gave us the opposite.

[Edit: a lot of stuff edited because it's a digression.] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May she live a long, healthy, and glorious life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 03:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can hear him even now--that built-up roar.  What a tragic story he has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawrence Taylor is the greatest NFL player I've ever seen--the one guy who looked like Jim Brown must've looked.  Campbell is second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked those little derricks on their helmets.  Though the baby blue...ugh.  Still, I hate those stylized bulls they use now.

Sad about Campbell--such a great, powerful runner.  Barely can walk now.  The NFL is a brutal game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh you're right!  Nations don't impose different laws on multinationals!  And multinationals such as Dennys, IHOP, Olive Garden, and many of the dozens of multinationals identified [here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_restaurant_chains) have no interest in lobbying national governments regarding the many different nations' wage laws.  And any pushback has nothing to do with the various sociopolitical forces inherent in those nations.

And expectations about tips don't [vary from nation to nation](http://www.cntraveler.com/stories/2008-11-11/etiquette-101-tipping-guide) based on those forces.  Conde Nast!  Wow!  It must be a nutcase too!

How foolish I must be.

Sarcasm off, no one legitimately could argue that wage concerns don't lie at the heart of capitalism or that the U.S., for better or worse, is the world's leader in capitalism.  So *of course* business interests, including those of multinationals, affect wages, including those of servers.

And businesses own the media.  That's simply ipso facto.  And owners *control*.  So I don't see whatever issue you think you have with what I said.  Business interests have defined the U.S. since at least the industrial age--and that's not necessarily the case in nations such as Canada or France, both of which have much more liberal histories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travesty that Cliff Harris isn't in the Hall of Fame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same reason Americans don't do a lot of stuff.  Business controls us.  Particularly multinational business.  Business controls everything: the message, the rules, the politics, the laws, the morality--all via propaganda.  Has for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got the 2d-highest winning percentage in Cowboys' history (which admittedly is faint praise, given the dogs Jerry has hired, and the absolute lack of control he gave to any except Garrett since Johnson left). 


But you remind me: when I was a kid, circa 1973, the Cowboys lost some game, I don't remember which, and a teacher came to class on the Monday and said he'd sent a telegram to Landry at halftime, saying that he should be fired.

Of course the Cowboys were only halfway through their run of 20+ consecutive winning seasons, went on to lose 2 classic Super Bowls, to win another, and to appear in the NFC championship game in the 80s 3 years in a row, and Landry is considered one of the greatest coaches of all time.  But to my teacher that day he wasn't even *passable at best*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cliff Harris: How Dak Prescott leads Cowboys reminds me of Roger Staubach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cowboys have found a defensive line.  Nobody move.  

Speaks for itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two of the three of them are gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleepeating.  It's a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NFL's scheduling formula is [here](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Football_League_regular_season). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 16:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romo's had that quick release, and I don't remember White having that pocket awareness.  But as far as being one of his own worst enemies, yep there's a parallel.  Also worth noting that White was the Cowboy's passing leader in a number of categories when he retired-and that White's teams were better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concur.  Jones should be in the Hall of Fame.  As the article implies, Irving is still very raw.  Still, we're definitely all rooting for him, and if anyone can bring out his talent it's Marinelli. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 06:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Jones finally wised up enough to get out of his own way.  

In Garrett he's got a guy who couldn't care less about the credit.  He just wants to win.

Whether he's the greatest coach ever is sort of beside the point (though he reminds me of Landry in quite a few ways).  The real issue is that he's the only coach Jones ever has hired who can get along with him.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been able to figure out this either/or thing yet.  People saying Romo can't do this, Dak can't do that.  We've seen what Romo's been able to do his entire career.  However, like it or not, he's 36, near the tail end of his career, and hasn't played a full season in almost 2 years.  Additionally, demonstrably his body is beginning to wear out, and he hasn't been as mobile as Dak in probably 10 years.

In contrast, Dak clearly still has limitations; he lacks the ball control, consistent form, and pocket awareness of Romo.  But his reads are splendid, he doesn't risk the ball, and the game doesn't seem too fast for him.

It doesn't weaken Romo's legacy to say that it's unrealistic to expect him ever to rise to the heights of his younger days any more than it does Dak's potential to say he still needs coaching.

Additionally, as I mention elsewhere, almost half the 2016 team didn't play with Romo as a consistent starter.  To them he is a locker room presence, but it is clear that this team long since has bought into what Dak brings.  And there is no question that he is an excellent student who has risen to the occasion.

Instead of arguing one or the other, we should be glorying in the facts that we got to root for such a splendid playmaker in Romo and that the future looks bright with Dak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the starters on offense were nearly identical.

Again, no they're not. Hanna (who was the 2d starting TE in 2014) hasn't played all year, so Swaim (who's started the most at 2d TE), Prescott, and Elliott all are new starters. That's a 28% change. I.e., more than 1/4 of the starting offensive unit is different from 2014.

To illustrate the extent of the change, no one offered a 28% cut in pay would suggest that the amounts would be "nearly identical".

Not to mention that almost every one of the starters (9 out of 11) in 2014 started 15+ games, whereas this year significant absences/changes include Collins, Butler, that Dez missed 3 games, and that Beasley has had a profoundly increased role.  Only 7 out of 11 have started 14+--an 18% drop.

I'm not saying these things to argue with you, but simply to help us understand the extent to which the team has changed.  It's a different group on both sides of the ball.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had the same roster in 2014.

Sorry, but this is incorrect, as you can see [here](https://www.google.com/search?q=cowboys+roster+2014+vs+covboys+roster+2016 ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8) (2014) and [here](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/teams/dal/2016_roster.htm) (2016).  Only 31 players remain from the 2014 team.  That's a change of almost 42%.

Of the significant contributors this year, Anthony Brown, Maliek Collins, Elliott, David Irving, Byron Jones, and Prescott all are new.

This is a substantially different team from the 2014 group.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who shall not be named 

Good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely there's no reason to denigrate one player simply to support another.

Romo's been spectacular his entire career.  He's made every team better.  Hasn't been his fault so many of the teams sucked.  

That said, Dak's been pretty impressive too.  Says something that the only other rookie ever to take his team to 13 wins was Roethlisberger.  That's heady company.

Cowboys still may need Romo before the season's done.

Only worry I'd have is rust.  And that a hit wouldn't finish him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely it is.  *There's only one way to change it.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've had a 2-party system for 200+ years.  The way it works is: when all other candidates fall away, we're generally left with 2.  

So yeah. It was their fault, and the fault of the other approximately 43% of the electorate who didn't vote.  But /u/m1rado only mentioned the young.  So I was speaking in context.  And no I didn't mention  everyone else--because the list would've been way too long.

Definitely started at the top though.  Hilary was no prize.  Engage in Hilary-hatred all you want; I won't argue with you.

But in this case, the GOP clearly has been against the open Internet for a long time.  So we had the Dems, who supported it, and the GOP, which didn't.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  A *suggestion* is very different from implementation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is the Dems lack the fortitude or will to do it.  GOP has been running strategic circles around them for almost 50 years, ever since they developed their longterm plan after Goldwater.  Result we see: gerrymandering, GOP control of most of the states, professional development and implementation of its message, and now co-optation of the "outsider" Trump for a rightwing adminstration.  

In contrast, Dems have seemed like amateurs.

It certainly seems as though the GOP has no interest in a 2-party system.  And *that's* scary.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 00:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Dems had any guts at all, Obama would name Garland based on the Senate's [waiver](https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/obama-can-appoint-merrick-garland-to-the-supreme-court-if-the-senate-does-nothing/2016/04/08/4a696700-fcf1-11e5-886f-a037dba38301_story.html) or [implied consent](http://readersupportednews.org/pm-section/78-78/35673-three-ways-president-obama-can-appoint-the-next-supreme-court-justice).  Any court challenge could take *years*.

GOP's shown it's willing to risk a Constitutional crisis; no reason the Dems shouldn't.  A little late to worry about precedent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a rehearsal! How Cowboys toyed with Lions, put rest of the league on notice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with the fact that Constitutionally he wasn't allowed to run.  I like that no matter how bad a President might be, we only have to put up with him, at most, for 8 years.  This really is the last defense we've got against despotism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Young voters had their chance and screwed up by not rallying behind the Dems.  Hilary screwed up by running a lousy campaign.  Dems screwed up by letting the GOP outmaneuver it at the grassroots level for the past 50 years (since Goldwater, when the GOP famously developed its longterm strategic plan), by complying with so many political/legal changes that wrecked their base, by refusing to challenge the GOP's historic recalcitrance at refusing even to vote on Garland, and by nominating an unappealing candidate.  

My point is that a *lot* of groups have had a hand in this fubar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  unnecessary and unjustified burdens on providers

Good grief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods had an internal discussion about whether to allow the posts; /u/niehaus very politely offered to withdraw /r/cowboys from his scripts.  Ultimately we thought they were pretty cool.  So he was nice enough to start them up again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboys are just having fun now.  It's pretty cool to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess: maybe they don't want to risk him for the playoffs, and they want to decide if Sanchez really can be a viable backup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can tell, what we've seen is the developing ability of entrenched powers/money to use the Internet as a propaganda tool to feed biases, thereby dividing the masses on wedge issues.  We see the power of confirmation bias all around us.  A divided populace is far more easily defeated than an united one.

The result is as you say: the breakdown of civics and the rise of despots.

What it means, I guess, depends on how much you care about the value of self-governance.

Personally, I find it remarkable how willing as a species we are to surrender self determination based on transparent promises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably quite a bit older than you, and as I look back at my life there definitely were some years that were worse than others.  So grieve for your dad, but feeling selfish about hurting isn't a reason to beat yourself up.  Truth is, it was a bad year for you.

There will be better ones.  Sincere condolences.  

But remember: this is how it should be--parents always should die before their children.  My best friend lost his son.  It's been 20+ years, and he still hasn't gotten over it.

Doesn't lessen your grief, I know.  But he lives on now in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine died the day after Christmas when I was six.  You have my condolences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aging of the baby boomer population may have something to do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you report accounts for ban evasion, which ones get suspended? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask because, after banning an account recently, a new account showed up almost immediately, defending the banned account's behavior.  But only the new account got suspended.  But I remember other times when both were.  So I'm uncertain.  Thank you in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 07:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the FO is planning on trying to trade him

Maybe yeah.  But wouldn't it make sense for them to let him showcase himself?  To maximize any return value? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 07:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Others have given decent reasons why the Cowboys might not want to risk Romo, but I'm wondering if maybe concerns about his back are more significant than we think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another 25% should be about that fake punt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping Lee turned them on.

Was nice to see Irving playing a lot more.  He's got some skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh.  Yep I'm no expert.  Roundworms, hookworms, tapeworms.  That's what a google search shows for cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, we respond when mods report users to us.  As we told you repeatedly.  Didn't seem as though we were asking for too much from you, but clearly you disagreed.  You didn't do what we asked; you didn't get the result you wanted.  That's the way it goes.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 11 teams have more.  Wow!  They're actually slightly better than average now!  Pretty amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods of /r/cowboys changed our policy this year, after it became clear that a lot of NFL teams' mods had begun working together to cut down on trolls under certain conditions.  Essentially when a mod from another team's sub notifies us of any problem accounts, we review the accounts and respond as seems appropriate.  Definitely we've banned accounts since our change.

I won't apologize for that guy because we had nothing to do with it.  But please don't think he's representative of our sub as a whole.  We welcome civil discussion and fans of all teams and work hard (to much criticism from trolls within our sub) to keep it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I reported a few trolls to them

You reported *one* troll to us, not "a few".

In any event, we didn't do anything because our policy is only to police users in other subs when we receive reports from those subs' mods.  As far as I understand, this is the policy of *every* NFL sub's mods.  If it's not, it's certainly not unreasonable, especially in this case, as that particular user doesn't have much of a history in /r/cowboys, and seems to have been set up as a troll account anyway.

We specifically asked you, more than once, to report any particular user to the mods of this sub, for example, /u/spazsquatch, /u/icebreak, or /u/xylan_treesong, and told you that if the mods of this sub saw a problem they'd let us know.  *They* are the ones responsible for policing this sub, with users' help, and they are *excellent* mods.

Instead of doing that, you vented on us.

Next time, maybe you should try simply being reasonable.  Might get better results.

Sorry for the loss.  Hopefully the Lions will have better luck against the Packers.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am *not* an expert.  But it looks like ~~a pinworm~~ some kind of cat-related worm (one of my cats had those once).  Check your cat's box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 22:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen images like this before, but there tends to be disputes as to whether they're to scale.  Anyone know if this one actually is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 22:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Diamonds.*

Miracle Mile was in many ways a bookend to a period which began with [Testament](http://www.rogerebert.com/reviews/testament-1983), a period of social upheaval in which Reagan surprisingly reneged on a Conservative ideal at the time that the more nukes we had the better; during that period the U.S. reduced its nuclear arsenal pursuant to [START II](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/START_II), and Jonathan Schell wrote his seminal work [The Fate of the Earth](http://www.sup.org/books/title/?id=418).

Along with the above line, I'll never forget the heading of one of Schell's sections: *A Republic of Insects and Grass*.

This was before the U.S. descended into such partisanship; at the time it still seemed that we the people could control the country together.  We certainly had an effect on nuclear arms.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the guy who body-slammed Zeke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beaten by 3 TDs, it makes them a lot less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Lee's rant may have set this team up for a Super Bowl run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Lee's rant turns things around for Cowboys defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Points out the importance of NOW in sports.  Windows don't stay open, and there's no guarantee that anyone will get another chance.  We talk a lot about potential and what could have been.  But all we have is what is.

Romo's had a great career; he's added a lot to his teams.  Not particularly his fault they didn't break through.  But he's hardly the only great QB never to win a championship.  Marino, Tarkenton, Gabriel, and White all come to mind.

As fans, we have to appreciate what we're seeing.  And recognize that the bittersweet is a big part of sports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really like to know what was said at halftime (and by whom).  The defense looked totally different in the second half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottom line: it doesn't matter what anyone else thinks.  All that matters is the final score.  This is what Garrett has been teaching since he became head coach. He's finally got a team that appreciates the lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for the Bears, 49ers, and Browns, they played pretty good teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your pist history shows that those are the only kinds of posts you've *ever* made.  We're not interested.  Thanks though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Dez Bryant showed he's the X factor of Cowboys' Super Bowl hopes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 07:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I mentioned it was caught by automod.  Been approved.  Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 06:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang I knew I was going to have to find that post.  [Here you go.](https://www.reddit.com/r/cowboys/comments/5abp2q/day_after_thread_2016_week_8/d9f7hi8/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
