<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5492</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M: 19, 166lbs, ~20% BF. Goals: Summer cut and strength gain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up everyone? I first started my cut in May and so far have lost around 12lbs. After switching workouts about 4 weeks ago and this already being mid-July it is time to step it up. I'm looking for someone to help me get the motivation I need to stay one track and also not take that dreaded trip to Five Guys haha.

Same goals would be preferable as I am competitive by nature and would love to try and race someone to get fit first.

Here is some more info I posted on /r/fitness about my cut: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/comments/3d0wvr/routine_critique_diet_4day_split_for_cutting_male/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY. CAPTAIN KIRK MADE HISTORY YESTERDAY. THAT IS A GOOD REASON TO DRINK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up around that so I am completely fine with that, just wanted to check.

And also Yes, Yes and Yes to your questions. I was pretty skeptical when I heard that so it's nice to hear that I'm on track. A redditor yesterday told me to go up to at least 50g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 14:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it bad to have meats such as pepperoni and salami in my diet while on a cut?

I currently eat between 20-30g of fat per day on a 1400-1600 calorie diet. I was told thi is too little fat so thought these might help. But I don't want to overeat and consume more fat that I should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CAPTAIN KIRK BE LIKE "LOLJK GUYS, I CAN BASEBALL" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was some body switching done over in LA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, welcome our new Kirk Nieuwenhuis overlord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope Cole can replicate last season because if everything pans out

Letang-Maatta

Cole-Pouliot

is a pretty scary top-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Routine Critique + Diet] 4-day split for cutting: Male, 19 years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 18:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after a few weeks of tweaking my workouts/diet I think I have found a good balance for my goals. I was hoping /r/fitness could take a look and give some criticism on what could be done, if anything.

Stats: Male, 19, ~166lbs, ~20% bodyfat (not sure how accurate)

Goals: Lose body fat while maintain or even increasing strength. Also set building blocks for healthy lifestyle

Background: So I started doing getting serious about weight loss and fitness in June and found a program on bodybuilding.com to use. I didn't like it as it focused completely on hypertrophy, but also I felt like I was just wasting time at the gym instead of making progress. I consider myself to be somewhere between beginner and intermediate (played lacrosse and had organized lifts for a couple years) so was looking for something more than a 3-day split. I found PHUL after a few days of researching routines and I really like it. I have changed some of the workouts to more strength based than hypertrophy because I am relatively weak and am happy with the size I am at currently. Below is my 4-day routine plus have added in my diet to make sure I am cutting correctly.

**Routine**

For reference here are my 5 main lift 3x5 maxes:

Bench: 145lbs

Squat: 175lbs

Deadlift: 165lbs

Bent-Over Row: 155lbs

Overhead Press: 85lbs


Day 1-Upper Power | Day 2-Lower Power | Day 3-Upper Hypertrophy | Day 4-Lower Hypertrophy
-----------------|-----------------|-----------------------|-----------------------
Barbell BP: 3x5 | Back Squat: 3x5 | Barbell BP: 3x5 | Back Squat: 3x5
Incline BP: 3x6 | Deadlift: 3x5 | DB Flye: 3x10 | Barebell Lunge: 3x10
Bent-Over Row: 3x5 | Leg Press: 3x6 | DB Shoulder Press: 3x8 | Leg Extension: 3x10
Lat Pulldown: 4x8 | Leg Curl: 3x8 | DB Lat Raise: 3x10 | Leg Curl: 3x10
Overhead Press: 3x5 | Standing Calf Raise: 3x10 | DB One-Arm Row: 3x10 | Leg Press: 3x10
DB Shrugs: 3x10 | Cable Side Bend: 3x12 | Seated Cable Row: 4x8 | Calf Press: 4x10
Barbell Curl: 3x10 | Russian Twist: 3x30 | Preacher Curl: 3x10 | Cable Crunches: 3x10
Skullcrushers: 3x8 | Side Plank: 3x30secs | Tricep Pushdown: 3x10 | Plank: 3x1min
 |  |  | Toe Touches: 3x20


I have 3 rest days (one between day 2 and 3 and two after day 4). I use 2 of them to do cardio and on those days I run about 2 miles. So far I have seen good progress on all of my lifts except for bench press (more mental than physical).


**Diet**

At this point I would love to have criticism on my routine but if you feel like taking a look at my diet that would be very helpful as well. My TDEE is estimated at between 2400-2600 calories. I am currently eating around 1400-1600 calories a day. I am only counting macros and my grams per day are: Protein (170g), Carbs(160-180g), Fat(20-30g). I do good at hitting them all, except carbs I am sometimes low. Below is my diet which is usually pretty consistent throughout the week.

*Breakfast:* 4 eggs (3 egg whites, one whole); One slice of whole grain bread and one tbsp of peanut butter (on lifting days) or one packet of instant oatmeal (on off days); 6 ounces of unsweetened coffee with 2 ounces of 1% milk.

*Lunch:* 4 ounces of baked chicken or one packet of starkist tuna salad; 1 ounce of black beans or one whole wheat tortilla or 2 slices of whole grain bread; 2 ounces of spinach or 4 ounces of mixed vegetables (carrots, green beans, peas, corn); One apple or two baby clementines

*Dinner:* 6 ounces of baked chicken; 1 cup of instant brown rice or one medium sweet potato or 2-3 ounces of whole grain pasta (with 2 ounces of tomato sauce); 4 ounces of broccoli or 4 ounces of mixed vegetables

*Snacks:* One banana (before workout); 2 scoops of ON gold standard protein powder (in8 ounces of water); one scoop of C4 blue razz pre-workout; one small handful of cashews (on rest days)

You basically have my entire routine and diet here, please feel free to critique and offer any advice as needed. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 17:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derrick Pouliot. Already having played under our coach in juniors he is ripe for a breakout season next year if he can get big minutes. 

Plus, [this is the face](http://imgick.oregonlive.com/home/brightcove01/width620/img/23/260825828001/201403/2796/260825828001_3288290201001_vs-531535c8e4b07df59d2d762e-1592194017001.jpg?pubId=260825828001) of a future elite defenseman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you seriously trying to troll or are you just 13? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 19

Favorite: Kris Letang

Hate: Brandon Dubinsky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a long day. I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's gay with a dash of something else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 09:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the new guy in the NFL, Leon Sandcastle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I wish people would stop misspelling names.

Martin St. Louis is as easy to spell as Dought Hamilton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruins sign Matt Beleskey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rangers acquire Nashville goalie Hellberg for 6th rd pick in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brassard out 4-6 weeks after surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Signs Goaltender Steve Michalek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blues sign Pat Cannone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/TSNAaronWard/status/616356905330561024

One year, $3M deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Memes, advice animals, and low-content posts will be removed on sight

Literally right in the sidebar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thompson inks two-year, two-way deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I just don't feel like Bennett is the guy for a 3rd line role. But I also thought he would eventually be a top line winger. So I'm probably wrong
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leafs sign Marc Arcobello </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 22:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more that comes out, I feel as though Bennett might be moved with Kunitz/Sutter.

Edit: Rewording </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bennett? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Sutter gets moved I believe that Sundqvist will do fine as a 3rd line C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he ended up on the 4th line for a portion...which is not the place for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 21:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume we probably offerred him a two-way for the same amount </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more milk in his diet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harrington is not a depth guy...he is still a prospect with great upside. In terms or potential I'd put him as our 3rd best d-man prospect.

Kapanen, why he was a late 1st rd pick I don't know. It was a steal. We gave up our best, and probably only real, forward prospect.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope mostly injuries and rehab. Although he was poorly used by Johnston for part of last season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WE OUT HERE FAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JIMMY RUTHERFORD OUT HERE MAKING DEALS FAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. Talented kid, just too many injuries to consistently contribute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably will give Bennett the chance to prove himself now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITS BASED GOD JIMMY RUTHERFORD IN THE HOUSE YALL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got Kapanen, Harrington and a pick. BASED GOD JIMMY RUTHERFORD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pouliot not going to Toronto in kessel deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT THE FUCK IS GOOD SALARY CAP?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PHIL THE THRILL IN BLACK AND GOLD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brad Richardson to ARI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oilers sign Letestu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comeau.....y u leave us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nate Prosser Re-Signs With Wild </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CHI signs Tikhonov </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIN signs Nate Prosser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beauchemin has NMC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOP TAKING OUR DEFENSEMEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna miss him, but with Zatkoff being much cheaper it was the right move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's over. Yashin out of contract with Islanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryan Lerg signed a one year (2 way) deal with the Sharks at $600 000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan White signs a one-year, one-way contract with #Flyers for $800K </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 01:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beauchemin will hit the market tomorrow as UFA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe?....nope. No thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would not be surprised. I've heard GMJR is loyal to his players and loves to bring them back when he can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a goddamn life saver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] (Music Video) Music video featured on reddit a while ago. Has a twist ending to it. Summary in description. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this music video on reddit I believe a month or two ago. I remember a lot of it, except of course the band name and song name.

Sort of an indie style song, upbeat tempo. Starts off with a kid in a car with an attractive woman. Then it shows different lives, each with something taboo occuring throughout the video. One is a guy beating up his neighbor, another is a guy having sexual relations with a neighbor's daughter, one is a wife cooking her fat husband and the last is a girl hoping someone shoots her religious dad.  At the end the kid in the car gets in an accident and it shows that from each perspective of the lives it was something the characters wished would happen, but actually didn't.

Hope this helps. I would really like to know the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That too.

But like, world class runners can't even do that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 miles in 20 minutes? Thats a little over 3 minutes per mile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had started to do something like this but personal matters had gotten in the way and I never got it running.

Here's my take on the 1st rd picks of the Coyotes for the last 10 years if anyone cares to take a look: http://www.reddit.com/r/hockey/comments/2y2t24/a_look_back_at_the_arizona_coyotes_last_10/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindback? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 02:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the beauty of the what if...but I do think Toews is more talented than Staal and even if he isn't who he is now he wouls still develop into a top-tier player.

But you could also argue that with the talent, you have Crosby as 1C, Toews as 2C and move Malkin to the wing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably go with J. Staal. In that case definitely not 3 cups but 2010 I would think so. Incredibly deep team.

Or pass on J. Staal and go with Backstrom (C). Which, on a line with Kane would be so exciting and dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inb4 what if Tuukka Rask? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
