<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9189</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoes squeaking during a basketball game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few:

 Adolf Hitler being denied by the Academy of Fine Arts in Vienna. This forced him to join the military in World War I and his experience in the military drastically shaped his views.

 Franz Ferdinand visiting Sarajevo on the 28th of June, which is Vivdovan, a Serbian nationalist holiday. Serbian nationalists such as the 19 year old Gavrilo Princep (who assassinated Ferdinand) believed that a symbol of foreign imperialism such as their Archduke visiting Sarajevo was an unacceptable insult.

 When Mark Sykes of the British Empire and Francois George-Picot of France drew a straight line putting various extremely polarized ethnic, political, and religious factions all in the same country, and forcing them to get along. Guess the country(ies).

Spoiler Alert: It was these.


This one action probably caused most of the turmoil we see in the region today.

 In 1347, a single ship from Caffa traveled to Sicily and infected rats, fleas, and people spread the plague all across Europe, causing as many as a third of Europes population to succumb to the disease. This paved the way to the end of Feudalism and eventually the rise of industrialism, as lower populations did allow the social order to be slightly more egalitarian. There was more land to be owned (Because everyone was too dead to farm it) so poorer farmers became estate owners over time. This also reformed European notions of disease, paving the way to the European Renaissance and the Scientific Revolution.

 Constantine Is conversion to Christianity after his vision at the Battle of Milvian Bridge caused Christianity to become the most influential religion in the world, and also inadvertently caused the collapse of the Western Roman Empire.

 (Note: This is the most far out one) Julius Caesar, created the Roman Empire. Rome conquered several parts of Asia Minor and unified the southern-most territories and Northern Africa, which made the region ripe for conquest for the Caliphates of the Middle East. Fast forward a millennia or two and then you have the Ottomans, which quasi-started World War I, which triggered World War II, jumping the US and USSR to superpower status, and created the turmoil in the region today (Told ya it was far out). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when the Americans united against goverment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so tht is your  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
