<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6396</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still fringe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Anthropologists and historians who study this would be absolutely thrilled if it turned out to be true.

Grant money would start flowing like water from the faucet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Randall Carlson found nano diamonds across the globe. 

That idea has been [challenged and possibly refuted](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/12/161219115304.htm)

 But it goes againstAcademic science because, well they've been taught that man killed off all the large megafauna in North America. 

Science requires a rigorous process of vetting findings before a hypothesis is largely accepted. Other lines of evidence are needed and other hypotheses to explain similar results need to be investigated. Is this is a long process? Yes. Is it sometimes [unfair and cruel to researchers](https://www.hakaimagazine.com/article-long/vilified-vindicated-story-jacques-cinq-mars)? Yes. But if we accepted every idea that had a marginal shred of evidence with no further investigation, we would still believe Piltdown Man was real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbus reaching the New World </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a better question, I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the Sahara formed about 7 million years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did humans create the Sahara Desert? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say this question is not answerable. As you said, it is complicated and depends on the sub-field and specialty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1491 by Charles Mann </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration to Denmark is nothing new  just ask the Vikings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweeeeeeeeeet

I might have to reinstall Stellaris  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do the Dyson spheres do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, don't worry about it. I barely talk to anyone from high school. You may have grown up with some of these people, but you find out real quick that once you're not all cooped up in the same building five days a week you have very little to hold on to.

Just make sure that when you go to college you talk to people in your classes, especially in classes for your major. One of my best friends today I met in my archaeology classes because we were both the biggest Mesoamerican nerds around. At the same time, make sure to go to parties when you can. If you have to ask where parties are being held, do so. People should be more than willing to point you to a house party, even if it is a party to promote their frat/sorority.

Making friends is weird, man. You can't stop trying, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's happening to Stellaris? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://img.pandawhale.com/post-29513-there-are-dozens-like-us-gif-I-NYgW.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. When the Spanish showed up the Aztecs were on their way to subduing Tlaxcala. With Tlaxcala out of the picture, the Aztecs could have better consolidated their territory and tributary provinces. If the Spanish were temporarily repulsed the Aztecs could have prepared and strengthened their position against further Spanish incursion. It did not take long for the Aztecs to adapt to fighting horses or guns/cannons. Spears were lengthened and warriors would zig zag in the field to avoid the already poor accuracy of the Spanish arquebus.

I think you severely underestimate what Mesoamericans could do. Take the Mixton War, for instance. If the Spanish had not thrown tens of thousands of Aztec and Tarascan allies at the Caxcanes and their allies, the Spanish would not have been able to break the rebellion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  involve the Skywalker story

Confirmed, Rey is Luke's daughter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://books.google.com/books?hl=en lr= id=Hud8NSEJ3ToC oi=fnd pg=PR7 dq=Moctezuma%27s+first+dinner ots=fjQ8emdIp8 sig=3rZ4qcw-D9qUIyUxkpt-l3GP1MM#v=onepage q=Moctezuma's%20first%20dinner f=false

Scroll down to Chapter 3, "Moctezuma's First Dinner" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure. My expertise is in Mesoamerica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to scale this up for me for Halloween </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they practice tattooing

There is some limited evidence for tattooing in the Americas. The [momia tolteca](http://arqueologiamexicana.mx/mexico-antiguo/momias-y-tatuajes), which isn't actually Toltec, was found to have geometric tattoos. And the Spaniard [Gonzalo Guerrero](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gonzalo_Guerrero) seems to suggest that the Maya practiced extensive tattooing given the fact that he enculturated himself into Maya society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Precolumbian chickrn bones found in Chile are pretty definitive.

Work from a few years ago on chicken DNA has [challenged](http://news.nationalgeographic.com/news/2014/03/140318-polynesian-chickens-pacific-migration-america-science/) the idea that chicken bones found in South America were Polynesian in origin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They have also found remnants of a sort of kayak vessel of Polynesian design in Mexico or California.

Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to actual [article](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/03/07/1619040114.abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Middle Pleistocene hominin cranium from Gruta da Aroeira (Portugal) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Portuguese skull may be an early relative of Neandertals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could call them *Tlatlacateculo* or "owl men". They were actual assassins the Aztecs used to kill others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Tenochtitlan was ~1 million people

Closer to 200,000 people, mate

 And they would have a lot of freedom considering that we don't entirely know how the whole city was laid out.

[We have an idea](http://www.historytoday.com/kate-wiles/tenochtitlan-1524), but you are right that we don't know what it looked like exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not see the sale. Checking now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had not come across those brands yet. They are still expensive. When I went looking for bags I was hoping to spend no more than $100. How naive I was. I came across this bag from [Copper River Bag Co.](http://www.copperriverbags.com/medium-14-newtown-voyager-laptop-bag-distressed-tan/). With the leather strap it is sub $200 at least. I just need to debate whether I want to drop that much money or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly how I felt. And this may be controversial, but I felt the same way with Lost and Battlestar Galactica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current bag is not leather, but I have other leather items that I take care of and maintain. I like them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ruins of Tikl, Guatemala, before restoration. Classic Period Maya city. Taken 1890-1891 [750x573] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Article](http://www.livescience.com/58232-ancient-tomb-decorated-with-vibrant-murals-found-in-china.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vibrant mural found in 1,000 year old tomb in Datong City, China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Article](http://www.livescience.com/58232-ancient-tomb-decorated-with-vibrant-murals-found-in-china.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Vibrant mural found in 1,000 year old tomb in Datong City, China [1200x803] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am tentatively getting pumped for Mass Effect Andromeda. I would preorder the game, but I've learned to not do that and just wait for reviews. But waiting just sucks ass. In the mean time I can finish my ME3 playthrough. I'll say it, I liked the game and didn't mind the ending.

Yesterday I spent way too much time looking for a leather laptop/messenger bag. I never realized how expensive those things were. All the affordable ones I've found on Amazon seem to have issues with straps breaking and the seller not refunding/replacing, weird smells, or the leather staining your clothes. I just can't afford a $500+ quality bag right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP you may be interested in this post I made on /r/Anthropology a [few weeks ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/Anthropology/comments/5vuxng/any_archaeologists_out_there/de558wg/?context=3). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bluefish Caves have been repeatedly dated to 24,000 years ago. And new work at Monte Verde has pushed the date of occupation back to 19,000 BP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work from a few years ago on chicken DNA has [challenged](http://news.nationalgeographic.com/news/2014/03/140318-polynesian-chickens-pacific-migration-america-science/) the idea that chicken bones found in South America were Polynesian in origin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bluefish Caves are dated to 24,000 years ago](https://www.hakaimagazine.com/article-long/vilified-vindicated-story-jacques-cinq-mars). [Meadowcroft Rockshelter and Cactus Hill](http://scienceviews.com/indian/pre_clovis_sites.html) date to 16,000 years ago. Buttermilk Creek from ~13,200 and 15,500 years ago. [Debra L. Friedkin Site](https://www.thoughtco.com/pre-clovis-sites-americas-173079) from 14,000 to 16,000 years ago. Guitarrero Cave to 12,100 years ago. Manis Mastodon to 13,800 years ago. The list goes on. Suffice to say that, yes, there are gaps but they are being slowly filled in as more and more sites are found. If you are not fortuitous in finding a washout or a field with very thin soil that has been plowed, you need to go hunting in caves or dig down really deep to find such old remains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This otter looks like it just saw something scandalous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Aztecs had judges in their markets which could pass sentences should someone be caught trying to pass off counterfeit cacao beans as real cacao beans. To prevent counterfeiting, the beans would have had to be inspected to make sure people were not taking out white fleshy part and replacing it with mud, amaranth dough, avocado pits, or something else to replace its weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
* Writing

Writing is a big thing people talk about, but don't quite understand when it comes to Mesoamerica. The only writing associated with the Olmec comes from the Cascajal Block. This is a block of stone that is associated with the Olmec and covered wit [signs](http://www.famsi.org/mayawriting/cascajal/cascajal_drawing.jpg), though the signs are not made in any particular order. Some scholars have argued that this is a form of pictographic writing in which signs are used to recall memorized knowledge. But to date, no one has been able to translate it.

Epi-Olmec (or Isthmian) should not be confused with the Olmec. This is a later culture than the Olmec who did produce [writing](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:La_Mojarra_Inscription_and_Long_Count_date.jpg), though there is a debate whether we can translate it or not. Epi-Olmec is organized using a familiar system of glyphs in columns and rows like Maya writing. The Zapotecs in Oaxaca also produced a glyph based [writing system](http://blogs.uoregon.edu/mesoinstitute/files/2013/12/DSCF8526-2a7la1b.jpg). I'm not sure on its status of translation, to be honest.

Maya writing is a syllabic based writing in which [phonetic signs are combined to forms glyphs](http://www.jaguarstones.com/maya/images/glyphs/Younger%20brother.png). These glyphs represent words like nouns, verbs, adjectives, etc. Within the glyphs are also grammatical elements like possession, tense, direction, etc. Maya writing goes as far back as the Late Formative murals at San Bartolo, but Late Formative Maya writing hasn't been translated yet. It seems like Late Formative writing is a bit different from its later Classic form. Classic Maya and Postclassic Maya writing has been translated. This was thanks to, ironically, Friar Diego de Landa who burned hundreds of Maya manuscripts in the early colonial period. De Landa seems to have had some major remorse and did what he could to preserve what little knowledge about Maya writing that was available to him. While he was able to record phonetic signs for parts of words, he never did figure out how to combine them into glyphs. He was working under the assumption that the writing was an alphabet in which each glyph was a letter. It took centuries before Yuri Knorozov, a Soviet scientist, was able to make the first translations of Maya writing.

The Aztecs made use of a pictographic system of writing in which signs were used to recall already memorized information. These signs were incorporated in their artwork in order to relay information. Sometimes this was really straightforward with tributary lists showing a drawing of an item and a number. Other times the signs were used to convey more complex information such as the Aztec migration myth from their homeland to the Basin of Mexico. In both cases, Aztec writing differed greatly from the Maya, Zapotec, or Epi-Olmec. Their writing was not phonetic symbols combined to form words and was not organized into neat columns or rows.

So this post is getting really long and I'm going to cut it off there. I tried to cover a lot of general information without getting too specific. Let me know if you have any other questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some major differences between the Olmec, Aztec, and Maya would be:

* Ceremonial centers

While the Olmec had ceremonial centers are places like La Ventana, San Lorenzo, and Tres Zapotes, these were strictly ceremonial centers. The architecture constructed here was largely temple structures. You do not see the same level of urban structures like you would in a Maya or Aztec city which would have palaces for elites and numerous houses and storage buildings for merchants and commoners.

* Farming

The Olmec occupied floodplain areas in Veracruz. Earlier in the Archaic period, the Olmec took advantage of the fertility of the floodplain and farmed this area. As an insurance against too much flooding, they also farmed nearby hills and created low mounds that would have risen above the flood waters. While the hills provided security in arable land, they sometimes lacked sufficient water or the ability to grow diverse crops. This practice continued into the Formative period.

The Maya farmed using a couple of methods. The more famous method was to create milpas or fields in the jungle which they would use for a few years while rotating crops and then leave fallow to recover. Another method was to create terraces to prevent erosion and provide more arable land. The area around Caracol is heavily terraced.

The Aztecs were known for their chinampa system. A chinampa is a raised bed of earth located in a lake. The Aztecs would drive stakes into the lake bottom for support and then add layers of reed mats and earth until the mound was stable and ready for farming. They would then plant their crops on these raised beds while using the lake water for irrigation. I've heard that they would also plant some tree species along the edge of the chinampa for support. Supposedly a chinampa could get two or three crops a year compared to normal farming.

* Deities

Deities between the Olmec, Maya, and Aztec are not as similar as you may think. Some kind of feathered serpent deity or figure was shared among them, but you would be hard pressed to say that it was the exact same deity. Olmec deities are somewhat harder to discuss since they left no writing and their cultural practices had changed or were replaced by the time the Spanish arrived. For the Maya we can look to their own writing and colonial writings to piece together their mythology and beliefs. For the Maya they have deities like the maize god (sometimes called Hun-Hunahpu), Ah Muzen Cab (god of bees), Ah Puch (god of death), and Kinich Ahau (solar deity). The Aztecs may have similar gods that occupy similar positions of belief like Centeotl (god of maize), subject6396 (lord of the underworld), and Tonatiuh (sun god), but the beliefs and mythology surrounding Aztec gods are completely different from their Maya counterparts. That does not mean that certain concepts were not shared such as the four directions of the world, a concept for the heavens and underworld, and an axis mundi (sometimes associated with a tree) that linked the underworld to the earthly plane and on to the heavens.

* Politics

It is hard to pin down Olmec politics. As I mentioned above, they left no writing behind and their culture in the Formative period did not remain static enough until the arrival of the Spanish. The Olmec most likely had rulers who may have been equal parts priest, king, and warrior. However, burials for Olmec elites have not really been recovered. The environment of Veracruz does not lend itself well to preservation unless you are deeply buried in swamp muck like the wooden busts found at El Manat. Scholars have argued for decades as to what the political system of the Olmec may have been. Some link the Olmec to an empire that spread out from Veracruz and reached places like Guerrero, the Basin of Mexico, and the Maya region. They base this idea on similar looking artwork which has not quite held up to critique. Where one scholar sees an empire expanding its influence via artwork, another scholar sees local elites adopting aspects of Olmec culture and art for their own purposes to gain power and prestige. Recent dating of the cave art at Oxtotitlan in Guerrero puts the artwork as contemporary or even earlier than the Olmec. This may throw another wrench into the idea that the Olmec were very influential. Likewise with more work in the Maya region uncovering Early and Middle Formative sites that are contemporaneous, yet clearly different artistically from the Olmec.

Starting with the earliest urban centers in places like Ceibal in the Middle Formative period, the Maya appear to have always seem to have occupied city-states in which they shared an overarching culture and language family. At no point has the Maya region ever been unified in any sort of empire, though large alliances did occur. Some recent work at Classic period sites have lead some scholars to argue that Calakmul did, in fact, form an empire and then crushed their rival, Tikal. However, this hypothesis is still very new and very fresh and must run through the academic gauntlet as people support or contest the idea and as more evidence is uncovered. The Maya continued to occupy city-states through the Classic period and into the Postclassic and colonial periods. Many people have heard of the Classic period collapse, but collapse is not quite the correct word. Things definitely changed for the Maya in the last few centuries of the Classic period, but it was not some apocalyptic event in which hundreds of thousands of people died and the survivors huddled in their huts for centuries until the Spanish showed up. Instead, the collapse was more complex. There was a restructuring of politics in which the former Classic period god-king, both spiritual and political ruler of the city who could communicate with the gods, was replaced with a more secular king, council, and priestly order. Now, not every Postclassic city may have followed this, but they definitely did not hold the same religiously backed political influence they once had. The percept that the Postclassic was somehow less or trivial compared to the Classic is, in part, the result of academic research during the past century+. People, including academics, were enamored by the idea of a lost jungle cities and the idea of this collapse. As a result, there is a disproportionate amount of research conducted on the Classic period which gives a skewed view of how we view the past. People see that we know less about the Postclassic, combine that with the idea of a collapse, and conclude that the Maya really did meet some apocalyptic end. The reality is that some urban centers were abandoned in the last few centuries of the Classic period, more warfare did occur, famine and drought did occur, but these events were haphazard and not continuous throughout the area. For every urban center that was abandoned, you see an increase in population in another center or the reoccupation of an Early Classic classic center. For every sign of warfare you see an extensive trade network of goods from much further away than before. For every instance of evidence of drought and famine, we find evidence of prosperity and abundance. That is why we see large centers like Chichen Itza, Coba, Mayapan, Q'umarkaj, and Uxmal form. That's why we see places like Nojpeten not only continue, but thrive and resist the Spanish until 1697. The fractured nature of the Maya region allowed them to continue on when disaster hit an area. They were quite resilient

The Aztecs, unlike the Maya, are categorized as an empire. The Aztecs were really an alliance of three city-states in the Basin of Mexico. The most famous one is Tenochtitlan, the city for the Mexica, but there is also Tlacopan and Texcoco. These three city-states banded together to overthrow the Tepanecs and eventually went on to conquer the entire Basin of Mexico and onward. The Aztecs were not quite a territorial empire. They would go to a city and demand that a city give them tribute. If the city refused each envoy from the Triple Alliance, the Aztecs would then raise their armies, conquer the city, replace their leader, and demand a heftier tribute. Those that surrendered were able to keep their rulers and their men did not have to die in battle. Needless to say, many groups tried to rebel against the Aztecs though none were able to coordinate together well enough to completely throw off the Aztec yoke. Groups like the Tlaxcallans may have been on their way to being subdued by the Aztecs if they had not allied themselves with the Spanish. Others, like the Tarascans, the Aztecs were not able to conquer and instead constructed a series of defensive fortresses. The Aztecs may have been trying to strangle the Tarascans economically as they were with the Tlaxcallans, but those plans were never able to come to fruition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to know, where was Cummings when the House Oversight committee was looking into Hillary's wrongdoings? If you watch any of their sessions with Comey and other related people, Cummings did nothing but downplay Hillary's wrongdoings and deflect. I'm glad he's going after Trump and all, but come on. That's the same party over people tactic Republicans pull. We're not going to get anywhere if parties won't investigate their own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kind of reinforces what he is saying about the Saami being marginalized and discriminated against, doesn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indigenous salmon-fishing Saami criminalised by Finland and Norway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indigenous salmon-fishing Saami criminalised by Finland and Norway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we are just picking and choosing lines,

 When soldiers did misuse their equipment, they cut hands from living people to cover their activities.

and

 There were, however, a number of notable examples of white colonial administrators known for particular sadism. These included individuals such as Lon Rom, Lon Fivez (known as the "devil of quateur"), and Ren de Permentier who collectively served as inspirations for the character of Kurtz in Joseph Conrad's 1899 novella Heart of Darkness

And to bring in [another source](http://www.digitaljournal.com/blog/11297)

 Severed hands

 Such was the brutality of Leopolds Congo that those who failed to meet the rubber quotas set by the Belgian officers, were routinely flogged with the chicote or had their hands severed (the chicotte was a whip made out of raw, sun-dried hippopotamus hide, cut into a long sharp-edged cork-screw strip. It was applied to bare buttocks, and left permanent scars. Twenty strokes of it sent victims into unconsciousness and a 100 or more strokes were often fatal. The chicotte was freely used by both Leopold's men and the French).

 Leopold used a private mercenary force, Force Publique (FP), to do his terrorising and killing. White Officers commanded black soldiers many of whom were cannibals from tribes in the upper Congo and others had been kidnapped as children during raids on surrounding villages and raised in missionaries.
A FP junior officer described a raid to punish a village that had protested, in the following words. The commanding officer ordered us to cut off the heads of the men and hang them on the village palisades, also their sexual members, and to hang the women and the children on the palisade in the form of a cross."

This also doesn't change that fact that people were being brutalized </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were busy being subjugated. You would have a right difficult time getting things done when Europeans were [chopping off your hands](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atrocities_in_the_Congo_Free_State#Mutilation_and_brutality).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is working under the assumptions that all Native Americans were hunter-gatherers and that modern hunter-gatherers who live in marginal areas are representative of all hunter-gatherers regardless of the environment they live in. These assumptions would, of course, produce smaller estimates. However, we know that not all Native Americans were hunter-gatherers. Most of them were agriculturalists who may have supplemented their farming with hunting as early European colonists did. We also know that modern hunter-gatherers are not representative of hunter-gatherers in the past since the marginal areas they currently live does not have the same carrying capacity as more fertile areas non-hunter-gatherers currently occupy. These marginal areas restric population numbers since overpopulation would lead to catastrophe. That's why you have higher population estimates by both Dobyns and Thornton who factor these things into their estimates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is just one hypothesized population estimate. Thornton (1990) estimates 7 million people and Dobyns (1983) estimates 18 million people. Part of the difficulty in estimating populations is that European diseases often raced ahead of Europeans entering an area and then recording the population.

Dobyns, Henry (1983). Their Number Become Thinned: Native American Dynamics in Eastern North America. Knoxville: University of Tennessee Press.

Thornton, Russell (1990). American Indian holocaust and survival: a population history since 1492. University of Oklahoma Press. pp. 2632. ISBN 0-8061-2220-X. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the "x" is pronounced with a "sh" sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the transatlantic slave trade was mostly owned and run by Jews not white Europeans 

Source?

 The white slaves would become known as "Rednecks", a name that is still around today, because their fair skin would burn while the toiled in the sun all day.

[Etymology Online](
http://www.etymonline.com/index.php?allowed_in_frame=0 search=redneck) makes no mention of white slaves in relation to this term.

 I take it you mean Europeans specifically living on the North American continent?

No, I mean Europeans everywhere. Europe itself would not have grown in population as it did after 1492 without using New World plants. Just look at the history of the potato.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, there's no evidence to support that hypothesis. Where you are basing this idea from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bones, teeth reveal the harsh conditions endured by the ancestors of indigenous Finnish cattle and sheep breeds, particularly in the Middle Ages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  America as we know it was built by Europeans. Not Africans. Not the natives.

Except for all those slaves.

 All of the infrastructure, buildings, scientific advancements, etc. are (for the most part) European.

Not all. Europeans would be nowhere without New World plants. They would not have seen a population explosion after the 1500s if it were not for maize and potatoes not to mention other fruits and vegetables like tomatoes, tomatillos, beans, squash, chiles, pineapple, cacao, vanilla, avocado, quinoa, amaranth, etc. European countries would not have been able to become wealthy or even send colonists to areas like Virginia and the Carolinas without exploiting cash crops like tobacco and cotton, either. These plants required careful cultivation and ingenuity over thousands of years, especially maize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  we took the land that they claimed no rights to

That is a common misconception. Perhaps these topics on /r/AskHistorians will enlighten you,

* [How accurate is the popular US perception that Native Americans lost their land "because they didn't understand the concept of ownership?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1g8v2t/how_accurate_is_the_popular_us_perception_that/)

* [Why do many Native-American cultures not have any concept of land ownership?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/27i79m/why_do_many_nativeamerican_cultures_not_have_any/)

* [How did Native Americans view land ownership?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1eya7m/how_did_native_americans_view_land_ownership/)

* [What legal ways (if any) were Europeans using to claim rights to new found lands? Did Native Americans or other groups have ideas about land ownership already?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3cly9y/what_legal_ways_if_any_were_europeans_using_to/)

* [How did Native Americans (or other tribes for that matter) avoid 'Tragedy of the Commons' problems?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1guyfn/how_did_native_americans_or_other_tribes_for_that/)

* [What would the trinkets traded to Natives for Manhattan have been worth to other tribes?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1ti8ui/what_would_the_trinkets_traded_to_natives_for/)

 and were mostly doing nothing with

Also a common misconception. Natives heavily modified their landscape for their own purposes. The Amazon jungle, for instance, is one giant orchard along its many rivers. Natives purposely planted and cultivated trees to provide for themselves a secure food source throughout the year to supplement any farming or hunting they did.

The Moche and Hohokam both created extensive irrigation systems in their respective arid regions of the Americas to bring water for farming and drinking. 

The Inca heavily terraced their mountain and hillsides to provide farmable land to support their empire of millions.

The Aztecs created a system of damns in Lake Texcoco to separate the salt and fresh waters of the lake. This allowed them to create a source of fresh water for drinking and farming while being able to continue to exploit salt and freshwater plants and animals.

 I would be more than happy to discuss them having their own land in America.

They had their own land. Two continents worth until 1492. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But they didn't have the written word

The Zapotec, Epi-Olmec, and Maya all had full-fledged writing systems. Teotihuacan, uie, Xochicalco, Mixtec, Mixteca-Puebla, and Aztec had pictograph based writing systems.

 Also did you seriously call a hill fort (that's what Cahokia is, right?) 

Cahokia was a ceremonial and urban center for tens of thousands of people. They had urban settlements up an down the Mississippi, Missouri, Ohio, and other minor rivers that flowed into the previous three rivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The current Native Americans were just the last group that migrated to the new world via Asia. they genocided and enslaved the previous wave,just as the previous did to the ones before them. the native Americas were not originally there, they conquered it just as the settlers did, they just arrived slightly earlier.

There's no evidence for this. Archaeologists have proposed multiple waves of migration to explain genetic and linguistic dissimilarities between Native populations, but these hypotheses do not propose any kind of genocide of the previous wave of migration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Zimbabwe: African City of Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't because it needs a massive overhaul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks, dude. Maybe next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like climate change deniers and environmental scientists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, it's all good. 

I just wish there was a way we could use that topic as an example for educators and how they need to change their curriculum. But then, who knows how old those people are, what countries they live in, and what educated they received? Can we really fault a 54 year old Bulgarian who only went to high school for not knowing these things? 

The lesson, I think, is that I shouldn't sound like such an asshole when I try to educate people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,000 year old mummy shroud discovered in museum collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this isn't the nano-diamond people trying to counter the refutation that came out this [past December](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/12/161219115304.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/history [delivers again](https://np.reddit.com/r/history/comments/5y8dr4/why_werent_native_americans_as_technologically/) by demonstrating that despite decades of New World archaeological and historical work, ignorance and stereotypes continue to persist.

Highlights include:

* ["The Eurasians built many whole huge cities. Because they could."](https://np.reddit.com/r/history/comments/5y8dr4/why_werent_native_americans_as_technologically/dep2nnk/)

* ["they were hunters and gathers who were one with nature, and injected shrooms regularly to communicate with other beings."](https://np.reddit.com/r/history/comments/5y8dr4/why_werent_native_americans_as_technologically/deofdtl/)

* ["There was no reason for them to be."](https://np.reddit.com/r/history/comments/5y8dr4/why_werent_native_americans_as_technologically/deny8gj/)

* [me: "So you are saying Native Americans are one large homogenous group from the Arctic to the Tierra del Fuego? That their neighbors were so culturally similar that two entire continents were completely culturally and intellectually stagnant?" them: "Basically?"](https://np.reddit.com/r/history/comments/5y8dr4/why_werent_native_americans_as_technologically/deoboux/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fermentation into drinks was relatively recent.

Fermented drinks may have been the reason why maize was domesticated.

  Alcohol was reserved fro the ruling classes.

Not necessarily. People could and did drink often. Feasting was an important part of my cultures and feasting involves drink.

 domestic animals

Natives had several domesticated animals like the dog, llama, muscovy duck, and guinea pig

 writing on paper

Mesoamerica made use of paper as far back as the first century AD

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a number of books on the Maya in the /r/AskHistorians [book list](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/books/americas#wiki_latin_american_history) if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purepecha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps the section [Cross-cultural communication and lingua francas](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/language#wiki_cross-cultural_communication_and_lingua_francas) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mayan culture

Maya* culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discovery of widespread platinum may help solve Clovis people mystery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the huge post, but you didn't really give me a definition of "very few". You say "significantly smaller number", but don't specify a number to compare it to. So how about you just give me a number for "very few"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But only a very few.

How do you define "very few"?

And I don't mean to sound condescending. I apologize </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not cast [Jamie Costa](https://youtu.be/Shg53iv4B9o) if you want to keep the Robin Williams take of Genie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I'm saying that you cannot measure how advanced a people are by focusing on just one thing or one category of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But that's the thing, I have stopped and examined it. I know there is a wide variety of hut, that there is a wide variety of simple planting methods, that there is a wide variety of coracle/canoe design, that there is a wide variety of ways that they sewed together things like animal skins as coverings and painted beads to sew on the clothing in different patterns.

You haven't though because you assume everyone lives in a hut. Or that they farmed the same way or the same things. You are relying on this perception that all Native peoples are somehow Plains peoples when that is completely false.

 But if I said, as a historian from the future, that vehicles in the 20th century U.S. were still on the combustion engine era, telling me that I'm painfully generalizing a huge region and I could find such rich variation from the Tin Lizzie to the Grand Caravan, that wouldn't mean that automobile technology had advanced beyond the combustion engine.

You realize you are illustrating my point, right? You are focusing on just one thing and putting up an arbitrary goal post so that when people do not reach it, you can say they failed. Any level of progress or advancement is an artificial construct created by your own personal knowledge and bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Iroquois remained in the Stone Age

Stone Age is a term applied to a specific chronological time period in many parts of Europe. Stone Age not necessarily indicative of technology level, but marks a change in cultural development. This term cannot be applied appropriately to other cultures outside of Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not many large constructions were made in the Americas. Some, yes. But compared to Eurasia, it was a pittance.

What do you define as a large construction?

 The Eurasians built many whole huge cities.

You know the Americas had cities before the arrival of Europeans, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Aztec and Maya are at the bottom part of what we technically call North America.

But they are still in North America.

 The natives from Canada down to Florida and across the entire Midwest - making up probably about... 3/4 to 4/5ths of the entire landmass of "North America" - had about the same technology level (or earlier) as the rest of humanity did two thousand years earlier.

You are painfully generalizing such a huge region. If you stopped and examined this area, its history, and its cultures, you would not say such a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's wondering (and now I confess I am also curious) how they got that far behind

You both are assuming that there is an end goal that every culture/civilization is somehow working towards. History isn't a game of civilization. People are not working towards building a ship to go to Alpha Centauri. There's no real answer to this question because the question itself is flawed. It requires a definition of what "advanced" means and that definition invariably is set up for most non-Europeans to fail that test. You talk about "advanced", but you only consider some technological developments. No one ever stops to think of cultural, social, linguistic, artistic, etc developments. You see the issue in trying to answer that question? You could have some advanced technology, but totally be devoid of a dynamic and artistic culture. Or your language may be set up in such a way to inadequately express certain ideas or concepts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Aztec and Maya are in North America.

If you want another example in North America, look at the Hohokam canal system in the Phoenix area of Arizona. Natives created an extensive irrigation system in order to farm in the desert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're interested in visiting ruins, I wrote [this post](http://tlatollotl.tumblr.com/post/142930176516/tlatollotls-beachless-yucatan-vacation) on Tumblr awhile ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My time to shine!

I wrote [this post](http://tlatollotl.tumblr.com/post/142930176516/tlatollotls-beachless-yucatan-vacation) on Tumblr for people who want to visit ruins. I have some really great choices if you're willing to drive a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Maya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI and CIA launch criminal investigation into 'malware leaks' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cortes was near invincible to arrows, spears, and slingshots.

No he wasn't. His men were repeatedly injured by all of these things.

You also forgot about the tens of thousands of Native allies Cortes used to conquer Tenochtitlan. It makes a very big difference, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey OP, you may want to check out the /r/AskHistorians podcast /u/400-rabbits did on the conquest of Mexico. You can find part one [here](http://askhistorians.libsyn.com/askhistorians-podcast-episode-004) and part two [here](http://askhistorians.libsyn.com/askhistorians-podcast-episode-005). 400-rabbits does an amazing job of covering the conquest of Mexico. I think you'll really enjoy it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone linked directly to the paper in [this topic](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5y9vd3/studies_of_ancient_dna_found_in_the_dental_plaque/) two hours before you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone linked directly to the paper in [this topic](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5y9wds/dna_in_hair_samples_collected_from_aboriginal/) three hours before you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  injected shrooms 

How does one inject shrooms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lots of slaves most of the time.

No, not slaves. It was mostly commoners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You have a bunch of nomadic or semi-nomadic tribal entities

And that is where your presumption falls flat. Most Native peoples were agriculturalists who farmed by the time Europeans arrived to the New World. Do not think U.S. Plains people in the 1800s as the standard from which all Native people are like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you are going with this. You want to make a comparison between the New and Old World where the New World fails by default. You choose an arbitrary goal post and when New World peoples cannot reach that goal post to your satisfaction you flunk them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Native Americans routinely burning the undergrowth of forests in the US Northeast to promote certain plant growth isn't changing the environment? Natives cultivating and planting tree species in the Amazon to secure food throughout the year isn't changing the environment? Natives also creating nutrient and carbon rich soils in the Amazon to farm isn't changing the environment? The Inca heavily terracing the mountains and hills of the Andes in order to plant food isn't changing the environment? The Aztec controlling the salinity of Lake Texcoco through the use of dams to create fresh water area of the lake to farm and drink with while maintaining a saltwater body to continue to exploit salt water based plants and animals isn't changing the environment? The Maya who defrosted huge swaths of the Yucatan to maintain their cooking fires and to create limestone plaster isn't changing the environment? The Moche constructing long irrigation canals to bring water from the mountains to their arid plane isn't changing the environment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm saying is that European agricultural practices are not as effective for all other agricultural practices. Case in point, the potato. Europeans planted the potato as they would any other crop. This made the potato susceptible to temperature change and the spread of fungus from guano-based fertilizer. If Europeans had planted the potato as Andeans did, at the bottom of troughs of earth widely separated from one another, the potato famines experienced by Europeans would not have been as severe with the fungus unable to easily transmit to other plants and the plants protected by frosts or temperatures that were too hot.

So you are assuming that using a horse in conjunction with maize, chiles, beans, squash, cacao, vanilla, goosefoot, yucca, quinoa, potatoes, tomatoes, tomatillos, pineapple, etc would somehow magically increase their effectiveness even though these foods were domesticated and cultivated without the use of a horse for thousands of years.

Populations estimates are difficult to calculate, thus the large spread.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Due to this, the Americas had a hard time making large sprawling cities,

There are cities all over the Americas. Cahokia, Emerald Mound, Teotihuacan, Cholula, Tikal, El Mirador, Calakmul, Cusco, Chan Chan, the list goes on.

 I think the Aztec capital was impressive too, but probably didn't have stone (correct me if I'm wrong.)

They had stone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A big reason was lack of beasts of burden. 

Why? The Americas were able to support 50 million to 100 million people by 1492. Trade networks stretched up and down the coasts and  in the interior (i.e. copper from the Great Lakes found in Louisiana, turquoise from New Mexico found in southern Mexico, tomatoes from South America found in Mexico).

  If you wanted to build something huge, it was a major, time-consuming undertaking that required a lot of human labour. If you wanted to move very large amounts of anything, you either used a boat or a lot of people, or didn't bother.

While this is true, large constructions were still made without the use of any sort of pack animal to move the construction material. Native Americans were perfectly able make some of the largest constructions in the world. The Great Pyramid of Cholula, for example, is almost twice the volume of the Pyramid at Giza and it was constructed using only human laborers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It also helped that Europe had the horse while the Americas did not.

This rings of a notion that Europeans somehow dominated the Americas because of the horse. They would not have been able to do so without allying themselves with other Native peoples. It isn't as if Cortes and his band conquered Mexico all by themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, you may be interested in the FAQ section [Technology and Civilization in the Americas](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_technology_and_civilization_in_the_americas) over at /r/AskHistorians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  leads to completely different environments that forces culture (social, intellectual, and technological) to adapt, leading to a faster rate of evolution/advancement. On the other hand, Native Americans and Aboriginals "mastered" a rarely changing environment early-on, meaning there wasn't that much of an incentive to advance culturally/technologically.

There's no changing environments or landscapes in the Americas? Does that mean Yukon is as desert like as Atacama? Or San Diego as lush and tropical as the Amazon? Or the Rocky Mountains as flat as the Great Plains? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd take a guess the lack of contacts. 

So you are saying Native Americans are one large homogenous group from the Arctic to the Tierra del Fuego? That their neighbors were so culturally similar that two entire continents were completely culturally and intellectually stagnant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Horses have a much more mundane benefit, they can pull heavy ploughs in fields to produce enough food to support large societies.

The Americas had anywhere between 50 million and 100 million people by 1492 and could support them with farming done without horses. You overrate the effectiveness of the horse on all forms of agricultural practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps these previous topics will answer your inquiry.

* [How accurate is the popular US perception that Native Americans lost their land "because they didn't understand the concept of ownership?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1g8v2t/how_accurate_is_the_popular_us_perception_that/)

* [Why do many Native-American cultures not have any concept of land ownership?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/27i79m/why_do_many_nativeamerican_cultures_not_have_any/)

* [How did Native Americans view land ownership?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1eya7m/how_did_native_americans_view_land_ownership/)

* [What legal ways (if any) were Europeans using to claim rights to new found lands? Did Native Americans or other groups have ideas about land ownership already?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3cly9y/what_legal_ways_if_any_were_europeans_using_to/)

* [How did Native Americans (or other tribes for that matter) avoid 'Tragedy of the Commons' problems?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1guyfn/how_did_native_americans_or_other_tribes_for_that/)

* [What would the trinkets traded to Natives for Manhattan have been worth to other tribes?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1ti8ui/what_would_the_trinkets_traded_to_natives_for/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How do you encounter these theories in grad school for archaeology? Is it zany fellow students? Is Clyde Winters one of the graduate advisors at your school?

I should rephrase my sentence. I don't encounter these people in graduate school and none of my professors have expressed support for these kinds of ideas. I have encountered people that do support fringe ideas. One person was in an undergraduate course on Greek archaeology while I was earning my BA who did ask about Atlantis. While in graduate school I met another person at a bar outside of class who was talking about ley lines under the Egyptian pyramids. Most of the people I have encountered that support the idea for pre-Columbian trans-Atlantic contact have been through social media because of the Tumblr and Instagram accounts I manage on the side. These accounts are dedicated mostly to Mesoamerican archaeology and New World archaeology more broadly to get people interested and wanting to learn about the history, people, and culture of the Americas. This inevitably butted heads with people pushing other ideas.

I should have said that as a graduate student in Mesoamerican archaeology, this study concerns me because of its possible implications by people who support these fringe ideas on social media. Many of the accounts that push these ideas have many more followers than I do and can thus reach a far larger audience than I. It is difficult by myself to gauge the real world impact of how these ideas are embraced and spread by others. When people argue over these ideas, it can become nasty with people making personal attacks against the other. Most of the arguments I have seen are between Native and Latino users defending their history, culture, and heritage from those wishing to take it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure about that? Look at all the massacres from [1830 to 1911](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Indian_massacres#1830.E2.80.931911). And those are just massacres, not wars, battles, or conflicts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [66 statues of Pharaonic goddess Sekhmet discovered in Luxor, Egypt](http://www.egyptindependent.com//news/66-statues-pharaonic-goddess-sekhmet-discovered-luxor)

* [Dead Sea documents reveal 2,000-year-old Jewish family tale](http://jewishnews.timesofisrael.com/dead-sea-documents-reveal-ancient-jewish-family-tale/)

* [England's 4,500 year old Grime's Graves flint mine shaft opened to public in its original archaeological condition](http://www.edp24.co.uk/news/take_a_look_inside_a_prehistoric_mine_shaft_at_grime_s_graves_which_has_been_opened_to_the_public_for_the_first_time_1_4919223)

* [Heritage bodies have major task ahead saving mosques   secular buildings as Isil retreats](http://theartnewspaper.com/news/iraqi-troops-in-push-to-recapture-old-city-of-mosul/)

* [Jihadist tunnels uncover Assyrian winged bulls in Mosul](http://artdaily.com/news/94344/Jihadist-tunnels-uncover-Assyrian-winged-bulls-in-Mosul#.WL-qFvkrLIU)

* [Exceptional grave reveals 7,000-year-old garments Stone Age man was buried in: embroidery, red deer teeth](http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/exceptional-grave-reveals-7000-year-old-garments-stone-age-man-was-buried-1610257)

* [Where did the Scythians come from?](https://phys.org/news/2017-03-scythians.html)

* [Discovering evidence of Pre-Clovis people and waiting 40 years to be proven right: the Story of Jacques Cinq-Mars](https://www.hakaimagazine.com/article-long/vilified-vindicated-story-jacques-cinq-mars) - **A must read!**

* [Advanced Radar Tech Could Save Ancient City of Angkor's Collapsing Monuments](http://www.livescience.com/58064-radar-could-save-collapsing-angkor-monuments.html)

* [2,000 Year Old Road Discovered In Israel, including coins from 29 CE](http://forward.com/fast-forward/365189/2-000-year-old-road-discovered-in-israel/)

* [Archaeologists in Alaska uncover campsite used by survivors of doomed 1813 Russian ship](http://www.foxnews.com/science/2017/03/06/archaeologists-in-alaska-uncover-campsite-used-by-survivors-doomed-russian-ship.html)

* [Skeletons Found Under a Florida Wine Shop May Be Some of Americas First Colonists - The skeletons, found in St. Augustine, Florida, likely date to the first decades of the oldest European settlement in the United States.](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/remains-early-colonists-unearthed-st-augustine-180962385/?utm_source=twitter.com utm_medium=socialmedia)

* [13.000 year old pine forest discovered in The Netherlands ](http://nltimes.nl/2017/03/06/remnants-13000-year-old-forest-found-amersfoort-jog)

* [Underground bronze treasures discovered in Chengdu, China ](http://en.people.cn/n3/2017/0306/c90000-9186476.html)

* [First Viking Tower excavated in Denmark dates from 700s CE](http://sciencenordic.com/%E2%80%9Cviking-tower%E2%80%9D-excavated-denmark)

* [770BC-256BC Tombs of noble women found in North China with bronze, jade, clay, bone burial wares and bronze musical instruments](https://archaeologynewsnetwork.blogspot.com/2017/02/tombs-of-nobel-women-found-in-north.html#RiItvBUqhTcZyXat.97)

* [Tree ring study to establish date of Thera eruption which led to collapse of Minoan civilization: A turning point for Western civilization](https://archaeologynewsnetwork.blogspot.com/2017/02/tree-ring-study-to-establish-date-of.html#KXTHy2PMyxXo1kWI.97)

* [Peat bog study reveals raw materials were being mined in Upper Silesia, Poland 12,000 years ago](http://scienceinpoland.pap.pl/en/news/news,413346,scientists-raw-materials-were-being-mined-in-upper-silesia-already-in-the-stone-age.html)

* [Oldest-known Image of Confucius Found in Tomb of Disgraced Emperor. A hand-painted mirror, decorated with a painting of the philosopher, was discovered in the tomb of short-lived ruler Liu He.](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/oldest-known-image-confucius-found-tomb-disgraced-emperor-180962358/)

* [People Began Domesticating the Amazon Rain Forest 8000 Years Ago](http://mentalfloss.com/article/92765/people-began-domesticating-amazon-rain-forest-8000-years-ago)

* [Their Hearts Were in It: One Renaissance Couple's Final Gesture](http://www.livescience.com/58082-renaissance-couple-buried-with-embalmed-heart-spouse.html)

* [Lusitania telegraph machine lost because lift bag burst during recovery mission which wasn't supervised by an archaeologist ](http://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0301/856521-telegraph-machine-lusitania/)

* [Recent study of Cambodia 550-meter stone staircase that's partly carved directly into large boulders](https://www.cambodiadaily.com/morenews/archaeologists-scale-history-of-ancient-staircase-125883/)

* [Harbour wreckage very likely HMS Tamar, report finds](http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/education-community/article/2075489/harbour-wreckage-very-likely-hong-kongs-most)

* [Mapping an archeological dig in Ecuador](https://blog.dronedeploy.com/drone-mapping-creates-digital-record-of-endangered-archaeological-sites-d298e36c90c7#.qsfbv52j5)

* [Tree scars record 700 years of natural and cultural fire history in a northern forest](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/03/170301105557.htm)

* [Fabled 'Atlantis Alloy' Recovered in Greater Numbers From Ancient Shipwreck](http://www.seeker.com/fabled-atlantis-metal-ingots-continue-to-emerge-from-the-seas-of-sicil-2290338231.html)

* [Americas first immigrants had to wait 8,000 years to be admitted ](http://www.economist.com/news/science-and-technology/21717352-checkpoint-americas-first-immigrants-had-wait-8000-years-be-admitted) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Maya practically defrosted the Yucatan to create fuel for their cooking fires and to create limestone plaster to cover their buildings. The Aztecs created an extensive chinampa system in Lake Texcoco along with a dam system to control the salinity of the water. Both of these cases does not sound like working with nature.

Don't fall into believing the noble savage myth promoted since the 1970s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more of a race and politics question, but relates to your work.

How can you prevent pseudo-scientific writers, such as Clyde Winters, from using your study to bolster their narrative for pre-Columbian trans-Atlantic contact between groups like the Olmec of Mexico and various West African groups? 

With paywalls in place for many peer-reviewed journals, the expensive cost for academic level book publications, the lack of academic level book publications in book stores, and the easy access to internet websites that feature and promote pseudo-scientific writings, it seems like more and more people are believing these fringe ideas that ancient Egyptians or West African groups sailed to the Americas to give civilization to Native Americans. Another popular fringe idea is that Native Americans were actually black/African in appearance before white Europeans enslaved them rather than importing people from Africa and/or more recent Asian migrants killed the rest and then somehow became the Native Americans we all know today.

If it sounds convoluted, it is. Yet people on social media repeatedly express their support for these beliefs at the detriment of real Native American people losing their history, culture, and identity. Despite the overwhelming genetic, linguistic, and archaeological evidence that disproves these pseudo-scientific ideas, people ignore the evidence and pick and choose studies to support their beliefs. By arguing that facial structure has a genetic component, those that believe these pseudo-scientific narratives will most likely try and use your study to revisit topics such as the appearance of the Olmec colossal heads. They can and most likely will justify their beliefs by using these heads, saying they look African in appearance even though the colossal heads are artistic expressions of people set in stone and not an actual person's head, and citing your study to back their beliefs.

This is not an easy question to answer and I understand if you don't want to try and answer it. I only ask because this is something I encounter as a graduate student in Mesoamerican archaeology. People's identity and feelings can be very much wrapped in an ethnic or racial origin and having people undermine that identity causes conflict and strife for both parties. Historically, phenotype classifications have led to a lot of awful events and not just for slavery in the U.S. We can look at a much more recent event in the Rwandan genocide in which Tutsi and Hutu were killed because of nose shape and neck shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Way more environmentally friendly

Why? It's not like Natives didn't modify their environment or even pollute it before Europeans showed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  advanced metallurgy

The alloying techniques for gold, silver, and copper by Native smiths were so great that the Spanish were routinely fooled by the metal objects they took from Natives. What they thought was gold or silver was mostly copper with the gold and silver brought to the surface to appear gold or silver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of volume, the Great Pyramid of Cholula is almost double the Great Pyramid at Giza. Cholula is estimated to have a volume of 4.45 million cubic meters while the Great Pyramid Giza has a volume of 2.5 million cubic meters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it was built over 2,000 years ago. The Aztecs, as a culture, did not emerge until 800 years or so ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The death of millions of Natives from European diseases in the decades after the Conquest of Mexico created a stockpile of sacrifice points to draw from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Aztecs would embody this idea of a poet-general. Aztec nobles were trained at the calmecac in the art of war as well as subjects such as astronomy, calendrics, rhetorics, poetry and religion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an awesome article, thanks for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an archaeology graduate student becoming involved in academia, the criticism and attacks on other researchers is all too real. I did not know the story behind Cinq-Mars and the Bluefish Caves until now, but I was familiar with Dillehay's story with Monte Verde. This kind of controversy is very real and very alive today in anthropology and not just for pre-Clovis archaeology. The attacks and criticisms of the Rising Star Cave is one such example. Another example is Phil Weigand's rediscovery of guachimontones in Jalisco, the region that I currently study. I'm not saying that we should be skeptical and even critical at times regarding evidence, but we should not be attacking someone with so much vitriol that they withdraw from academia. I'm glad to read that Cinq-Mars is getting the vindication that he deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Vilified to Vindicated: the Story of Jacques Cinq-Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did the Scythians come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So if the Aztecs were out campaigning in, say, modern day Oaxaca, the brunt of the military force would have come from the Triple Alliance proper?

According to Hassig, that is what it sounds like though he does not offer a ton of detail on the subject.

 What would 'marching separately' entail, if you know? Did they just have a different path? Were they at least led by trustworthy people, or would they have been led by their own captains? Having a tribute army lead themselves seems kind of iffy, especially if they kind of hate you as well.

Marching order began with priests bearing images or figures of the gods. They left one day before the warriors. The next day the military orders and veteran warriors with generals left from Tenochtitlan. The third day the rest of the soldiers from Tenochtitlan with the farmer-soldiers grouped according to unit. Finally, soldiers from the cities listed above would then leave one day apart from the other. Needless to say, the entire army did not march at once.

Hassig says that this was not based on ritual, but done for logistic reasons. If an army of tens of thousands began to march, the end of the column would not be able to march until hours after the head of the column left. By staggering the days in which soldiers left you could avoid the standing and waiting. Also by staggering the days it creates somewhat of a less burden on towns that had to pay tribute such as food along the way. The staggered deployment also reduces camp size and the amount of water needed for the troops.

Different routes could be taken so that multiple groups could arrive simultaneously at one destination. However, doing so leaves these units open for attack and reduces the effectiveness of gathered intelligence about the terrain, towns, and conditions ahead. If using multiple routes, if a unit was attacked en route there would be no or fewer units behind them that could reinforce the attacked unit. Using a single route allows staggered units to reinforce each other along the route should someone attack.

Hassig does not discuss who led the units during a march, but presumably it was generals or other high ranking military leaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps the sections [Historians' views of Gavin Menzies' "1421: The Year China Discovered the World"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/historians_views#wiki_historians.27_views_of_gavin_menzies.27_.221421.3A_the_year_china_discovered_the_world.22) and [Travel and contact across the Atlantic before Columbus](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_travel_and_contact_across_the_atlantic_before_columbus) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't quite answer your question, but in my attempt to find out how spicy Aztec food was I found that chiles were used to treat ["roughness of the face"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5us4ad/was_enduring_the_consumption_of_extremely/). To me this sounds like it could be acne. I would not try their curative method, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps the sections [Historians' views of Gavin Menzies' "1421: The Year China Discovered the World"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/historians_views#wiki_historians.27_views_of_gavin_menzies.27_.221421.3A_the_year_china_discovered_the_world.22) and [Travel and contact across the Atlantic before Columbus](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_travel_and_contact_across_the_atlantic_before_columbus) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modern hunter-gathers relocate to maximize foraging efficiency, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advanced Radar Tech Could Save Ancient City of Angkor's Collapsing Monuments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "ahuacatl" means "the common fruit" with a secondary definition of "testicle". The Nahuatl word most commonly used for testitcle is "atetl" which literally translates to "a rock in water". I have never seen a text that makes use of "ahuacatl" for testitcle. All other words that make use of ahuacatl as a root word are words related to the fruit (i.e. avocado tree, avocado orchard, a type of avocado, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does anyone not eat vegetables? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other states don't have [pasties](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pasty), [thimbleberry jam](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rubus_parviflorus), and four of the largest freshwater lakes in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is growing evidence that a comet impacted the ice sheets over North America

[There's also growing evidence that refutes this claim](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/12/161219115304.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/51s5yi/was_there_such_a_thing_as_aztec_death_whistles/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the exact history of domesticated cotton in the Americas isn't something I'm well versed in though.

Neither am I which is why I completely forgot about cotton. So I guess cotton and gourds are the only two crops that were present in the Old and New World </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We could forgive $1 trillion in future loans. 

Why are we forgiving future loans rather than current loans? I'm talking about current student debt. Forgiving that debt frees up a large monthly payment people do not have to pay. Anything they purchase with that money will have taxes associated with it helping the local and state governments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think spending an extra $500+ a month per person would not stimulate the economy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have the locations mixed up for maize, tomatoes, wheat, and barley.

The only common crop used between the New and Old worlds are gourds which were both independently domesticated. Gourds are great to use as vessels and water storage containers without the need to develop ceramics or make bladders from animal tissues. For the Americas, gourds seem to have been domesticated about 10,000 years ago (Smith 1997). At this time people had been living in the Americas for at least four thousand to ten thousand years. Other crops like maize and tomatoes were domesticated several thousand years later after the gourd (Coe 1994).

---

* Coe, Sophie D. America's first cuisines. University of Texas Press, 1994.

* Smith, Bruce D. "The initial domestication of Cucurbita pepo in the Americas 10,000 years ago." Science 276.5314 (1997): 932-934. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Ross Hassig's book, *Aztec warfare: Imperial expansion and political control* (1988: 54-55), he mentions that the Aztecs would marshal troops in response to the severity of the thread. For small threats and small armies, seasoned troops were usually marshalled first beginning with soldiers from Tenochtitlan, then Tetzcoco, and then Tlacopan. Should a threat be serious enough or should the Aztecs require a greater number of people, they would begin to marshall troops from cities within the Basin of Mexico and then their surrounding territories and finally the most distant territories. If the threat was of the utmost severity or they needed their maximum amount of troops the Aztecs would marshall youths and old men to aid in the fighting. 

Troops were marshalled by a high official such as a commanding general. The order for troops would work their way down the political hierarchy until it reached the calpolli level where neighborhood or barrio leaders would let those in their calpolli know of the order. 

Most soldiers were only part-time soldiers. For the most part soldiers were simply farmers who were mobilized in the fall and winter to fight larger conflicts when grain stores were full and the wet season were over. The Aztecs did have professional soldiers such as the jaguar and eagle warrior orders and could, presumably, be called to fight during the spring and summer when the commoner soldiers were busy filling, planting, sowing, and harvesting their crops.

As for how the order would go from Tenochtitlan to the territories, Hassig does not say. My guess would be that a runner would be dispatched with the order to mobilize should the need arise for non-Triple Alliance cities and settlements to provide soldiers for the war effort.

Should territorial cities and settlements need to provide soldiers, Hassig (1988: 68) briefly mentions in the marching order that subject towns were obligated to provide soldiers to the Aztecs for war once a year, presumably as part of their tribute obligations. These tribute soldiers marched separately from the Triple Alliance cities, Tepanecs, Xilotepecas, Matlatzincas, and "the rest of the cities".

I hope this answers your question. Please let me know if you have any other questions.

---

* Hassig, Ross. Aztec warfare: Imperial expansion and political control. Vol. 188. University of Oklahoma Press, 1988. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not believe there is sufficient evidence to confirm that the Aztecs could read Maya hieroglyphic writing. That is not to say because the Maya were no longer writing, but that their writing was much more restricted in the Postclassic. Rather than having texts featured on stela or monuments proclaiming the feats of a king, their genealogy, and major life events as the Maya liked to do in the Classic, by the Postclassic writing was restricted to murals within buildings, painted vessels that were often sent as gifts to other nobles, and in paper or deer skin codices. The use of the hieroglyphic system continued to the colonial period as evident in Friar Diego de Landa's writings. After his famous torching of Maya books, de Landa felt remorse years later and attempted to preserve what knowledge he could of their writing. Unfortunately with de Landa's limited understanding of other writing systems he was only able to create a list of sounds associated with some signs and did not record how words or sentences were formed. It wasn't until the 20th century that epigraphers made a breakthrough in understanding that the glyphs used in Maya writing were syllabic with parts of glyphs coming together to form words. Difficulties still lie today in understanding logograms, or glyphs made up of a unique symbol with little to no syllabic elements incorporated into their design. Without someone telling you what a logogram means or finding a text where a scribe wrote out phonetically what a logogram was, there is no real way of translating the glyph. Often these logograms are the names of people or places rather than verbs, other nouns, or other grammatical elements.

For the Aztecs, their interaction with the Maya region was largely indirect and distant. Between Central Mexico and the Maya region there were many physical, social, and political barriers to cross. That did not stop the Aztecs from conquering or controlling territory as they made their way east to the Maya region, most likely in the hopes of securing more stable and secure trade routes for goods like cacao, quetzal feathers, and other goods. Instead of using a hieroglyphic system of writing like the Maya, Zapotec, or Epi-Olmec, the Aztecs made use of pictographs in conjunction with artwork to act as mnemonic devices to recall already memorized knowledge or to create simple tributary lists from their territories. While Aztec art and writing could become very elaborate, their writing does not come close to being able to be read without outside context as Maya writing is able to be read.

But, who knows? Archaeologists are always finding new things. It is certainly possible, though unlikely, that there was someone in Central Mexico that could read Maya writing. It would be difficult to prove, even with Maya writing on murals or vessels, without other likelier explanations (such as importing a foreign artist for the murals or foreign vessels to gain prestige/power/capital).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malinche could speak a Mayan language, but there is no evidence that she could read the writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please consider posting this to /r/whatisthisthing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mayans weren't even relevant anymore by the time the Spanish arrived.

The Itza Maya managed to hold out against the Spanish until 1697 when a Spaniard used treachery to justify their conquest. The Spanish colonial government were perfectly happy to let the Itza continue to thrive as an independent indigenous state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would be nowhere without New World produce that was carefully and deliberately cultivated. Maize, potatoes, cacao, vanilla, tobacco, tomatoes, tomatillos, chiles, squash, beans, pineapple, avocado, the list goes on. Maize and potatoes provided high yield staple foods. Chiles provided a cheap way to spice food without importing more expensive spices from Asia. Tobacco provided the economic incentive for English colonists to settle the US eastern seaboard. Cacao and vanilla have provided staple flavors for desserts the world over. To say they were not influential is to express a profound ignorance of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5a0kc3/saturday_reading_and_research_october_29_2016/d9ct0rg/) over at /r/AskHistorians on Day of the Dead if you are interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Aztecs sacrificed people and animals because life itself was the greatest thing you could offer the gods. The gods created the world, created life, created maize, bring rain, ensure crops are bountiful, etc. It would be almost insulting to offer them anything less than the most precious thing you could ever own, life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Maya were always a loose collection of city-states with a shared culture and language family. No one city-state controlled an sort of empire, though they did make alliances.

When the Spanish arrived it took them a long time to pacify the area. As soon as they conquered one city-state everyone else rose up against them. If they moved on to another city-state the one they conquered rose up in rebellion. The last Maya kingdom to be conquered fell in 1697 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make pasties!

Make four batches of this [pie dough](https://smittenkitchen.com/2008/11/pie-crust-102-all-butter-really-flaky-pie-dough/) and set aside.

Cut up 5 pounds of potatoes, 2 large onions, 2 medium rutabaga, 5 medium carrots and place in a very large bowl. Add 1 pound ground pork and 1 pound ground beef. Add salt and pepper to taste. Mix that all up.

Take each dough ball and cut it into thirds. Roll the dough out very thin. I like to use a medium plate to cut the dough into a nice circle. Save the scraps for later. Using a 1 cup measuring cup, add a heaping cup of veggie and meat filling to each dough circle. Fold the dough and crimp. Repeat until all your dough balls are used up. Roll the scraps together and make a few more. 

Bake the pasties at 350 for ~ 45 minutes. If you want to eat some right away, bake for 15 minutes more. If you want to save them for later, at the 45 minute mark pull them out of the oven and let cool slightly. Then put them in freezer bags and throw them in the freezer. When you want to eat one, bake for 1 hour at 350 degrees and do not thaw them out.

If you did all this, you should have at least a dozen pasties. When I make these I usually spend about $40 between a bag of flour, the butter, meat, and veggies.

Pasties were the peasant food for copper and iron miners in Michigan's Upper Peninsula. They are now a staple regional dish. Most people eat them with ketchup, some eat them plain, and heathens eat them with gravy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way of knowing for certain. Disease was not introduced until Cortes and his men showed up at Tenochtitlan. While smallpox did kill a few million in the 1520s, it wasn't until the 1540s that the Basin saw 12 million people killed from an outbreak. I would say that if disease was somehow introduced, the Aztecs would have been weakened and may have lost territory as their subjects rebelled against them. However, if the Aztecs were hit by an outbreak so, too, would everyone else. So their more unruly subjects may have been too weak to rebel.

By the way, there was no Maya empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "WE WUZ KANGZ" is a fucking annoying and racist meme. I hate it.

And yet, if you go on Instagram and find people who post revisionist Afrocentric history, they repeatedly tell you that they were kings or even gods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the [UOregon](http://whp.uoregon.edu/dictionaries/nahuatl/index.lasso) dictionary, no words show up for squid or octopus in English or Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this post on [Tumblr](http://korracrat.tumblr.com/post/157412099965/are-you-even-native-american) a few days ago about a woman who looks white despite her mother being Native. Sometimes you roll a hard 1 in the genetic lottery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it is authentic. Featherworking was an art form that did not survive the colonial period.

As Nuevo Mundo says, the creature is either a coyote or an ahuizotl. I'm not too sure why this figure, if it is an ahuizotl, differs from other depictions of the creature.

The headdress is known as [Montezuma's headdress](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montezuma's_headdress), though it probably was not actually Moctezuma's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps the section [Technology and Civilization in the Americas](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_technology_and_civilization_in_the_americas) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Native Americans did and can grow facial hair. Moctezuma had a beard when Cortes visited him in Tenochtitlan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, the Maya and Aztec are in North America not South America.

For North America, I suggest the Florentine Codex by friar Bernardino de Sahagn. It is a lengthy tome of 12 books that cover all aspects of Aztec history, mythology, beliefs, and knowledge. You can find an English translation done by Charles E. Dibble and Arthur J. O. Anderson  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 378 pages is a long book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the works that Hassig cites,

* Clark, James Cooper, ed. Codex Mendoza: The Mexican Manuscript Known as the Collection of Mendoza and Preserved in the Bodleian Library, Oxford. Waterlow   Sons, 1938.

* Clavijero, Francisco. "The History of Mexico, 2 vols." New York: Garland (1787).

* Nuttall, Zelia. The atlatl or spear-thrower of the ancient Mexicans. Vol. 1. Peabody museum of American archaeology and ethnology, 1891.

* The Chronicle of the Anonymous Conqueror. In The Conquistadors (Patricia de Fuentes, ed. and trans.): 165-181. Norman: University of Oklahoma Press, 1963

* Sahagn, Bernardino de. "General history of the things of New Spain: Florentine Codex." Trans. Arthur JO Anderson and Charles E. Dibble. Santa Fe: School of American Research (1950).

* Durn, Diego. The Aztecs: the history of the Indies of New Spain. Orion Press, 1964.

* Del Castillo, Bernal Diaz. The true history of the conquest of New Spain. Vol. 2. Lulu. com, 1910. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct that fringes are made out of feathers. In section "Defensive Weapons" in Ross Hassig's book *Aztec Warfare* (1988: 85-88), he covers the topic of shields. While Hassig describes different construction material and methods for shields, he does not describe the fringe as anything but feathers. However, Hassig does not specify which feathers were used for the creation of a shield fringe, only that shield used feathers and the feathers offered protection by deflecting projectiles. If you look at the [feather shield](http://www.mexicolore.co.uk/images-5/543_16_2.jpg) located at the Museum fur Volkerkunde, Vienna, you can see that the feather fringe of this shield is not made with long feathers like the quetzal feather. Instead, it appears to have been made from shorter feathers. If feather shield construction is like other featherworking in Aztec culture, these feathers should have come from any number of birds and have been dyed before being attached to the shield.

I hope this clears up any confusion.

---

* Hassig, Ross. Aztec warfare: Imperial expansion and political control. Vol. 188. University of Oklahoma Press, 1988. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look on the bright side, only one of the five lakes can be detrimentally polluted without violating treaties with Canada. The other four should at least still be protected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["Learn about how Hotep and Alt- Right / white nationalists have found common ground. Most don't understand but now you will."](http://hotepnation.com/hotep-altright/)

jfc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be interested in this question on Aztec prisons that I answered on /r/AskHistorians 

https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3v7dkq/if_the_aztecs_didnt_have_prisons_where_did_they/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Began Domesticating the Amazon Rain Forest 8000 Years Ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persistent effects of pre-Columbian plant domestication on Amazonian forest composition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Began Domesticating the Amazon Rain Forest 8000 Years Ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late Pleistocene archaic human crania from Xuchang, China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late Pleistocene archaic human crania from Xuchang, China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Their Hearts Were in It: One Renaissance Couple's Final Gesture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harbour wreckage very likely HMS Tamar, report finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they did not have writing. The cooperating and competing lineages is a hypothesized political system based on archaeological data. The Teuchitlan culture lacks any palace structures or elite residences. Elite status is expressed in how elaborate their burials are and how elaborate their mortuary goods are. The way these guachimontones are constructed also hint towards a system of cooperation with sections of the temple constructed differently from every other section. Normally this might be thought of as simply work groups like at Chan Chan, but Chan Chan has clear signs of elite individuals. I recommend reading Beekman's 2008 article that covers this topic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hancock is a joke and writes nothing but fiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps these two previously answered questions will answer your inquiry.

* [Why are Native American names (Like Sitting Bull, etc) translated into english and not kept in their original language?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1l7ff0/why_are_native_american_names_like_sitting_bull/)

* [My history teacher was once told that sitting bull was actually named shitting bull, can anyone prove or disprove it?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3iqucd/my_history_teacher_was_once_told_that_sitting/cuitwwx/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps this previous question answered by /u/400-rabbits and /u/The_Alaskan will answer your inquiry.

* [How effective was Native American weaponry and armor when compared to contemporary european equipment in 1500?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5sfepz/how_effective_was_native_american_weaponry_and/)

You may also be interested in our section [Pre-Modern Non-Western Warfare](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/faq/militaryhistory/nonwesternwar) in the FAQ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tree scars record 700 years of natural and cultural fire history in a northern forest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a couple years ago the news about finding orichalcum. I didn't know it at the time what orichalcum was actually composed of. This article says that it is "an alloy made with 75 to 80 percent copper, 15 to 20 percent zinc, and small percentages of nickel, lead, and iron." And this was based on an X-ray fluorescence study. It's cool that they were able to determine its composition. Hopefully with the larger sample size they can chemically source the metal to the mines. This will most likely refute its connections to Atlantis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fabled 'Atlantis Alloy' Recovered in Greater Numbers From Ancient Shipwreck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fabled 'Atlantis Alloy' Recovered in Greater Numbers From Ancient Shipwreck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using the browser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maximum avatar size is 128x128? Seems a bit archaic, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be interested in this previous question on [Aztec gold working](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/487of5/how_did_the_aztecs_manage_to_create_beautiful/) that I answered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing! You should be able to access these articles on Researchgate.net by clicking Download. Let me know if you can't.

https://www.researchgate.net/publication/285947727_Corporate_Power_strategies_in_the_late_fromative_to_early_classic_tequila_valleys_of_central_jalisco

https://www.researchgate.net/publication/231922536_The_chronological_context_of_the_central_Jalisco_shaft_tombs

https://www.researchgate.net/publication/231753737_THE_SHAFT_TOMBS_OF_THE_ATEMAJAC_VALLEY_AND_THEIR_RELATION_TO_SETTLEMENT

https://www.researchgate.net/publication/231829736_Agricultural_pole_rituals_and_rulership_in_Late_Formative_Central_Jalisco

https://www.researchgate.net/publication/231930166_Political_Boundaries_and_Political_Structure_The_Limits_of_the_Teuchitlan_Tradition

https://www.researchgate.net/publication/225150376_Recent_Research_in_Western_Mexican_Archaeology

Here are is a fun article about an interesting find at the site of Los Guachimontones

http://s3.amazonaws.com/academia.edu.documents/30392332/article_folsom.pdf?AWSAccessKeyId=AKIAIWOWYYGZ2Y53UL3A Expires=1488392442 Signature=YEFW6YFYUaaHQ0XDPCt4gatTreQ%3D response-content-disposition=inline%3B%20filename%3DFolsom_Points_from_Los_Guachimontones_Si.pdf

If you prefer books I recommend these two,

* Townsend, Richard F. Ancient West Mexico: Art and archaeology of the unknown past. Thames and Hudson, 1998.

* Beekman, Christopher and Robert Pickering. Shaft Tombs and Figures in West Mexican Society: A Reassessment. Gilcrease Museum, 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Study of bullet damage to ancient rock reveals networks of tiny fractures hidden behind the point of impact](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/researchers-shoot-stone-blocks-study-impact-warfare-heritage-sites-180962323/)

* [Archaeologists uncover vast Roman copper mining operation in Spain](http://www.haaretz.com/archaeology/1.774629)

* [6 copper axes, pottery shards from 2,000 BC unearthed in India ](http://www.thehindu.com/news/national/copper-axes-point-to-an-ancient-culture-story/article17383808.ece)

* [Researchers at the University of Miami Survey Shipwrecks Using Helicopter-Based Technology](http://www.rsmas.miami.edu/news-events/press-releases/2016/um-researchers-survey-shipwrecks-using-helicopter-based-technology/)

* [Earliest Iron Age gold in Britain found in farmer's field: twisted metal neckbands, bracelet](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2017/02/28/iron-age-gold-found-farmers-field-earliest-ever-discovered/)

* [Ancient human footprints discovered on Welsh coastline are 7,000 years old, say researchers](http://www.walesonline.co.uk/news/wales-news/ancient-human-footprints-discovered-welsh-12667046)

* [Palaces of Ancient Persia Were Built with 'Fire Temple' Wood](http://www.livescience.com/58032-ancient-persia-palaces-fire-temple-wood.html)

* [The preservation of cultural resources is important to understanding history, Great work by US National Park Rangers](http://kxan.com/2017/02/27/archaeology-smuggler-caught-with-500-stolen-artifacts-at-big-bend/)

* [Prehistoric Aurochs Image Opens Up A New View Of Human Evolution: Researchers discover a 38,000 year old image of an aurochs engraved on a limestone slab at the rock shelter Abri Blanchard in the Dordogne region of France](http://www.npr.org/sections/13.7/2017/02/27/516981799/prehistoric-aurochs-image-opens-up-a-new-view-of-human-evolution)

* [600BC palace discovered under shrine demolished by Isil in Mosul](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/27/previously-untouched-600bc-palace-discovered-shrine-demolished/)

* [81 Anglo Saxon coffins and 200 pottery pieces unearthed in 2016 while digging fishing lake in Great Ryburgh, England](http://www.edp24.co.uk/news/how_finding_81_anglo_saxon_coffins_while_digging_fishing_lake_in_great_ryburgh_nearly_ruined_me_1_4908533)

* [Trails crisscrossed Colorado long before Europeans arrived: some passes show artifacts dating back thousands of years](http://www.gjsentinel.com/news/articles/routes-trails-crisscrossed-area-long-before-europe)

* [The First American Revolution](http://www.archaeology.org/issues/249-1703/features/5301-new-mexico-pueblo-revolt)

* [Archaeologist unearths 1846 epic story of 15 year old American girl slave who escaped to Toronto via Underground Railroad](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/steal-away-home-1.3998495)

* [Jeep buried for 40 years in sand dune unearthed](http://www.nbcboston.com/news/local/Entombed-Jeep-Stuck-in-Cape-Cod-Sand-Dune-to-be-Unearthed-414432093.html)

* [Carried to International Space Station in 2015: 13,000 year old stone spear point from Illinois](http://www.sapiens.org/blog/curiosities/clovis-point-space-station/)

* [Intriguing Burials, Artifacts Unearthed at Ancient Egyptian/Nubian Site](http://voices.nationalgeographic.com/2017/02/24/intriguing-burials-artifacts-unearthed-at-ancient-egyptiannubian-site/#.WLC469QYFRY.reddit)

* [1,000 year old toy boat discovered on Norway's coast](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/02/170224093535.htm)

* [Just Like Van Gogh: Prehistoric Artists Used Pointillist Technique](http://www.livescience.com/58007-pointillism-found-in-ancient-artwork.html)

* [Ancient sanctuary from obscure religion that competed with Christianity unearthed in Corsica](http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/ancient-sanctuary-obscure-religion-that-competed-christianity-unearthed-corsica-1608421)

* [Where were all the women in the Stone Age?](https://phys.org/news/2017-02-women-stone-age.html)

* [Second largest Maya jade found in Belize has unique historical inscription](https://phys.org/news/2017-02-largest-maya-jade-belize-unique.html)

* [Unique document about the Aztec: Census from the area of today's Mexico was made 500 years ago](http://scienceinpoland.pap.pl/en/news/news,413247,unique-document-about-the-aztecs-studied-in-poland.html)

* [Roman / Punic ruins unearthed by Farmer in Tunisia.](http://kapitalis.com/tunisie/2017/02/23/patrimoine-des-vestiges-a-kairouan-detruits-au-bulldozer/)

* [Why Did Greenland's Vikings Vanish? Newly discovered evidence is upending our understanding of how early settlers made a life on the island  and why they suddenly disappeared.](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/why-greenland-vikings-vanished-180962119/?utm_source=twitter.com utm_medium=socialmedia)

* [Temple of Artemis at Ephesus turns into swamp due to neglect](https://archaeologynewsnetwork.blogspot.com/2017/02/temple-of-artemis-at-ephesus-turns-into.html#yaTYIsT5w7qB8X2Y.97)

* [McDonald's opens restaurant-museum over ancient Roman road in Italy](http://www.thelocal.it/20170223/mcdonalds-opens-restaurant-museum-over-ancient-roman-road)

* [Beachfront Construction in North Carolina Unearths Long-Lost Ship](http://www.builderonline.com/building/beachfront-construction-unearths-long-lost-ship_o)

* [Medieval burials on Yamal peninsula in Siberia may have been ritualistic sacrifices](http://siberiantimes.com/science/casestudy/features/f0290-medieval-burials-on-yamal-peninsula-may-have-been-ritualistic-sacrifices/)

* [Skull Similarities Suggest Multiple Migrations into South America](http://popular-archaeology.com/issue/winter-2017/article/skull-similarities-suggest-multiple-migrations-into-south-america) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was more than just her emails. Stop repeating that same old line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Teuchitlan culture of Jalisco, Mexico. They were contemporaries with Teotihuacan and the Maya, yet show no interaction with either group. Instead of building pyramids, they built [guachimontones](http://i.imgur.com/d69q8K8.jpg). Instead of burying their dead in pit burials or cremations, they buried them in [shaft and chamber tombs](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-MzjguqLaFx8/Ty6ninCSTFI/AAAAAAAAHu0/xcX22tHHBhE/s1600/Shaft+tomb+diagram1.jpg). Instead of having kings, they had cooperating and competing lineages. They did so many things differently from the rest of Mesoamerica, yet there were no physical barriers separating the Tequila valleys from the Basin of Mexico where Teotihuacan is located. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably andesite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unlikely copper was used to shape the andesite blocks that make up the wall in the photo. If you read my post on /r/badhistory in the stickied comment, I summarize two articles on Inca stonemasonry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But Im not sure if copper was plentiful in the Andes or not.

Copper was very plentiful. South Americans had a thriving metallurgy practice as far back as 2155 BC for gold and 1432 BC for copper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got mine from Roy's in Houghton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is your favorite place to get Pczkis for fat Tuesday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't speak for the other great lakes, but I could imagine they're in remotely similar peril.

I think Superior is good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.popkey.co/638ba5/qr9WA.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't downvote you, dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
