<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What're you're plans?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice nice. And not much. Laying in bed wat hing the the new season of family guy on Netflix. 

Too fucked up to get on the computer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm experienced with other drugs as well though. DXM is honestly one of my favorites. It just makes my brain feel clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With DXM? 

Didn't start dabbling until a few months ago. 

The highest dose I'd ever gotten to was 300MG. 

THIS IS INSANE

So nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am fucking great right now. time is going by so slow though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ebb a flowin? eek a mowin glowin throwin samoan.

keep it goin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I just make a. Other text post for the report? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 05:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't usually throw up with gel caps. 

I feel fantastic now. 

Thanks god for voice to text. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 05:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im feeling pretty great

pretty disconnected

pretty
great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 05:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks brother! Take it easy! :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About an hour ago. Gel caps. Then I walked to mcdonalds and got a mcchicken and some HiC :p I'm feelin pretty good rn. 

That's awesome though man. I hail from the US. Live right on the coast of Lake Ontario. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty decent. Watching football with my dad. Starting to come up right now. 

Thinkin about playing a game later. Debating between Overwatch, Journey or Grow Home. 

What are you up to man?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surpassing my personal highest dose tonight. Tripping 750 MG HBr with 50 MG DPH. Anyone wanna talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 07:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Quick. The Anti Terrance Williams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some /u/TheElderSproles roastage right there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add in the fact that Coachman was in the WWE and yeah...I don't see the big deal here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was excited but that's only because I followed him in college. 

I didn't think he was going to Beas pro ready as he is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 03:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back the Kelly green.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 04:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father literally dips his bread/toast/bagels into the tub of margarine. 

It makes me hate my existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 22:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the only person in my circle of friends that liked Diary of the Dead. But I also love Grace Encounters. The sequel was mediocre, but still worth at least one watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna have to go with Cabin in the Woods. It's one of the only movies (including non horror) that just doesn't get old in my opinion. 

While I liked It Follows I didn't like it as much as Starry Eyes, The Conjuring or I Saw the Devil. 

EDIT: I also forgot about Sinister. That one is ahead of It Follows for me as well. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headlight donuts. I've only ever seen them in upstate New York.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that supposed to mean? 

Not being sarcastic or trying to sound like a dick, just genuinely curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/sexyabortions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A condom with holes in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather after his stroke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Roast of Rob Lowe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pat Tillman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't take parenting advice from someone who's kids you wouldn't wanna raise. 

Don't take diet advice from someone you wouldn't want to look like. 

Don't take financial advice from someone who's shoes you wouldn't want to be in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll try our best! Keep beating the piss out of the Bills!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a Dallas fan who holds the Patriots as his second favorite team, all I want to say is WOW! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be completely honest. I thought that Arizona was going to clobber you guys. (When you factor in the fact that Gronk, Brady and Solder were  out, you were on the road in week one and Garapollo was starting his first game)

But holy shit. You guys pulled it off. If my grandfather were still alive he'd  still be cheering (and it's almost 3am lol)

I'm very scared to see what you guys do this year, considering that Arizona is one of the favorites to win the NFC. 

Anyway, that's all. Have a nice week everybody! Until next time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Kindergarten. I was released from class within a half hour of the second plane hitting. I remember coming home and my whole family was there trying to get through to my uncle who worked at the WTC. He actually had the day off. Crazy how it all works like that. 

I remember I even had some of my neighbors over, very strange. 

The whole neighborhood stuck together after that. My dad actually had most of the neighborhood over to watch football today. 

That's definitely one of the silver linings. Unity. 

Never forget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have leftover pizza and chocolate milk. 

I'm a broke 20 year old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 00:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of games that wouldn't shock me either way, the one that would shock me the most would be Miami over Seattle. But even then, miamis D line might feast. But even then, the Legion of Boom might feast.

I'm really excited for that game tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC gaming related: First time playing Killing Floor with my two cousins when I got my first PC. Game was brutal and terrifying and fun as hell. 

Non PC gaming related: Being a kid and playing the campaign for Resistance: Fall of Man with my cousin Nick. Staying up for 24 hours straight and beating it in one sitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got the game yesterday, played for about two hours or so. I'm level 5 I think. 

The heroes I've been doing the best with are: Pharah, Genji, Roadhog, Zenyatta and Bastion. 

The ones I've been awful with are: Widowmaker, Tracer, Winston and McCree. 

Any tips for a new comer that wants to be at least average with all the heroes? 

Any tricks with any characters that the game doesn't tell you about? 

Also what are the coins for? 

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MyFantasyLeague, 10 team, keeper, snake.

1QB, 2-3 HB, 2-3 WR, 1-2 TE, 1PK, 1D/ST

QB: Brees, Bortles, Prescott, Tannehill
HB: Jamaal Charles, David Johnson, Jeremy Hill
WR: OBJ, Demaryius Thomas, Maclin, Larry Fitz, Stefon Diggs, Kevin White
TE: Coby Fleener, Martellus Bennett
PK: Justin Tucker
D/ST: Bengals

Notes: 

I kept David Johnson from last season

Took OBJ with the first pick

I have 4 QBs due to critical error, I read Bortles' bye week wrong, thought it was week 6, it isn't. It's the same week as Brees' so I took Prescott and Tannehill near the end of the draft. 

Did that fuck up my team? I feel like my team is pretty solid. But then again everyone feels that way the day after their draft.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Dusk Till Dawn. 

Had a friend tell me it was a movie about two brothers commuting heinous crimes while trying to get out of the US through Mexico. He didn't tell me a thing about the vampires. 

I loved the first 45 minutes. As soon as the vampires showed up I realized I made a huge mistake. 

It isn't terrible, but I felt like I wasted my time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 - Steve Nash

2 - Michael Jordan

3 - Lebron

4 - Kevin Garnett

5 - Shaq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 00:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet we could drown a toddler in your panties right now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone hates you because of stuff that happened before you were born.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhydon. Always Rhydon. 

Close second and third would be Nidoking and Vileplume.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 12:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For someone that has Grow Home in their backlog and played it once, is it worth another go? It was extremely confusing the first time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 09:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree with all of your points except for one. 

What didn't you like about Revelations 2? Rev 2 was my favorite RE game since RE4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excluding my team:

Knicks
Thunder
Wolves
Pacers
Warriors

Honorable mentions to the Hawks and Hornets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last New: Fleischman's.

Next: Tangeuray

Current: Fleischman's

Fleischman's isn't bad, bought a bottle of it tonight using it in a Tom Collin's right now and I enjoy the aftertaste. Tang is my favorite by far and I haven't had it since June so that's definitely next.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witcher 3. I watch my friends play it, and it looks awesome, I watch people on YouTube play it and it looks awesome, I read about how awesome it is on here and when I played it (mind you I've tried 3 times since it came out) it just seems bland. 

I don't find Geralt interesting in the slightest. Every other character was just an asshole, and all of the quests that people were telling me were so fun and interesting were just fetch quests. 

I mean shit the witcher sense just turns the game into a scavenger hunt, and to me it's not fun at all. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN NEIN!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 19:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw :( please don't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I normally do (and have done with DkS1,2 and BB) is play trough the game and beat it once without the DLC, then when the DLC drops I create a completely new character and play through the game and DLC with the new character AND the original character. That way I can experience the DLC with two different builds. That's just me personally though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 03:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be the next Solaire!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 03:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for the kind words. Take care yourself. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH GOD

Thank you! 

\ [T]/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barry Church was ranked as the 19th best DB last year. I don't see why you would want him to be a cap casualty personally. 

Who would we be able to get to replace him? Idk if there are any free agents tha would be as productive as him. 

He's also respected greatly by the defense, and is one of the leaders of the group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this community :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WWE pay per view :p and no I'm on PS4 :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, I'm stuck on Aldrich at the moment. I'm definitely down to coop though! I'll be on after SummerSlam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a blast! I'm only level 70 though :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Mine is Kuwait_Grips!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4 Kuwait_Grips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never go hollow, not while I have her to fight for. She's my Fair Lady. 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do once I get home! I'm Kuwait_Grips!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way ahead of ya! I actually finished NG+2 of Bloodborne with my friend a few weeks ago, it prompted us to buy and play DkS3 together! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 22:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE ENB. I actually went through DkS1 again while he was uploading his from the dark series. 

I haven't watched much of AGS, I'll have to check him out.

The Kayplays sounds fun to watch! It'll be like living out DkS1 again!

I like VaatiVidya a lot, I recently just started watching TheDemodcracy(sp?) and I enjoy his community rank videos and personal opinions on bosses. 

OnlyAfro is a guilty pleasure of mine too, even though some of his videos are hit or miss.

Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Sword users are GIVEN cancer. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! \[T]/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean I don't have to quit smoking? :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! She was finally given access to her cell phone so we have been able to talk for the first time since July 2nd! It'll be tough not being there for her but the best I can do for the two of us is not crumble under the pressure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! It's been an uphill battle, but I've been finding solace in the little things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mortal Kombat 5? Is that Deadly Alliance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if he did it with the scrubs in Columbus it would've been more impressive ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DBs? You mean DB Cooper right? 

Same thing really ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one my dad and I talk about all the time is what if we drafted Moss instead of Ellis? 

I was still young when that draft happened so I don't have much to add other than looking at stats. My dad says it could've revived our dynasty. 

What do you guys think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Pinwheel vs. Prowling Magus and Congregation

PM and C

Round 2: Pontiff Sulyvahn vs. Raime, the Fume Knight

Sulyvahn

Round 3: Velstadt, the Royal Aegis vs. Executioner Smough (If Smough gets 8/10 stomped or more, give him an Ornstein.)

I think without Ornstein Velstadt takes it 8/10, with Ornstein it's Pikachu and Snorlax 6/10

Round 4: Champion Gundyr vs. Knight Artorias (If Gundyr gets 8/10 stomped or more, give him an Iudex Gundyr.)

Even with Iudex I think Artorias stomps. 


Round 5: Darklurker vs. Dark Sun Gwyndolin

Gwndolin was one of the most difficult bosses in the game for me personally. So him. 

Round 6: Three Ruin Sentinels vs. Dragonslayer Armour (If the Ruin Sentinels get 8/10 stomped or more, give them a fourth Ruin Sentinel.)

Gotta go with Dragonslauer Armour

Round 7: Aldrich, Devourer of Gods vs. Gwyn, Lord of Sunlight (If Aldrich gets 8/10 stomped or more, give him a Gwyndolin.)

In their primes? I guess Gwyn either way. 

Round 8: Burnt Ivory King vs. Vordt, of the Boreal Valley (If Vordt gets 8/10 stomped or more, give him another Vordt.)

Ivory King, both ways. 

Round 9: Twin Princes vs. Afflicted Graverobber, Ancient Soldier Varg and Old Explorer Cerah

Twin princes. 

Round 10: Sir Alonne vs. Champion Gundyr

Gundyr

Round 11: Ornstein and Smough vs. Throne Defender and Watcher (If O S get 8/10 stomped or more, give them another Ornstein.)

Again. In their primes I'm going with O S

Round 12: Crystal Sage vs. Moonlight Butterfly

Crystal Sage

Round 13: Iron Golem vs. Dragonslayer Armour

Armour

Round 14: On-foot Nameless King vs. Raime, the Fume Knight (If Nameless King gets 8/10 stomped or more, give him his Dragon.)

Nameless King, by God. 

Round 15: King Vendrick vs. Manus, Father of the Abyss

Manus. 

Round 16: Gwyn, Lord of Sunlight vs. King Vendrick

Gwyn

Round 17: Dancer of the Boreal Valley vs. Knight Artorias (If Dancer gets 8/10 stomped or more, give her a Vordt.)

Artorias either way. 

Round 18: Gwyn, Lord of Sunlight vs. King Vendrick vs. Soul of Cinder

Gwyn, again. 

Personally I feel like the most powerful characters are out of Dark Souls 1 with Gwyn, Artorias and Manus. DkS1 is very top heavy. 

If you go by game difficulty it's a different story. But a lot of people would go by the game they played first I think. 

Nice post! I love From Software games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Staubach. Without a doubt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 06:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see The Sentry get his own movie. 

And even though Silver Surfer was in Fantastic Four 2, I'd like him to get his own movie as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I don't like the Eagles at all but I forgot how great they were with McNabb at the helm. 

As much as I hate to say it at least one of those teams should've won a ring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys made my Grampa happy by getting rid of Chip Kelly. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad has chronic diverticulitis. It's awful. Usually he's bedridden for a week. Hopefully Bruce gets better soon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 11:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy. Gin is my absolute favorite. 

Try a Tom Collins. 

One part Lemon juice, 2 part Gin, 2 part tonic, 1 part simple syrup (I personally put in a teaspoon of sugar and stir). 

Then work your way down to gin and juice (whether it cranberry or orange or even pineapple. Grapefruit juice is good as well) 

Then gin and tonics. 

The problem a lot of people have with gin in my experience is the aftertaste, but when you have the gin aftertaste along with the aftertaste of a fruit juice it evens out to make a nice smooth flavor. 

I may or may not be intoxicated ATM so I apologize. 

Tanguerey all the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 11:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Granted there are a lot of recommendations, but personally I didn't start liking whiskey until I had Crown Royal. Jack is good but I always get "Jack Face" from it due to the aftertaste. Whiskey is one of my go-tos. My personal rankings best to worst. (No flavored whiskey mind you) : 

Crown Royal
Johnny Walker
Jack Daniels
Black Velvet
McGillicuddys
Evan Williams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's the first one I thought of when I read the title. 

She's got a good enough heart to let you leave Ariamis even after you decimate the inhabitants there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliens: Colonial Marines. 

It was supposed to be THE Alien game. There were gonna be squad mechanics, RNG factors and different classes. You were gonna be able to explore Hadley's Hope and be a Xeno killing badass. 

Then the game actually came out and it was a watered down Call of Duty with Aliens thrown in (with some of the worst AI I've ever seen personally). 

Extremely disappointing. The worst was that my dad bought it for the two of us to play together and we played for about an hour and gave up. 

I ended up beating it with one of my friends and that was the only fun I had really. 

The multiplayer was fun but it didn't last long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! Thank you though. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP][PS4][SL43][+4] Dancer of Boreal Valley (dancerhelp1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 06:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to solo her all night and have been struggling to finish her off. Would love any help at all! :D

Password - dancerhelp1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend suffers from anorexia and bulimia and is currently in an inpatient treatment facility about 700 miles away. 

I'm waiting for her to come home. She's been gone since the last week of June (she actually left the day before my birthday). 

We've been writing each other about once a week as she's not allowed to use Facebook or her phone. 

I miss her. So god damn much. I just can't wait to wake up next to her again. 

:(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would the Yankees Quadruplets have been as successful if they all played for separate teams? 

What if Cano stayed in New York?

What if Gehrig never had ALS?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Four Kings, solo, Dark Souls 1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the guy you replied to but to me it's mostly to just add a little extra to oral sex. And she likes it, so it's a win win. 

Has to be fresh out the shower though..usually.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen Brit Floyd, The Machine and Crazy Diamond. 

Of the three I'd say that the best show put on was Brit Floyd, but I feel like The Machine sounded more authentic than the other two. 

If I was going to see one of the three again though it would definitely be Brit Floyd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 06:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My top three are Melo, Kyrie and Chris Paul all on quick. I also hear that Durant and Curry are really good. I've been dabbling into Westbrook recently and I really enjoy his.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we were already roasted :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 20:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that why my mom abandoned me? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 11:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm being completely honest I don't like Steph because I'm jealous that he isn't on the Clippers. 

He's the perfect underdog story. People passed on him in the draft and said he'd never make it in the NBA, ends up winning back to back MVPs (one of them the first ever undisputed MVP) and brings a title to Golden State. 

Another reason I don't like him is because I'd been trying to get friends and family into basketball for years and they were never into it, now all of a sudden they're all Warriors fans and claim Steph to be the GOAT. 

It's funny because since the Warriors lost in the finals those same people are saying he's overrated. Smh. 

TLDR : I don't like him because he's good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 03:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texans fans hate Cowboys fans.....I'm sort of indifferent to the Texans myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 09:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What teams in the east do you think he'd fit the best on? I was thinking the Pacers and Knicks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 08:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, snail down. The BEST show on television.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nathan For You, The Eric Andre Show and Check It Out! are some of the best shows on television right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up baby dick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tracy Mcgrady or Melo? 

Blake Griffin or Draymond Green?

Nash or Curry?

Shaq or Kobe? 

Kevin Mchale or Kevin Garnett?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack from Mass Effect 

The main Super Predator from the movie Predators (if there is a main one) 

Bender from Futurama

General Grievous from Star Wars

The Iron Giant from The Iron Giant (does that count? If not give me Master Chief I guess) 

This just seems like the most fun lineup IMO 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 19:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. I thought it was within the context of the show rather than extrapolating. My bad! But I guess you can say that Hot Pie is one of the few characters that could be immensely happy. 

NINJA EDIT: should've read the description better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 11:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue Bronn, the jailer that Tyrion gave the gold to after his trial in the Vale, and Hot Pie. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
