<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright I read the Ivern is a clunky champ post and I might have the build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before you judge the build i finally tested it and it wasn't bad at all.


So here it is:


Runes:
Movement Speed Quints, Hybrid Pen Marks, Scaling Health Yellows, Scaling Ability Power Blues (or you can do flat ap or mr, up to you).


Masteries:
Fury, Double Edged Sword, Natural Talent, Bounty Hinter, Piercing Thoughts, Fervor of Battle, Savagery, Assassin, Merciless, Dangerous Game.


Build:
Core- Bloodrazor(red), Nashors Tooth, Frozen Mallet, Berserker Greaves.
Optional- Maw, Blood Thirster, Deadmans, Zzrot, GA, Banshees, Duskblade, Ludens Echo, Hextech Gunblade, GLP (Honestly up to you guys after core but i recommend at least 1 tank item.)


Max bushes first and then shield. Bushes give on hit damage scaling with ap and +10 base magic damage per level. I got ahead pretty fast and was doling out tons of damage to squishies, and even against a Nasus :D.


Anywho try it out yourselves and see if you like it :D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna try ap/as ivern though. The bushes give bonus ap damage to auto attacks i think? if you build him like razor beak + nashors go movement speed quints, magic pen marks, ap blues and scaling health yellows, liandris + defensive items maybe like a deadmans and zzrot he might be okay. Bush's for his auto's and q for gap closing. I haven't tried it yet but maybe someone wants to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 16:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kid sucks at acting. Not trying to be mean but he really took me out of the episode when he had a close up or did anything. He used to be pretty good. Probably just stopped caring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. And no one is home when it happens sometimes too. Nothing that tilts me more than having 1k+ ms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 01:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i think the P B's was what contributed the most to their defeats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thank you. I theorizes that a person getting hit with the nado after using ult would catch them in the ult as well but wasn't sure. Kinda sad i didn't discover this :(. But glad i now know :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Yasuo Mechanic (at least I think) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i got to play Yasuo for the first time in a while. I had my tornado up and our alistar knocked up an enemy. I threw my tornado at the same time i ulted off his knock up (my intention was to layer the cc because i threw it at the person already knocked up.) Anyways i blinked to the target and rather than the tornado being thrown from the 1st position it was thrown from where i blinked. I don't have video to replicate it though. I thought I knew everything about Yasuo's mechanics but this is new to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you're just retarded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You miss my point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta take what people say on the internet with a grain of salt. No one is not guilty of talking shit on the internet because of the anonymity. Just look at Sneaky, someone calls him a fat nerd or says he's a lesbian and he's like, hell yeah sneakyGasm. Love that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 03:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A user is already working on it but if he changes his mind or doesn't feel up to it i'll make sure to contact you :D. Thank you for your response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 03:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A user is already working on it but if he changes his mind or doesn't feel up to it i'll make sure to contact you :D. Thank you for your response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the new one? I liked the old one better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else getting crazy lag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too man, me too. I've promoted and demoted so many times its dumb. Plat is a struggle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool story man. I've never been to any type of LoL event but i think it would be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you riot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bless your ignorant no common sense heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it all. That is reddit in a nut shell. gj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sign me up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlecruiser Aurelian Sol, his ult would be a Yamato Cannon and orbs would be wraiths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats man. Ill just keep grinding too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're being a fuck face imma int you idgaf. What you gonna do about it? You wanna act like a little shit you can lose like one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck in the Godzilla Sneaky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ??? It didn't help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/4zonnh/yasuo_has_seen_a_huge_surge_in_winrate_almost_58/?st=ISNBHBJD sh=3d58b3f7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 16:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same man. Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yasuo's Last Breathe :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nevertheless that was pretty epic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny i was just contemplating if i should play some teeto lel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What bug? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you dude. That'll show that nocturne trying to clean you up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. Needless to say it has tilted me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, i guess you're right :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
