<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7026</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 07:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get the tour guide guy that drinks from a flask?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sold my soul to the devil for those two lentils and now they are gone. Now I'm back to sucking the nutrients out of soggy cigarette butts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience is that raccoons are better at taking my goodies than sharing. One time a raccoon stole my bounty of 2 lentils, thus ending our friendship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least your raccoon is alive you fat cat!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a load of this fat cat with a fancy ditch!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extravagance of it sickens me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, a lot of people seemed to be put off by her statements about the writing of Eileen. Check this out if you haven't seen it. A short interview where she clarifies what she meant (last question).. 

http://youtu.be/tBEGOyNBNF4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read Eileen but I got excited for this collection after reading one of her stories in the New Yorker. Lots of weird people doing weird stuff in her stories.. How do you guys feel about her? 

Edit: title is "homesick for another world" don't know where I got stranger from.. My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ottessa Moshfegh's new short story collection "Stranger from Another World" out today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, how long does this guy take to get home!? I have work in the morning!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day six and I'm twitching at a bar I want one so bad. Fuck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite book is still Johnny Cash's autobiography Cash by Johnny Cash..  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading the last few of your posts I think you should strongly consider seeing a therapist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banana in the tailpipe!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, you're always a great help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't look like bed bugs to me. The remains they leave are typically like black dots. And usually not out in the open. Not an expert though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of my climb ups not powdered? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them have the talc powder in them but it seems that like three of twelve don't have any powder whatsoever. Should I put cimexa in them or go out and buy talc powder? 

Edit: I got talc baby powder (not cornstarch) at the store and poured it all over my finger and applied it that way, as the store didn't have cotton balls and I couldn't really tell if tissue paper was applying it well. Also put a small puff of cimexa in for good measure. Do you guys think this is ok? Just got a new mattress and frame and don't want to fuck this up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How worried should I be about ceiling droppers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they really do this that often? I got my bed pretty bed bug proof with a new mattress, new mattress case, the traps on all the legs, new bed frame, and there is literally nothing in my room except the bed and a cimexa drenched dresser.. But I'm worried about stragglers climbing the walls and ceiling and dropping down like a god damn freak show horror movie. Do they really use this tactic often to get to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
