<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6782</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 09:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah bit more "South-East" than me haha. Any plans for the car?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 06:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2010-2012 stock facelift WRX rims, wrapped in 235/45/17 tyres. 

http://preview.netcarshow.com/Subaru-Impreza_WRX-2011-800-1f.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 06:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bloody well hate it, it literally rained for some 10 seconds yesterday, the exact moment I drove out of my garage. I just gave it a full wax a few days ago too. Sigh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 06:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, can't drive a turbo here on Ps anyway (bar a few automatics/CVT) so stuck regardless. Thanks though :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 05:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm South East as well, 3165 :) What type of Lib did you get?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 03:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, 2.5 N/A.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 03:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wet mud + sun would be heaven, so fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 03:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am, you probably have seen me driving around and at various car meets too. What part of Melb are you in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 03:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll gladly trade some of the rain we've been having here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't the sun be out more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 15:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 02:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always loved the [OZ Ultraleggera](http://image.superstreetonline.com/f/features/9332848/0708epcp_07_z+2007_volkswagen_gti+oz_ultraleggera.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 00:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well done, I love hearing this sort of stuff. Really nice take on both Nangs and Disciples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, didn't even see this reply until now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 04:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic, well done! I wish I could do something this good myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 08:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find Gumtree fine, you will get heaps of low-ballers but I've personally never come across any 'scammy' looking people. I've recently sold a few things within the range of $100 and bought something for nearly 1k and every person I've come across has been genuine and fine to deal with. That said, I detail my ads as much as possible so the buyer knows exactly what to expect, plus I include heaps of photos and try to reply ASAP. The same cannot be said for the ads I am interested in. It's usually easy enough to tell if someones genuine simply by their manner of communicating. Use common sense and you will be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 05:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 16GB of RAM and mine stutters horribly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit, lucky you posted that then! Funny how these things start with such simple beginnings. My pics were at the place where we stopped during the last cruise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 17:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeees haha, it is! Surprised that you stumbled across this, I think I came across your car in Auto Detailing the other day too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 10:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty neat road up but there's always heaps of cyclists, super slow traffic and tourists so it kind of ruins it. That said, the view from up there is great, shame it was almost sundown though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It's just below Arthur's Seat: https://www.google.com.au/maps/@-38.354117,144.947282,3a,75y,338.3h,91.44t/data=!3m6!1e1!3m4!1s8AwuM8V5CV6hSUQk3HaJbg!2e0!7i13312!8i6656 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally a sunny day in Melbourne, so I took the opportunity for a quick wash and drive! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 09:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck peeps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any quantifiable evidence to show that shorter suspension leads to better handling in game? Does this "better handling" lead to the car actually being faster around corners or bumps? Does it also affect the spring rates?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not right at the moment since the place is still easily controllable by the two of us, but we may need some more later on. We'll definitely be sure to make it known when we do need applicants. Additionally, we still need to sort out how we'd select people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has any testing actually been done to see if it makes a difference? I usually just buy what looks good because honestly I have never noticed any performance impact. Maybe there's some minute difference like off-road tyres where they're better over curbs or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose I don't really have *a* 'favourite' as such but my most driven vehicle would be the Comet. The only reason I drive it so much is because it's ridiculously fun and IIRC the only rear engined sports car in the game. It also sounds pretty decent and not everyone online tends to have one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with what you think it was intended for. The vehicle is made for the offroad paths but not really the rock-crawling aim that most people thought it was for. That said, I tend to use my normal (non-armoured) Kuruma or Sultan for these types of paths. The ground clearance doesn't really come in too handy for the intention and only really aids during the "rock crawling" type off roading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me wonder why content keeps coming yet the game performance keeps dropping. I've always had this theory that some of the "DLC" is just either unfinished or previously finished things that they've had lying around that they keep releasing to make people think they're still working on the game. I.e. they only ever released 75% of the game but they've always had some 90~ complete.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  most of them are design decisions, not things that don't work as intended

You're right I think. So unfortunate that they chose this route. I would even go as far as arguing that the game performance hit may have been chosen as a method to stop the cheating online, but they didn't realise how much of a performance hit there would be. Of course this is just speculation, but knowing R* I wouldn't be surprised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recorded and uploaded, with music cut off. 

http://youtu.be/2IJyvLkLAHY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's starting right now! 

I'll try and record with Audacity and leave it running.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening in now, hope there's some interesting conversation. Thanks for the heads up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I agree with R* is dedicated to their game, their actions seem like sometimes they're very clumsy making it seem otherwise. Considering the changes they have made up to date, it looks like they are continuously adding more content but ignoring support for the foundations of the game itself (eg. matchmaking, performance issues, game launch issues). What it indicates (in my opinion) is that while they do care, they just seem to be bandaging all the issues and expecting their code to be a workaround rather than finding the source of the issues and fixing that instead. 

It almost feels like R* is a few different companies all working in different directions, and that they are not focussed in fixing the game but rather adding content and expecting people to be satisfied with it. After all, the game only broke after adding new content, it was otherwise fine. I wonder how this will all work in the long term, especially when R* decides to end support for the game. On top of this, what does this imply about the long term playability of online? Will the game keep breaking as more updates are released?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully the new sub will prevent any clearly manipulated posts from slipping through the cracks since it will be run by impartial moderators. We'll try our best! 

Cheers!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding the current state of GTA's PC performance: Is it realistic to ever expect the game to run as intended? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Regarding the current state of GTA's PC performance:  Is it realistic to ever expect the game to run as intended?** 

As many of you may be aware, the latest IGG patches have demolished some player's PC performances. Personally I have experienced the PS3 version of the game running very poorly too, to a point where simply driving a car at full speed will make the game not render any objects or the map itself. In the long term with new content being constantly added, will there ever be a point in time where the game will run smoothly on all platforms? It seems like it isn't in R*'s interest as they have already received money for the game. Have there been any other games that have had similar issues? How have they been handled?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's do this. Finally we'll have a place for no garbage posts. You can create the sub and mod me? Or should I do so?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted a GTAV discussion only subreddit without all the garbage gifs and pictures. I seriously feel like creating it myself so people won't need to filter through all the rubbish gifs to get to the 0-point discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apoc Dreams by a very long way. Preferably with the live ending too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more black now! Cheers :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe some day, but now even at stock height getting up my driveway is difficult!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New shoes on the Lib! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 08:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot is filled, first in has the place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Pacific Standard Setups   Heist - Hard - 40/20 Split (Right Now!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Place has been filled
**
Looking for 1 player on PC right now for the Pac Standard (all setups + final heist). Will pay 20% of the final cut to those who join. Please add us on RSC and send a message there if you would like to join. We would like to finish this as soon as possible and we have plenty of experience. Our R*SC names: timoloney   ThickishTunic15

It is expected that you have all relevant heist gear (Heavy Vest + Helmet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 10:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS3 controller, your method does work, I just prefer having it on the HUD all the time like GTA 4 if that makes sense!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 10:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol you're right!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
