<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5839</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im gonna try hellfire now. But someone Said in the thread that spell mechanics ARE very byggde there compared to wargate. And spell mexhanics ARE pretty important if I wanna pvp.

Is it true ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> should I join Hellfire or wargate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been very interested into playing some "tbc" and these two servers seem to be the most popular at the moment, looking at this subreddit (except warmane's Outland who's going beta testing tomorrow?).

which one is recommended for someone who's into pvp?
All I've seen in this subreddit is 50/50 where some people say wargate is scumbags, and some people say hellfire is scumbags.
all I want is high pop server with pvp oriented people and alot of activity.

which one? :) thank you :D 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do have to say that "project-ascension" is a VERY promising pvp oriented vanilla server BUT with a twist.
The twist is that YOU make your own class.. You have the ability to mix spells from every class in the game and make your unique character.
There Will be THREE different servers from soft-core to hardcore server. In hardcore server it is FFS (free for all) Where everyone can kill You. This forces you to join groups, guilds etc to survive.
Other than that, the server is pretty blizzlike where You raid, bgs, arena and stuff.

It is still in beta but I do have to say that this is the most fun I've had in any private server for sure! I've been playing all night this saturday instead of actually Going out with friends. You should definitely try it out dude. Its soo much fun. 


This video is helpful: 
https://youtu.be/3_D7D-a1omI  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I'm about to test blackrock. Is there anything that people hate about that server? is there somekind of p2w? because I can't find such thing. the only thing I can find is that people are complaining about how hard it is to gear up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
