<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject573</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, marketing is pure shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do you think the stated goals of empowering latinos and helping them not to be left behind are bad?

I missed the stated goals. Where are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bob never claimed as such.

https://twitter.com/wikileaks/status/757277230250745856 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Vox article. They did not even know the date Hillary ordered her emails to be deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was any part of the 2012 platform implemented? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did the reddit community alter comments without notice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you need karma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You edited more today?

Fuck /u/spez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump was the default, largely due to the the Democrats.

The dnc worked with the media to pack the government with donors. The people found out and did something. Unfortunately, the Dems had already doubled rigged the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary was not progress. Have you read the emails? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X will get you banned from TV, just for saying that, probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Park already did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell the school what happened (regarding having to use a food bank).

Also, take your story to the Daily Californian and the more mainstream press.

What the school did to you is not right and everyone needs to know what it is doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, just a bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Trump before the election, emails are the evidence of rigging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primary vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A national voter ID would be unconstitutional.

You should not even need to register to vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 00:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have bigger problems. My primary vote not meaning anything seems pretty important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump ran unopposed and Clinton had already secured sufficient delegates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been reading this thread?

My first comment discussed this.

The rigging of the election was widely claimed and reported.

No one in a position to dispute it, disputes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't 'random'. CNN broadcast his claims on Sunday night before the election, without disputing them.

Trump now wants to stop investigating Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the attached memo: https://wikileaks.org/podesta-emails/emailid/1120

Trump was part of a 'Pied Piper' dnc/Clinton/et al.  strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should argue detrimental reliance.

The school promised something that you relied on, then they took it away.

If the school had acted properly, you would have acted differently to secure your education.

UCB is at fault and should rescind the bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been reading the DNC and Podesta emails for the last six months?

The rigging was widely reported and Trump was claiming it, completely undisputed by every network, on the eve of the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work on the primaries first.

My California vote *did not matter*.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DWS: "Correction, I usurped her." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 09:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are black holes now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They vaporize it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the professionals. There is no proof Russia is the source of the email I linked to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither article mentions WikiLeaks.

The CNN video ran "Obama: It is in our interest to work with Russia" at the bottom... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Hillary proved she was crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their?

What is the relevance of these videos?

If you continue this conversation with non-sequitors, it will be over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a TV. I just tuned to CBS' radio station and I don't hear Obama.

Do you have a link to a recording?

If you were actually involved in intelligence, you would not be here, engaging in these discussions (at least, if you were on our side).

Ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then head straight to hillaryclinton.com . The YouTube video I made is almost entirely me playing the video that is on her front page (Tim Kaine said that you'd find Hillary's "plan" [or something] there).

I have not read every email. I have spent hours (5-10+ probably) searching through the DNC, Podesta, AKP, and possibly other archives. I have reported on many of my findings.


And then you posted a link to a damn youtube video.

So, you haven't watched it.


 Goddamnit, this is why we ended up with Trump as President- we're in a post-fact world.

Yep. With Hillary we likely would have been "factless". At least we are picking up the pieces now.

 The truth doesn't matter- all that matter is how someone else interpreted the truth for you.

The truth might be the only thing of matter.


No, I'm not going to watch your damn youtube video.

Yep.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why Rogers wouldn't have said that if it were the case.

Russia has probably gotten material off machines in the US that someone didn't want them to. Wikileaks has seemingly published many leaks and the statement you linked to was just not specific at all.

I am sorry they did not issue a specific statement on one specific email you are referencing. I am sure you know more than our intelligence operations. You should point that out to them, they could use your assistance.

Already on it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There were more than two leaked questions.](https://wikileaks.org/podesta-emails/emailid/57027)

Have you read any of the emails? The DNC and many other organizations colluded to manipulate the American public into voting for Hillary (who would have stuffed the government with her donors).

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LTjTJHAmTl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That statement does not say, nor does it give any actual evidence, that Russia was involved in leaking the email I linked to.

Further, the Director of National Intelligence, whose office put out that joint memo, has just resigned. He also lied under oath to Congress a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know that every time he accused Hillary of something, it was because he, himself, was guilty of that very thing.

I don't think we know that. Is he under FBI investigation for spreading classified materials? I'm not aware of it.

I sure hope someone is looking into whether the election was, in fact, rigged.

There are many people looking at it.

It was "rigged". Look at who Trump works for. Look at who was pushing the Clinton campaign. Read the emails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not aware of an agency communication that says Russia was responsible for leaking that email. I don't think you can link me to such a communication, either.

Rogers' statement is entirely consistent with either a DNC or other US source. His statement says nothing about hostile entities, nor foreign entities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City halls have been notoriously corrupt. Same for nation states.

...naive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What evidence do you have that the person who leaked this email was working for a "hostile foreign entity"?

Political appointments are a symptom of corruption. They should not exist.

Do you know if Jordan Kaplan still exists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DNC National Finance Director put out a call for appointments on 4/20/2016.

Why would a finance director be involved in selecting board and commission candidates?

https://wikileaks.org/dnc-emails/emailid/20352 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the day before the election, Trump was telling people that the election was rigged and that Hillary was corrupt. He was right, and he won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was also a TV celebrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've given an explanation. Only facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that MSNBC broadcast a statement that is false. Donald Trump was not the first TV celebrity to run for president.


I'm not aware of a correction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it a problem? Or why do they seem to push many messages? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delta won't even play them on board (as of about last week).

Edit: [They also didn't show anything on board during the conventions.] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MSNBC seems to push many messages, whether the people giving the messages know it or not.

It's "well known that Reagan was an actor", yet NBC broadcast a "fact" that contradicted that, apparently uncorrected. This is a huge problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I think "sucked" is just an opinion. I'm trying to state only facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read Wikipedia's article on Reagan?

 Television
Though an early critic of television, Reagan landed fewer film roles in the late 1950s and decided to join the medium.[26] He was hired as the host of General Electric Theater, a series of weekly dramas that became very popular.[26] His contract required him to tour GE plants sixteen weeks out of the year, often demanding of him fourteen speeches per day.[26] He earned approximately $125,000 per year (about $1.07 million in 2010 dollars) in this role. The show ran for ten seasons from 1953 to 1962 and, as a result it increased Reagan's profile in American households,[49] especially as he had appeared in feature films mostly in supporting role or as a "second lead".
His final work as a professional actor was as host and performer from 1964 to 1965 on the television series Death Valley Days.[50]
Reagan and Nancy Davis appeared together on television several times, including an episode of General Electric Theater in 1958 called "A Turkey for the President."[51]

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ronald_Reagan#Television </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I say otherwise?

MSNBC broadcast that Donald Trump was/is the first TV celebrity to run for president. Ronald Reagan was a TV celebrity who ran for president in 1980 and 1984. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take notice that MSNBC is lying to you, or is ignorant, about him [Trump].

Edit: Added [Trump]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't an offhand comment. [Please watch the context.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=23AQ1xIUR7E) This was MS/NBC's prime time election evening coverage.

[Ronald Reagan hosted a TV show in 1976, just four years before being elected president.](http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0001654/)

Donald Trump's primary show, *The Apprentice*, is produced and broadcast by NBC and its associates and affiliates.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was. His [IMDb page](http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0001654/) is shown at the end of the video.

His last billing before becoming president was as a host of an episode of *Walt Disney's Wonderful World of Color* (1976). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ronald Reagan was a TV celebrity who ran for president [MSNBC claimed Trump was the first] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very likely that it was the US. Psychological operations on the US public have been authorized.

John Kerry reportedly had Julian Assange silenced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Broadcast Anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact WikiLeaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks: Trump lost CIA drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 20:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks: Trump loses CIA drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 10:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Donald Trump has urged us to all come together as a united people.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=owuq_An4cnk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please link to your editorial strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no issue in naming a source; only in using the credentials of a source as a basis in an argument unrelated to the credentials of the source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The democrats *were* "rigging" the election. They got caught. Full stop.

WikiLeaks should publish everything it has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can we know that you have not received information on Donald Trump's campaign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The New York Times reports that American officials say there are probably no direct ties between WikiLeaks and Russian intelligence services.](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/09/01/world/europe/wikileaks-julian-assange-russia.html?smid=tw-nytimes smtyp=cur)

If something is a fact, shouldn't it be published, even if we don't have all the facts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it wouldn't.

My guess is that there is still access for others outside. They just need a view (and a device). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see live video, from multiple angles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven't been silent.

About 20 minutes ago WikiLeaks tweeted that Julian was still disconnected:

https://twitter.com/wikileaks/status/796760659987939328

Assanges internet connection has not been restored. We have the necessary contingency plans. Staff doing AMA now: reddit.com/r/IAmA/comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general. Sorry to hear that you saw those things. Is it possible for you to link to a video of one of those instances? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am capable, however my time is limited.

I expect people that make claims to back them up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should people be concerned for their safety?

Did anything actually happen yesterday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which subreddit is appropriate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Janet Reno Dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 01:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The emails are implicated in another criminal investigation. How is that nothing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI says posting was automatic and that all protocols were followed.

Please read.


Article used this source (which, frustratingly, does not link to an FBI source): http://talkingpointsmemo.com/edblog/fbi-releases-statement-on-marc-rich-docs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Factor circles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your limb broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I said or implied that *no* where. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I am one of those millions and my primary vote meant nothing.

Zero say in any parties' elections for all voters in CA. That's not an anecdote, it's over a tenth of the country's population and is also the single largest political grouping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 06:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My California primary vote was *worthless* and I ended up with a serial liar and a wannabe pussy grabber to vote for in the general election.

Please tell me more about voter apathy.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you able to find out what those 40 people were working on?

Should we be expecting a completely new product coming out of Twitter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The service isn't quite the same as when it started. Last year, the semantics of a main user action was changed, invalidating all previous "favorite"s into "like"s. The mobile application also doesn't always show a chronological feed (and even permanently removes those out-of-order messages [which Twitter determined you would be most interested in seeing] from your mobile feed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is a threaded chat platform different from a chatroom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you please give a timestamp about where RMS told you **what to do**?

I'm pretty sure he expressed at least once that people should be free to choose whatever they want. His *opinion* just seems to be "reject non-free code (unless someone has a gun to your head)". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either a bank will *create and front* the money, then sell it to others, or the company will raise the money directly from others (bonds). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the fastest way to teach new players might be to just walk into them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 00:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't you get a deadline extension because of your illness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This eco-friendly baja is made of completely recycled yarn, a super-soft blend of 50% polyester/40% acrylic/10% cotton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did notice the background could be better, but it hasn't been too distracting.

I think I've noticed some hiccups while clicking a lot, but I think the drones usually all came out in around 22ish clicks.

I think the game is mostly smooth, though there is the occasional lag/hiccup. I wish it were easier to move slow and to stop your self. I usually keep my mouse near my targets, but to stop, I have to get my mouse nearly directly on my ship and the speed change gradient is too small to be easily useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't want to have to push my mouse button 22 times to spawn my drones. I just want to hold it down for a few seconds to spawn them all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you make a library open for use and it turns out to have a security bug in it that nobody found, it stands to reason you'd want to be protected from lawsuit for it.

If that were the real concern, wouldn't the MIT license be far more standard and provide even more protection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the relevance? Isn't Trump making the argument that he's not as bad as someone who was actually president? So, his behavior shouldn't disqualify him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the contract? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some time is ok, but with the after-round time and the pre-round time, I think it is about 1.5-2 minutes of downtime between rounds....and there isn't really anything to do during that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downtime before rounds is way too long </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless I am missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The passage of time is relative to an observer. Does Unix time handle time dilation? ntp seems to only give barely good enough synchronization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the use case. This was just a trivial change to add the feature you complained about not existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 00:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) a carousel that cannot be stopped or paused. Maybe that's fixable with a hidden checkbox though. However I've never needed a carousel that 100% ignores user interaction.

http://codepen.io/anon/pen/Gjdwgd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you discussed this with Andy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course she has recourse against the bank. The bank had her falsely arrested. That is a huge violation of someone's rights.

Police do not monitor bank accounts for theft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 08:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Technical note: The simulations are not synchronized, so YSWVLV!] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [web, alpha preview] trumporb.it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 08:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enter orbit around Donald Trump's massive head: http://trumporb.it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 23:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I could rotate a large disk and levitate it by sufficiently slowing its rotation down quickly enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Students who live in the city get to vote like everyone else in the city. Why should they get a special seat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney can already stream live video, including sports, as you say. Why is an adviser involved? Why wouldn't this more likely be a case of commission-stuffing?

Every time Twitter pops up a message on my phone unrelated to a person/account I follow, we get a day closer to my writing its replacement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IS RAPE THE PRICE TO PAY FOR MIGRANT WOMEN CHASING THE AMERICAN DREAM?

fusion

Before they can reach the American Dream, many migrant women have to survive a Mexican nightmare.



The link doesn't work, so we can't read the full article, but the clickbait invokes threats of violence with nationalist language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just telling you what the documents say.

It wouldn't be hard to believe that someone posted something someone else wrote. It happens all the time in politics and business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 20:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can just look at the claims. Palmer claimed to post it and also claimed to not write it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
