<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject845</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what happens when you teach your children slave mentality. You risk losing them. It's not heroism. I'd rather teach my daughter to survive than to be a sucker helping others get ahead at the cost of her life.

Also, forcing a child to go out into the world before she's ready is not an inherently good thing. Listen to your kids. If they'd rather stay home there might be a good reason for it. When they're ready they'll go and how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cite your source. I come to reddit when I'm *not* working. You're miserable. Keep to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a blow-up doll on pof years ago. I swear to god I got a kazillion replies. Men with ... mommy issues or something along those lines. I'm not here to diagnose but that's one reason to seek out men who aren't looking for women on a web site lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bahahaha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell you what the problem is. Guys who use only online dating have no balls because they become accustomed to the virtual process of hitting on a woman, as you'd do in a video game.

Women who are worth a dime know this. So we'll go to a bar and meet someone with the balls to talk to a real live woman. We don't care if it requires beer or drunkenness--at least you can smell his fucking breath and use non virtual chemistry to take in his pheromones ;)

Be a man. If you want a woman, get offline.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where u live lol - in a real city he's average. Ugly people tend to move away. Don't ask me why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
