<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This a great video. It deserves more views and likes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I am no longer a Creationist [Evidence for Evolution] (FULL Movie 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't know of any verses that talk about the same body resurrected.

There are the gospel accounts about the empty tomb of Jesus, just for a start, though it doesn't necessarily follow that post Jesus resurrections will be different.

Here is the Catholic Encyclopedia on the subject. It's pretty detailed. 

http://www.newadvent.org/cathen/12792a.htm

In my experience, religious cults sometimes follow their scripture, but they all deviate from what the words literally say, with varying justifications. 
I don't believe in resurrection at all, so the problem doesn't arise for me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the bible link. It's never surprising when the bible contradicts itself.

You can easily find discussions online among Christians about the resurrection of the body vs the resurrection of the spirit. The Catholic Church, the largest Christian sect with 1.2 billion members says its the body.

Protestantism, the second largest group of Christians with 800 million, is mixed on the question, Eastern Orthodox with 270 millions say its the body, Oriental orthodoxy says its the body, Anglicanism is mixed (I am pretty sure I discussed it with an Anglican Vicar some years ago, though I can only find sources saying the body at the moment), the Mormons say its the body, and so on down the list.

I'll guess that you are from a Protestant background, as am I. Well, the views of churches vary on many things, but this type of resurrection is certainly a standard doctrine of worldwide Christianity. It's the more modern Christian groups who tend to have adopted a spirit-only model, as they in some ways have adapted more fully to modern scientific knowledge about atoms and chemical processes.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the 9/11 Commission report. There is a news article about it here:

http://www.nbcnews.com/id/5485376/ns/us_news-security/t/sept-panelcriticizes-dullessecurity-screeners/#.WL66etLyi70

I just find it surprising this is not widely known. No-one seems to care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But nobody is trying to blame the airport screener.. (except me..)

They were not identified in the 9/11 Commission report which detailed their failings.

I do think that the fact that if they had performed their duties correctly, that those hijackers would have been stopped and probably that plane saved, was significant. I am not sure offhand which of the targets that plane hit.

Whenever I comment about this people comment back to defend them, but I don't know why. They were not doing their jobs properly and this had the worst possible consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A standard Christian doctrine is that the dead will reanimate their dead bodies with the same atoms composing them as in life.

It's not clear how this will work with saved cannibals of saved victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah they are pushing the moral angle. 

I guess it would be even more difficult,  but warning about the Boxing Day and Japanese tsunamis would save more lives. (Enormously more if we don't count the wars following 9/11). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each one you kill would be replaced by one one grade more authoritarian.  If you want to go the other way you need to persuade everyone that they are safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not usually policy to evacuate such large buildings fir a small fire. Most likely just that floor would empty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phone the airports on the day and tell them about the hijackers and their boxcutters. 

Not many people seem to know it, but two of the hijackers at Dulles set off the metal detector,  and the TSA officer there tried wanding them to find thd source, but didn't resolve it straight away and so gave up and allowed them through. This was a direct failure to do his or her job properly.  I wonder why that person isn't known for it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't worry Neil. It was bound to happen sooner or later." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just seems to be another iteration of the Leavers telling the rest of us to suck it up and get on with it.

Cornwall may not have got what it deserves, but it has what it voted for.

I voted the other way so no, I am certainly not inclined to shut up about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   there are many good arguments against it

What are those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stalagmite

You must have been having a real piss-up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its a perk of the job then, free ammo and use of the gun in his private time? How would you feel about him using a police car in the same way (assuming its unmarked of course)

I am British, and our cops don't usually have gusn on duty, let alone off, and yet they seem ok and not particularly targeted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should he pay for his own ammo?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ehrman's Cambridge Lecture on Forged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to scale a wall quickly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a simple policy of anybody who enters the country illegally is always deported, either to the country that they last came from or to the country that they claim to come from.

There is the little matter of international law to consider there. If we just break it arbitrarily that will encourage other countries to break it arbitrarily too. We have a duty to offer asylum to people in certain circumstances. Doing so correctly is often a time-consuming business.

That international agreement exists in part because it's good for the West to protect dissidents from enemy countries. Once safe they tend to exert pressure on their regimes at home in various ways. Consider the effect all the Soviet and German dancers, artists, scientists, writers, and businessmen in the west had during the Cold War.

That said, I don't think we have our system set up optimally. I think Australia has one good policy on asylum in that they will offer asylum, but anyone entering Australia illegally is banned from settling in Australia. Other Australian polices on it are really bad though, and they have high rates of suicide among their pretty terrible refugee camps in the desert.

However, if we were to ban illegal-entrants from settling in the UK, we would have to allow some way for asylum seekers to claim it before entering, which they currently do not have. Doing that would probably encourage applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the law aside there are two main elements to a person's Britishness, which are their place of birth, and their cultural affiliation. 

Anyway Tony49UK does have some very cursory opinions. Perhaps we can encourage him to look a bit deeper?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sending up devices to space isn't just done for vanity's sake, but is useful in developing a country's economy and other things.

Just as a random example, the Indian weather satellites have predicted adverse weather events and allowed for action to be taken on the ground to save lives and property.

http://thediplomat.com/2014/10/indias-impressive-space-program/

Also by employing scientists and engineers they keep them in India, rather than having them migrate away to the West, which I imagine you would approve of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If being born in the UK doesn't make you British, what does?

Its worth noting that currently being born in the UK does not in itself make one British.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/British_nationality_law#British_citizenship_by_birth_in_the_United_Kingdom_or_a_qualified_British_Overseas_Territory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is they were following each other in a line, and scared of the cat so they kept a safe distance from it, and the lead bird saw the birds at the back of the line and started following them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think /u/smarfed knows that. Hair-apparent would have been a better way around IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who cared to could always look up the figures and see what proportion of govt income was spent on the EU. The sad truth is millions wont undertake even simple research before forming an opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/StarWars/comments/5xiyde/where_can_i_find_a_making_of_version_of_anh/deifqgd/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it. Thanks dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was making a political statement, which was his right as a European citizen.

Edit: or it should be his right - what's special about anti-religious political statements? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say that sky fairies really piss me off. I have no right to not be offended and so I just suck it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why the owner was incredulous. African Grey live for 50-60 years, so it would easily still be alive 4 years after going missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find a 'making of' version of ANH? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recall seeing a full-length cut of ANH on youtube or some video site, which was made up almost entirely of out-takes, rehearsals, test shots, commentary and interviews, and de-constructed SFX shots.

I want to recommend it to a friend, but now I can't find it again. Any ideas what I should search for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the brand of these trainers? I can't read the logo. The pic is on the ASOS site but I can't find them there, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, wind varies. That does not render it useless though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That applies to all types of generation though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BRISTOL PROTEST: Furious demonstrations hit city centre over man who stuck bacon to mosque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody recognise the brand of these trainers? I can't make out the logo. The pic is from ASOS but I can't find them on the site. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be expanding wind. It can't be a complete solution, but wind levels have predictable averages, and it's rare to have no wind over a wide area like the USA or EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for the record, I know some Romanian people who are just normal working people and art students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kenny Baker interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 11:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least its Not Poodle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment. You missed having a greater reliance on preserved foods rather than fresh. I guess this goes before losing unseasonal produce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rod Stewart must not be allowed to much about with his friends! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He likes turtles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's homo alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen a few articles about this place before. Its basically a glass and iron dome and smaller room with a tunnel leading to them, with one shaft on the shore with a spiral staircase down. It's pretty old so pre-dates current laws about emergency exits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I am saying that. However, white people have a wider variety of hair and eye colour than the other races. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cappuccino with art. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think... he could be among us, incognito... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be difficult to use it for much - it lacks escape routes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link.  It is nearly spot-on. It supports the claim that all races are better at recognising their own race than other races. I couldn't find figures specifically about the percentage recognition and whether this goes as low for recognising white people as -say- with recognising Asian people.
Anyway I shan't argue the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Political Correctness shows *some* awareness of the situation and isn't driven by daft conspiracy theories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such confidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I googled it and was sad it had gone. I still have a neat military beret and some badges from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope all this rubbish about 'SJWs' burns itself out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh. Actually it was pretty cool in 2006. It did seem remarkable compared to other online communities of the time. I still see aspects of that community today. There is much more noise now though. For the first time I find I am meeting other commenters who just can't understand what I am talking about. My comments aren't heavily technical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No its off-line too, but fortunately I live in a pretty cool spot so don't meet too many assholes in the flesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writings didn't seem to have any value. I seem to recall reading that the mother of the guy who found the Dead Sea scrolls started burning the first batch he brought home while he was out.

Then there is this:

http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/edmonton/irreplaceable-dinosaur-fossil-destroyed-at-alberta-dig-site-1.1181588 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tomorrow's World: Mobile Phone 13 September 1979 - BBC - I think this is a pre-cellular early digital dialling system which did not take off due to lack of bandwidth availability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also before we could read Egyptian hieroglyphs, lots of papyrus writings and scrolls were just burned or thrown away when found in tombs etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And as fertiliser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm. Maybe it has finally jumped the shark. I still see good in it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laurence Corner - the last of - army surplus (vid showing last days of very-long-running shop near Euston in 2010) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear. Reddit is here to make the world feel good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "This channel is racist! He is against whites!" lol

There seem to be more and more of those types of comments online lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a rule I'd say leave up your downvoted comments. The points don't actually mean anything and it helps the conversation be understood to leave them. The voting often lunges one way and then corrects itself anyway. If you are in general a good person your votes will be a net positive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that black or Asian people say that all white people look alike? It seems unlikely. I'd be interested if there is any information about that.

Confusing Jackson and Fishburne might also mean an offhand attitude to black actors,  like they aren't distinguished for their individual achievements, and are generic. or it might just mean a lack of interest in black actors compared to white actors, which could be racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you delete your comment?

I think it is perceived as racist when white people mistake one black person for another, as it seems as though they don't recognise them as individuals in the same way as with white people, or that they think 'they all look the same'.

With the Mandela thing.. I do find it a bit odd that people think Mandela died in prison. I guess it demonstrates a lack of awareness of black history to not know about his eventual release from prison and his achievement to become first black president of South Africa, and to not know that black people were deprived of the right to vote until then.

While it might not be racist as such it does seem a bit ignorant about race history and issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a joke, or did he really forget what party he is with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess courthouses have more assholes around them than typical buildings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unless, that is you have evidence that says that white people mix up black people because of the fact that they are black, and they are the only race to do so.

Does that strike you as unlikely? I don't know of any data, but white people have more physical variation in hair and eye colour than black and Asian people. Also I think lighter skin shows more texture more easily, and this could mean a tendency for white people to use those things for recognition.
Black and Asian people in their communities would need to rely on other features for recognition.

There are stories about the media mixing-up black actors in a way which doesn't seem to happen as much or as painfully as with white actors.

http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/tv-movies/samuel-jackson-laurence-fishburne-mixup-don-alike-article-1.1608899

https://mymajicdc.hellobeautiful.com/3646283/give-us-strength-white-medias-emmys-coverage-mixed-up-so-many-black-actors/

Even if it is not statistically true, it seems to be something which black people are concerned about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article from 2012 implies that some Jewish people thought the bears were Jewish:

http://www.jta.org/2012/02/29/jewish-holidays/hanukkah/sad-but-true-jan-berenstain-bears-not-jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen any other episodes with Holly? I think the ending of this one would be puzzling without that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww. Can it be true? Does He hate us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if reddit has been getting dumber all this time it must have been AMAZING in 2006. Oh wait. It was.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the Victoria Line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the cinema I have seen the originals twice each and the late-90s reworks once. No I didn't notice either of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an enjoyable documentary about Juggalos here. This story makes more sense in context:

https://vimeo.com/29589320 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she can end an 8-month pregnancy out of convenience.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's Lpless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bart's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if you were called Alan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shangri-Las -Leader Of The Pack Video with High Quality Sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have used dormice, which have a much better mass to surface area ratio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I always thought it started with one mushroom dropping spores in a ring around it, then when the mushrooms from those dropped spores the ones inside the ring wouldn't grow as the nutrients in the soil were exhausted, leading to an expanding circle.

TIL.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conversations With History: Bart Ehrman (lots of interesting material about the biblical explanations of suffering) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Interesting Point About Prophecy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, stick your face in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you notice any? I don't think I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Most Pointless Star Wars Movie Changes You Never Even Noticed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those tyres look very dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thomas Edward Lawrence was a gay white male who wrote *The Seven Pillars of Wisdom* and generally quite liked Arab Muslim culture.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/T._E._Lawrence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir John Major Slams Theresa May's 'Cheap Rhetoric' In Bruising Brexit Speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother fed her daughter tapeworms to make her skinny for pageant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I gather from photos that sometimes there is cling-film involved.](https://images.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fmedia.gettyimages.com%2Fphotos%2Fatmosphere-of-body-sushi-by-cheetahs-dancers-at-cheetahs-gentlemens-picture-id143811931%3Fk%3D6%26m%3D143811931%26s%3D594x594%26w%3D0%26h%3D0LXS2V4HolhK73dFispcFoX27B64OM_qBOH3jtwmdk0%3D f=1)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, of course it would be... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video asks people to match religions with texts to improve 'faith literacy' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a practice of serving Japanese food from naked people's bodies. I am not sure how traditional it really is, however.

http://galeria.trojmiasto.pl/org/960096_Pokaz-Body-Sushi.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctor Who anime. (reposted from 5 years ago) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't put the whole egg in your mouth. It would choke you anyway. There are slightly smaller Cadburys Creme eggs which have no toy inside which would be similarly deadly if swallowed whole. I suppose those are legal in the USA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I buy the for the toy and eat the chocolate on the path toward that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he doesn't try to reverse into the workshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Carpe Testis* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess if it broke it would hit you with a huge chunk of glass. Or, it would just crack and flood and not allow you to escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are torrents. (I see these aren't allowed as submissions, but ok in comments yeah?)

www.skytorrents.in Search for 'classic albums mvgroup' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she cleaned the buttplug between victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you reminded me. I once had a short-lived thing with a girl who was still recovering from her last relationship. She had a rule that we could have sex but neither was allowed to have an orgasm.

I found it rather wearing, of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they know the ores are precious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have a round digit anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That had the potential to turn a bit psycho... perhaps his being into you was preferable to being into dismemberment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see. Yes that's quite funny. She is staring that the balloon-knot but then her head hides it from us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it sometimes asks me for two or even three capchas in a row. Perhaps some of those are brand new ones and it slips them in when it sees a user who is accurate on previously-checked ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would i have gone about that?

I don't think you could really do that without just seeming like you know nothing about 20th century art. There is loads of that type of thing. The good stuff was around 100 years ago. That's when this idea was new and interesting. There has been a century of intellectual progress since then.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Readymades_of_Marcel_Duchamp

I guess the real key idea is that physical craft and skill ceased to be so important in the machine age. After we could make objects without manual skill, the value in object and artworks had to be in the ideas they presented, not so much in their physical forms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about art which requires craftmanship and effort, but not by the artist?

There is a lot of that around, including many of the great historic painters from the pre-modern eras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tens of thousands of the greatest minds in history have been contemplating art. Not all art on show is good. Its actually quite thrilling to realise that and be confident of a criticism which is not coming from ignorance.

/r/delusionalartists/ is goodish for bad art, though that's not quite what you are hoping for I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you must be thinking of Cher. I am pretty sure a shear is a pointed stick used as a weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's a steer. A shear is the name in geometry for a circle, but in 3d. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised to see no mention of goatse anywhere when I went to the Turner show. It wasn't even in the visitors book. I had to put it there myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is better:

http://www.tate.org.uk/art/artworks/manzoni-artists-shit-t07667 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a sculpture from the Turner Prize show in London just recently.](http://i1.mirror.co.uk/incoming/article8916489.ece/ALTERNATES/s615/Turner-Prize-Shortlist.jpg)

I think the problem here is that if this is supposed to be mocking contemporary art, then artists are waaaay ahead of the cartoonist in mocking themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-hot mothers are less likely to be voted-up I suppose. You had better hang out in the new queue for fugly mothers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are thinking of Shia. Shear means a very steep cliff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think he was bonding over your dissection skills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did he draw maps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? He called your vag sweet nectar? Could be worse if he huffed your socks at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think it's a generational thing, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Innocently playing around with them is ok. It's if the kid shows an abnormal or uncomfortable interest. The dolls in the article I saw had vaginas, buttholes, mouths, hair in the right places etc. if kids started fitting them together in sexual ways it is a way in for the investigator to ask them why they are doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will also need to go down into the ground for some distance. I'd think 1m at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lovely puppet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HISTWEE!


https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thomas_Becket#Assassination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 11:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I just find it funny that people refer to a film without acknowledging the original play with the same name, in a thread about referring to a location without acknowledging the original location with the same name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anatomically correct dolls have been used to test whether children have been sexually abused.  Basically kids will have different reactions to and interest in the sexual features if they have been exposed to sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It rather appeals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No link? Are you an animal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it shows a failing on the part of the (probably male) architect, in not planning the necessary scale of the facilities for men and women.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lido is very beachy.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lido_di_Venezia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys are talking about the Baz Lurhman film. I don't *think* they are being ironic, given the subject matter of other nearby comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 10:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh. It's a play too. Set in Verona, Italy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedens feminist foreign minister has dared to tell the truth about Saudi Arabia. What happens now concerns us all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen several kicjstarters recently that seem just to be marketing for humdrum products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a nightmare of over-complication. I bet wired earbud connectors still are being marketed in 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are they more likely to vote correctly on the bot comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh there were bits of the roof of my building on the pavement across the road this morning. I didn't think much of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ed is unfortunately not very charismatic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You silly-Billy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. I didn't get that at first, so it does supply another layer, that I was looking for. 

It's significant, I think, that [n the artist's tumblr](http://cosmicscomic.tumblr.com/post/157534152538/and-the-translation-is-im-so-sorry) he or she put "and the translation is I'm so sorry" as the punchline at the end of the comic. Whereas, the redditor posting it here 'put the fricking punchline in the title', as we used to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While its true that humour and many creative things are subjective, don't fall into the trap of thinking this means nothing can be criticised, analysed, or tuned-up in different ways. Comedy is often very technical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Oh, Hmmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it's interesting how many commenters in the thread seem upset by the way we are analysing it. Its true that explaining jokes can ruin them. However comedy writers are often analytical in their approach and jokes don't always appear fully-formed. They can be engineered from pieces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do get the reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't read it as 'the coffee-stain is their language', but rather that the little alien is worried the Tetrapod has done something bad by accident with his coffee-ring. However without knowing what the symbol means it doesn't supply any punchline that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes maybe it would work if it built-up the mysterious shapes and made them seem puzzling and important, as in the film, had the other character invested in solving it, then revealed them to be cup-rings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does need something else. If I were a comedy-writer, I'd have this in the work-in-progress pile, waiting for some other layer to occur to me. Putting the panels in a odd order would probably do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...? I am saying it needs a little more to be funny... Something with some element of humour would do it.

Edit. Actually no. It appears that *isn't* the joke. The joke is that he said sorry at the same time as creating the need to say sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I feel that only funny things are jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there is no actual joke here, except that their language can look like a cup-ring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently FAT is used in digital cameras and most memory cards. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File_Allocation_Table

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journey between land and ocean - beautiful footage shot along Iceland's Ring Road 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can be true but I'd say be careful not to generalise too much. Addiction is a complicated thing, and though addicts can be bloody annoying, they aren't always in control of themselves, by definition.

On the other hand, some do take steps out of addiction on their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Is there an Echo in here?" 24 views. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What levels?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poke it with your loofah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you sabotage foundations in such a way that they pass inspection during the construction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   if you assume you have no agency, and wait for others to 'do something', nothing will change. 

That's true but I am doubtful that any addicts wait for others to sort them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You find angrier articles that way.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a cardboard panel on my pc for a while. On balance I think it was an unacceptable fire risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was real horrorshow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be good to state what his MEP salary has been.

I'd cut the parts about the death penalty and anti Muslim activities, as many of his casual supporters would approve of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammaring would be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were there any known incidents of Japanese Americans acting as spies or other anti American activities?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New guy in my office keeps Hi-Fiving and fist-bumping people so I can't leave while he is still there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some district heating schemes for estates in London. I think the PDHU is the biggest, which covers more than one estate.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pimlico_District_Heating_Undertaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What drawers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm in a minority politically speaking, that most of the country disagree with me about the EU. 

For every 1.00 Remain votes there were only 1.08 Leave votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll lose the right to live in the rest of the EU. I had been thinking about moving somewhere warm when I retire and perhaps somewhere cheap to make the pension go a bit further. That future is made more difficult now. Also my assets which are in Sterling will be worth less.

A person owning a 300k property is about 60k worse off than they were before the vote.

I can't think of any positive effects on me personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the key to the wardrobe. It didn't turn anti-clockwise because it was already locked. If somebody hid in it they would have to unlock it, and close the door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe they think the message is important and not getting out as much as he can publicise it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says in answer to a question at the end, roughly: if you don't want to listen to him, don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can do it as well, if he chooses. I'd like to see John Major do one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you misunderstood. Bob is a Jewish person. By definition killing all Jewish people entails killing Bob. I don't see the relevance about threatening the president. If you said 'all presidents must die', that would include the current president. Whether that is legal or not is another question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Punching Nazis Totally Works  Defiant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to worry that somebody was hiding in my wardrobe. I got into the habit of always testing the key to make sure it was locked when I was in the room.  FSM knows what I would have done if the key had ever turned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not always. 

It's the definition of an addiction, that you keep doing it when you know it's harming you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why he had to become human to have a physical relationship with Lois.  Otherwise, he would have blown her apart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About 1,800 'vulnerable' day-old chicks dumped in field - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even eat puffins! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean a prawn. A prion is an old home for religious people like monks or nuns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying "all Jews must die" entails saying "Bob the Jew must die". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you must punch someone, make it a Nazi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Shrek Forever After* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how long it will be before self-driven races beat F1 timings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full Tony Blair speech - 17th February 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 13:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James O'Brien vs Tony Blair's Hard Brexit rebellion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do morals come from? (ft. Cosmic Skeptic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did know an Australian who pronounced it Laygo. She might have been an outlier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
