<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9409</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raw vote totals - you could calculate the % of eligible voters numbers. 

Obama received 69.5 million votes in 2008. Hillary received 65,844,610 votes in 2016, about 3 million more than Trump. To compare, in 2004 Bush received 62,040,610 votes and in 2000, 50,456,002.

 * 2016: 65.8 million for Hillary
 * 2012: 65 million for Obama
 * 2008: 69.5 million for Obama
 * 2004: 62 million for Bush
 * 2000: 50.4 million for Bush

As you can see, those numbers aren't purely related to population growth. There wasn't a population explosion between 2000 and 2004.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say that you saw this in 2008 - Obama is the most voted for candidate and Clinton is the second most voted for candidate in American history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okie dokie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia undoubtedly meddled in U.S. election: top intelligence official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who buy records also have hi fi sound systems. I think that might be an older, wealthier crowd. I don't know anyone under 30 who has a hi fi system - millenials are too broke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get the marketing momentum behind the page? What were your initial steps?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck!

My usual piece of advice is just to check out what your competitors are doing. What are their content themes? Hashtags? How do they interact with their fans? 

Social networking is, above all, community building. If you provide value in your content and interact with your fans in a meaningful way, you'll do well.

You should also be very clear about what you want the Instagram page to do for you. Instagram doesn't drive a lot of traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your suggestion to keep expanding? What good would housing that's a 2 hour commute to Toronto do? We just don't have the transit for that type of sprawl, and it's bad for health. 

Exurbs at low prices, I think, would really hurt the housing market in the long term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great, but it's not super easy to customize to that degree. D3 is more work but it's a lot more flexible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The structure of the site and content are very solid. The colour palette and fonts are also pretty good. My only changes are to some of the styles. 

I think I'd change the top menu items to the serif font that you have for your paragraphs, just to make it look a little lighter. White is a good colour for that. 

I'd change the colour of the red fonts in the Network With Me section. Pull a red directly from your main photo for the icons, and use another colour for the text. 

The three images need to have all the same theme. I love the first image of the mountains, that's a great choice. They're all actually good, individually. But the image of the spark doesn't have anything to do with the mountains, and the forest doesn't look like it's from the same photo set either. 

Since it's such a massive photo, you can zoom in and get smaller pieces for the sections underneath. Also, open the huge photo in Photoshop or another program and save it at 1,400 pixels wide. That's as big as you need for a website. No need for an image as huge as you have (https://bryarcole.github.io/img/jgoerugd_y4-john-towner.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not highcharts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're from Crowdbabble, where I work. It's a social media analytics company that does Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and LinkedIn. Mostly used by agencies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang. Sorry about that drop - I blame the new algorithm? 

I think that maybe you can build your community and get those likes by interacting with your audience more. I did some digging - images posted below. 

Looking at your follower growth, it does look like you've slowed down a bit recently: likely due to the lower engagement.

To up your engagement, check out your top hashtags - the ones your followers or any users liked and commented on the most: http://imgur.com/AxDlwuj Forgive the graph weirdness! We're trying a new layout and the PNG download isn't perfect yet. 

You might also post more on Sunday nights and Wednesday afternoons, when your followers comment on your posts the most: http://imgur.com/LfcQNkT The darker the blue in that image, the more engagement there was on that day and at that time. 

Just a few suggestions!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A story from the Great Trail project, which aims to connect Canada from coast to coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 06:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://fightspam.gc.ca/eic/site/030.nsf/eng/00287.html

Cornerstone of the law is not contacting people without their consent. On LinkedIn, it might be more of a grey area, because the emails usually pertain to their industry or business. You could argue that they maybe consented by advertising their name and industry/openness to stuff about that industry on the network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 06:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any links? I'd love to see them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does writing a genuine review count as a small online task? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of thought leaders, I really like AdWeek. Drew Neissen's interviews are also great - he gets giants in marketing to actually discuss their strategies rather candidly.

I also do a monthly roundup of good articles (November here: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/2016/12/05/top-reads-for-brand-managers-movember-2016/). The piece on Adidas was my favourite for that month. A lot of lessons from a huge rebrand. I was very surprised, because I don't expect that level of depth from Buzzfeed.

Here's the Adidas piece: https://www.buzzfeed.com/reggieugwu/the-man-who-made-adidas-cool-again?utm_term=.snJQ7PNdk#.ld8b5aGlq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SEO is an entire industry for a reason - ranking is a complicated business. How is your meta data? Headings? What's your keyword density? 

How many backlinks does the article have? To get on page 1 of google results, you typically need at least a few dozen links to the article. Some keywords require thousands of backlinks to rank on the first page, just because of the competition and number of results. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing to be wary of is the anti-email spam laws in countries like Canada, which crack down on unsolicited emails collected via social.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Data mining and stats are huge, and only getting bigger. 

For art/design, you probably want to aim for creative. Here's a fairly typical art director job, which would take you a few years to get to: https://workforcenow.adp.com/jobs/apply/posting.html?client=HLK1 jobId=11960 source=IN

Account management is the 'other side', and you won't get to use your art/design skills. Sample job: http://elevatedthird.applytojob.com/apply/5QBun4/Account-Manager

For now, focus on getting funding for college. Max out your grades and complete exciting projects that you're passionate about, even if you have to start the projects or teams yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought you guys might like this article very heartwarming. A mosque and a synagogue work together to sponsor a very bright woman (Fulbright scholar, academic) and her family to get to safety in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian family to reunite in Toronto, thanks to unlikely partnership of a synagogue and a mosque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't want to wander into the uncanny with a weirdly robotic 'person'. Be a friendly chatbot with a strong voice, like the QZ chatbot or Slack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to find the metrics that work for you - they're different for every brand and platform. Engagement rate and follower growth rate are pretty universal across platforms, but you might find more specific ones help you succeed more than others. For me, best posting time and most engaging keywords tell me the most. I find that when I use those two metrics on Twitter and Instagram particularly, engagement goes up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you tweet the same thing in rapid succession, you will get flagged as as spam account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, #dumpBMW and #dumpKellogg were both pretty unavoidable for the brands. They were trapped - I think that more brands will be trapped in a similar way in 2016.

They're both really interesting examples, becuase not acting and acting were both considered political actions. BMW and Kellogg were both advertising on Breitbart before the election. Some consumers were angry that they were advertising on Breitbart (a right wing website). Others were angry that they were considering not advertising on Breitbart. So, in either case, the brands were being 'political' without any real escape. Taking advertising out = left wing, keeping advertising = right wing. The brands were totally trapped. 

Or, #dumpstarwars was set off with one of the screenwriters tweeted something anti-Trump way back in October. If you're a big brand, how do you prevent that sort of thing? Ban all employees from using social? 

It's very true that this has been going on for a while. I think that with situations like the above, it might heat up this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely has a lot to do with the election, as I said in the article. I don't think that politics will die, though. I think that people are more divided in the US and quick to lash out at the other side, especially on social media. Campaigns like #dumpkellogg and #dumpBMW will keep going.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I included an example of 360 in the article, but I haven't seen any 360 live examples from brands yet (they just launched it). I will keep an eye out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought you guys might appreciate this. Pretty funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook just launched 360 live, which is pretty cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The surge of conversational news app, I think, means the end of link pushing on networks like Twitter. Twitter was really built to be conversational, so I will be very happy if we go back to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What marketing buzzwords, aside from 'high engagement'?

It's a hard trend to encompass, but it's basically physical processes that unfold flawlessly - see the two sample videos in the article. They're usually labeled "satisfying", "soothing", or "hypnotizing". They do not have a set production value: the video of the man chopping noodles in the article was shot on a phone, and the one of the handwriting machine was obviously made professionally. 

It's not a trend that's actually been identified as such before, so there aren't many other articles about it. It's a hard one to label, but you recognize the videos when you see them. 

In 2016, these videos were usually by individuals and proved extremely sticky. I think brands will adopt them in 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most processes that we interact with are concealed behind a screen, so were more hooked than ever by video that shows physical processes unfold. Humans love to watch amazing things at peak performance: beautiful machines working flawlessly, a process unfolding perfectly, a touchdown executed with great skill. Its hard to come up with an umbrella term for videos that capture these wins. These videos appear under different labels: soothing, flawless, win, watch this [machine or person] do [their job] perfectly.

Brands can capture high engagement with video content showing off the physical processes they perform smoothly. Like the noodle maestro video above, any seamless physical processes showing mastery are basically guaranteed to grab eyeballs. If your brand doesnt have a lot of physical processes to capture, you can create one  as OK GO did in its Rube Goldberg-esque The One Moment music video. Budget seems irrelevant to this trend: low production value videos of dominoes falling in beautiful patterns have millions of views on YouTube.

From the article: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/2016/12/27/2017-trend-forecast-mesmerizing-video/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few predictions for social media marketing in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social media in 2017, a few predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I did a little digging and came up with some predictions for 2017 social media trends. Some trends are huge and will really shift the landscape of social media, some are smaller ones that will likely burn out (like mesmerizing videos). Live video will be big - you've heard that before! 

Here's a link that goes to articles on each of the individual trends with examples and more detail: https://medium.com/@crowdbabble/social-media-in-2017-e604d58e8048#.ndratllpw

For marketers, social media in 2017 will be a challenge and opportunity. With the decline of content marketing and the rise of new technologies, like VR and AI, marketers will have to create new strategies to keep up. The status quo on social is shifting.

**Conversational Social Media**
Your social media fans and followers dont want to hear from you, they want to talk with you. In 2017, social media is going back to its roots.

**Marketing Gets Political**
Culture wars will rage on social media and brands will be caught in the middle. No brand will be able to escape from politics in 2017. 

**Live Video**
There are more opportunities than ever to connect with your audience in realtime. How can you make the switch from evergreen content to on-demand?

**Mesmerizing Video**
This is a smaller trend, but its a powerful one: wonder through video of seamless processes. 

**VR and AR**
Virtual reality and augmented reality are now built into most mainstream social networks. 

What other trends are you guys looking forward to in 2017? Or afraid of? I think that live streaming in virtual reality is going to be massive, since it's now offered through Facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retin A is really harsh on your skin. Start with only the Retin A, then incorporate other actives one at a time. You'll want to be on Retin A alone for at least 4 weeks so you can see how bad the flaking is before you add anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Year in review on social media for brand managers, with trending topics for Facebook and Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016: Year in review on social media, with trending topics on Facebook and Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAY! PM me the account name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live video and live audio are going to be huge on social media next year -- basically taking traditional live broadcasts, and bringing them into social networks. I wrote a post on it here: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/2016/12/21/2017-trend-forecast-live-video/

Facebook is even allowing live streaming in virtual reality (360 degrees), which is pretty incredible. That advance is pretty crazy - it'll allow people to feel like they're part of live events elsewhere, in realtime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 trends for social media marketing, including blogging, and when to use them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rising video trend for 2017: mesmerizing physical processes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a new problem for us, just showed up over the past few days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We track the times when our users are online and the posts that attract the most engagement. Then, we use that info to post at the right time with content that our users like. So, analytics -- strategy. Helps a ton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty cheap way to get Twitter followers that aren't interested in your content.

Instead, look at what your top competitors are doing. And what Denny's is doing, because they're amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know if you're having trouble seeing the images!

There's a lot of texture and detail in these maps, which makes the income gap more material and real (to me). I submitted it because it looks very different from other data vis that I've seen. It's not the typical minimalist, 'clean' style and primary colours that are so prevalent here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Income gap between rich and poor visualized on maps of Chicago, New York, and Los Angeles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the heck are all these spam links doing in our Google Analytics language list? Vote Trump?! Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of texture and detail in these maps, which makes the income gap more material and real (to me). I submitted it because it looks very different from other data vis that I've seen. It's not the typical minimalist, 'clean' style and primary colours that are so prevalent here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to look at the top posts by big brands on social media. Not ads exactly, but ad copy. I rank them by most engaging, the ones that got the most likes and comments. Every year I compile the most engaging 5 Instagram posts for big brands and share them on Twitter as a sort of 'best of the best' list. 

Social media is a great resource because it's all public and easily accessible, just find the pages/accounts of the brands you admire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you guys checked out Nielsen social? It's amazing for Twitter listening for entertainment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How effective is this, really, in cities? The city where I am is quite bright at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you guys don't steal my money, I'm happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pro tip: never, ever use Grabby. They're crooks who will steal your credit card info and never stop charging you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just thought I'd warn fellow email marketers! I used Grabby.io to try to extract emails from a list of websites that mentioned one of the companies I work for. The data itself was garbage - it treated @png and @jpgs as emails, the company won't stop charging me.

I've sent Grabby several emails asking them to stop charging my card and stop the projects, but they've charged me for two extra months. At this point, I don't know how to get them to stop charging me. I've asked them to delete my account, cancel the projects, but I just keep getting charged. I thought the issue was resolved in November, but I checked my credit card statement in December, and there was another charge from them. They're like a really bad gym, I think I might have to cancel my credit card to get them to stop. 

Avoid Grabby.io at all costs!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your best bet might be to try out a social media analytics platform to see all the different metrics in action.

This is pretty much a textbook for digital marketing, very well regarded: https://www.amazon.ca/Digital-Marketing-Strategy-Integrated-Approach/dp/074947470X/ref=sr_1_19?ie=UTF8 qid=1482359607 sr=8-19 keywords=marketing

The Whuffie Factor is older, but it's still solid: http://www.thewhuffiefactor.com/ Tons of insight about community building, rather than link selling. 

Social Media - The First 2,000 Years is great for understanding social media in-depth. It explains the appeal of different social media platforms, and looks to their origins in history.

The Art of Immersion is another good one on social media and entertainment, from New York University. https://www.amazon.ca/Art-Immersion-Generation-Remaking-Hollywood/dp/0393341259/ref=pd_sim_14_3?_encoding=UTF8 psc=1 refRID=JSFGKDE8WQC6FVMZ3G0K
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merca 20 and Taringa are both great platforms to reach Spanish audiences, but you'll need a native speaker to navigate them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should start with the influencers already in your network. Get a list of your followers, and sort it by influence. These people already like your brand. 

Alternatively, you can get a list of engagers and do the same thing - people who have liked or commented on your posts. These are even more engaged in your brand, and probably more likely to do a shoutout if you send them free product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the size of the idea. 

Is it a content theme? A new brand identity? One spot or commercial? It's a concept. Very few 'ideas' that I know of include complete execution, that's a final product. They usually include some documentation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live video will only get bigger in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will live content do to evergreen content marketing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook, Instagram, and Snapchat are stepping on Periscopes toes. With the exception of Pinterest, almost every social media platform now offers live video, including Twitter, with livestreams of big events like the election debates.

As evidenced by the conversational social media trend, evergreen content is dying. Users dont want to click through slideshows or read how-to articles. They want to know whats going on now in exclusive, exciting experiences that are more valuable because theyre ephemeral. As social media becomes more politicalwith Facebook on the forefront of election coverageinterest in live video will surge because its breaking, raw, uncensored. Grassroots.

The most watched live video of the year, with 164.7 million views, was shot in a car on a smartphone. 

In 2017, how will you shift from evergreen to live content? Do you see yourselves moving into live video?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most watched live videos of 2016 weren't by big brands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that doing a case study of your current strategy and your competitors will help you a lot. Show them the numbers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! We're building new Instagram and Pinterest analytics. Would you be at all interested in beta testing? 

On both networks, do you find earned or paid to be the most effective?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 05:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment helps! What do you think about companies using conversation rather than content marketing going forward? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another 2017 trend prediction: Moving away from content marketing, back to social media's roots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. You might like this article on crowdculture marketing, from HBR: https://hbr.org/2016/03/branding-in-the-age-of-social-media

Unique perspective on the rise of 'political' branding (intentional, not decided by a mob of angry people on social media). Builds on earlier concepts about brand voice and personality / community marketing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On LinkedIn, people want to like and share content that makes them look good as professionals. Videos on innovation in their field, articles on cutting-edge technology in their field, etc. They want to show off to their peers. Their LinkedIn engagement with your brand is part of their image in their industries. And to their bosses.

Intelligent, more formal content will do well on LinkedIn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really great example of a proactive strategy when it comes to politics - JC Penny picked a side, and it worked really well with their demographics. The brand didn't wait for social media to assume a side/bias for them. 

BMW, Kelloggs, and Star Wars aren't really taking ownership of the left in the same way, even though they've bene put into those categories by the #dump boycotts on Twitter. It'll be interesting to see if it plays out in the same way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> relevant username </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire your fearlessness in the face of controversy. You'd be a good person to have on board a brand team during a boycott. I can't wait to see if any of the #dump campaigns by Trump supporters will have a long term affect on the targeted brands. I'm going to do an analysis in a month or so on Kelloggs, BMW, and Star Wars to see if their follower counts / engagement went down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that brands should avoid politics, but most won't be able to in 2017.

Look at Star Wars, Kelloggs, and BMW examples in the article. They did not try to be political. They didn't comment on the election at all. But social media users thrust political perspectives onto them. So now they're embroiled in these big controversies and boycotts that they basically had nothing to do with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. It will be interesting to see if any of the #dump campaigns by more right-wing social media users have any affect on these brands' bottom lines, or if indeed the complainers weren't customers in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Kellogg and BMW are in the same situation in that they can't avoid the risks you're talking about. 

If Kellogg and BMW pulled their advertising from Breitbart, they would be attacked by the right. If they kept their advertising on Breitbart, they would be attacked by the left. 

So they can't avoid controversy. Many brands will be caught in a similar catch-22 in 2017, where political views are thrust upon them and staying neutral is impossible. 

There is literally no way, in that situation, for them to stay apolitical. It's a challenge that many more brands will face next year. 

Star Wars is another interesting example, where it was decried as "feminist propaganda" and the hashtag #dumpstarwars got started. How does the franchise avoid politics from there? It didn't seek out politics. It didn't try to participate in the election. But it's embroiled regardless. 

The Burger Chef example is an interesting one (though fictitious), because there a brand was able to bridge the gap between opposing sides. But it also couldn't avoid politics all together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the article - left versus right mostly. Star Wars is a great example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But brands can't avoid politics. As I said in the article, a lot of brands have political views thrust on them - like BMW, Kelloggs, and Star Wars. They tried to run far away, they failed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best thing for you to do on social is to see what your competitors, and best-in-class brands, are doing. What hashtags are they using? What are their content themes? Their image style/voice? How often do they post? Etc etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool! 

Tweeting about this now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading up on Facebook ads will probably be quite beneficial to you. You can hypertarget them, and retarget users who have visited your site/store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What trends do you see for marketing in 2017?

I just wrote a post on culture wars, and the increased politicization of social media. I think that brands won't be able to avoid being political in 2017 - if they don't proactively take a stance, their audiences will still choose or assume views for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preparing your small business for 2017: marketing trends to watch out for, including culture wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! This is Katie from Crowdbabble. I posted this over on /r/socialmedia, but I thought it might be useful for you as well. 

I'm writing a new series on marketing trends in 2017, and the first is culture wars and the increased politicization of social media. It's become impossible for brands to avoid politics on social media. Are your social media accounts boycott ready? Do they have to be? I want to hear your thoughts. 

Full post with images here: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/2016/12/13/2017-trend-forecast-culture-wars-and-your-brand/

Text below:

The 2016 Presidential Election and Brexit ignited a culture war in the West that many brands became embroiled in. Including your own.

In the 2010's, crowdculture marketing took off as brands embraced likeable causes to increase engagement, like Dove's body positivity campaign. In 2016, politics and identity politics clashed with marketing campaigns in an epic way as crowdcultures became more polarized online. In 2017, that culture war will intensify. No brands will be spared.

Social media users are inundated with political content, and participate in it readily. Does that mean your audience wants a break from politics? Do they want to engage with content that's not aligned with any cause? As seen by #dumpstarwars and #dumpkelloggs, social media users want to know what side your brand is on.

In 2017, brands will struggle to avoid losing followers by picking a side; social media marketers need to be reactive strategies prepared just in case. Alignment can come from anywhere: #dumpstarwars started when a Rogue One screenwriter tweeted his disagreement with Trump. Suddenly, the entire franchises brand identity shifted to the left. The ensuing Twitter debate drew a line between #dumpstarwars and Star Wars supporters, picking a side for the brand when its official channels hadnt sent a single political tweet.

Being proactive and taking a side on social media can be a huge opportunity for small businesses, attracting demographics who agree with your views. But brands wont be able to keep fans and followers who disagree with their politics  even if no views are concretely stated.

Divided audiences are the biggest challenge for big brands that have appeal across crowdcultures and the political spectrum. Lose-lose is possible by staying neutral, but win-win is impossible when picking sides. Social media users will not support brands they disagree with; in 2017, they will go out of their way to attack them.

In 2016 BMW pulled advertising from Breitbart after complaints from female audience members, when its ads appeared next to an article about how feminism makes you fat. The giant was then inundated with angry #dumpBMW tweets and Facebook posts from conservative audience members  appeasing one half of its audience angered the other. The controversy redefined the BMW brand, winning big with some.

In 2017, many businesses and influencers will find themselves in the same predicament as BMW: a catch 22 where both acting and not acting are political, and remaining neutral is impossible. 

Appealing to increasingly polarized audiences who demand alignment on controversial causes is a challenge, probably the biggest challenge, brands will face in 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advertising and cultural warfare: in 2017, every brand will be political </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome case study! Very thorough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Marketing Forecast: Is your brand prepared for cultural warfare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting a new 2017 trend forecasting series. First trend: culture wars and divided audiences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I'm starting a new series on social media trends for 2017, focused on those relevant to marketers and advertisers. You might remember my crisis management series and election case studies from earlier this year.

First up: culture wars. You can't avoid them. You should prepare for them. Are your social media accounts boycott ready? Do they have to be? I want to hear your thoughts. 

Full post with images here: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/2016/12/13/2017-trend-forecast-culture-wars-and-your-brand/

Text below:

The 2016 Presidential Election and Brexit ignited a culture war in the West that many brands became embroiled in. Including your own.

In the 2010's, crowdculture marketing took off as brands embraced likeable causes to increase engagement, like Dove's body positivity campaign. In 2016, politics and identity politics clashed with marketing campaigns in an epic way as crowdcultures became more polarized online. In 2017, that culture war will intensify. No brands will be spared.

Social media users are inundated with political content, and participate in it readily. Does that mean your audience wants a break from politics? Do they want to engage with content that's not aligned with any cause? As seen by #dumpstarwars and #dumpkelloggs, social media users want to know what side your brand is on.

In 2017, brands will struggle to avoid losing followers by picking a side; social media marketers need to be reactive strategies prepared just in case. Alignment can come from anywhere: #dumpstarwars started when a Rogue One screenwriter tweeted his disagreement with Trump. Suddenly, the entire franchises brand identity shifted to the left. The ensuing Twitter debate drew a line between #dumpstarwars and Star Wars supporters, picking a side for the brand when its official channels hadnt sent a single political tweet.

Divided audiences are the biggest challenge for big brands that have appeal across crowdcultures and the political spectrum. Lose-lose is possible by staying neutral, but win-win is impossible when picking sides. Social media users will not support brands they disagree with; in 2017, they will go out of their way to attack them.

In 2016 BMW pulled advertising from Breitbart after complaints from female audience members, when its ads appeared next to an article about how feminism makes you fat. The giant was then inundated with angry #dumpBMW tweets and Facebook posts from conservative audience members  appeasing one half of its audience angered the other. The controversy redefined the BMW brand, winning big with some.

In 2017, many businesses and influencers will find themselves in the same predicament as BMW: a catch 22 where both acting and not acting are political, and remaining neutral is impossible. 

Appealing to increasingly polarized audiences who demand alignment on controversial causes is a challenge, probably the biggest challenge, brands will face in 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can create your own datavis by downloading in Excel and going to Charts -- Insert Chart -- pie. Or you can use a third party analytics tool that does the visualizations for you (not free).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 03:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live video everywhere! 

More insights data on every platform - impressions and reach on Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 03:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about brand experience design or onboarding/marketing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You asked!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Have you tried Crowdbabble? We do everything but Adwords right now. We do capture paid vs earned media for Facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried Crowdbabble? We go pretty in-depth in our Facebook reports. We do daily, weekly, monthly metrics including engagement rate (custom time range, so you can measure whatever you want). 

We also do automatic PDFs or Excel reports to your inbox either weekly or monthly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, look at what your competitors are doing. Who are they engaging with? What are their content themes? What's their visual style and voice in their captions? 

Definitely start with the influencers in your own network, first. Get a full follower list and start with your most influential followers. 

Beyond that, relevant hashtags are a good way to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a full list of the definitions for almost every metric on Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and LinkedIn: https://www.crowdbabble.com/social-media-analytics-glossary/

You could try different analytics tools and do social media audits of different brands (local, smaller). You can then send those audits to the brands for free. Learning by doing is usually the best. 

Also, try not to drown in blogspam. There is so much garbage out there. You need a holistic approach to social media marketing, not Top 10 Tips articles. I do a monthly roundup of great articles, and you can find similar roundups around the web.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Content calendars are a great idea, based on your content themes. 

You need content themes that you stick to regardless of the breaking news - posts that will go up in addition to the breaking news posts. There is content that the station will have scheduled for holidays, events, etc. You can prepare for that stuff. Does your audience also want evergreen content? That's a question you'll need to do some research to answer. 

To find out what else to post aside from breaking news (if anything), follow your competitors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a great social strategy. This is an entire field of business - how to build an audience online. I'd suggest following your competitors and doing a lot of reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your engagement rate?

Have you looked at solutions like #paid (hashtagpaid), to see what you could potentially earn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish migration from 1850 to 1925, men vs women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foiled again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comparing average movie ratings + critical reception for each major Hollywood studio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 04:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird! Have you tried asking over in /r/facebook as well? I'll look around and see if I can find anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 00:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried a social media analytics service like Crowdbabble that tells you what your competitors are doing?

If you see their most engaging posts, hashtags, filters, posting times, etc, that should give you a good place to start for your social strategy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to tweet: https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/347191326112112640 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's best tweet about Putin, before his visit to Moscow in 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great project! Definitely ask your family and friends to retweet it and share. Facebook usually drives more traffic than Twitter, so that would be a great idea as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linking isn't allowed in the main post, but here is the original tweet: https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/347191326112112640

And a screen cap: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/crowdbabble_social-media-analytics-tool_blog_trump-top-tweet-post_7000tweets_i-love-russia_347191326112112640.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Putin will be going to The Miss Universe Pageant in November in Moscow... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...if so, will he become my new best friend? - Donald Trump, President Elect of the United States of America, June 19, 2013
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite tweet from Donald Trump about Russia: "Do you think Putin will be going to The Miss Universe Pageant in November in Moscow - if so, will he become my new best friend?"

Link: https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/347191326112112640 

Screencap: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/crowdbabble_social-media-analytics-tool_blog_trump-top-tweet-post_7000tweets_i-love-russia_347191326112112640.png
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Twitter, Donald Trump celebrates pageant in Moscow and slams climate change as a hoax (good laugh/cry) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best insults from the 2016 Presidential Election on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ones that I talk about in the article are Adidas, Salvation Army, and Tesla. All three have innovative campaigns currently running on social.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Data Set: 7,300 Donald Trump Tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A third party analytics solution will track and store your page consumption metrics, including event RSVP and page checkins. Do you have a budget for a service like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build your community on other communities. Work with influencers, your existing brand advocates, and other pages in  your community to build a bigger audience. Are you leveraging crowdculture at all? If so, there should be a built in community there that you can use. 

And by crowdculture I mean: https://hbr.org/2016/03/branding-in-the-age-of-social-media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a full list of most metrics that Crowdbabble currently tracks here: https://www.crowdbabble.com/social-media-analytics-glossary/

Some of the formulas are included. The ones directly from the APIs do not have formulas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a roundup of my favourite non-blogspam pieces this week: https://medium.com/the-social-reader/top-reads-for-brand-managers-movember-2016-4267e151d957#.pji1rm58g

They're all in there, but Buzzfeed, New York Times, and Adweek are great sources for social media marketing inspiration. Not blogspam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an album of more: http://imgur.com/a/eELNl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree :) Now I can do a poster for any novel that I have the full text of, with custom sizes. I've gotten up to three by four feet, bigger than that and my computer explodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! You can buy them here: https://www.etsy.com/ca/shop/Murmurous?ref=hdr_shop_menu

Use discount code KEEPREADING for 25% off. 

If your school wants to do a bulk order, we can talk about a steeper discount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it works! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's a program / programming language. The predecessor for HTML5's canvas stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea! I make custom prints for $65 each (risograph) or $35 each (regular colour printer). If you'd like a custom one, let me know!

Edit to add: I also do F. Scott Fitzgerald, Lewis Carroll, and one Louisa May Alcott (Anne of Green Gables). Here's a big album: http://imgur.com/a/eELNl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Frequency analysis, yes. I used an open source word cloud library and customized it in Processing. I do not arrange it after the fact - I do the transform in Processing around a stencil black and white GIF, where it detects and fills in only white areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with the supreme court in jeopardy. Unless there are mass protests, this is going through and it's going to stick for a few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which car is the most liked on Instagram? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best! Post it in /r/tinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm doing a sale for Christmas :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I screenprint classic novels using Processing and Project Gutenberg. What do you think? [OC] [979 x 734] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Great Long Reads For Marketers, November (I Sorted Through The Blogspam So You Don't Have To) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMAZING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top long reads for brand managers from November (Adidas rebrand case study, Tesla, and two others) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which theme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else going to this artist's workshop? This Saturday, December 10, in the Annex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.facebook.com/events/1842737962660749/

I'm obsessed with marbled paper so I will definitely be there! 

The details:

"On December 10, 2016 Navillus Gallery will introduce its new program, with the artist - a series of workshops, artist talks, and mixers to coincide with each new exhibition. 

Alongside the current exhibition, REFLECT:TROPIC 
featuring work by Christie Lau and Kirk Mechar, we will be 
hosting a workshop with Toronto-based artist Christie Lau.

The workshop will demonstrate the process and technique of Laus sculptural frames in her new MSR series. 

Participants will get the chance to experience first hand what it is like to work with the same materials and create the intricate flora that adorn Laus work. In this 2 hour workshop, 
participants will get to sculpt and customize their own frame with the artist and and receive a custom marbled paper with 
personalized calligraphy by Lau." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We drive a lot of traffic to this page, and it's worked pretty well for us: http://www.crowdbabble.com/start-free-trial/

We've been through quite a few sign up flows and separating the free trial flow from the paid user flow helps a ton. This page doesn't mention any pricing, only the free trial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://trumptweetgenerator.com/

Amazing! That's such a cool website. I am going to see if I can fix the csv link and clean out the characters this coming week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the pairing of high brow and 'low brow' here. What were the same questions, did you find?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could totally see how they would go together - families on the road with nothing but each other, basically attacked from all sides in one way or another. Good suggestion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really interesting. I haven't read either (hangs  head in shame), so I might try pairing them this winter. They seem like good winter books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they compliment each other?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 20:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! Pairing fiction with non-fiction - good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
