<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8579</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When she is caught clawing underneath the couch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 14:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my mum was my age, 19, she was taking care of a 5 month old baby (me) whilst moving in with my dad, purchasing there very first house together. She was very put together and grown up at that age, compared to me.

I'm 19, a live at home uni student who is starting university all over again in September after dropping out of my first course last year. I am obsessed with harry potter and anything Disney and have no plans for my far future as of yet, although I am independent financially and I have just finished paying of my part of a family holiday. I have a lot of growing up to do. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 02:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah I totally forgot about this part, thanks a lot :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bond between Harry and Pettigrew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 02:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am rereading the third book again and have very nearly finished it but something Dumbledore has said to Harry has threw me a little; "... The time may come when you will be very glad you saved Pettigrews life." 

I just wondered, did this ever come about in any way, shape or form in any of the later books? I am trying to think back to when I last read them and can't seem to pinpoint anything that would make harry or the readers think this. 

TDLR; Was there a time Harry was glad he saved Pettigrews life?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 02:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should say this to the next person who calls me dwarf or hobbit at work

I'm 5ft 1  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 02:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try being a 5 ft 1 19 year old :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 01:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those shoes don't go with that dress...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 22:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How big is your 'yard' :L  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 18:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thought process on seeing this picture:
Well hello 
Your hot
Let's like you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 01:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, seems there is quite a few of us, who knew haha I think people are just to much in a rush to notice anything in that area and nope not recently :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is outside my university! Hello fellow Manchester redditor!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 11:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a 'friend' who thought women's breasts were made out of water and that they were just two balls of water hanging on a girls chest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 11:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at university now and in the middle of changing courses, I kind of wish I never went  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 02:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate this! As soon as you turn 18, adults automatically expect you to know what the hell you want to do for the rest of your life! I just feel like screaming in there faces then grabbing my teddy bear and taking a nap like a child! Because that's what I feel like!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to be? I'm 19, my last boyfriend (about 2 months ago)  wasn't allowed anywhere near the stairs! We had to sit where my parents knew we couldn't get up to anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 11:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the sudden realisation the other day that the next flare for me, on this subreddit, is OLD. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I walked to my local asda only to realise, once I got there, that it was Sunday so they closed at 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 18:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 02:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was automatically implied with the previous statement!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I realise that my next available flair for this subreddit it 'old' as I shall be turning 20 next year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 00:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 23:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I want crumpets right now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 14:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manchester, the most northern you can get haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 12:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from England to, I was just being nosey haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 00:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where abouts in the UK are you from? If you don't mind saying 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 02:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who did your mum use as inspiration for the faces? Famous people? People you know? Or are they all a figure of her imagination?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 11:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We probably won't but that shouldnt stop you from hitting on us, if anything it gives girls like me a huge confidence boost when a guy hits on you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my beauty :') </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 01:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was warm yesterday so I left the house without a coat on this morning, now I'm cold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 16:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fussy kitty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 02:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have an 8 month old cat and lately she has been very... Fussy? We give her all the attention we can, take turns playing with her every night etc but when we stop she will meow at us for hours until we get up and play again and if we ignore her she will try and fight us by play biting our hands, scratching arms etc. She has even taken to climbing on our fire place and knocking of everything she can because she knows we will have to get up to replace it.
Do you guys have any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 01:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just made yourself look like a right idiot, I suggest you hide under a rock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 01:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The things I would do to that man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 23:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very good attitude to have :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 01:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was in Manchester :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bus driver was actually cheerful.and making jokes with everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 01:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realised why my 15 year old brother made a reference to pineapple juice this morning...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is something about his eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 23:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 19:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sat on a bus feeling Ill as anything and you have just made my day hahaha funny stuff :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dick Van Dyke was rather a handsome gentleman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 13:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 14:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little chest always does ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I came across this picture of Mark Whalburg... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 10:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 10:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped reading at 'superspeed'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 00:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told by my mum and dad that dj vu was when your mind dreamt what was going to happen the next day and I always felt special whenever I had one because I thought I was secretly psychic... You just ruined it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google chrome adds: Extension not worked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 19:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past couple of weeks I have been seeing the very annoying pop up ads and Link ads every time I have come on to Google chrome. I have tried going on to the actual ad provider website to disable it several times but it just re enables it self straight away, even when they inform you that it shouldn't. 

Having no luck this way, I decided to Google it and all I got were suggestions to download the Google extension 'ad block'. So I downloaded this but it doesn't seem to have done anything! I am running out of patience for these annoying ads as they are making my Laptop slower and will often crash the Google Chrome browser so I am forced to shut it down! 

Can anyone here suggest a solution? HELP!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 23:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was only one strawberry in my 'strawberry and grape' fruit pot from tesco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 18:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 01:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always loved Jeffery in prince of bell air more than the others, I looked forward to the snarky remarks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cocoa's first experience with the window cleaner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 15:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 02:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have just made my day :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 22:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As all good snitches are :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 10:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was intended to be but I made it a week after Christmas and by that point we had taken the tree down haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got crafty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 09:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 03:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all a victim of this one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your guilty pleasure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 03:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 11:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 18 and want to do the exact same thing but instead I feel like I need to go out with a friend and people I don't know just to not seem boring  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
