<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you autistic? The narrator said this in the cannon manga. I added the part about machi so that people who have only seen anime would know I'm talking about the manga INSTEAD of the anime. To differentiate. THE OBJECTIVE NARRATOR said this in the real manga. Reread a comment and try to understand it before you jump on it thinking you're gonna prove them wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The narrator (machi in anime) straight up says that hisoka doesn't have a grasp on others strength compared to him because he believes there can't be anyone stronger than him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some Freud type thinking. "You're sexually frustrated because everything" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What good Paying jobs do most people forget about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What book if I may ask? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hisoka has no idea how strong people are compared to himself. In the manga and anime it says that hisoka views himself as the strongest ever. He obviously isn't the strongest ever thus him wanting to fight Netero proves that he doesn't understand neteros strength  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending of the CA arc is one of the best ending to any arc in any show. Also the next arc which is short is very good. It's one of my favorites. If you like the strategic parts of HXH then you'll love the next arc. As well as if you're a big Killua fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 06:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like a lot of shoujos so that isn't the issue. I'm just trying to get across that naho is pretty shitty of a person in all honesty. I'm enjoying the hell out of this show btw I'm just stating my thoughts on our main character and my perspective of her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suwa is best girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 19:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUWA IS A FUCKING GODLY MAN AND NO ONE CAN BE BETTER THAN HIM!! HE WOULD BE A MUCH BETTER MC THAN NAHO. I've begun to hate naho as a person and suwa is a god among men. Sorry for the shitpost but I needed to say this somewhere.  Up until recently naho hasn't really tried to stop kakerus suicide. She's just been trying to date him. Which yes is hinted at in the letters but goddamn since the beginning she has only cared about that. All of her interactions with kakeru have been with the intent of a romantic relationship/her romantic feelings. Instead of doing everything she can to save him, until recently, her main goal has been romance with him not killing himself as an extra. So FUCK NAHO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 08:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Razor considered them strong nen users. This is similar to how the high level nen users were astonished by Killua and gons emmission jumps. These are feats of strength rather than skill IMO. It's similar to how a guy can be super jacked and you'd be like "well fuck he could beat the shit outta almost anyone" but then someone with martial art skills could come and whoop their ass. Gon and Killua became almost masters of basic nen using their monster prowess. But if it came to Intricite moves like mixing types to do thing they were still novices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 05:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with all of these but I'd like to add philosophy for chrollo due to his nihilistic beliefs. It would be a good catalyst for pika to hate him. Pikas going into the scientific psych stuff then chrollo comes in and tells all the students opposite stuff using philosophical theories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would go well with my username? I can only think of similar to trafalgar laws ability  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems I've been mistaken. After looking at your history I can see that your posts are majority theories and such so your posts do contribute. But your comments normally don't. Most of your comments are patronizing, outrages claims, unneeded or attacks on people. I'm all for being a dick to people but goddamn there's a reason you're looked at as the troll of this sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this is from the scene where gon and Leorio visit kurapika in the hospital after having his eyes stolen from fake pairo. I could be wrong though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude most of what you post and comment doesn't "contribute to the sub". This guy has a question for the HXH fanbase because he doesn't understand something. Don't be a cock to make up for how much of a disappointment to your father you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone asked something similar and the answer was just search "phantom troupe requiem" on YouTube. It's an amazing scene which proves to a lot of sceptics that this show is more mature than first shown while not showing true spoilers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gon is physically stronger than naruto. 

Naruto while being clumsy is still better at fighting. (Naruto trains martial arts and fighting while gon trains nen. Gon uses his nen to fight but still it's not martial arts training.)

Special ability- 
Naruto- Multiple weak clones which opens a lot of options and does residual damage
Gon-Jajanken which is a one shot but is extremely hard to land and predictable.
 
Speed- Gon wins but not by much. 

Weapons-Naruto has explosive kunai which can do huge damage possibly even a ko.

Winner- Naruto. 
Naruto's Arsenal of skill weapons and abilities gives him more options and opportunities to win. Gon is physically stronger and faster but it's not by a big enough margin to instantly win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CA Arc with Kite alive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think the chimera ant extermination would've changed if kite was alive when they stormed the palace and joined the team. (This is if all the situations were the same with the ants powers and nen abilities. Also the same time but kite is alive and gon San obviously didn't happen)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 04:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be wrong but I think it's also said that gon could reach that after several decades of pure training and doing nothing else. Similar to Netero but longer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys please stop talking about chrollo making a different plan. No ones dumb enough to think chrollo wouldn't make a different plan. But the question is about the plan he made for hisoka. Idgf about his other potential plans. This post was about if during the fight hisoka was switched with Netero could Netero win IN THAT SPECIFIC POSITION. I think the Buddha for sure would win due to its almost infinite options in striking ability and speed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gon X Pitou is an atrocity in my personal view of it. When I see someone ship that it might as well mean you're spitting in the face of everything togashi did in order to develop gon as a character. Of course I over react highly but still if you ship that it physically hurts me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the first ep of 1999 and then watch 2011. 1999 shows you something in the first ep that 2011 doesn't and helps set up another later arc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But which ones the nickel and which is the dime?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paristons theorized hatsu fleshed out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so there's a lot of theories about paristons nen ability and my personal favorite is that he has the ability to turn on someone else's hatsu remotely. Here's my shitty hatsu that I came up with for this. 

Hatsu:StopLight

Description: By saying code words the user can trigger someone else's hatsu to do certain things

When the target hears the word "green light" their hatsu will go off. For example silvas giant nen balls would appear at his hands. This can be useful to either hurt himself or make him use up his aura until he's out. This ability can be used an endless amount of times but takes 30 seconds recharge. On time based abilities like killuas or conjured items the ability lasts 10 seconds. So if used on shizuku she can put her vaccuum away after 10 seconds.

When hearing "Yellow Light" the targets hatsu cannot come out or be used for one minute (if not already out) and if the hatsu is already in use or out it has to stay out for 30 seconds. In the second scenario gons jajanken would be stuck being powered up for 30 seconds and Killua would be unable to turn off his ability like he could when it's normally forced on. Yellow light can only be used 5 times in 24 hours

When hearing "Red Light" the target is unable to use their hatsu, and if the hatsu is already in use it stops and goes away. Red light lasts 20 minutes and can only be used once a day.


Requirements: For the user to use this ability on a person they must 
-Know the name of the hatsu
-See the hatsu
-Know the requirements of hatsu
- Have the target Say one of the colors "Red,Green or yellow"
-The target has to hear one of the code words for it to take effect
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 14:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah the nen difference is humongous. But you need to realize how OP leorio's ability is. Warp punch is an ability that's used to send blasts of nen at tumors and bloodclots inside the body using sonar. Leorio is a doctor and in a fight only needs to send nen blasts, not even a real punch, at certain vital positions such as muscle tendons and even the heart if wanted. While razor is getting ready to spike the ball leorio can already be turning off his arms, legs and whatever else he wants.  Warp punch is quite an OP hatsu for detaining people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 13:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I voted for leorio and left what I thought was a fairly convincing reason. I thought his hatsu could handle razor well. Eh even if the few leorio voters were real most were just trolls so I guess it's fair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 21:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ging has stated that warp punch most likely is used with warp nen blasts into area of a body where tumors are via sonar. Leorio can warp anywhere without seeing it as long as it's touching the medium he uses sonar on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People think I'm trolling by voting for leorio but leorio has on of the strongest hatsus we've seen and can easily take down any enemy by attacking their insides. Razor would win 100% if he gets close to leorio but he can't defend against the warp blasts on muscle tendons, pressure points and possibly the heart, but I doubt leorio would actually try to kill. Razor is overall the better fighter and nen user but I'm giving this to leorio because of the fact that he has options which give him a for sure win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
