<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5070</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might [this](https://bizon-tech.com/us/bizonbox3-egpu.html/) work?

Thanks

EDIT: Thanks for downvoting me just because I didnt know that bizon was a fraud. I am just happy that you can feel superior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> External GPU MBP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using an External GPU on a Macbook Pro is possible, right? Soo I have a GTX1070 and Im planning to buy a 2016 macbook, but which of the chosable CPU's wouldnt bottleneck my 1070 to an extend where its not worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks. I will have to carefully decide whether I should go with a MBP then since Most of the time im rendering while editing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macbook Pro for 3D modelling / Applemouse charging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wanted to get a MacBook Pro but I mainly use - other than office - Blender for 3D modelling and CAD+T for work. And I wonder how these programs would perform on a Macbook Pro? I always hear that the Apple software for video editing runs superb on MBP  but what about the programs I mentioned?

Another quick question: How is the Applemouse charged? Lightning or USB-C? Lightning would seem counterintuitive. 

TIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How familiar are you with the gear wars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which programm did you use? LOOKING AWESOME btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pictures like these are the reason why I love this sub so much. Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for offering a comparison to an actual painting. More people posting here should do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but an Apple customer is a unique breed

At that time the Brand Apple was unique.
Now... the comstomer base is unique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I will remesh / decimate the tree. For the plane I just added enough subdivions and scaled the plane on the Z axis with random proportional editing enabled.

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just doing low poly because its easy for a beginner... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 11:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to achieve a low poly design, with smooth shading on the ground plane I would kind of get the opposite of a low poly render, right? 

My current lighting setup are three point lamps. And it looks very odd, so thanks for your suggestion.

Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beginner seeking help. How to improve this and what are my biggest mistakes so far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 11:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant. Stop. Watching. 

Great work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 11:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which program would be capable of creating things like that? Blender? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gaming on a Mac? I never owned one, but thats just not what these things are built for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im in the same boat. My Ipad 2 is also just too old now and I'm wondering how the new iPads in March will be. I've heard Apple is not working on an iPad OS so I think there wont be much of a difference. Do you think the pricedrops for the current Ipad pros will be big? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One is a Laptop, the other a desktop. Both looking absolutely great, but are different things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats very interesting! Thanks for posting :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The touch Bar is able to do a lot of things but where its placed you cant rest your hands and therefore wont use it as much. Thats contradictory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. A whole event just about a "touch bar" that forces you to look ridculous while using it. 

I know it could be very handy for a lot of situations and it also is well-implemented. But that's it, and a touch bar like this wont help Apple to compete with the new products Microsoft has been releasing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They round the numbers of the screensize down. So its more than one inch actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not phtorealistic but the all pastell colored look is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 19:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For cheaper prices for the 9,7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am still hoping for an ipad refresh, but i guess that will take another 6months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great this is the best subreddit after all. Keep it up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I warned /u/suddensavior now do something against it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 14:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deserve Depression? Do you mean that these people that "deserve it" are pricks or that they've gone through a lot of hard times? Anyway no one deserves depressio.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pfostieren geht wohoo. Erffnet den Circlejerk! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 10:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Golden Gate in the Background is Cruz' halo. 

This is Accidential Renaissance! Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they actually are making a huge deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja super. Gibt es dann die flairs auch fr alle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja bitte. Warum kann ich denn in diesem Unterreddit nichts Pfostieren?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it really changed from red to orange due to the new interface for the watch application </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really waiting for some serious reviews of the pixel camera, I never heard of the rating system they used to brag about the camera quality but thats probably my fault. No camera bump, thats amazing :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The google home was the part that I liked the most. It actually sounded useful, contrary to what I expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think they give the press only information about andromeda? Cause that was my main reason for watching the stream too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that was my first thought as well. They really did but I never watched a Google livestream before so I don't know. The sneaky Apple jokes were kinda awkward too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Livestream is over. What are your thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there's nothing we can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its all about the RNGesus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks alot! I am fully satisfied :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I dont understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming PC for my cousin, 1000 budget. Austria. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What will you be doing with this PC? Be as specific as possible, and include specific games or programs you will be using.**

* Playing games like Rainbow Six Siege, Grand Theft Auto 5 and Modded Minecraft. (More games to come in the future ofc.) For Work he'll just need office.

**What is your maximum budget before rebates/shipping/taxes?** 

* 1000

**When do you plan on building/buying the PC? Note: beyond a week or two from today means any build you receive will be out of date when you want to buy.** 

* In about 3 to 4 weeks.

**What, exactly, do you need included in the budget? (Tower/OS/monitor/keyboard/mouse/etc\)** 

* He'll need a Tower/OS/Monitor. Nothing else.

**Which country (and state/province) will you be purchasing the parts in? If you're in US, do you have access to a Microcenter location?** 

* Austria, Salzburg (Hardware is fucking expensive here)

**If reusing any parts (including monitor(s)/keyboard/mouse/etc), what parts will you be reusing? Brands and models are appreciated.** 

* None

**Will you be overclocking? If yes, are you interested in overclocking right away, or down the line? CPU and/or GPU?** 

* No overclockig

**Are there any specific features or items you want/need in the build? (ex: SSD, large amount of storage or a RAID setup, CUDA or OpenCL support, etc)**

* 1TB HDD would actually be sufficient. If the budget allows it he would appreciate an SSD.

**Do you have any specific case preferences (Size like ITX/microATX/mid-tower/full-tower, styles, colors, window or not, LED lighting, etc), or a particular color theme preference for the components?**

* Design doesn't matter.

**Do you need a copy of Windows included in the budget? If you do need one included, do you have a preference?**

* Windows 10

**Extra info or particulars:** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the story:
She was born at my farm 3 years ago. And 7 months ago a friend of us, who was helping us with the haying somehow overrun her with the tractor in the dark. We tried to find her, nothing. After a week she finaly appeared again with one leg fully smashed (and some other wounds) and it took us 4 more days to catch her and bring her to the vet. Right after the surgery she was acting as if nothing happened and she is now again playing with her 3 other brothers and sisters. :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has a third leg - I promise ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really dont know much about cat breeds and she is just a typical farmers cat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It was really hard for her to recover. But she happy as always now again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My three legged cat doing a restrained blep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Sounded ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoofs hard man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
