<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7377</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 17:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Coinmap.org](http://coinmap.org) is a good map of physical locations that accept them. Purchase flights at Cheapair, book hotels are Expedia, buy electronics at NewEgg. I'm sure others will jump in with further suggestions... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that this is going to get down-voted to oblivion but now is the perfect time to raise all taxes on fossil fuels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 18:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that this is going to get down-voted to oblivion but now is the perfect time to raise all taxes on fossil fuels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 04:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Affinity Bridge](http://affinitybridge.com) are pretty trustworthy. Located in Vancouver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Or even just offer it as an option for purchasing Play Store credit (which is all that Microsoft is really doing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bet you 1000 bits that they are. Now how do we find out if I have to send you 1000 bits or I get your house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 00:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually their payment processor (Bitpay) allows vendors to set a percentage to keep in Bitcoin. Apparently roughly 50% of Bitpay users chose to hold _some_ Bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 00:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. (Google, are you listening?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 00:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the US. There were scores of countries helping every step of the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last day to respond to the province's transportation plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 23:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Provincial Government is current developing the plan, B.C. on the Move. Billions of dollars will be spent on this plan. Please take action to help ensure that cycling and walking get their fair share.

[Complete the Transportation Plan Survey] (http://surveys.givingopinions.ca/s/b637o/)

The deadline for your input is Dec. 12 at 4pm.

We strongly encourage the Province to implement a comprehensive Active Transportation Strategy building upon the BC Road Safety Strategy which commits to a long term goal of zero fatalities.  Safe and comfortable access for people walking, cycling, riding transit or using wheelchairs should be an integral part of the plan and of all the roads and bridges in BC.

By  donating http://bccc.bc.ca/donate  to the BCCC, you are supporting our efforts to make cycling safer and more comfortable for people of all ages and abilities across BC. Any  contribution http://bccc.bc.ca/donate  is much appreciated! Cycling facilities should be safe, convenient and comfortable for people of all ages and abilities including children and seniors. This includes bicycle paths and protected bike lanes that that are designed to be safe for the higher speed cycling required for long distance commuting, training and exercise.

Recommendations

- p. Accelerated provincial investment in walking and all ages and abilities cycling infrastructure totalling $100 million per year:
- p. Funding for auditing, planning and upgrading cycling and walking facilities on provincial roads and bridges including shoulders and separated paths;
- p. Increased Bike BC cost sharing funding to complete cycling networks in communities; 
- p. Cost sharing funding for complete streets with all ages cycling facilities that are also safer and more comfortable for walking; and
- p. Funding for trails and paths used by cycling and walking tourists and residents.
- p. Improved cycling and driver education;
- The adoption of improved standards for facilities that are both appropriate for all ages and abilities and higher-speed cycling;
- p. Universally available cycling skills training for children with provincial funding support;
- p. Improved standards more funding for maintenance and hazard removal on roads, shoulders paths used by cyclists;
- p. Legislation to improve the safety and legal protection of people walking and cycling including a safe passing distance (1m) law and allowing riding two abreast;
- p. Legislative changes allowing municipalities to cost-effectively reduce speeds on walking and cycling routes;
- p. The implementation of a comprehensive cycling tourism strategy; and
- Increased provincial funding for transit and legislation that gives municipalities and TransLink the authority to implement new funding sources for cycling, walking and transit improvements.
Take Action

Complete the Transportation Plan Survey http://surveys.givingopinions.ca/s/b637o/  Before Dec. 12 4pm

The survey asks for three infrastructure priorities. Please include cycling and walking projects in your community. There are some suggestions from around BC below. 
p. Possible projects include:

- Trail or path networks or regional routes
- Wider shoulders or a bike lane along a road or highway
- Separated paths along a busy road or highway
- A wider shared path on a bridge or overpass
- A new cycling and walking bridge over a busy highway, railway, river or stream
- Improved access to a bridge
Some Suggestions

- Acquire abandoned rail line between Kelowna and Vernon for a safe cycling and walking corridor http://www.bccc.bc.ca/2554/acquire_abandoned_rail_line_between_kelowna_and_vernon_for_a_safe_cycling_and_walking_corridor
- Agassiz-Rosedale Bridge http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/agassiz_rosedale_bridge  - Improve for cycling or build an alternative
- Highway 4 to Tofino - Sutton Pass to the Visitor Centre at the T junction http://www.bccc.bc.ca/highway_4
- Kamloops http://www.bccc.bc.ca/4349/kamloops_suggestions  - Path between Valleyview and Barnhartvale that parallels Hwy1
- Kamloops http://www.bccc.bc.ca/tugboatgirl/kamloops  - Bike path along Columbia Street. Separate bike path parallel to Hwy 1 from Orchard's walk (Grand Boulevard) to Dallas Drive. Bike path on Halston Bridge and Westsyde Road
- North Shuswap Cycling/Walking Trail  http://www.bccc.bc.ca/blaupland/north_shuswap_cycling_walking_trail
- Complete the Salish Sea Trail Network http://www.bccc.bc.ca/complete_the_salish_sea_trail_network  - Salt Spring Island, Southern Vancouver Island
- Sea to Sky Highway Cycling Facilities Upgrade http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/sea_to_sky_highway
Metro Vancouver

- Alex Fraser Bridge Cycling Access http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/alex_fraser_bridge_cycling_access
- Experience the Fraser - Hope to the Salish Sea http://www.bccc.bc.ca/experience_the_fraser
- Ironworkers Memorial Bridge Access http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/ironworkers_memorial_bridge_access
- Upgrade Lougheed Hwy - Coquitlam, Maple Ridge, Mission, Deroche to Harrison Mills http://www.bccc.bc.ca/peter/upgrade_lougheed_hwy_2
- Upgrade the Lougheed Hwy - Coquitlam http://www.bccc.bc.ca/oldjohns/upgrade_the_lougheed_hwy
- UBC/UEL Cycling and Walking Improvements http://bikewalkubc.org  -  NW Marine Dr http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/nw_marine ,  Chancellor Blvd http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/chancellor ,  University Blvd http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/university ,  16th Ave http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/sixteenth ,  SW Marine Dr http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/sw_marine ,  Imperial Dr http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/imperial
HUB's Priorities

- Protected, paved, lit bikeway directly connecting the Central Valley Greenway in New Westminster to Coquitlam Centre
(by way of the Port Mann Bridge and parallel to Lougheed Highway).
- Protected, paved, lit bikeway connecting Richmond bike routes to the U.S. border (parallel to Hwy 99), and to the ferry terminal in Tsawwassen.
- Protected, paved, lit bikeway from Coquitlam Centre through Port Coquitlam, Pitt Meadows and Maple Ridge (parallel to Lougheed Hwy).

[Complete the Transportation Plan Survey Now!](http://surveys.givingopinions.ca/s/b637o/)
  
More information: [http://www.bccc.bc.ca/transportation_plan](http://www.bccc.bc.ca/transportation_plan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last day to respond to the province's transporation plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 23:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Provincial Government is current developing the plan, B.C. on the Move. Billions of dollars will be spent on this plan. Please take action to help ensure that cycling and walking get their fair share.

[Complete the Transportation Plan Survey] (http://surveys.givingopinions.ca/s/b637o/)

The deadline for your input is Dec. 12 at 4pm.

We strongly encourage the Province to implement a comprehensive Active Transportation Strategy building upon the BC Road Safety Strategy which commits to a long term goal of zero fatalities.  Safe and comfortable access for people walking, cycling, riding transit or using wheelchairs should be an integral part of the plan and of all the roads and bridges in BC.

By  donating http://bccc.bc.ca/donate  to the BCCC, you are supporting our efforts to make cycling safer and more comfortable for people of all ages and abilities across BC. Any  contribution http://bccc.bc.ca/donate  is much appreciated! Cycling facilities should be safe, convenient and comfortable for people of all ages and abilities including children and seniors. This includes bicycle paths and protected bike lanes that that are designed to be safe for the higher speed cycling required for long distance commuting, training and exercise.

Recommendations

- p. Accelerated provincial investment in walking and all ages and abilities cycling infrastructure totalling $100 million per year:
- p. Funding for auditing, planning and upgrading cycling and walking facilities on provincial roads and bridges including shoulders and separated paths;
- p. Increased Bike BC cost sharing funding to complete cycling networks in communities; 
- p. Cost sharing funding for complete streets with all ages cycling facilities that are also safer and more comfortable for walking; and
- p. Funding for trails and paths used by cycling and walking tourists and residents.
- p. Improved cycling and driver education;
- The adoption of improved standards for facilities that are both appropriate for all ages and abilities and higher-speed cycling;
- p. Universally available cycling skills training for children with provincial funding support;
- p. Improved standards more funding for maintenance and hazard removal on roads, shoulders paths used by cyclists;
- p. Legislation to improve the safety and legal protection of people walking and cycling including a safe passing distance (1m) law and allowing riding two abreast;
- p. Legislative changes allowing municipalities to cost-effectively reduce speeds on walking and cycling routes;
- p. The implementation of a comprehensive cycling tourism strategy; and
- Increased provincial funding for transit and legislation that gives municipalities and TransLink the authority to implement new funding sources for cycling, walking and transit improvements.
Take Action

Complete the Transportation Plan Survey http://surveys.givingopinions.ca/s/b637o/  Before Dec. 12 4pm

The survey asks for three infrastructure priorities. Please include cycling and walking projects in your community. There are some suggestions from around BC below. 
p. Possible projects include:

- Trail or path networks or regional routes
- Wider shoulders or a bike lane along a road or highway
- Separated paths along a busy road or highway
- A wider shared path on a bridge or overpass
- A new cycling and walking bridge over a busy highway, railway, river or stream
- Improved access to a bridge
Some Suggestions

- Acquire abandoned rail line between Kelowna and Vernon for a safe cycling and walking corridor http://www.bccc.bc.ca/2554/acquire_abandoned_rail_line_between_kelowna_and_vernon_for_a_safe_cycling_and_walking_corridor
- Agassiz-Rosedale Bridge http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/agassiz_rosedale_bridge  - Improve for cycling or build an alternative
- Highway 4 to Tofino - Sutton Pass to the Visitor Centre at the T junction http://www.bccc.bc.ca/highway_4
- Kamloops http://www.bccc.bc.ca/4349/kamloops_suggestions  - Path between Valleyview and Barnhartvale that parallels Hwy1
- Kamloops http://www.bccc.bc.ca/tugboatgirl/kamloops  - Bike path along Columbia Street. Separate bike path parallel to Hwy 1 from Orchard's walk (Grand Boulevard) to Dallas Drive. Bike path on Halston Bridge and Westsyde Road
- North Shuswap Cycling/Walking Trail  http://www.bccc.bc.ca/blaupland/north_shuswap_cycling_walking_trail
- Complete the Salish Sea Trail Network http://www.bccc.bc.ca/complete_the_salish_sea_trail_network  - Salt Spring Island, Southern Vancouver Island
- Sea to Sky Highway Cycling Facilities Upgrade http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/sea_to_sky_highway
Metro Vancouver

- Alex Fraser Bridge Cycling Access http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/alex_fraser_bridge_cycling_access
- Experience the Fraser - Hope to the Salish Sea http://www.bccc.bc.ca/experience_the_fraser
- Ironworkers Memorial Bridge Access http://www.bccc.bc.ca/richardcampbell/ironworkers_memorial_bridge_access
- Upgrade Lougheed Hwy - Coquitlam, Maple Ridge, Mission, Deroche to Harrison Mills http://www.bccc.bc.ca/peter/upgrade_lougheed_hwy_2
- Upgrade the Lougheed Hwy - Coquitlam http://www.bccc.bc.ca/oldjohns/upgrade_the_lougheed_hwy
- UBC/UEL Cycling and Walking Improvements http://bikewalkubc.org  -  NW Marine Dr http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/nw_marine ,  Chancellor Blvd http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/chancellor ,  University Blvd http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/university ,  16th Ave http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/sixteenth ,  SW Marine Dr http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/sw_marine ,  Imperial Dr http://bikewalkubc.org/moti/imperial
HUB's Priorities

- Protected, paved, lit bikeway directly connecting the Central Valley Greenway in New Westminster to Coquitlam Centre
(by way of the Port Mann Bridge and parallel to Lougheed Highway).
- Protected, paved, lit bikeway connecting Richmond bike routes to the U.S. border (parallel to Hwy 99), and to the ferry terminal in Tsawwassen.
- Protected, paved, lit bikeway from Coquitlam Centre through Port Coquitlam, Pitt Meadows and Maple Ridge (parallel to Lougheed Hwy).

[Complete the Transportation Plan Survey Now!](http://surveys.givingopinions.ca/s/b637o/)
  
More information: [http://www.bccc.bc.ca/transportation_plan](http://www.bccc.bc.ca/transportation_plan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 18:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the nicest aspects to this is that Google now has to up their game when they announce acceptance. It won't be sufficient for them to merely add Bitpay as an option for Play Store purchases. They will need to develop something internal and innovative for anyone to care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they wouldn't be able to claim they have over a billion users anymore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google should be hanging their heads in shame today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soon, the internet will be impossible to control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 16:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 16:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the future without a doubt. Most jurisdictions are just awaiting formal legal clarification around equity crowdfunding. Meanwhile many projects (eg. Swarm) are just moving ahead in the absence if a firmal legal framework to support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 21:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I can't comment on how things work for your 503C's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 19:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the issuance of a charitable tax receipt currently requires a conversion to fiat. It doesn't necessarily have to be right away and at least in Canada there seems to be a little leeway as to when and how the valuation is made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! Fun fact: I hand-coded the HTML (in MS Notepad if memory serves) for Greenpeace's first website back in '94! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW if anyone is considering a crowdfunding campaign I am currently working with [a platform that accepts credit cards, paypal, bitcoin, litecoin, darkcoin as all "offline" payment methods](https://dana.io). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 17:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, at least here in Canada IF you:

* Collect the required personal information from the donor necessary to fulfill the legal requirements of issuing the charitable tex receipt AND
* You convert the XBT to fiat soon after receiving it so that the charitable contribution is being recorded in the equivalent amount fiat (in our case CAD). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 17:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the first [non-profit I worked with to implement it](http://peacegeeks.org/donate) has been accepting it for almost 2 years. They are even setup to give charitable tax receipts for it (if the donor provides their full information) - they just haven't updated their page to reflect it yet. I'm not aware of any feedback they have ever received to suggest that they shouldn't be accepting it. I also worked with [a local university](https://bitcoinfoundation.org/2014/10/simon-fraser-university-campus-on-a-mission/) to accept it. Same thing. 

One other advantage to accepting bitcoin donations is because of its relative anonymity you are facilitating financial support from those may have a real need (or at least wish) to preserve their privacy. One example would be that resource-extraction employee or executive that secretly supports a [Greenpeace](http://greenpeaceblogs.org/2014/09/22/greenpeace-now-accepting-bitcoin-donations/)-style organization but doesn't want his/her support to be traced back such that s/he loses their job. Don't kid yourself - those kinds of double-agents are out there in droves and just need encouragement and the means!

The current state of cryptocurrency reminds me a lot of the early days of the web. I worked with a lot of non-profits in the early '90s to get them on the web and it was exactly the same thing. Some just couldn't see the future and didn't see why they should. Others were concerned that the internet was only used by drug dealers and child pornographers and they didn't want to be be associated with that. Well we know how that story played out. I feel crypto-currencies are currently at that same state that the web was in the mid-nineties. It's still very clunky to use but it behooves everyone to try and understand how it's going to affect them and the organizations they care about.

_(Edit: cleaned up some sentences and added last paragraph)_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 03:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone creates one that weighs less than 50lbs, is worn on the shoulders, and has over 2 hours of flight time then I will care.

Be nice if it comes in on the quiet side of 100 decibels while operating too. Not holding my breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 03:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find some threads in here that compare the various brands. Once you've settled on a brand then you'll just need to decide on a colour and know her calf circumference to choose the size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She would probably appreciate a foam roller and/or compression socks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 02:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a longtime member of both the bitcoin community and a technology consultant for non-profits I would say its (current) importance for non-profit organizations depends on what sort of work you do - in two different ways.

The first is if your work is in an area that overlaps with the core values of the bitcoin community - those of individual freedom, civil and human rights, open source technology, etc. If your organization works in those specific areas then the chances are that you can attract monetary support for your work in the form of bitcoin (and other similar currencies) especially if you commit to spending what you get back within the community (ie. purchasing needed services and goods from others that will take bitcoin).

Secondly there may be some advantage to adopting bitcoin if your organization has a need to make payments with leaving a smaller information fingerprint (eg. you have a strong desire from an operational security perspective not to have your payments traced - think Wikileaks or various human rights organizations). Also... if you work in international development and regularly send money overseas bitcoin can greatly expedite money transfers and reduce costs if you are properly setup on either end of the transfer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 02:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought the world would be a much saner place if the voting age was dropped to 14 and the driving age raised to 25. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 00:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't say anything about your exercise regime?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NP. That's strange one. I'm an ardent user of VLC and it runs fine on all my boxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 18:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Launchpad bug report time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 18:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could well be. Don't know much about that project :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 16:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was that [fire in Thailand a few weeks ago](http://bitcoinexaminer.org/fire-destroys-massive-bitcoin-mining-operation-thailand/). That would be part of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 16:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try:

     sudo apt-get purge vlc
     sudo apt-get install vlc

Could also clean out _~/.config/vlc_ just to be sure.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 16:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... the Intel is usually pretty trouble free. Does the freeze leave anything in dmesg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 00:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. What video driver are you using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 02:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Psilocybin mushrooms](http://mobile.nytimes.com/2014/11/30/opinion/sunday/can-mushrooms-treat-depression.html?referrer _r=0)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 00:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drupal Commerce has a few modules that allow Bitcoin support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 16:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _"If the real Jesus Christ were to stand up today,
he'd be gunned down cold by the C.I.A..."_ 
- [The The, Mind Bomb (1989)](http://www.songlyrics.com/the-the/armageddon-days-are-here-again-lyrics/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 15:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to [consult a professional](http://www.scientificamerican.com/article/mental-health-crises-online-is-social-media-a-friend-or-foe/). Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 03:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you are rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 02:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live near the seaplane base and they are irritatingly noisy and produce way too much smelly exhaust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 01:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crappy idea. Replace huge ferries full of cars with smaller, faster boats that are passenger only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 00:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second this. The endowment lands are night are awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't do much mountain biking anymore but I can't imagine that it wouldn't work well for it. I [mount mine on an instrument pod on my road bike and it's my primary computer](https://imgur.com/unkFTFR). If I were mountain biking with it I would probably just wear it on my wrist for recording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 01:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FR620 is great for cycling too. GPS is very accurate and you can add a sensor for cadence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 00:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that was an easy decision once he saw that public opinion had swung against him and those $1,000/hr Denton's lawyer's bills started appearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 21:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely still secure but yes it needs updating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 17:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or get it shipped to a post office box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 17:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend installing [Poweramp](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.maxmpz.audioplayer) as her music player. It's a top-rated music app (the first app I ever paid for) and has a mono switch and L-R balance. This will allow you to route all sounds through both chanels (mono) and then set the balance to only output through the desired side. It actually won't matter if you don't change the balance except that you may save a little power by not driving both channels. The link above is to the trial version so you can confirm that it does what you are looking for. You get to the balance and mono switch through the little symbol comprised of 3 circles at the top-right . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 16:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitcoin is the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 18:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's not actually as concerned about monitoring the kids as the parents.

That aside you may find it interesting to know that before she became principal she was a vice-principal at a junior high school where she said that 90% of her time was spent dealing with conflicts related to FaceBook posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 15:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dana.io](https://dana.io) is the top crowdfunding site like Indiegogo or Kickstarter but I'm biased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 15:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're a serious roadie [these are the routes favoured by others of your ilk](http://labs.strava.com/heatmap/#11/-122.98659/49.19089/blue/bike).

(Edited link to zoom a little closer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best social media monitoring service for an elementary school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 15:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was asked by a friend who is the principal of an elementary school to recommend a service that would allow her monitor to the social media in and around her school, especially FB, Twitter and Instagram. I know there are bunch of competing services out there (Bottlenose, etc.) but they are very geared towards competitive analysis for business. What would you recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 03:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cycling and swimming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 03:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The figure is [actually 79% and is comes from a survey conducted by HP](http://www.coindesk.com/hp-survey-79-us-organisations-plan-adopt-digital-currencies/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This may help clear up the confusion](http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/2mnnwy/official_world_bank_report_bitcoin_is_not_a_ponzi/cm5wsbc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll just leave this here](http://insidebitcoins.com/news/world-bank-report-bitcoin-is-not-a-ponzi-scheme/24346) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they do this? It shouldn't make any difference to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 11:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different projects. Not to be confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 02:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 01:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's road you're looking for you might want to try one of La Bicicletta's Tuesday night Stanley Park rides to meet some people and help find your cohort. Another option would be to search for some people of comparable ability on Strava and ask to ride with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Torres del Paine, Patagonia [OC] [3000x2220] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 21:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 00:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank had a good point. We need our own beer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monte Fitz Roy, Patagonia [OC] [2360x3200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 00:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lago Argentina, Patagonia [OC] [3000x2220] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 00:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monte Fitz Roy, Patagonia [2368x3200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 17:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 13:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run it as the default browser, with adblock and ghostery, on both my N5 and N7. Works awesome. Great work, Mozilla! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 13:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are an amazing experience that I actively encourage anyone who isn't at risk of psychotic episodes to try at least once. I encouraged my 70 year old father to do his first this spring and he thought it was amazing and now has a regular practice and plans to do another every year. My mother does her first this next March and I'm anxious to hear how it is for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 12:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using an N5 for the past year for running, cycling and hiking. Strava records well for the cycling and running although I've recently switched to a Garmin Forerunner 620. The GPS is great for hiking and I only use Google Maps (even here in Patagonia) and [the camera, shooting in HDR mode is just fine for me](http://i.imgur.com/OvghqHF.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monte Fitz Roy, Patagonia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 11:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 22:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replicas??? That will teach me for not reading the entire article before commenting. Then this really is an blatant propaganda exercise straight out of [Starship Troopers](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jQcUa38KNFo list=PLbK1p7OpuDT3HuW3wR3dM8lnzgXIaseCa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 22:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than giving them to the police like the US is doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 22:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great Britain Pound (Sterling) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 01:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should work as long as there is not a bunch of vegetation blocking the lines of sight. You may look at trying a couple of [OpenMesh](http://www.open-mesh.com/) routers if you're not so into rolling your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may as well not bother using Tor as most of what it does for you will be negated by running Flash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 22:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably shouldn't use the one in your repos - at least not for Debian or Ubuntu. Add the [repos from the project](https://www.torproject.org/docs/debian.html.en) which will you give you the current version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking forward to buying another Coke for 2 bits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 11:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an old fart who's first lesson in inflation was in the early '70s when the price of a pop jumped from $0.20 to $0.25. I still remember being gob-smacked that anyone would have the audacity to charge me the whole of my weekly allowance for a single bottle of Coke.

Now it's been years since I've had a Coke but I am truly looking forward to the day that I can buy another one for 2 bits. When I do I'll be sure to post a selfie of me enjoying that sickly sweet, over-caffeinated action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Merchants And Carriers Are Trying To Block Payment Systems They Can't Track </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 21:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 14:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! I assume this means those of us who refuse to install Java can soon start using I2P? That's always been what prevented me from jumping on board... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 17:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 15:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Snowden only uses it for interviews and other communications intended for public consumption. He would never use it for anything he considered "private". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 22:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just [build your own for cheaper](https://www.adafruit.com/products/1406). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 22:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a static or dynamic IP on your home server? If you have a static you merely need to add an "a name" record that associates your resisted domain with your IP address. You should have no trouble doing that through Go Daddy. If it's a dynamic IP then it's a little more complicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 23:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 13:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't notice this but am running CM11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 21:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been paying 7 employees this way for the past 6 months. None of them are complaining and only thing I've noticed is that the higher their technical computing skill level, the more excited they are to be being paid in Bitcoin - even with the volatility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 15:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could only happen if your wage is denominated in Bitcoin. No one here has stated anything except the obverse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess this means we're officially mainstream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 01:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 23:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt anyone sees darkcoin replacing bitcoin at this point. Complementing sure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. I thoroughly enjoyed that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 18:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've been trying this out and it works quite well. Be great when the group chat is working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 03:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be honest when you fill out the application form and you should be alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 03:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a problem for you to be a reiki practitioner. It's just that they ask you to not do any other spiritual practises (including yoga, martial arts, etc.) during the retreat so that you can see the full effects of what you are being taught.

There were an few incidences about a decade ago of reiki practitioners experiencing psychotic episodes when they combined the two practices which led to this requirement for vipassana retreats.

Personally I always tell people that vipassana retreats are suitable for anyone who isn't at risk of a psychotic breakdown. Just be prepared to not practice any other disciplines for the 10 days of the retreat. It's not too much to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 17:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing more than the fact that there are others that want them. All money is nothing but a story -- the more people who believe the story the more utility a currency has as a medium of exchange. 

To fully appreciate this watch the lectures for the course _[A Brief History of Humankind](https://www.coursera.org/course/humankind)_. Lesson #8 - _"The Direction of History"_ covers the history of barter and how we came to have and use the money that we do. The whole course is highly recommended.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately there's no Qi coil. Deal-breaker for me too :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately there's no Qi coil. Deal-breaker for me too :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on whether you root it or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Internet Of Someone Elses Things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 21:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Internet Of Someone Elses Things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 21:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 18:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might [learn something from Canada here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marc_L%C3%A9pine). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see that dogecoin has a cycling jersey. I would definitely order a "Slaying of Bearwhale" jersey (hint, hint) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polygamy and the question of Bountiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 01:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polygamy and the question of Bountiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 01:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 21:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Or 12.5 cents](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bit_(money) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 17:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time I tried this (a year ago) it wouldn't let me burn directly to a USB. Can't remember why but the solution was to burn it to a CD first, boot that, and then run the install to USB script from within Tails. Hopefully that has been remedied by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 13:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you feel any identification with the punk ethos you might try the [Noah Levine-inspired _Against The Stream_ community](http://www.againstthestream.org/) at 4300 Melrose Ave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 02:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ChickieNobs](http://www.technovelgy.com/ct/content.asp?Bnum=1559). Yum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU-Canada Trade Agreement 'Celebrated', Text Officially Released; Even Worse Than Feared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 17:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for peer access to the EU banking system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 20:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will it let us vote in Estonian national elections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 19:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $266 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it bend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I sold my 2012 N7 to a friend who's in grad school so she could read PDFs on it. She reported just last week that it's still working great for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great project. Keep up the good work. I look forward to building one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thanissaro Bhikkhu](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thanissaro_Bhikkhu) AKA Ajahn Geoff is a major contemporary figure in the Thai Forest Tradition. You can download many of his books and talks for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 02:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to send as many as possible to the women in the [Destiny Reflections project](http://bitcoinvista.com/2014/09/02/canadian-university-bitcoin-donations-ease-pain-of-human-trafficking/) to use for life-blogging and bitcoin wallets.

They don't need to be the latest-greatest so these would be perfect. I've looked into the cheap new FireFoxOS phones but they aren't quite ready to do what I want to do. I would install CM11 and the necessary software and then ship them over to [Lauren and Laurie](http://www.coindesk.com/simon-fraser-first-canadian-university-accept-bitcoin-donations/) to hand out to the women they are working with.

_(NB: I was one of the people who donated to this project)_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 21:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you going to share the recipe for building your own like the [OnionPi project](https://learn.adafruit.com/onion-pi/overview) does? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the price, off contract, rumoured to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 06:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not scifi but Ghost Dog is a great watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 19:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just make coffee in a plunger pot and save yourself considerable $. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 18:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually that means removing access to their mother's milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately that would contradict the "support has ended" part. However [this solution](https://www.reddit.com/r/Ubuntu/comments/2hh7h4/a_new_bash_security_update_for_ubuntu_is_out/ckt3c0a) (given below) should work for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simon Fraser University embraces Bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simon Fraser University embraces Bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simon Fraser University embraces Bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simon Fraser University embraces Bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic. Give it a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 00:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but you're going to have to cite the study.

Just which school of media do you subscribe to if I may ask? Have you ever seen a press release get picked up that didn't include contact information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 21:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually providing their contact information does make them a whole lot more believable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe in censorship based upon writing ability. In addition the blog author provides his mailing address, phone number as well as a contact email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 18:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related: http://www.cbc.ca/news/world/american-shakedown-police-won-t-charge-you-but-they-ll-grab-your-money-1.2760736 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada Warns its Citizens Not to Take Cash to USA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 18:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 17:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a good fit for [PeaceGeeks](http://peacegeeks.org), a Vancouver-based charity that provides tech solutions to organizations working on human rights issues in conflict-affected areas of the world. They work primarily with Drupal though but your CSS skills would be greatly appreciated. The also provide all the ongoing maintenance and hosting so you wouldn't be locked into providing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great startup idea involving bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 18:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a week ago I spoke about the need for development of digital currency services in the B2B space. Today there is a very interesting idea being explored in /r/bitcoin that interested entrepreneurs should take a look at.

https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/2hb6fn/to_get_to_the_moon_bitcoin_must_find_a_use_case/ckr34rw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least in the Canadian context (where I am) it makes a lots of sense as we have a constitutional clause for gender equality. Thus (the argument goes) we can use this to mandate improvements for cyclists if we can demonstrate that current urban design policies unfairly disadvantage women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 19:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do it on a bootable thumbdrive? Don't you develop locally on a (L/W/M)AMP stack? Why not just run them from there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 21 Photos of Women Who Shatter the Stereotype of What a Real Biker Looks Like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goatse. Same as the clear web. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please provide your informed and cited rebuttal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 01:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a constitutional lawyer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 01:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much expertise do you need to note that Canada's constitution can now be over-ridden by a trade agreement for the next 31 years? It's either true or it's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's New Investment Agreement With China Will Take Precedence Over Canadian Constitution for 31 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 22:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's New Investment Agreement With China Will Take Precedence Over Canadian Constitution for 31 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 22:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider every bit of carbon fibre I ride on to be a personal contribution to carbon sequestration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghana goes green with bamboo bikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 00:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 05:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was [demonstrated just last month](http://www.thenewamerican.com/tech/item/18928-snoops-could-hack-smartphone-gyros-to-record-ambient-conversation). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 05:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes the 910 better than the 620? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 03:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't a joke to Robelus! They must have a hate-on for the CRTC right now over that forced change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 03:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not too bad of a landscape stand either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poetic Slimline + a neoprene zip-case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I challenge Reddit to hold Bitcoin and use it to pay employees and suppliers rather than converting immediately to fiat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the CRTC forced the big 3 to drop their roaming charges last month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you don't have roaming setup properly. Try switching your settings to 2G when you are in these areas. That should kick you straight over to "Wind Away" ( ie. roaming) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 03:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree that it's a necessary stepping stone. All I'm advocating is for us to start concentrating on the next step. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 01:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If were going to make UWW into a hero of the digital currency community we should at least get them to commit to holding Bitcoin and using them for payments within their own organization's internal operations. I'm for one am tired of another "so and so is now accepting Bitcoin" when all it means is they are taking it and converting it to fiat. We need to to start upping our game and only making a big deal when they are doing more than just that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 03:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a great service. Does anyone know if there's anything like that in India? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 03:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's not that brainwallet. It was the name given to an HTML5 wallet app for FFOS that I tried out. It looks like it's since been removed from the market as it was developed just as a proof of concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to know this. I've played with the Flame (official Dev phone) and it scans QR codes just fine - better than my GNex ever did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are currently 2 - proxywallet and brainwallet. They are virtually identical, right down to a lack of support for scanning QR codes. Other than that they are perfectly capable of receiving, storing and sending Bitcoin (with the nasty caveat that you have to *manually* enter the address that you are sending to). I don't know how FFOS registers mime-types but clicking on BITCOIN:// URLs was a bust too. So... there is some progress but it needs some more work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _"The internet?! Is that thing still around?"_ - Homer Simpson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planet earth vs. roads: The epic conflict that will define the future of the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 17:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 05:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second that. Booked several international flights and only had to provide a first and last name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 05:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good! Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't full nodes learn about each other through IRC channels on Freenode anymore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Future According to Stanisaw Lem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 03:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 17:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about it a but more I think there is a significant opportunity to develop enterprise spending tools involving multi-sig. By that I mean tools that would allow employees to initiate transactions that would then need to be approved via another key. This is a key function in large organizations to manage expenditures. Run with it! ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 15:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admit to not being familiar with the B2B space so haven't given it much thought beyond a realisation for the need. Since most in the digital currency space are familiar with its advantages I guess we could start by looking into how B2B international banking, escrow, etc. currently happens and look for entrepreneurial opportunities there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 04:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a crowdfunding platform that supports bitcoin, litecoin,   darkcoin as well as PayPal and offline payments. The money that has flowed through so far is led by offline payments followed by PayPal, then Bitcoin, Litecoin, with Darkcoin last. I'm a pragmatist about this and realise that a lot of people use PayPal and that Bitcoin isn't going to take over overnight. Remember I've been here since 2010. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 19:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see a breakdown of how many campaigns there are like yours that come nowhere close to their goal. You may consider fund-raising with a platform like [dana.io](https://dana.io) next time that flows money straight through to you and let's you set the percentage you wish to pay to use the platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 19:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I'm super bullish on bitcoin and have been since I came across it in 2010. I have a start-up that includes bitcoin support and have invested some of my bitcoin 'winnings' into other start-ups in the digital currency space.

Concerns around security and ease of use are being addressed rapidly (eg. Circle, BitPay, Coinbase, etc.)

I think the area that needs the most attention right now is the development of B2B services. The ball is already rolling nicely with retailers accepting it (eg. Dell, Cheapair, Expedia, Overstock, NewEgg, etc.) however each purchase made through those services results in downward pressure on the price of bitcoin since all of those are cashing out to fiat right away. 

The entrepreneurial space needs to begin focussing on developing services that encourage companies to hold bitcoin and to pay their employees and suppliers directly in bitcoin.

In case it's not obvious by now I am a digital currency 'true believer' - ie. I think that state-issued and controlled fiat is a lower rung on the evolutionary ladder of currency/payment technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't just mis-type addresses. Bitcoin addresses have considerable checksum error correction built in. However... it is prudent to send a micro transaction first and receive confirmation from the recipient before sending the balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 16:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central banks have to challenge bitcoin's supply in-elasticity for simple existential reasons. Nothing to see here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 07:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could also have been a pure gift economy. Where is the evidence that it was credit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reason #2113 to go all-in on digital currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 19:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you just setup a free WordPress or Tumblr site to look like a campaign? Or, if you have a few tech chops you could try [CrowdTilt Open](https://open.tilt.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 18:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great converstation to be having. Now that B2C adoption is well underway entrepreneurs in this space should be starting to look at closing the loop so that bitcoins are held and used to pay suppliers rather than being immediately cashed out for fiat like most of the B2C adoptees are currently doing.

Maybe we could brainstorm a little here on ways to get current adoptees (seems one of the best places to start) to pursue this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 02:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cheapair](http://cheapair.com) accepts bitcoin. Booked a few flights already. Awesome service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah... they're just gonna buy Circle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Terraforming Venus Be The Solution To Population Growth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 19:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
