<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1922</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 07:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust wikipedia about Islam.  Why not just listen to her and find out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 03:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if he runs with Jill Stien as Pres   Vice-pres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 03:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the suspect was labeled a terrorist, this would be front page news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 relatives shot in head in Ohio as 3 children survive; killer thought to be loose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 03:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 20:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you learn about it, the less scarier it is.

[What does Sharia law mean?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2ga1b4/serious_muslims_of_reddit_what_exactly_does/ckh5gia) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 03:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the person who asked the question deleted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 03:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wiz Khalifa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link.

 Alas, our simple Muslim brethren! Now what are the obligations  your, mine and that of every Muslim? What does our honour demand? It demands at least to have faith in the truth of Islamic Shariats decree on this issue, viz., capital punishment for an apostate and dualist-infidel. But it is up to the Government to respond to the Shariats call. However, this much is within our reach that we cut off all social connections with them and dont let them enter our gatherings and face them boldly everywhere.

 There is a lot of things you can call capital punishment for but I was looking for text that explicitly tells Muslims to go out and kill ahmadis which is what one article seems to suggest. This just says to cut off social connections from them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islam: The Religion Of Truth - Abdur Raheem Green </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 14:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why is it so difficult for you to understand that Ahmadi Muslims are under threat and certain Muslims want to kill them and wouldn't bat an eye while doing it?

When did i deny this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 05:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only seen leaflets exposing the group, but not any leaflet that says they should be killed. Even the articles don't appear to show it.  Did anyone else find it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you think every Muslim is going to be fine with that? You think there won't be some Muslim groups who think that your theoretical government is preventing true Islamic laws to manifest in the land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The topic was deleted. I believe this was the deleted passage:

 : (      :   ).
[  338/5]
Al-Qurtub said:
And if the Muslim meets the kfir, who has no covenant, it is permissible to kill him
[Tafsr al-Qurtub 338/5]

  : (               [   6/2]
Ibn Kathr said:
Ibn Jarr mentioned an ijm that it is permissible to kill a kffir if he has no covenant
[Tafsr ibn Kathr 6/2]

  : (        :        ) [  259/9]
Imm al-Nawaw said:
As for the kuffr who have no covenant and no safety, then it is permissible to kill him, whatever religion he is upon
[Rawdat Al-Tlibn 259/9]

  : (      -     -      ) [263/8]
Ibn Muflih said:
And the killing of a kffir does not require any atonement, because his blood is a permissible as that of a pig
[Al-Mubdi 263/8]

  : (              ). [ 264/1]
Imm Shfi' said:
Allah Tabraka Wa Ta'al made the kfirs blood permissible unless he pays jizyah or is given a covenant of safety by the Muslims for a certain amount of time
[Kitb Al-Um 264/1]

 : (             ). [ 522/4]
Al-Shawkn said:
As for the kuffr, the general ruling on their blood is permissibility as shown in the verse of the sword, so what about the one who fights in war?
[Al-Sayl Al-Jarr 522/4]

      -  -: (     :  !).   .
Al-Farq Umar said to Ab Jandal, may Allah be please with them:
Verily, they are mushrikn (polytheists), and the blood of one of them is the blood of a dog
[Narrated by Imm Ahmed   Al-Bayhaq]
 : (                ) [ 120/10]
Al-Sarkhas said:
There is nothing wrong with a person who killed murtadn before inviting them to Islam because they are kuffr and the da'wah of Islam has reached them
[al-Mabst 120/10]

 : (     :     ). [  369/4]
Al-Shawkn said:
And the mushrik, whether he fights or not, is permissible to kill as long as he is a mushrik
[Al-Sayl Al-Jarr 369/4]

 : ( :       :       ). [  101/7]
Al-Ksn said:
The general ruling is that all those who are from Ahlul Qitl (the people of fighting is the kuffar), it is hall to kill them, whether they fought or not
[Bad'i Al-San'i 101/7]

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logical1ty's response to "the killing of a kffir does not require any atonement, because his blood is a permissible as that of a pig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Saudi Arabia forces its own brand of Islam, so yes it is.

Well you have to pick one "brand". No matter how you look at it, there will always be  people who are displeased with the government, those in authority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Islam is suppressed in Muslim countries, that is why you get instability.

Do you consider Islam to be suppressed in Saudi Arabia? And what do you suppose we do about countries where Islam is suppressed.

 Algeria, Egypt, Pakistan, Turkey, are all places where Islam has been suppressed during different times. Egypt, Algeria, and Turkey had coups because of that very reason.

I think that was only part of the reason why the uprisings occurred. And it's not like those countries are doing much better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, they tagged your topic too: 

https://www.reddit.com/r/ahmadiyya/comments/4dpzlo/and_it_begins_the_day_it_is_revealed_that_asad/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We can start off with getting rid of the idiots in power in Muslim countries to begin with.

That can be very dangerous. Look at where the recent uprisings in Muslim countries have got us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 06:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shahid Kamal has a lot of other good videos on YouTube about leaving Ahmadiyya. [His website here](http://thecult.info/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 16:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He was recently on the news about a Islamic conference](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wnkmijVg3cg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $160 billion Pfizer, Allergan inversion scrapped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Came to Islam - Abdur-Raheem Green </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian Ex-Gangster Accepts Islam | WhyIslam FIFA Highlights #9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 03:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 00:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [story](http://www.cnn.com/2016/04/03/europe/uk-kids-human-arrow/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panama Papers: Fifa ethics lawyer Juan Pedro Damiani under internal investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 22:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that Ahmaidyya's Prophet Mirza Ghulam Ahmad himself declared that anyone who rejected him is not a Muslim, right?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say Ahmadi's aren't Muslim in this topic. I said their beliefs, like believing in the false prophet Ghulam Ahmad, is against Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I find it hilarious that people will say ISIS are Muslims here

No one in this sub supports Isis's extremist actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shia's don't post here articles that go against mainstream beliefs.  And just like every other ahmadiyya article, this discusses Ahmadi beliefs in their prophet, Mirza Ghulam Ahmad, bringing the "peaceful version of Islam"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong subreddit.  Post it to /r/ahmadiyyat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Beauty of Allah's Creation - Shaykh Hamza Yusuf | Beautiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 01:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A more in-depth video about how ISIS gained support in Iraq and Syria.](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/frontline/film/rise-of-isis/) The point is that these radical groups start because of the context they are in. If you don't want to take the time to understand their history and just label it as "Islamic terrorism" then you won't understand how new groups can be formed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The attack in Brussels looks like it was ISIS-related. People forget the context which allowed ISIS to arise, so here is a short video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Browsing reddit in the last 24 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 02:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Crisis of ISIS: A Prophetic Prediction | Sermon by Hamza Yusuf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 01:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Even if it is a mistake in interpretation by a lunatic (or many groups of lunatics), a perfect text would acknowledge and account for this risk. That's if it's a mistake, these radical Islamist groups seem to have no trouble finding Surah and Hadith that unambiguously justify their actions. What's so hard to get about this?


I've researched a lot about terrorist groups and i can tell you that it's not as simple as "the religion says we should do it, therefore we should do it", there is almost always a large political motivating factor as well, but i don't want to go into yet another side topic and talk about terrorism now. 

I don't agree with your opinion however, that a religious scripture (or any text at all) should be blamed because of someone's misinterpretation. You can misinterpret even the most simplest sentences. I can interpret your comment as a physical threat to me and call the FBI and tell them you want me dead.  You however will not be charged with a crime, because my misinterpretation alone does not put you at fault. 

 Alright, let's ignore new issues, 

lol then please stop bringing up new issues like the narration about killing apostates which Muslims don't consider authentic anyway. It just makes me question your intention and where you learned about Islam. I ignored the rest of your comment which lead into tangents.

 It is dishonest to make somebody believe something that isn't true. You can make someone believe something that isn't true by saying something untrue- let's call that a lie.

Let me clarify further: A lie is **saying something untrue**.
For example, if i pretend like i'm struggling trying to carry a box and throw it to my friend, when it's actually just a empty box. I did not lie, unless if i were to verbally mention that "the box is heavy". You could say that i "mislead" my friend or i "tricked" my friend.  Or even "deceived" my friend, (although personally i use the word "deceive" if you are intending to cause harm).  Can you give an example related to the original context (New Muslim convert) that fits under the definition of a lie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 00:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sounds like it's already a moot point. So claiming to be of any religion is pretty pointless, as it's basically meaningless?

I gave you a clear example twice already. Someone can claim to be of a religion (Muslim, Christian, Jew, etc) and we can accept them as such, but that doesn't mean all their actions are favored by their own religion. What's so hard to get about this? 


 What the translation 'literally' says (barring that there's something lost in translation, which is possible) is that 'those different from you' are universally described as having 'hatred already appeared from their mouths.'

No it doesn't. No Muslim i know would ever make a silly mistake like that. If you started from the beginning of the Quran and sequentially when upto chapter 3:118, then you should know that that's not how the Quran describes those who aren't Muslims. Not even close.

 By which you mean, read it after growing up in a culture shaped by it and having your sense of community and belonging depend on your accepting it?

Everyone has to watch out for being biased. What religion did you grow up in?

 Soooooooo.... it's only perfect if you're trying to convince yourself it's perfect?

I basically said the opposite; that you should NOT hold biases like this.  And you continue to misinterpret not only the Quran, but most of what i said throughout this entire conversation. The fact that it took me nearly 10 responses to explain to you how /r/islam wasn't "*explicitly condoning lying about religion*" says a lot, and i'm still not sure if you accepted your mistake on that issue. Also i  don't see why you keep bringing up new issues when you can't agree with what i said before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I appreciate your sentiment, but you basically just said that every Islamic terrorist group counts as being Islamic.

I was trying to explain that there is a difference between Islam and Muslim.  Muslims can do actions that are against Islam, just like Christians can do actions that are against the teachings of Christianity. Being a Muslim doesn't mean that all of your actions will be Islamic. I can consider someone a Muslim if they say the declaration faith, but that doesn't necessarily mean that doesn't i accept their actions or say that all their actions are Islamic. 

 It's easy to say that 3;118 only counts for people whom "hatred has already appeared from their mouths,"

Because that's literally what the translation says.  As mentioned earlier, any sentence in any language can be misinterpreted or misunderstood. You're basically questioning the essence of communication   language. Or are you asking why can't God just said us revelation that we could all understand without effort? Or even better, why can't God just make us all believe in Him? If He wanted to, He could have made us all accept Him but this is not part of God's plan.

I would say that a good portion of the Quran, especially the main themes of the Quran, are clear. But if you want to understand the Quran, then you have to be sincere and fair with yourself. And put aside any preconceived notions or any bias prejudices you may have while you read. It helps to understand the Quran if you read in sequential order, (even better would be to read in the original language), and if you have trouble, you can ask someone more knowledgeable for clarification or check a commentary of the Quran.  If you are reading the Quran with the intent of finding flaws and mistakes, then that's what you will likely see in the Quran, (the same can be said about reading any book). You need to come with the proper intent/purpose. So why are you interested in reading the Quran? What do you hope to get out of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   But, there is a difference between someone believing something false about you as a result of miscommunication or innocent assumption, and believing something false about you because you're intentionally trying to make them believe something false about you- that's the line between misunderstanding and dishonesty.

But since you can never know the other person's intention, you can never know for sure if a person is intentionally trying to make you believe something false or if it's just a misunderstanding. I could assume you're lying and there would be no way for you to prove to me that you weren't anymore. You could try to explain, but i could always assume that to be lie too or just part of another lie. That's not even how we typically use the word "lie" in common vernacular today.

 Creating a false belief in others without actually speaking a falsehood is just something really skillful liars do to protect themselves while still deceiving.

They aren't lying if they aren't speaking falsehoods. And i wouldn't say it's creating false beliefs in others, it's more like ignoring to answer questions or changing the subject. Like if someone asked me if i was a Muslim, and i chose to not answer. Then that's not a lie, regardless of the other person's interpretation, and regardless of me wanting to keep it a secret.

 "Just be quiet and you'll be safe." That attitude is the brick and mortar of tyrants. Or, would you argue that Islamic theocracies never abuse the power they get from forbidding criticism? 

I would say it's allowed to talk in private but usually just public declaration of blasphemous speech is forbidden. And yes, of course  there are some Muslims who have abused this rule and forbid any criticism or hurt people unjustly. Muslims should be open to intellectual criticism, IMO.

 Honestly, I'm in favor of prison reform, and I think public lashing needs more consideration as an alternative to incarceration.

Some countries like Turkey do go with the prison route instead.

 Okay, this is gonna sound pretty meta, but... how can you tell if you're a Muslim? Any discussion of Islam's problems will prompt a chorus of how the offending party is "not really Muslim," which proves that it's possible to follow Islam and believe the teachings and consider yourself Muslim and yet you are "not really Muslim."

It's not really about who is or isn't Muslim, it's about what actions are and aren't Islamic. For some reason many people believe that if someone is a Muslim, then all of their actions must be Islamic, which is not true. The average Christian commits many sins according to their own religion and even Christian priests make mistakes, sometimes big ones, so why assume Muslims are all perfect in their religion? If someone says they are Muslim, than i'll accept them as a Muslim by default.

  Quran 3;118 seems pretty clear in saying that "real Muslims" aren't allowed to have kaffir friends, so a non-Muslim pretending to be Muslim around Muslims is about as Muslim pretending to be non-Muslim with his non-Muslim friends. After all, you can never know for sure what their real intention was.

Of course we can have friends who are non-Muslims, we can even marry certain non-Muslims. I don't know of any notable Muslim scholar who has said that we cant be friends with non-Muslims. 3:118 is talking about not being intimate with those whom "hatred has already appeared from their mouths", more can be said from this from the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nursery 'raised fears of radicalisation' over boy's cucumber drawing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 17:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nursery 'raised fears of radicalisation' over boy's cucumber drawing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 17:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like they're actually sending books like "Wahhabism 101" or "how to be Wahabi Muslim". It's probably just books referencing Quran and hadith.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You could, although it would be the result of innocent misunderstanding, as I have not been intentionally convincing you to have an untrue belief, whether by speech or lack thereof.

Well that's part of the problem. I could assume you're lying and you could say it was never your intention. But i can never know for sure what your real intentions was. I could also assume that you lied about your "real attention".  

 Cool! I just got my first Kindle, this'll be a great way to try it out!
Thanks for taking the time to speak with me, this is very informative!

Glad to hear it, i hope you get something out of it.

 Afterthought; Are you allowed to lie about not being Muslim? I know many Islamic countries have a death penalty for apostasy, so if you were raised in Islam and stopped believing, you could die if anyone found out.

The death penalty that happens today is exaggerated IMO. True, certain Muslims countries say they have the death penalty for apostasy but it's actually more about freedom of speech than disbelieving. You are not allowed to say blasphemous speech in public, like saying "Islam is wrong/evil", etc. I've been to a couple of Muslim countries, and i can tell you that there are many people there including Saudi Arabia, that don't believe in Islam, but they won't be executed or face any punishment or anything. Unless they were to, for example, make a public rant on the internet about how bad Islam is or something. Then they might be flogged or lashed, but even that may not always be as harsh as it sounds. [Public lashing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dYS_nduLkdU).

  If you're allowed to lie about being Muslim for your own safety, is the reverse true?

It would be irrelevant, since you already aren't a Muslim, why would the rules of Islam matter to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Somali Child Sex Trafficking Ring That Wasnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 23:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Khalid Yasin is NOT talking about isis. That's why i said to talk about general rules and not real world, because he isn't talking about any Muslim group attacking. ISIS didn't even establish their caliphate until after this speech was made...

Muslims =/= ISIS. ISIS is just one Muslim group that is fighting other Muslim groups. Why are you putting all Muslims together with ISIS? Why not put all the Muslims together with any of the Muslim groups ISIS is fighting against? Either case would be wrong.  It's like me lumping all Christians together with the Army of God (Christian group which uses violence to fight abortion).

 Generalizations only work until it comes to the real world and you learn that generalizations don't work.

General rules do work but only when you apply them properly.

 Perhaps Yasin doesn't understand the broadness of what he is conveying to all these people, however if just one person in the audience took what he is saying as a green light to attack the USA or Germany or the UK it is one too many.

It's not the speaker's fault for your misinterpretation.  It's like me interpreting your comment to mean that it's fine to attack Muslims, but it's never fine for Muslims to fight back. That would be really messed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 05:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter if a group is identified as a country or a nation or whatever.  If group A attacks group B, why would it be bad for group B to fight back against group A? Try to put aside any real world example and first look at things generally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If someone were to believe a western country was at war with Muslims ( which they are) this may be enough to have people take up arms against them.

If country A attacks country B, why is bad for country B to fight back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 18:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He brought up European countries to point out that they go much further in warfare than Muslims did in their history.  He then says that Muhammad (pbuh) would never go past the limits, boundaries and only fight the people who were at war with him. 

 Perhaps I am misinterpreting, but if I am misinterpreting there are bound to be many others that also do.


His answer was sloppy, but he didn't say anything close to  attacking Western nations. I'm not sure how you interpreted the video that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 14:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What bothers you about this clip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 04:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that you should go through the life of Muhammad (pbuh) in context.  Every nation that goes to war engages in similar war tactics because these acts are necessary to win wars.  America just recently destroyed 500 million cash reserves and several kilograms of gold stored by ISIS. I don't think anyone that is against ISIS would complain about that, so why are Muslims blamed when they do something similar in war?  Khalid Yasin's answer is a bit over the place, but that's essentially what he's saying in this clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 04:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i gave you a dictionary definition of lying. If you define "lie" to mean something else, then go ahead. But Islam does not permit lying according to the definition i gave ("saying something incorrect").  So if someone were to ask me if i was a Muslim and i don't respond, then that's not a lie using the definition i gave. 

The problem with your definition is that it leads to interpretive problems (which i think you hate). If i assume your a Christian this whole time, and you are an atheist, then i can claim that you lied to me. You deceived me by not being open to me about your lack of faith. You could claim that you weren't trying to act Christian, but i could claim the opposite and there is no objective measure that we both could agree on to always determine who in fact is right here.

 Can you recommend some? From what I've seen, most of Islamic history is an expansion of conquest and subjugation that makes the British Empire look like the Salvation Army.

More like the opposite. Here's a highly recommended biography:
http://www.amazon.com/Muhammad-Life-Based-Earliest-Sources/dp/1594771537 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Lying_by_omission


http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/lie


Lying is a false statement made with deliberate intent to deceive; an intentional untruth; a falsehood, for simplicity i would consider it a "false statement". Choosing not to talk about a subject is NOT lying about it.  You don't have to "lie by omission", you just don't have to talk about it. Also, "lying by omission" is not necessarily a lie depending on the example.   

 I know almost no Islamic history

And you've already made plenty of wrong assumptions. I suggest learning from Islamic sources if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A lot of the cheering muslim pieces of shit were in Patterson, NJ. If u don't believe me, go look up the news reports and video footage yourself. 

Where is the proof that there were "thousands of cheering Muslims" in New Jersey? I can't find it anywhere.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 20:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There may have been some people who really hate American's foreign policy so much that they might have been happy at the news. But Donald Trump's claim about how there were thousands of Muslims cheering in New Jersey is completely ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 02:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could just visit their subreddit to see their content... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Aren't you sick and tired to see that Muslims keep telling us

lol then why do you keep visiting /r/islam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 00:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because he isn't a Muslim. He could interpret it differently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a reminder.

edit: Muslims perform a funeral prayer with the body present sometimes at the mosque, whenever a Muslim dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 02:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for asking a tough question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 00:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're allowed to define it how you like, but a lie of omission is still a lie.

So if i don't talk about a subject, i'm considered to be lying about it? That's not correct. 

 Yes, Medina became muslim for purely commercial reasons, 

That's not true. Where did you learn Islamic history from? And it's not like they declared war with the people of Mecca without any reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 00:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What does it matter to you what Non-Muslims think about Muslims? 

I'm interested because the topic is about Islam and i'm interested in Islam. Why are you interested? Are you going to avoid my question again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 14:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it matter to you what other Muslims say about Islam in their own sub? Are you still interested in the religion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 13:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't crosspost to this sub. I post in both subs without brigading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 02:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could, you know, not crosspost yourself. Unless this is also an issue that's stopping you from converting to Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 05:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that keeping something private is very different than lying about it.

 Are there any countries ruled by Islamic theocracy where Islam was NOT introduced by military force?

A lot of modern Muslim countries were shaped in the last 2 centuries after invasions of foreign powers. The very first state established by Muslims 1400 years ago was without military force.

 Why not some shimmering scroll of platinum, marked with God's script that taps into the psyche of every human that looks at it, making it legible to all who read it?

What exactly would that look like? Don't you think that would be criticized too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refugees weep as they are welcomed in Germany by mob shouting 'go home' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 20:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Given the low threshold by which muslims in western nations will claim persecution, that's basically saying they'll lie whenever.

lol, you're trying to hard to avoid the fact that you were wrong. Ironically you're the one lying here. 
You said *"most of the people in the thread were explicitly condoning lying about religion for convenience"*. Cmon, you should be able to admit that you were wrong here, I mean you can check the topic again for yourself when the proof is right in that topic.  I only see 2 comments that mention lying, one which mentioned "significant persecution" and the other mentioned "Moors during the Spanish Inquisition".  Yes, sometimes Muslims do go through severe persecution for their beliefs. It happens.  We don't know what OP's situation exactly is. Please be honest and fair.


 there's nothing in the Ayah about what they 'really believe,' only what they say. 

In the Arabic, Inna (Indeed) is used to emphasize something for confirmation. And it wouldn't make sense to refer to Muslims as "shaitain".
I just found out that another Muslim corrected you on these same verses and said basically the same thing as me. It's very clear from the Arabic, and even the English translation with context, that it's talking about people pretending to be Muslims, and not the other way around.

 A perfect text can be translated without needing to interpret it or make assumptions about what the author intended to say.

This is the issue with any language or with any text. Any sentence can be interpreted differently. 

I apologize if i sound harsh, but your points are not correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this is why you should research how a charity organization helps people before giving them money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 05:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then how about editing your post.

edit: that's better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 04:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such a terrible post. You're basically opening the door to backbiting here, you even mentioned two scholars by name... seriously?  Every Muslim, including scholars have faults, but there is a better way to address it publicly like this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody declared him as a prophet. Someone asked a question about Buddha, and practically all the answers said "we don't know". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 20:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mistake. Those verses (and 2:14 in particular) are only talking about **non-Muslims pretending to be Muslims**, not the other way around.

Sorry about the typo. The verse wouldn't make sense if it was talking about Muslims pretending to be non-Muslims, because it talks about how they (non-Muslims pretending to be Muslims) go back to their own group of evil ones, and then they admit what they really believe.

 The majority of /r/islam begs to differ

Proof? No one in that topic was condoning lying, except for the few comments that said it's okay during persecution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 16:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The verse explicitly talks about pretending to be the same as those who you are with, muslim or non-muslim. 

No, those verses are only talking about ~~Muslims pretending to be non-Muslims~~ non-Muslims pretending to be Muslims, not the other way around.   *but when they are alone with their evil ones, they say: "We are really with you: We (were) only jesting."* - this is talking about the hypocrites pretending to be Muslims. When they go back to their own group of  evil ones, they admit what they really believe.  It doesn't make sense if it was the other way around.

The Muslim community that is being addressed can be divided into two: those who believe, and those who are pretending to believe, the latter being discussed here. Also like i said, Islam doesn't allow lying so you can't lie and say that you don't believe (except for in rare circumstances like persecution according to some scholars). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! How did you know so much about me from one post?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 01:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always check the topic for yourself to see that i'm telling the truth. It's better than responding with an ad hominem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 19:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  most of the people in the thread were explicitly condoning lying about religion for convenience.

That's not true. The top 6 answers in that topic weren't condoning lying.  I only saw two comments that allowed lying, but they mention that this is the case for persecution. 

 it says 'claiming to be muslim around muslims

If you read the rest of the verses in that context, this is about the hypocrites.  They claim to believe but they don't actually believe. Are we agreeing on this? I'm not sure what you don't understand from these verses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 17:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any actual statistics that say Muslim men are responsible for 91% of child rape in UK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 17:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you were wrong. The verses you quoted are about hypocrites claiming to be Muslims but don't actually believe. That person was talking about whether or not to reveal to anyone whether or not he was a Muslim. Islam doesn't permit lying, but you don't have to expose yourself being a Muslim if there is fear or concern. (Some scholars may also permit lying, if there is fear of significant persecution and no other alternative). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 22:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could ignore them. Some of them aren't really ex-muslims, and a lot of ex-muslims that are there are young and expressing their frustration they have experienced with their families and Muslim community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astronomer here!  A lot of ELI5 requests on gravitational waves, and what this means.

Gravitational waves were predicted by Einstein to explain how two things millions of miles apart can be aware of each other (think, why the Earth goes around the sun).  Basically, it is a ripple in the fabric of space-time itself that everything with mass gives out, and bigger things give off bigger ripples.  These ripples are predicted to travel at the speed of light- so, to go back to the Earth-Sun example, if the Sun disappeared this second you would have a 7 minute delay where the Earth would keep going on its orbit *as if* the Sun were still there.

Now, LIGO.  These guys did an amazing experiment where they basically had two stations, one in Louisiana and one in Washington State, where you're basically shooting a laser down a several mile long tunnel in a hope to see a ripple as a gravitational wave passed through.  This is *insanely* precise work- as in, as precise as a human hair's diameter *over three light years from Earth*.  What's more, this is only sensitive right now to the biggest, strongest gravitational wave signatures right now, such as black hole mergers- so we are not detecting planets with this anytime soon for example- but hey, gotta start somewhere!

Finally, I can't emphasize how *huge* this is!  We are literally going into a new era of astronomy right now, and I think that's no exaggeration.  Think of it this way, most of astronomy right now has been done with light, ie electromagnetic waves- with some exceptions, like cosmic rays or space missions- but pretty much all astronomy has only been with EM waves.  Now we will literally have a new tool in our toolkit and will likely learn all sorts of new things we won't have even expected.  I can't wait!

[From this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/459bpr/gravitational_waves_from_black_holes_detected/czw4zh1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim grandfather Mushin Ahmed 'beaten to death by Dale Jones near a mosque' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar problem, (i think it's because they updated something with online transactions). But they fixed the problem right away after i sent them a message.  Just send them another email and try explaining the problem again and ask for a refund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 21:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are thousands of recent religious groups, some of them get large like [these groups](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_new_religious_movements), but that's not proof that they are upon the truth. So what made you conclude that the religion you are on is the truth and the right path? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 00:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a Khalifah is enough for you, why does the ahmadiyya community need a PR campaign about "true Islam"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mirza Ghulam Ahmad considers those who reject him as non-Muslims. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 22:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **"God Almighty has conveyed it to me that every person to whom my call is conveyed and who does not accept me is not a Muslim and is accountable to God for his default."**  -This is found in the book *Tadhkirah*; it is the last "revelation" in March 1906.

This passage appeared in the first English edition (published 1976, reprinted 2004), but for some reason it was removed in the second English edition (2009).

[You can see it here in Tadhkirah, Year 2006](http://i.imgur.com/vIl9KEz.jpg)

[But that same passage is removed from Tadhkirah, Year 2009](http://i.imgur.com/fatLI8X.jpg)


You can also find it in the Urdu version:

                                   
([Tadhkirah, p.519](http://www.alislam.org/library/browse/book/Tadhkirah/?l=Urdu#page/519/mode/1up))


[This is further discussed in this forum](http://www.thecult.info/forum/viewtopic.php?f=4 t=496).


-----


[Ahmadiyya sub doesn't believe this](https://www.reddit.com/r/ahmadiyya/comments/4xrtw9/do_you_see_nonahmadi_muslims_sunnis_shiites_etc/?st=itwtrubm sh=86c42d52)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it was a Sunni mosque. The Ahmadiyya community puts money into PR work and they have a good presence in the media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't accept [Mirza Ghulam Ahmad](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mirza_Ghulam_Ahmad) as a prophet. His followers keep spewing the same generic rhetoric, about how they follow "true Islam" and the real peaceful and loving teachings of Islam. They often focus on preaching secular and progressive values as being part of their faith, making it easier for them to proselytize.  What they don't tell you is all the [bizarre and erroneous writings of their prophet](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/1vltgo/some_questions_for_the_ahmadiyya_community/) and how differently they interpret the Quran and hadith from mainstream Muslims.  For a quick explanation, you can watch [this brother's videos on how he left Ahmadiyya.](https://www.reddit.com/r/Qadiani/comments/37ymyc/shahid_kamal_leaves_ahmadiyya_group_and_becomes_a/) I have also studied their religion for myself and reached a similar conclusion.

And if any of them tries the excuse about how we should unite,  keep in mind that the Ahmadi prophet himself said that anyone who rejects him is not a real Muslim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mary, Jesus and the Culture of Character Assassination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 23:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Topic removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 20:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone that didn't get it, this topic was meant as a joke. It played on the misconceived notions some people have about Muslims, particularly about how Muslims are secretly trying to take over and establish 'Sharia Law' in America.  It's also a joke on the "hate Jews" and "hate women" stereotypes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 20:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of us who were supposedly covering up or ignoring the evil actions of migrants, were just waiting for the facts and evidence to rise up before we got our pitchforks. We shouldn't pretend that there hasn't been a anti-immigrant circlejerk here in the last few weeks that was ready to jump on any case against immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 20:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't the fault of the police. The media outlets which spread her story without fact-checking should be held responsible, (along with girl for lying of course). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 teens escape from juvenile residential care facility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is The Washington Post article](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2016/01/29/an-alleged-rape-sparked-tensions-between-russia-and-germany-now-police-say-it-was-fabricated/). 

[Another article](http://www.dw.com/en/prosecutors-conclude-russian-german-teens-rape-allegations-were-false/a-19012239)

Obviously there have been other sexual assault cases, but there was never any proof for this particular case. A 13 year old girl simply claimed that she was raped. Her story was believed and was shown all over the news. But evidence revealed that her story was not accurate and she admitted that she had lied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [already posted](https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/43k357/teenage_girl_made_up_migrant_rape_claim_that/)

edit: topic was removed because it was discussed before [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/43994l/a_13yearold_girl_from_a_russianspeaking_community/?ref=search_posts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **tl;dr**: The girl claimed she had been kidnapped and raped by a group of men who appeared to be Middle Eastern migrants. The story didn't gain traction until it was broadcast by a Russian state television channel.  On the Russian-speaking Internet, news of the outrage soon spread, and the case was taken as a sign that a tolerant attitude to refugees and migrants had created a public safety problem in Germany.  This was followed by public outrage, with protests outside asylum-seekers' homes.  German foreign minister accused Russia of using the case as "propaganda" to inflame domestic tensions about refugees and migrants in Germany.

[WashingtonPost article](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2016/01/29/an-alleged-rape-sparked-tensions-between-russia-and-germany-now-police-say-it-was-fabricated/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenage girl 'made up' migrant rape claim that outraged Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 18:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that in the old days, dogs would often be kept outside the home so there wasn't an issue of cleanliness like there is today with pets. If you go to some other countries, dogs are kept outside and viewed as just another animal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman Catholic Convert to Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 17:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 16:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QW5r47WE1t8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 16:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping a Dog

Whoever would keep a dog for other than hunting, herding or farming will lose a great reward every day. (Bukhari)

The majority of scholars agree that an analogy can be made for all dogs of benefit, such as guarding the house or helping the blind. The ruling according to the majority is that it is haram (forbidden) to keep a dog simply as a pet/companion. (Al-Mawsooah al-Fiqhiyyah)

The Maliki opinion is that the hadith does not indicate prohibition, rather it is makrooh (disliked). There is also a rare opinion from a handful of Malikis that all of the prohibitions on owning a dog were abrogated, and thus keeping a dog as a pet is permissible. (Kifaya al-Talib al-Rabbani)

Perhaps the second hadith on this subject is somehow related to the first.

The angels (of blessings) dont enter homes with statues, drawn pictures of live beings or dogs. (Bukhari/Abu Dawood)

This hadith indicates that for some reason, angels of blessings (not protection or writing deeds) do not like to go into homes with dogs. The hadith seems to support the Maliki ruling of dislike, but still, it is not something a Muslim should do, since it is frowned upon by authentic scripture. For this reason, and God knows best, it is best for a Muslim only to keep a dog for some necessity mentioned in the first hadith. After all, if you must have a pet, you can always get a cat or a fish. That being said, those who insist upon keeping dogs as pets in their house have some  albeit small  support in the classical interpretations; it is not something that is established as a sin based on a clear, explicit text that would make someone a heretic or deviant for breaking the rule while deeming it permissible.

http://www.virtualmosque.com/islam-studies/faqs-and-fatwas/mans-best-friend-the-islamic-view-on-dogs/

Also the dogs the Arabs were familiar with 1400 years ago were wild dogs which are not like the many breeds of domesticated dogs that exist today.  I'm not saying this changes any rulings, but it can help understand how past Muslim scholars viewed the maintenance of dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 13:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read the book, is perennialism philosophy that big of a topic in the book, or is just mentioned a couple of times?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 14:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans are smart. They foiled our plan by somehow figuring out that Obama is a Muslim.  But they'll probably never see it coming when Trump does a 180 and introduces Jizya tax and polygamy to the public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 02:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for it. But be careful of posting this to infidel subreddits, we can't let them know of our takeover plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is afraid that Muslims will publicly support him, so i made him a campaign poster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 02:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 02:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where i found it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Britain a Christian country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Orientalism is used to perpetuate wars in the Middle East </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 14:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Blizzard for the Ages Headed for the East Coast Is Very Much the Real Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 20:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 02:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MEMRI tv, not surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
