<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was made by a man for free. I more than appreciate how he made it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT'RE YOU WEARING IIA?!?

^^^^^ummm ^^^^^khakis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmfaooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mooooooore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/Pippinacious , u/demons_dance_alone , u/iia , u/grindhorse , u/deadnspread , u/manen_lyset , u/Elias_Witherow

Nosleep elite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't let myself pee until I finish a story. 

No matter how bad I need to -.-

Self torture. North Korean style. 

As well as at least trying to find several storylines throughout the day . I pick the best one at the end of the day and write about it.

Sweet potatos are from the devil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a lot without a twist.... Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize for never changing up my writing style, please tell me how to be better. What would you recommend? How did you make your stuff better? I need to get better obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it's completely my pleasure! I love writing for y'all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, that would be too much money to make haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just sooooo much money I do not have lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha seldomly post here lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said it was not horror hahahhaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct fae:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will. Don't worry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorites i have written:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will let you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an android </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time passes quickly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be time soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find you amazing join us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choose now. Time is sparse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will definitely be chosen soon. I can feel it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it. You need to help us if you're chosen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon it will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are Life is Beta and We Need YOU to Join </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Letter of Recruitment From Life is Beta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, most of you havent heard of me, but I work for an organization that has saved your life probably more times than you know. We have all made our sacrifices to work here. 2 weeks ago, I made my biggest sacrifice.

My name is James Green. I am 19 years old and my mother and father passed away in an accident the night before. You know what the most messed up thing about it is? 

I knew about it, but I didnt warn them. No, you cant mess with destiny. Not for something this meaningless to the world. That was a hard lesson for me to learn, but I know I must make those sacrifices to continue working for the organization I love and trust. 

 I work for Life is Beta. 

We prevent catastrophes from happening, but we cannot stop every single death from happening. Thats why I did not tell my parents they were going to die on the way to a housewarming party. Some things are just not worth the time. 

Why am I writing to you guys?  It is because we need your help. What do we need you to do? Well, that varies. You will either be a carrier which is someone that constantly travels around the world (all expenses paid) and stops the disaster from happening. We usually send out 6 to 20 carriers for a single project depending on the workload. 

We also have people like me. We are the tellers.  We hardly ever leave where we live and we only stay in places Grant deems safe. Even though my parents died in a car crash, Grant still recommended I stay there for the time being. It was too risky for me to be seen. 

 We only have 15 tellers in our whole organization and 465 carriers. This used to be enough, but we have lost quite a bit of our people in the last couple of days.

A couple of the tellers, myself included, reported multiple deaths occurring. We couldnt find the source at first, but after Grant dug around he found out that there are other apps. They dont do the same thing as us. Their main focus is to eliminate or brainwash as many people as it could.

They dont keep themselves hidden like we do. We have found 2 apps and 1 device so far [New Eyes] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5y8310/an_app_called_new_eyes_has_taken_over_our_town/), [Time is Money] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ysv07/an_app_called_time_is_money_gives_you_more_than/), and a [childs tablet] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yfatq/my_son_is_seeing_things_i_cant_on_his_new_tablet/). The previous 30 carriers we sent out to counterattack the apps have resulted in utter failure. None of them came back. Half of them became obsessed with finding money through Time is Money and ended up being pieced apart by people we couldnt see. Seven of them worked on the boy that told the future from the tablet and ended up on the news the next day. Their bodies were missing, but their heads were found in front of the local Walmart. The final eight never came back. They were still alive, but whenever we contacted them they all said the same thing. You are not part of this. Do not talk to us. We are part of the next world. 

The thing is I did not see that coming. None of the tellers saw it coming. Grant was silent for a while after that. For the first time, we truly felt hopeless. 

Three days ago a teller was found dead inside of her house. Not a gruesome death. Just a shot through the head, but what disturbed us was the note written in blood on the wall. Life is Beta is dead. Join the New World.

We all moved into the headquarters after that. We were all provided transportation. I cannot give out the location, but if you decide to join you must download the app. It will show you one of two things. A screen that says, Its not Time or an animated version of yourself floating in the middle of your screen. If you get the Its not Time screen dont worry. You will be chosen in due time, but if you get the other screen choose kill. Once you choose kill, you will receive a phone call. Answer it and confirm your location with us. We will send someone out to get you to our headquarters. 

If you choose be killed you will set a target on yourself from our enemies without any sort of support from us. 

We dont have much time left. As I type this out in our headquarters, I have received the alert that 5 carriers and 2 more tellers were found in the eating hall, dead. They had the app New Eyes downloaded. All seven of them were found with knives shoved deep into their stomach and their eyes gouged out. I wish it just stopped there, but my phone has started to buzz nonstop. When I turned on my phone I noticed that nothing was different. While I started to put my phone away I received a text from Grant. I tapped on the message and my phone buzzed before jumping to a screen with me standing in the middle of a field. It was the field I went with my parents all the time. My parents came into the screen and walked up to me. As they got closer to me both of them started to chant, Life is Beta is dead, and so are you. End your life. Be free like us. I saw a shadow out of the corner of my eye.  

It took everything out of me to tear my eyes away, but as soon as I looked towards the shadow it was gone and I was standing alone in my room. I shut the phone off as quickly as I could, but the voices of my parents kept running through my head, and I kept seeing the shadow crawling beside me. I tried talking to Grant about it, but he was holding the shattered remains of his phone. Blood was trickling down from his hands. I tried talking to him again, but he cut me off and blurted out, Give me a fucking second. I need to find this blur. Its following me. I see him. Its because of this fucking app. Right when I opened the text that you sent I saw shit I never wanted to see. I tried talking to him, but he was silent after that.  

This is why we need more members. I know that it comes with risks, but this is to save potentially millions of lives. A lot of us will die, but they need to be stopped. People are dying in our organization as well as everywhere else. We are too weak to stop these invisible killers. We dont know where they came from or how they operate. All we know is that every single second the apps either kill or take over more lives. 

[Click this sentence to join our world] (https://rink.hockeyapp.net/apps/7838945bf88147bd9a945878783855a9/app_versions/2). We have only made the Android version of the app. If you have an Apple device I am sorry. We just don't have the space for you in our headquarters as of right now. 

You must allow third party app downloads to download the apk. If you cant figure out how to download it we do not want [you to join us] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/). 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm sorry, but there is a whole series as well as an extra story that answers more questions, but yeah. let's go with that:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pm me and i would be more than happy to help:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> might wanna hit enter twice after each paragraph.

btw. wrong sub bud :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R/hayongnosleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deleted for being non-horror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday started like any other day. I woke up, took a shower, and got dressed before telling my wife goodbye and headed off to work. 

My wife always thought I worked as a financial consultant. Frankly, I dont think she ever really cared what I did, but that worked out even better for me. You see, I have a unique job. I am a contract killer, but I only deal with suicidal people finish the job. Of course, I make them send me a copy of their id and three photos holding up specific items to prove they are who they are. The job came with two main perks.

1) Job security: I never ran out of clientele. Word spreads. They never knew who I was, but I made it an easy process for the people that needed my services. 

2) A semi-clear conscience: Killing anyone is a terrible thing. Suicide is never the answer, but in my opinion, if someone goes through that much work to kill themselves they are going to find another way anyways. Plus, they have the option of picking when and where their death will take place. I always make sure they have a quick and painless death. 
I had one man to take care of today. His name was Matthew Johnson. His wife left him and took their kids with her. His business was failing. He was down to his last 20k. Matthew couldnt even pay all of his employees by the end of this month. Thats why he contacted me. I charged him the regular rate of 15k. Once I received the payment from him I gave him the call to alert him that he only had 10 minutes to live. I was sitting on a hill about 300 yards away from the entrance to his company. 

Nine minutes later, he walked out. I looked through my scope and aimed at the middle of his head. My phone vibrated, but I ignored it and started to steady my breath. I took a deep breath and squeezed the trigger right as I started to exhale. Matthews body became limp. The back of his head sprayed blood all over the entrance door and he fell over. I took apart my sniper and put it back in my briefcase before running into the woods. I ran the three-mile distance to get to the other side of the woods and towards the shopping mall I parked at. When I got to my car I put my briefcase in my trunk and grabbed the spare t-shirt from the back seat of my car. I quickly changed into the fresh shirt before walking into the mall.

It was about 45 minutes past 12 so I walked into the mall and walked to the food court to pick up some lunch. When I got my medium pizza and large coke I took my seat and checked my business phone. 

It was from a number I recognized the minute I saw it.

It was my wifes phone number.

I opened the message and read the message before dropping the phone on the table. She needed my services. I wanted to text back, but I didnt know how to respond back to

*Hello. My name is Amber Jefferson. I need your help. I dont have anything to live for anymore. My husband has been getting more and more distant with me. My friends have stopped talking to me. Both of my parents are dead. I was fired from my job, and I do not have any reason to keep living.*

After thinking while I finished my pizza I decided to text her back. I asked, Can you send me a photo of your id? Three minutes later, I received a photo of her id from her number. 

After I checked the id I sent her another text asking, Can you send me 3 separate photos. The first one of you holding a can of Mello Yello, the next photo of you holding a bag of sour cream and onion flavored sunflower seeds and the last photo of you and your husband.   

I received two photos from you within 7 minutes. After I received the photo of her holding a can of Mello Yello and a bag of Sour Cream and Onion Sunflower seeds she sent me a message saying that she would be able to send me the last photo tonight. 

I came home at 8 pm that night. When I got home, I grabbed a beer from the fridge and sighed before I put up the can of Mello Yello and bag of sunflower seeds. I walked up to my room and got comfortable in the bed. I turned on the tv and started to relax when I received a picture. It was a photo of my wife lying next to me in bed. There is the last photo messaged right after the photo. I kept the phone pressed towards my stomach in case she managed to see. 

After I saw the photo I turned off both of my phones and fell asleep.

This morning, I woke up and knew that today was going to be rough. I turned on my business phone and instantly received a text from my wife. 

*I will be standing in front of the address written on my id. You know how to get rid of me. Do it at precisely 12:04 pm.*

I checked the time and jumped out of bed when I realized it was 11:58 am. 

I sent her a text that said, Okay. Free of charge.

When I ran out to the living room I greeted my wife the same way I did for the past 2 years. I kissed the only photo I had of her. The photo I took of her the day before she shot herself on our front lawn.

With a sigh, I took the photo off of my wall and gave it a final kiss before taking the photo out of the frame and ripping it up. After I tore it up i  threw it into my fireplace and watched it become smoke. 

While I wiped away a couple of tears from my eyes I received another text from my wife. I opened up the text. It simply said two words. 


Two final words.

["Thank You] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was this true love? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfaoooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Contest!!!!! Battle Royale Style. Come Give Me Your Best Shot! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contest Rules: 

1) **Comment below** your best 2 sentence horror. 

2) It can be about anything. It just cannot pass **2 sentences**

3) Do **not** talk bad about any of the submissions. If you do I will ban you. I do not tolerate any type of trash talking. If youre best buds and I can see that it is in a joking manner I will let that pass, of course, and probably join in on the banter. Cause I like bantering.

How do you win?

The top 5 upvoted posts will move on to the next thread.

 From there I will place the top 5 in the comment section below. 

You can upvote your favorite from the list. **DO NOT DOWNVOTE** 

After 7 days the top upvoted comment will win!

Prizes:

1st Place: Will get a personal shout-out in my upcoming novel as well as a section in the back of the book for your story (with full credits on the piece) along with 3 sentences of whatever you want to write. (nothing bad. No unnecessary cursing. No hate speech. Just be nice) 

2nd and 3rd place: Will have their stories in the back of the book as well! As well as a little note by me on the bottom of your story about how much I love/despise/hate/most likely love that piece! 

**READY**

**SET**

go.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just wanted to be taller than 6"0 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 sentences of horror :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say growing pain is worth it in the end, and I believe it. 

I really do! 

It's just really hard to keep growing when the parts I sew onto my body start to rot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God i love that movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retirement gone completely wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Uncle Has Been Acting Strangely After His Retirement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived with my uncle ever since my mother and father passed away when I was in 7th grade. Though I missed my parents greatly, I quickly grew comfortable living with my uncle. I knew him since I was young, but he lived around 3 hours away so I only saw him about 6 times before I had to move in with him. The first two weeks was a bit awkward, but after a couple of trips to the gym to play basketball and several movies at the movie theater I started to get close to my uncle. 

He was there for every big moment in my life. He sat in the front row during my first basketball game, he dropped me off at prom, and he wiped away several tears on my graduation day. My uncle tried to convince me to go to college, but I told him over and over again that I dont need the extra education. There were plenty of jobs around our city that paid well without requiring a college degree. 

Six months later, I finally got a job as a sales associate at a nearby electronics store. When I told my uncle the good news he just grinned and said, You work there for a year. Just one year and let me know how you feel about the job. With a grin of my own, I said back, I mean. Ill probably like it better than working as a custodian! He let out a laugh and patted me on my shoulder before walking in the kitchen. I could hardly sleep that night. This was going to be my first job and I was a complete nervous wreck. 

Two days ago, my uncle retired from his job. He let me know the news when I came home, after just finishing my 4th month at my job, around 9 pm. As soon as he told me he retired I congratulated him and asked him what he planned on doing. He replied with a sullen look on his face, Live I guess. Not much else for me to do. Ill catch up on movies I wanted to watch. Ill try to stay out of your way. Im sure you have other things to worry about. Right as I tried to tell him that he was never in the way he got up and walked up the stairs to his bedroom.

After I cleaned all of the dishes I went into my room and sat on my bed while browsing through Reddit before my exhaustion took over me and I fell asleep. 

I woke up in the middle of the night at around 3 am. I heard a low humming coming outside of my room. I tried closing my eyes and ignoring the noise, but after waiting for 30 minutes for the noise to stop I got out of my bed and opened my door a little to peek out. My uncle was sitting in front of my room rocking his body to the left and to the right. Right as I cleared my throat he looked up at me and jumped to his feet before running downstairs to the kitchen. I ran after him and when I got to the kitchen he was nowhere to be found. I ran back upstairs to his room and looked through his slightly opened door. He wasnt there. I looked in the restroom, but he was not there. 

I ran back to his room and looked through the crack in his door again and almost screamed out loud when I saw my uncle sitting on the edge of his bed staring directly at me. I quietly took a step back and turned around to walk towards my room when I hear him start to whisper. It was faint and I couldnt really hear what he was saying so I called out to him, What are you saying? I cant hear you. His eyes locked onto mine before continuing in to whisper. Slightly panicking, I opened the door and walked up to him before screaming, Its better if you get rid of me. Get rid of me. Its better if you get rid of me. Just get rid of me!

I got to my feet and told him to get some sleep before running out of his room and into mine. I couldnt sleep that night. Every time I started to drift off I could hear my uncle walking past my door while constantly muttering, Get rid of me.

When I woke up last night I felt a strange calmness in the house. I walked out of my room and check on my uncle. He was asleep in his room. With a small smile, I got ready and headed off to work. The whole day thoughts of my uncle kept disturbing my thoughts. Was he going crazy? How did he keep disappearing? Why did he want me to get rid of him?

I ran out of the doors when my shift ended and drove to my house within 10 minutes. When I walked in I saw my uncle sitting on the couch staring at the powered off tv. I greeted him and walked into the kitchen and heated up a couple of Hotpockets. Right as I put the first Hotpocket on the plate I heard my uncle laughing. 


I walked out to check up on him and saw that he was staring at the tv and laughing at the blank screen. I asked him what he was laughing at, but he suddenly grew quiet and got up from the couch before walking upstairs into his room. 

I wanted to talk to him, but I knew it would just cause more problems. I ate my dinner in silence and walked up to my room. I opened the door to my room and saw my uncle standing in front of my window. I walked up to him and looked out the window. A couple of seconds later, he asked me, You know I miss my sister and your father very much. They meant a lot to me, but you meant so much more. I always wanted a son and you have made the dream a reality. For that, I am forever grateful. Thats why it breaks my heart when you wont just let me go. The house is yours. My money I saved is yours. You just. You just have to let me go. Can you do that for yourself? Hell, can you do that for me?

I turned to look at me and saw bits and pieces of his skin and flesh falling away from his body. After a bit, his exposed flesh and skin started to become a charcoal black. Smoke started to come off of his body. 

I fell to my knees and grabbed his legs. He tried to push off of me, but, I held tight. I dont want to ever believe hes dead. I want to keep thinking hes alive. I want to forget about the business he worked at catching on fire and taking the life of my uncle along with the building. I don't want to think he's gone. I really don't. In my head, he's still alive, and as long as he's still alive in my head his soul is trapped with me. 

I know my uncle wants peace, but I dont want to accept his death. I know once I accept his death. Its all over. Hes gone, and I can never [see him again] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh damn :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> btwww. since noone is on this shitstorm anymore and i'm lazy to message you. would it be cool to reach out to you on facebook and give you a call on there to discuss some stuffy stuff later? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so about that power bar..... i'm gonna need that. like right now.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn it. I was late :( ughhhhhh i wanted to read the drama and become the drama :/ anyways. I fully trust -30 Press- and in what they do. If you have a legitimate problem with the structure you should probably just privately message the moderators of -30 Press-. They are a staple part of what NoSleep is. 

So I understand if you don't trust them YET, but please understand that most NoSleep authors trust -30 Press- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh. i get quite a bit of stuff removed, but I understand every single one of them lol. It's just to keep NoSleep as good as it is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laundromat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My memory of what I once was is slowly fading away, but before I forget about the person I once was I decided to post my story here for the hope that I will one day come across it. 

Who am I now? I am a 29-year-old white male. My name is Ryan Freeman, and I love to listen to music while I cook exquisite meals. Im skilled in a lot of things, but my main passion is cooking. My goal is to be a chef full time at any well-known Italian restaurant. 

Who was I before? A fucking good for nothing unemployed 48-year-old male that never tried to make anything out of my life. The only reason why I wasnt out on the streets was because my father left me the house and every single cent he saved up when he passed away 2 years ago. 

I started to run out of money last month so I started going around the city putting in job applications and went to three job interviews, but I never got a call back after any of the interviews. 

Yesterday morning I woke up to the sound of my phone going off. When I checked the caller I couldnt help but smile. It was Jeff, my best friend, as soon as I said; Hello he told me that he got me a job at the company he worked for as a custodian. I know it may not be a glamorous job, but I was desperate so I asked him what I would have to do. With a chuckle, Jeff told me to just come in clean clothes and the job was mine. 

As soon as I hung up the phone I ran to my room to find a decently clean outfit, but after digging all around the floor of my room I could not find a clean shirt of pants. 

Plan B.

I grabbed the nicest looking dress shirt and khaki pants and ran to my car, I knew of a couple of laundry mats around my house so I drove towards the closest one about 2 miles away. 

Right as I started to drive past the entrance to my neighborhood I saw the most beautiful girl I have ever seen in my life walk past my rear view mirror. I looked to my right to see which house she came out of but all I saw was a single building sitting at the end of an empty street. 

Curious, I backed up and drove into the street. As I drove up to the building I passed by 7 people that looked like they belonged in movies. They all walked with confidence and seemed like they did not have an ounce of stress weighing them down. There were a couple of people walking towards the building, but they walked and looked similar to me. Defeated and broken down, but they still walked with a hop in their step. Kind of like, they were excited for what was to come. 

I was a bit disappointed when I parked my car and looked inside. 

It was just a laundry mat called Clean and Repeat. 

With a sigh, I got out of my car and grabbed my clothes and walked into the door. The smell of rotten copper hit my nose and I couldnt help but let out a loud gag. A guy walked up to me and asked, You new here? I nodded yes to him and he chuckled before saying, Well nice to meet you, man. I go by Bud. Ive been working here for over 12 years. Im guessing youre wondering about what we do here. We show up to people that need us the most. Anyone on earth can get to us, but only a few can find us. Youre one of the few! Congratulations! What we offer is a chance to start over. 

I looked around and noticed that there were only washers. Another thing I noticed was that most of the people that walked in here did not come in with any type of laundry. While I was looking around my eyes landed on a man crying in front of one of the machines. He called out, Im so sorry Gerald. You deserve a better daddy. I hope you can understand why I had to do this. With a final sob, he hopped inside of the washing machine. The door to the machine closed and I ran up to the man to get him out, but when I got up to him I saw his body slowly fall apart in the water. Soon, the water was filled with chunks of flesh, strips of skin, and torn up organs. 

Two minutes later, the water stopped and the door flew open. A guy in a red shirt walked up to the washer and dragged a lump of foam out of the washer. A scream of pure agony came from inside of the foam. I covered my ears and looked around, but everyone walked around as if nothing was out of the ordinary. Out of the corner of my eye, I saw an arm and a leg poke out of the foam. When I turned to get a better look I saw a naked man brushing the bits of soap residue off of him.

He looked completely different; he was younger, much better looking, and had a face full of ambition and dreams. Bud walked up to the guy and talked to him. The guy nodded at Bud and took the clothes Bud handed to him. He walked out the door with a huge grin on his face and a sense of pride in every step he took. 

When the guy walked out the door Bud walked up to me and asked, I know you hate your life. You are about to take a dead end job. Dont do that. Just get into one of these cleansers and you will walk out a new man. Everything you have done that was wrong will be wiped away from you. You will walk out a new man. A man that is full of purpose and most importantly a man that has a goal to strive for.

Without hesitation, I opened the door and hopped into one of the cleansers. With a grin, Bud closed the door and mouthed the words, No regrets. Scalding hot water started to pour all over me, but the pain was so intense I could hardly make a sound. By the time I could muster a decent scream I felt myself becoming part of something else. 

Something pure, but something that didnt feel right. 

I dont really know how to describe how it felt to be completely torn apart, but Ill try my best. Every regret and every bad or horrible thing I did in my life swam past my thoughts. 

The thoughts floating around the water in between pieces of my body. 

Judgment day.

Thats a good phrase to use to describe how it was like. I still felt the intense heat that filled every part of my body, and the memories of every single sin corrupted me mentally and physically. The time I made fun of my cousin for dressing like a girl, the time I beat up my awkward best friend to gain the approval of the more popular kids in my class, and the memory of sitting on the couch after my father fell down the stairs. He crawled around the floor like a helpless mutt for 20 minutes before taking his last breath just two years ago.  

The unbearable stopped as soon as the last memory faded away. I heard the door open and felt two hands grab me and pull me out of the machine. With each second the pain came back while my body started to piece back together. When I finally felt whole again, I let out a scream to express every bit of pain my body just went through before ripping past the foam and standing up in my new body for the first time. 

Bud walked up to me and handed me some clothes before leaning up to me and whispering, Enjoy your new life, but when we need you. You will need to forget everything and give your life to us. After all, you owe us for giving you a life you dont deserve. Give me a nod that you understand. 

Once I put on the clothes he handed me I turned to him and shook my head no before running out of the building and got into my car. I took one final look inside of the building. Bud was shaking his head while laughing and pointed at me. Scared out of my mind, I drove out of the street and stopped to take a final look at the building.

There was nothing there. 

It was just woods. 

When I got to my house I ran into my room and never left. I am still in my room now. Its been over a day, but my memories keep fading away. The only thing I remember now is what happened yesterday. 

Before I forget about my life I wanted to warn all of you guys. Please dont go into any secluded Laundromats. It may seem like a good thing, but I no longer own my life. Be thankful with what you [have now] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit pretty weather ugly woman was a damn work of art! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's gonna be a while before i get out of my comfort zone again-.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really wasnt my intention:/ i was trying to show the raw fear of someone with a mental illness going through something like that. 

Again, this story was just a bunch of firsts for me. It was me getting out of my comfort zone way too fast. Lol 

Thank you for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh i don't even know what css is XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 09:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummmmm.nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay. We did pet peeves. Now let's do the opposite! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is something you absolutely love reading on NoSleep? Which story has stuck with you for a long time?

To the authors: what is your favorite story you have written? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reuploaded the Story! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60757o/double_check_before_buying_used_game_systems/

reuploaded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60757o/double_check_before_buying_used_game_systems/

reuploaded~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60757o/double_check_before_buying_used_game_systems/

reuploaded!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60757o/double_check_before_buying_used_game_systems/

reduploaded!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60757o/double_check_before_buying_used_game_systems/

reuploaded!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60757o/double_check_before_buying_used_game_systems/

reuploaded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Double Check Before Buying Used Game Systems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a single 38-year-old father of a 13-year-old is quite the challenge, but my son, Jared, has made it far too easy for me. He was the poster child of a good child. He never got into trouble, excelled at every subject in school, and had a passion for the classical guitar. Of course, just like any other kid, he would do something wrong, but he was always honest with me. He would tell me what he did, and he would always seem legitimately sorry for his actions. 

That is why I was browsing through craigslist looking for an Xbox One. I knew he wanted one, but it was far too expensive for me to buy. I could barely keep up with the bills, but I checked for a decent deal every night before I went to bed.

Four days ago, I came across a new ad placed for an Xbox One with 4 games for just $75. When I clicked on the ad I saw that an enraged mother was selling her sons game system because he failed in all of his classes. After checking the time and seeing that it was 8:30 pm I called the number that was on the bottom of the post. 

10 minutes later, we agreed to meet at my house at 10 am the next day to make the transaction. Before she hung up the phone she said, I just want you to know something. My son. He is a smart kid. He is a really good boy, but ever since he got that stupid system he started getting obsessed over a game. I dont really know which one, but just monitor your son. I hung up the phone with an uneasy feeling, but I knew that my son was different. He deserved it.  

When my son came home from school he screamed out in joy when he saw me hooking up his new Xbox up to the tv. He ran up and gave me a hug and sat right next to me while I connected the HDMI cable to the system. I handed the controller to Jared and he started looking through the games. Once he picked out some sort of car racing game I got up and started getting dinner ready. By the time I put together the last chicken taco I turned around to call out to Jared to come in, but I saw he was already sitting on his chair. The whole entire meal Jared thanked me for getting him the Xbox and about how his first couple races went. When we finished dinner he got up and walked into his room. 

After I cleared out the dishes and washed them, I walked upstairs to my room and when I passed by his room I checked in his room and saw that he was closing up his school notebook and picking up his guitar. I had to get up early for a meeting the next morning so I fell asleep as soon as I walked into the room to the sound of my son strumming out Fur Elise. 

The next couple of days went by smoothly. My son would come home, play on the Xbox for about 1 to 2 hours, eat dinner with me, and then do his homework and practice his guitar before going to bed. 

Two days ago, everything changed. My son looked through his games, but after a couple of seconds he started going through the menu on the Xbox. I told myself to make sure I had some new games before next week. 

I made chicken soup that night, but when I was done making it my son was not sitting in front of the dinner table like he always was. After I called out to him 3 times without a response I walked out of the kitchen and into the living room. 

He was completely fixated on a game I havent seen him play before. 

It was just a yellow ball on the far right corner of the screen. There were smaller gray balls flying towards the yellow ball that I guess you tried to avoid. I tapped on Jareds shoulder, but he ignored me and kept playing the game. 

He never did this before so I just took his dinner out to the living room and placed it next to him. I told him to eat it whenever he felt like it. 

I never really worried about him. He always did the right thing. The next day was Saturday too, so I decided to let him play the game for as long as he wanted. After I finished my dinner I gave Jared a kiss on the forehead and walked to my room. I was used to falling asleep to the sound of his music, but the fast paced rhythmic tapping on his controller slowly guided me to sleep. 

I woke up at 5 am yesterday morning. The first thing I noticed was that I could still hear the sound of tapping. The second thing I noticed was that the tapping was completely in rhythm. Not a single tap was out of the beat that filled the otherwise silent house. I got out of bed and walked downstairs.

Jared was still sitting in front of the tv. I tapped on him several times, but he did not take his eyes off of the screen. I looked him in the eyes to get his attention, but the glazed look in his eyes made me start to panic. His eyes were a solid green. It wasnt the lighting or anything on the screen. His eyes were solid green. Without any hesitation, I grabbed the controller out of his hands and started to drag him to his room. He screamed and tried to get out of my grip, but I didnt loosen my grip until he was in his room. 

Through his tears and his screaming, he crawled to his bed and fell asleep. 

Curious, I went downstairs and picked up the controller. It was on the start menu so I just clicked on the option that said, Start New Game. 

I played it one time.

Just once, but it is taking all of my willpower to not play it again. I know its not good. Its called Desires Unknown. If you happen to come across the game please do not play it. 

It has taken up almost all of my thoughts. 

What does the game do?

When you start the game you are the dot on the far right side. Not just a pixelated version of you. No. A real life version of you. 

The gray dots that fly towards you?

Everything that you ever wanted.

The first couple of dots were my favorite foods. Lasagna, steak, roast beef, and spaghetti, but as the dots progressed, it soon became my son graduating from an Ivy League college, my wife surviving past the first 3 hours of Jareds birth and the promotion that would allow me to spend more time with Jared without having to worry about finances. It took me everything to avoid all of the temptations, but Im afraid to play again.

Im afraid to figure out what happens if you fall for any of the [temptations] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clickbait title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 05:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New here?:p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything that was said here haha.

Welcome to the sub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snitches get stitches. 

Er. Death maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just really feel like you aren't capturing what OP wrote as a whole. You're kinda just stuck on the start of it and jumping to the end.... Try reading it one more time, and drop down your defensive mind for one second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no we have always been really close and never had any problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *keeping an eye on y^o^u* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.o well come and find out lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah don't fuck with our cheetos... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to start keeping score haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was the best friend i could wish for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A real best friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Are Dying After My Best Friend Went Missing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friend (Zane) and I decided to go to the same college for our first two years. We were both against the idea of living in dorms so we used the money we saved up during high school to pay for six months of rent up front. We both got jobs within the first month of college. Between work and college, we hardly had time to hang out, but we quickly made it a tradition to eat Flamin Hot Cheetos and split a 24 pack of beer every Sunday evening while watching whatever was on tv.
 
The first four months went by in a blur. I managed to make a couple of friends get promoted to shift manager and make straight As on all of my classes. Zane on the hand lost his job, became more and quieter, and was barely scraping by with passing grades. I tried to cheer him up multiple times a day, but he would just either grunt in response or just ignore me completely.
 
Four days ago, Zane left and never came back. I didnt panic for the first day, but 2 days after not seeing Zane I started to get worried. I tried calling him several times, but he didnt answer. He wouldnt respond to any of my messages on Facebook or text. I went to bed with an uneasy feeling that night. The next morning when I woke up I broke down and ended up calling the cops.
 
They came over and got a couple of notes from me. I showed them a couple of photos from his Facebook and Instagram. Around 30 minutes later they told me they would try their hardest to find him and left. I tried going about the day, but during my classes, I couldnt really pay attention to what the professor was talking about. After my last class, I walked back home and changed into my work uniform and walked to the bookstore. The five-hour shift felt like it was never going to end. I started counting down the minutes during the final two hours. My counting was disturbed when I overheard a couple of girls talk about a man that was found dead outside of our school cafeteria. Curious, I walked up to them and asked them if there was any type of description of the man. After a couple of seconds of awkward silence, the girl holding a phone handed me the phone and pointed at the article. 

One look and I let out a breath of relief. The man in the photo had white hair. There wasn't really a description of how he was killed or who to look out for. Of course, I was scared that there was a murderer in our college campus, but I was relieved that Zane wasn't dead. I handed back the phone while thanking the girls and walked to the back to try calling him again. After my third unsuccessful attempt I walked out and walked around the store and acted like I was working for the remainder of the shift. 

When I got home I sat on the couch and waited there till around 4 in the morning. I knew he wasn't coming home, but I didn't want to give up hope. He was the guy that beat up my bully for me when we were in the 5th grade. The one that warned me about how my homecoming date was gonna ditch me once we got to homecoming. The one that motivated me to shoot for a full scholarship for whatever college I decided to go. The one that gave me the smile that I loved seeing when I told him that I got accepted with a full scholarship for the college he was going to as well.
When I woke up yesterday morning I got ready and walked to my first class. When I got to the class I saw a note from the professor posted in front of the door saying that classes were canceled for today. I checked my e-mails to make sure another student was pulling a prank on me, but the first e-mail I saw was an alert from the college office.

**Subject: Stay indoors. Do not leave.**

*We are sending out a warning for all of our student to not leave their rooms or their houses. Yesterday evening we have lost 8 students.*

*If you decide to leave be reminded that this is on your own terms. We suggest going out in groups. We are looking into the deaths of the students, but we are temporarily canceling all classes until we resolve this issue.*

I ran back to my house as fast as I could. When I walked inside of the house I swear I could smell the smell of the cologne Zane used since high school. I walked into the living room to see a familiar sight for the first time.

A 24 pack of beer and two bags of Flamin' hot Cheetos. 

On the news later that day they were covering the deaths on our campus. I instantly noticed two names. The bully Zane beat up, and the girl that planned on ditching me for the homecoming dance.

Zane, if you're reading this. I don't agree with this, but man, I sure do appreciate how much you really care about me. Be safe. This beer is in [honor of you] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=aymt_homepage_panel).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hehehehheh :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was the one that wrote [removed] bwahahahha i love comments that come from people super duper mad, because i know i struck a chord from inside their souls :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would definitely just say No lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> insomnia and not being able to sleep five days after?!?! I'm sorry:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugh anything dealing with the woods creep me out so bad :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should message the moderators :)

https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fnosleep

they will let you know why and if you can repost it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man that is genius! haha i just hate the people that would flip like 10 cigarettes over. 

don't be greedy with luck -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deleted for non horror but here you go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello my name is Malik, and smoking cigarettes ruined my life in a unique way. Until I started college I was always a straight edge kid. Not by choice, but because my mother and father kept me insanely sheltered. It was to the point to where I would have to give them a 3 week notice to go hand out with any of my friends. Every Sunday and Wednesday I went to church, and Every Tuesday and Thursday I would have Bible study with my father. I was forced to memorize 20 verses a week to earn the privilege of 30 minutes of tv a day and an hour of computer time a week. Both activities were under my mothers supervision. 

I loved my parents, but I always wondered what it would be like to have the freedom to make my own choices. That is why the day my parents dropped me off at my college was the best day of my life. It was 3 hours away from home, and since I received a full ride scholarship for college I was not bound by my parents any longer. 

The first three months went by in a blur. I still called my mother at the end of my classes for around 20 to 30 minutes to assure her that I was still studying the Bible every night. My roommate, Tyler, would sometimes sit on his bed and laugh at my obvious lies. 

After my daily phone call I would finish my homework while texting a girl I started talking to the first month into college. We met at a party and just clicked. It was the first night I drank my first beer. It tasted like shit, but after finishing my 3rd beer I got used to the taste. We danced together for a couple of songs before she walked outside while waving at me to follow her. For the next 3 hours, we sat around and talked about what we were planning on doing after college while she smoked cigarette after cigarette. She tried offering me one but I told her I didnt smoke. After we met that night we never stopped talking after that. Two months into our relationship she took my virginity and it was the best experience of my life. She was my first love, and I knew that I wanted to marry her.

One month ago she broke up with me. When I tried asking her why, she just shook her head before saying, Malik, youre a sweet guy. You really made me feel special, but we were just not meant to be together. Youre too nice. You deserve someone much better. She touched my cheek one last time before exiting my dorm room for the last time. When Tyler walked in an hour later he asked me if I was okay. I nodded my head yes and asked him if he had a cigarette on him. With a confused look on his face, he took out his pack of Marlboro Reds and motioned me to follow him. I smoked my first cigarette that day in front of the entrance to our dorm building. The first three hits of the cigarette sent me into a coughing frenzy, but by the time I finished the cigarette I felt a million times better. I was still hurt by the abrupt break up, but I was actually able to rationalize with myself that everything would be better after a couple of weeks.

I was hooked. Not hooked in the sense of being addicted, but addicted to the feeling of being at complete peace.

The next day I bought my first pack of cigarettes with Tyler. When I walked outside I ripped open the pack and tossed a cigarette in my mouth, but he snatched it out of my mouth and shoved it back into my pack upside down. When he saw my confused face, he laughed and said, Whenever you buy a pack of smokes you flip one upside down and smoke it last. Its just a superstitious thing, but we call it the lucky cigarette and I swear something good happens to me after I smoke it. 

***

You can call me crazy, but Tyler was right. Every time I smoked my lucky cigarette something really good would happen to me. It took me 3 days to finish my first pack. After I smoked my last cigarette, I got a call from my mother telling me that they sent me $300 dollars to do whatever I wanted with my friends. She apologized for being so strict my whole childhood. After an hour of talking, she told me to start enjoying life before hanging up the phone. 

The next pack took me two day to finish. When I smoked the lucky cigarette, I got a message from my ex-girlfriend asking to get back together, but I got the satisfaction of being the one to reject her. Over the next couple of weeks my life started getting better with each lucky cigarette I smoked, but it all changed two days ago. 

***

Two days ago, I woke up and smoke a cigarette while I ran to my first class, but halfway through my cigarette I accidentally ran right into a guy. He started to yell at me, but I ignored him and got to my class on time. After the class I smoked my next cigarette and as I finished it I saw my ex running across the street. About halfway across the street I saw a car come out of nowhere and slam against her body. She launched into the air and bounced three times on the unforgiving gravel. 

I knew she was dead. I didnt run up to her body like everybody else around me. I walked to my dorm building and ran up to my room. 

I smoke cigarette after cigarette in the room. I didnt care anymore. Before I fell asleep that night the smell of cigarettes filled the room. It was almost impossible to breathe in the room, but I lit up another one and took a drag. Tyler walked into the room and tried to tell me to take it outside, but after a couple of minutes of ignoring him he walked out of the room.  

I woke up yesterday morning to knocking on my door. When I opened my door, I saw two cops standing outside. They asked me if I could answer a couple of questions. It was a mixture of what Tyler was like and if he ever seemed depressed. Near the end of their questions I learned that Tyler tried to hang himself in the study room of our dorm building. He was still alive and had a good chance of survival. 

I skipped my classes that day to go visit him in the hospital. When I walked into his room he looked up at me and gave me a small wave. When I got close I asked him, Man why did you do it? You always seemed so happy. Was it something I did? He grabbed my hand and said, I really dont know why. It wasnt you or anyone else. After I walked out of our room I just felt more sadness than I ever felt in my life. It seemed like the only way out. I tried to think of something to say, but I couldnt think of anything. I walked out and smoked a lucky cigarette and another cigarette from my next pack. When I walked back into the hospital I saw a couple of people running towards Tylers room. I ran with them into his room. The heart beat monitor filled with a straight horizontal line. His body was completely still. I wanted to run up to his bed, but my feet wouldnt move. After a couple of second of staring at his dead body, I turned around and ran back outside and drove back to my dorm building. 

I have been here since yesterday. 

I am now writing to you all. It may be a small chance that this will happen to you, but please dont flip your cigarette over to make it a lucky cigarette. For some of you it may just be something that never affects you, but for people like me. It will ruin your life. The lucky cigarettes remain lucky, but every other cigarette will make your life that much worse.

I tried to just not smoke, but after an hour something bad happens anyways. So, I just kept smoking cigarettes yesterday. My father died of a heart attack last night, my mother was in the hospital after having a stroke, and now it has become harder for me to breather.

So that is why I have Tylers gun in my hand. The gun he hid in his desk in case shit went down. 

With the final drag of my final lucky cigarette I am hitting submit on this warning for you all, and accepting my final bit of luck.

[Death] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).



 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Non horror" sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is truly a wonderfult gift you have..

And a wonder style of writing. Sorry it may not help much after what you went though but.

Omg i love the way it was written  :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry. Its just technology is so fucked up:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after you get off of r/suicidewatch you try to bring other people down?

Sounds cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i really liked your series. Sad it has to end that way lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hm you should just ignore the criticisms. I would say try to at least write one more part and generally tie things together. Just so you can just come back later with adoring readers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously is amazing omfg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well damn. Imma check on my baby constantly tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit ive been waiting for this :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/wiki/reader_faq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here lately all of my hate mail is about.

1) Ughhhh another app story wtf.

2) Cannibals are fucking gross and you need to quit.

so maybe i should start writing more taboo stuff haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know that once I keep writing I will definitely get more comfortable with it. Lol

I'm taking baby steps and just started killing off younger children. I don't understand why people send hate mail about it though lol. You're an amazing writer. So I would just enjoy the story anyways haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugh, definitely actually writing out domestic/child abuse. I can't do it. I can't even read about it.

 Or babies getting killed. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow! It really means so much to me that you would take the time to tag me in a list of such great writers:c best of luck to your mother! I'm sure she will write an amazing story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh wow. Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you feel is the most attractive features of a pure bred stallion? 

Where would you rank "serious moonlight" amongst your stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> security cameras are creepy :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Cameras Proved My Wife Isn't Cheating on Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I have been married for twenty years. We got married three weeks after we graduated college. We had our ups and our downs, but at the end of the night I always felt just that much closer to her than the night before. My feelings for her never died away, but after we moved into the new house 3 months ago my wife has started growing more and more distant from me. It started with her ignoring a couple things I said, to blowing off on our monthly date. Now she will barely talk to me. 

Of course, I had my suspicions. Who wouldnt? That is why when my wife out on her daily walk yesterday, I texted my wife that I was going shopping and I would be back soon. I quickly got in my car and drove to the local electronics store. When a sales representative greeted me I told him that I would need a couple of hidden cameras. He gave me a nod and led me to the middle of the sales floor. With a wave of his arm he started to pitch me on the most expensive set. When he saw the look of concern on my face he gave me a smile and asked, So what is you budget? Trying to hide the embarrassment in my voice I managed to mutter out, 300 dollars. 

After a couple of seconds, he stuck out his hand and said, My name is Jack by the way. I took his hand and said, Glenn. With a look of concern, he asked, So I know it may be personal, but why are you getting the cameras? 

Im normally a really reserved man. I have never been one to open up to anyone, but something about his voice. The soft yet stern words that left the mans mouth made me fall on my knees and start sobbing. With a gentle nudge Jack said, Cmon to the back man. Lets talk. I want to help you. I got up to my feet and quietly followed him to the door in the back while avoiding all of the weird stares from other customers. 

Once we walked through the doors I saw a small room with a table and two chairs. Jack pulled out a chair and I sat in it while he took the other seat. Before he could ask me again I rambled on for what felt like hours about what my wife used to be like and how she was now. As I got close to the end of my story I felt another surge of tears, but Jack gently touched my shoulder and I felt all of my grief fade away. 

I looked up at him and for the first time in 3 months I smiled. He told me to wait up front and he would bring me what I was looking for. After waiting ten minutes at the front counter Jack walked through the doors with a small white box in his hands. While he walked up to the counter he started opening up the box and as walked up to me he put the box in my hands and told me to look inside. Inside of the box were three small monkey glass figurines and a small device with a screen. 

I started to ask, What am I sup-, but Jack cut me off and said, These three little guys run off of solar power and will never need to be charged. This guy is the monitor you can watch what any of the cameras see. The monitor you will have to charge once every two to three days depending on usage. He leaned close to me and whispered, Its normally 1400 for the set, but Ill let you have it for 300. Just dont say a word while I ring you up. 

When he rung up the camera set I handed him 300 dollars and he reached into his wallet and swiped it into the card reader. With a nod he said, Okay sir just sign the pad and youre ready to go! I signed the pad with my finger and he put the box and the receipt in the bag and handed it over to me. I mouthed out Thank you and hurried into my car. Slightly curious, I opened the box and turned the screen on. For the first couple of second the screen remained black, but after a couple of second of waiting the screen turned yellow and four blue lines shot out of each corner and met in the middle to form two words.

**Reveal Everything**

***

I picked up one of the little figurines and started looking around for the camera. When I couldnt find any I looked back at the screen and Camera 1 and Camera 3 were black while Camera 2 showed my face staring dumbly at myself in the screen. Satisfied, I drove back home and placed a camera in the living room, the kitchen, and our bedroom. 

My wife walked in from her walk around 7 pm and started to walk upstairs. I asked her if she wanted to eat dinner, but she just ignored me and continued to walk upstairs and into the room. 

When I woke up this morning I got out of bed, got dressed, and rushed out of the house without saying a word to my wife. 

Twenty minutes later, I got to work about an hour early. I grabbed the monitor and walked into the office and sat down on my chair. I checked the cameras but saw that my wife was still asleep. 

***

Three hours go by without an alert. I still checked on the monitor but my wife was still asleep the whole entire time. Around lunch time was when I got my first motion alert. I quickly turned the screen back on and saw my wife slowly getting out of bed and walking downstairs. My eyes bounced to the camera pointing at the living room towards the front door, but my wife just sat on the couch for about 30 minutes. 

That is when I saw it. Tiny black spots started to show up all around the living room. At that moment my wife started to curl into a ball on the couch. I thought it was the camera or the screen so I tried slapping the back of the monitor, but every couple of seconds the dots started grouping together. Each time the black dots grouped together I noticed my wife tensing up even more. I tried calling my wife several times, but she only looked at the phone before putting it on the table and stared towards the dots grouping together. 

I turned the screen off and wrote an email to my boss that I had an emergency and I would have to leave before running to my car. When I got inside my car I turned the monitor back on and saw my wife walking all around the house, but there was a shadow following behind her. When she opened the door to our room the shadow disappeared. I started driving home while still glancing at the screen to make sure my wife was still okay. I drove into the entrance to our neighborhood and parked in my driveway before checking the screen for the last time. The tablet dropped out of my hands as soon as I saw what was on the screen. A man with a deep red gash in his neck was bent over the body of my wifes body. Blood was around my wife.

I ran into our house and ran upstairs to our room. 

My wife is dead. Her midsection was completely extinct by the time I ran into the room. I looked around the house, but I knew that we were the only ones in the house that can be seen.

I gave the cops the monitor for investigative purpose. After being interviewed for 4 hours I was finally able to find a hotel spend the next couple of nights in. My wife is gone. My life is ruined. I took one of the cameras with me when I walked out of my house. When I smashed it against the wall out of frustration I only saw broken glass. 

Nothing else.

Just glass.

So please guys.

Please help me.

I dont [know what to do] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I.... I created you. It is I. 

Your f^a^t^h^e^r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please be nice to the mods lol. They work for free and we need to understand when it is just a day past the time period:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally through the comments of the story. This is not a place for immersion lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
