<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one eats like Gaston! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have. I've read it multiple times, and prayed about it earnestly multiple times. Each time, I get the overwhelming feeling that the book is a fraud. I get a warm, cozy sensation that starts in my chest and radiates throughout my whole being. Through this test of prayer, I **know** beyond a shadow of a doubt that the Book of Mormon is ill-conceived frontier bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure do love books that say that black people are cursed because of their unrighteousness. Man, I feel like a good person already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 19:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ammon Bundy is Mormon and has dropped some BoM references in interviews. They have someone in their group who calls himself "Captain Moroni."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 19:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. Read *Guns, Germs, and Steel*, take some anthropology classes, think about it logically. Absence of *expected* evidence is evidence of absence. 

"A fire-breathing dragon lives in my garage" Suppose (I'm following a group therapy approach by the psychologist Richard Franklin[3]) I seriously make such an assertion to you. Surely you'd want to check it out, see for yourself. There have been innumerable stories of dragons over the centuries, but no real evidence. What an opportunity! 

"Show me," you say. I lead you to my garage. You look inside and see a ladder, empty paint cans, an old tricycle--but no dragon. 

"Where's the dragon?" you ask. 

"Oh, she's right here," I reply, waving vaguely. "I neglected to mention that she's an invisible dragon." 

You propose spreading flour on the floor of the garage to capture the dragon's footprints. 

"Good idea," I say, "but this dragon floats in the air." 

Then you'll use an infrared sensor to detect the invisible fire. 

"Good idea, but the invisible fire is also heatless." 

You'll spray-paint the dragon and make her visible. 

"Good idea, but she's an incorporeal dragon and the paint won't stick." And so on. I counter every physical test you propose with a special explanation of why it won't work. 

Now, what's the difference between an invisible, incorporeal, floating dragon who spits heatless fire and no dragon at all? If there's no way to disprove my contention, no conceivable experiment that would count against it, what does it mean to say that my dragon exists? Your inability to invalidate my hypothesis is not at all the same thing as proving it true. Claims that cannot be tested, assertions immune to disproof are veridically worthless, whatever value they may have in inspiring us or in exciting our sense of wonder. What I'm asking you to do comes down to believing, in the absence of evidence, on my say-so.

-Carl Sagan, *Demon Haunted World* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Sorry for mis-interpreting your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well, I see all of these black swans. However, since I have special revelation from God, I will continue to assert that all swans are white." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, as /u/3rdAnointing says, it wasn't a translation. It was a scrying process via rock-in-hat. Words would appear, and unless they were written down exactly as God revealed, they wouldn't go away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 17:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tapirs. Llamas are 5.6-5.9 ft at the top of their head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 16:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steel: Smelters, mines, tailings

Wheat/barley: Pollen spores in lake sediment, fields that were harvested, granaries

Horses: Pastures, stables, bridles

Chariots: Wheels, bridles, whips, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 16:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there would be other signs. Bridles, stables, a whole culture around the tapir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 16:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google says they are 3.3 ft at the shoulder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 19:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there are many people within these religions that know that we are on many right roads. 

Source? Because, moving out of Utah, I came to the realization that the rest of the world really doesn't give a fuck about Mormonism. They don't know about it, they don't know what the prophets teach, they don't know the beliefs.

Five minutes ago I just answered a question from a coworker. She asked if Mormons could *listen to music*. Most people outside of Utah really, really don't know or care about Mormonism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 19:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does doing it by proxy jive with D C 132:15-17?

 15 Therefore, if a man marry him a wife in the world, and he marry her not by me nor by my word, and he covenant with her so long as he is in the world and she with him, their covenant and marriage are not of force when they are dead, and when they are out of the world; therefore, they are not bound by any law when they are out of the world.

 16 **Therefore, when they are out of the world they neither marry nor are given in marriage; but are appointed angels in heaven**, which angels are ministering servants, to minister for those who are worthy of a far more, and an exceeding, and an eternal weight of glory.

 17 For these angels did not abide my law; therefore, they cannot be enlarged, **but remain separately and singly, without exaltation**, in their saved condition, to all eternity; **and from henceforth are not gods**, but are angels of God forever and ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 20:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no direct advice, other than to try in /r/personalfinance. Some of them are tax wizards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which civs lend more naturally to Tall or Wide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I just started playing 5 days ago. With the snowstorm, I've gotten a lot of time in. In my first game (on easy) I had 5-6 cities as Poland. In my most recent game, I have 8 cities so far and still haven't found half the map (don't have astronomy yet).

Which civs are better for Tall or Wide? Going wide, do you have any tips to counteract Unhappiness?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fly me to the moon with your rocket science, -Themis- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 16:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IANAL, but I don't think notes count as being "recorded." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, absolutely. The reason I'm so open (to anyone, really) is to help de-stigmatize it. Frankly, depressed/anxious people are pretty lucky, since the general healthy public has a good grasp on what it means. 

OCD, BPD, and schizophrenia has a much larger social stigma, unfortunately. People fear what they don't understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 16:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subconscious knowledge that their beliefs are based on lies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 15:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, not always. I have major depression, and the only real symptom is an intense feeling of heartbreak and sadness. My sleep schedule, diet, and sex drive are not effected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 02:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not yet physically but emotionally and mentally.

Given that he assaulted a random woman because she *looked like you*, I guarantee he's hit her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing a disservice to Kmart. At least they have blue light specials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 00:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this devious agenda related to the much-feared "homosexual agenda"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 22:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is /r/bestoflegaladvice, a place where the best (and worst) of submissions to /r/legaladvice go.

You want to go to /r/legaladvice.

Also, pending more information from you (has he done this before, other behaviors, is there a pattern, what were the exact circumstances, etc.) I don't think anyone can answer your question satisfactorily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 14:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great reply, thank you. I always like your perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 19:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's one thing Joseph Smith said.

And it's been trumpeted by almost every prophet since. It's about as "doctrine" as you can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which parts of the Book of Mormon do you think are incorrect?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 19:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which parts of the Book of Mormon do you think are incorrect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm getting married! What is your dream kitchen items? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 17:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We love cooking, but currently have some Ikea knives and a hodge-podge of pans from TJ Maxx, Target, and the local grocery store.

What's your favorite set of pans? Dream knife set? Must-have kitchen gadgets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 21:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I know. But /u/chooseagency claimed that there were errors, I'd like him to name some. I already know the BoM is bullshit, he has reached the opposite conclusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between this and /r/legaladvice, I completely agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I'm glad you have a good relationship. Sorry for misreading your initial post, /r/relationships makes me smells shit where there is none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, sure, to a point. Getting upset because you play too many videogames? Understandable.

Her constantly questioning and being accusatory? The constant paranoia and non-trust would drive me crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But she already has cancer. Also, it's genetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  my wife does this shit all the time.

That sounds fucking exhausting.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 14:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are some of it's mistakes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 00:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on whether the Mormon thinks that Smith used a "tight" or "loose" translation. Tight = wrote exactly what God said, word for word. Loose = God revealed the general 'idea' of the passage and Smith injected his own feelings. Both have their issues.

I would argue that in practice, the BoM is held absolutely infallible.

I told the brethren that the Book of Mormon was the most correct of any book on earth, and the keystone of our religion, and a man would get nearer to God by abiding by its precepts, than by any other book. - Joseph Smith (History of the Church, 4:461.)

https://www.lds.org/ensign/1984/06/the-most-correct-book?lang=eng

If a Mormon says they don't think the BoM is infallible, ask them what they think is wrong with it. Chances are, they don't think anything is wrong with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lots of alcohol at a party the night before

You were drunk on the job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 23:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know that they are not actually real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 23:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of my favorite subs. I like to play "real or Poe," I think I lose every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 23:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a Mormon demon, [try shaking it's hand first](https://www.lds.org/scriptures/dc-testament/dc/129?lang=eng)

 4 When a messenger comes saying he has a message from God, offer him your hand and request him to shake hands with you.

 5 If he be an angel he will do so, and you will feel his hand.

 6 If he be the spirit of a just man made perfect he will come in his glory; for that is the only way he can appear

 7 Ask him to shake hands with you, but he will not move, because it is contrary to the order of heaven for a just man to deceive; but he will still deliver his message.

 8 If it be the devil as an angel of light, when you ask him to shake hands he will offer you his hand, and you will not feel anything; you may therefore detect him.

Remember: Demons are too stupid to try to lie by *not* shaking your hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 16:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's zero moderation. Mistake on TSCC's part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6PX8R642AZMNRNP568FM6KD

fum game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/AlFFHv1.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 15:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong here? They're committed to each other, and getting married. Or do you mean "go back to church so your child will be brought up properly"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 12:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 20:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're pretty poor at describing "Mormonism in a nutshell," though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 20:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it doesn't. I think you may be thinking of creat*inine*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 18:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or like when you're a kid, and try to come up with a "new" word that you give a definition to. It feels like a cheap party trick here, it shows Smith's true colors pretty clearly as far as revelation is concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  still mad about prop 8

What, now that TSCC got it's ass handed to them by the Supreme Court, we're just supposed to say "oh, that silly church. All is forgiven."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 16:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was still taught over the pulpit, from General Conference by a living prophet.

It was taught **in the temple**! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 16:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That women are worthless without a husband? That they can't feel beautiful until a man finds them beautiful?

What is the "good" message? Because I see a whole lot of shit messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent write-up, I liked how you explained things from an outsider's perspective. 

I do disagree with your last line, though; I think a lot of posters here can answer almost all questions better than the missionaries, on any topic relating to Mormonism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 20:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/TrollaBot subject577 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, I work 10 hour days, and I haven't gained any weight at all. Am I special? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have family in Southern Nevada, literally a ward over from the Bundy's. This is anecdotal, but they are very much Mormon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We Mormons love being considered "normal" even when we're not.

Whatever happened to "A Peculiar People"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this thread, and wish I could show it to my very Mormon family. "See," I'd say, "everyone who isn't indoctrinated thinks the basic doctrine is fucked up."

Mormons don't get how *weird* they look to the rest of the world.

Thanks for this fresh (on this sub) perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 15:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIK, they *tried,* and failed. Just like they tried and failed (via church-owned BYU) to find archaeological evidence anywhere in the Americas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
