<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors use deep-brain ultrasound therapy to treat tremors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost nothing else makes me more exhausted than a flight half way across the globe, but the only thing I do the whole time is sit, eat, doze off and watch movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I contacted his sister and she said that they are aware that he's been 'acting OCD' , but he comes from the type of family that is a bit 'hippyish' for lack of a better word and I bet that they'd believe some of his story.  The only thing that makes it difficult is that my friend is actually a dual citizen.  Right now he lives in Europe completely away from his family in America. He has some Swedish family, but other than that he is on his own. He's literally free to roam around the world unsupervised.  I contacted the embassy of the country he is from to let them k ow what's up.  His parents have tried to convince him to come home but they say that he is stubborn and won't listen to them (yeah of course he is).  I know he will live in denial, and his immediate family seems to be oblivious to the fact that nothing short of getting on a plane themselves and dragging his ass home to America will get him the real help he needs . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schizophrenia, OCD, or a combo? Worried about a friend who seems to be coming unhinged while traveling abroad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 13:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story ahead warning. I was supposed to meet my friend who I haven't seen for a long time in a foreign country while on a vacation.  My friend made it to the country but never showed up to the place he was supposed to come to on the date he said he would. I was eventually able to contact him while in the foreign country and he began to tell a quite peculiar story.  First, upon his arrival, he went to a different city for a 2 days.  He said that he initially got into an argument with a local taxi driver over a fare because of a simple language misunderstanding.  The next day he said he skipped out on a taxi fare because he 'was tired'.  It was because of these two incidents that he claims the residents of the city became angry at him and started to take his photos everywhere he went.  According to him, residents in that city had a 'secret group' on a messaging app for smart phones where they were all taking photos of him, plastering it on the group, and 'talking shit' about him.  The people of the city were also becoming openly hostile towards him.   He said that he felt threatened so ended up leaving that city for the country's main capital.  There he said that nearly 80% of the people in the city were still able to recognize him and were 'talking shit' in a mockingly/threatning way.  Mind you, we are talking about a massive megacity with over 10 million people, so I find it hard to believe that so many people were able to 'recognize him'.  He claimed that the group messaging app on the phone from the previous city was able to follow him and post messages to people who were part of the group chat for the new city he traveled to. But his story gets more peculiar. 

He says that his conundrum actually began way back at home in Europe.  Back home he said that he had been living with a 'mold problem' for several years and became 'infected' with a nearly impossible to cure fungal infection of many multiple subtypes of fungi.  He even had a name for his ailment--CIRS--chronic inflammatory respiratory syndrome, a conditions which he said causes him overall lower quality healthy and all sorts of problems ranging from heart palpitations and immune system problems to just being generally sick all of the time.  Part of the reason he agreed to travel to the country we were supposed to meet in was because he wanted to 'decontaminate' from his fungal infection, and the weather where we traveled to would be good for that. I was eventually able to track him down in the main capital city and was finally able to meet him.  After flushing out more details, I listen to him talk about how he had to throw out all of his clothes upon arriving in our destination country because 'they were contaminated'.  Right now he basically is walking around a foreign country with nothing but the shirt on his back and no luggage.  The only other thing he has is a backpack.  I also noticed that he was not wearing any shoes and asked him about it.  He said that he could not wear shoes because they are closed and that that makes it easier for fungi to grow inside of it.  He therefore wears sandals that he can easily throw away.  He also has been keeping his money, credit cards, etc. in plastic bags so that he 'doesn't contaminate them'.  In another peculiar set of events he described, he said that 'secret police' were following him because of the fact that he bought 'organic fertilizer/cleaner' or something.  I asked him what that was for and he said it was to 'clean my credit card that got contaminated'.  I asked him for more details about how he knew the secret police were following him and he talked about how he was visiting a local park and while going to the bathroom 'saw two shady looking men' enter the bathroom and go into the stalls next to him.  They also apparently had walkie-talkies and were saying things (but he couldn't understand because it was a foreign language).  Later on he also said that those secret police actually met up with American spies in that country who were also keeping dibs on him to see what he was up to, so right now he claims that basically the entire populace of the country is harassing him via  a messaging app, that he is being followed by secret police, and that even the American government is spying on him.  He also says that people everywhere are saying the same shit talk phrases over and over to him.  We made it out to dinner together after meeting and I asked him if his condition affected his diet at all.  He said it definitely did and that he now has to avoid gluten, wheat, sugar, processed foods, etc.--basically anything that won't help fungi to grow.  I asked him if he still drank alcohol and he said that he definitely avoids beer because it uses yeast, but that he will still partake in whiskey and 'dry red whine'.  Puzzled about the fact that he said that he could still drink red wine but not beer, even though wine still requires yeast, I asked about it and he basically had nothing but hand waiving explanations (basically he forgot or didn't know that wine still requires yeast and yet was still fine drinking it--for me this raises a huge red flag that everything with him is completely psychological).  Further in our discussion over dinner, he said that people everywhere were secretly trying to take his photo and record audio of him and what he spoke.  He said that people everywhere who he never met before nor ever interacted with would repeat to him what he said in English during other previous instances, but are clearly doing it in a mockingly way.  Additionally, I come to find out that my friend had also 'lost his passport' according to him, but I could tell that he was probably lying and didn't want to say that he basically threw it away because 'it was contaminated'.  I eventually was able to contact his sister through facebook and she told me that he definitely destroyed his passport and cut it up.  In yet another hard to believe claim, he also said that while he was sight seeing in the city, a soldier who was guarding a government building was secretly and mockingly trying to point his rifle at my friend while he was walking by.  My friend said he 'pretended not to see the soldier doing it', but swore he knew that the soldier was pointing his weapon at my friend.  

 I'm worried that my friend will eventually encounter some physical harm because he says that he keeps yelling at local people who 'are taking his photo and recording him'.  I'm afraid that they won't understand that he might be mentally ill and will think he is either high on drugs or is drunk and physically harm him as a result.  If that doesn't happen, I'm also afraid he might also get into trouble with law enforcement in a foreign country who won't be able to understand what he's saying due to a language barrier.  Additionally, I don't know if he will ever leave the country because he might think that 'there are spies' at the embassy he needs to go to in order to replace his passport that he destroyed.  I met my friend over dinner and he seemed functional and can speak coherently and write coherent emails.  His feet and hands were dirty, but the rest of his appearance was clean and OK.  He also ate food without problems, but his stories make no sense at all and reek of paranoia.  He's constantly afraid of being followed and is being 'harassed' by just about everyone.  He also said that he suffered from chronic lyme disease--yet another controversial syndrome that isn't recognized by established medical science after through review and study.  Any thoughts?   Is my friend slipping into psychosis and becoming schizophrenic?  Is it just extreme OCD? A combo of both?  My friend is also planning on 'leaving the country and going to Spain to detox' because of all of his 'problems' that he's encountered in the country he's currently in.  My other worry is that he'll be traveling all over the globe to reach his goal of 'detoxing' and his family may never hear from him again.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 12:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, no way that's true.  Granted I don't know the exact laws, but it seems like there is hardly any motor vehicle emissions controls and enforcement anywhere in Thailand.  I will say, however, that I find the air in BKK much better than Chiang Mai's.  I know a large part of that is due to the topography of the land, but goddamn, those shared taxi red trucks in CM are absolutely nauseating from the horrible emissions that they spew out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I ate] 'Mall food' in Asia blows away mall food in the West. Quite authentic Issan Style Thai food in a typical mall in Bangkok. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 11:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 01:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  Best fruit in the world. They sell them in the US at ethnic food markets but 1.) they're like $20/lbs often and 2.) they're low quality--the skins are already rock hard a ton of times.  You must absolutely try them if you're in Thailand (although they're not really in season right now).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 09:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I read and interpreted the article more it sounds more like a materials process than actually molecularly changing sucrose.  Carbon is just carbon, but if you arrange the material in one way you get a super material like graphene, another way a material like diamond, or another way a material that you can grill your steak in.  Maybe they found some other way to crystalize the structure of sucrose that has some sort of longer half life on the tongue so that they can use less sugar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 08:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glyco scientist here. I smell shenanigans.  A Japanese scientist already cracked a systematic way of reaching every sugar possible years ago--a strategy now called Izumoring--so I don't know really what breakthrough kit Kat food scientists have created :
https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16233597
. http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0168165606003233 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've always rented a car.  It costs a little bit more, but it gives you wayyyy more range and freedom. Just drive slowly to start to get used to driving. Taxis often ripoff tourists big time. Compared to Chiang Mai and Bangkok, driving around the Phuket region is a cinch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: what prevents countries from simply dividing their currency values by powers of 10? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 10:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay the course. If he's healthy all year there's no reason he won't breakout big.  It is hard to believe that he's still only 24 y.o. so he still has upside.   Don't forget, it can take players a looooooong time to come back from brain injuries which can be truly frightening.  It took Bergeron years to come back and be fantasy relevant after his devastating hits to the head.   Players that comeback from TBIs probably need to start all over from scratch again building up their confidence to go in dirty into the boards and to crash the net w no hesitation. Skinner is back baby.  Who knows what this kid could have done if he stayed healthy all those formative years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tried every combo possible today. The seat is even heated.  We absolutely need to make these thundermugs standard in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your toilet can do this you know you're not in Kansas anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 05:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that nearly all of the Presidentially pardoned turkeys are now dead due to the fact that the turkeys used for Thanksgiving are bred for the table and not for the ability to live long and healthy lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bergeron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 06:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One weakness for Obama's legacy:  foreign policy.  He wasn't really good at it.  Not really sure why the Dems pushed for war, expansion of NATO, and anti-Russian rhetoric so, so much.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, checkout Delaware--  21 states have tried to sue Delaware because DE takes over $400 million in unclaimed check money that should have gone to other states.  Check seizures account for 13% of DE's entire state budget and is used to plug budget holes, meaning DE is further enticed to take money that belongs to other states.     

http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-delaware-states-idUSKCN0YV1QS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't yell at you.  The problem is that biologists don't ask questions in the first place because they have no idea that they're doing something wrong.  If you came to me asking why you extraction were low, I'd gladly explain that if you extract a molecule with acidic groups using slightly basic aqeous solutions and an orgainc layer, you might be losing a lot of it in the aqeous because you made a salt which is water soluble.  The problem is getting biologists to recognize something like adjusting pH with HCl for a buffer that shouldn't contain Cl ions is wrong in the first place.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's obvious. Like I said, I see the worst of both worlds.  A lot.  Chemists that don't know fuck about doing cell culture and contaminate everything when they try to do everything themselves and test their molecules they made.  

If you're building a multimillion dollar pharmaceutical company and your biologists fuck up an inhibition assay because they didn't give 2 craps that the target they're working with has allosteric sites for chloride ions and they wrongly used HCl to adjust a buffer that's used in the screening assays, well then, you could advance a molecule on a  complete set of wrongly acquired data and waste millions of dollars.  And who'd be more at fault here, the chemists making the molecules for screening or the biologists making the buffers for their assays? There's no excuse for not caring or not knowing basic chemistry principles as a biologist/molecular biologist, as condescending as that sounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I apologize. My initial intent was not to sound like a douchebag and I can see now how my comment could be construed as such. But it was intended to at least instill a little bit of panic for anyone doing something like adjusting a TRIS buffer with something like NaOH.  The hope is that they'd go and look up acid base chemistry, relearn the concept of a Lewis acid, learn themselves how to properly adjust pH for buffers, relearn the concepts of ionic strength and it's biological importance, relearn which chemical groups are acids and bases etc.  If I simply gave the answers I feel like labrats wouldn't learn as much if they corrected themselves. So much of life, biology, and molecular biology is extremely sensitive to basic chemical principles and it is quite disconcerting the woeful lack of attention to basic chemistry I've seen in the lab constantly by people working in the biomedical sciences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. Why use enzymes that work a trillion fold faster when you have lowly paid lab serf sweat to catalyze the reactions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've spent 20 seconds to look up the actual structure of Tris before right?  You're not using HCl to adjust the pH of acetate buffers too right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10e, 100e, 1000e for me plz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or are a lot of biologists woefully ignorant of basic chemistry principles? Might this be a reason for the lack of reproducible science? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to sound judgemental or elitist or anything, but some of the basic lack of knowledge about chemistry coming from biologists has astounded me at times.  I'm talking about people in PhD programs or post-doc biologists.   For example, how important are buffers for almost all of molecular biology and biomedical work? Many times I've come across collaborators who work with our lab that are following a protocol to say make Tris-HCl buffer.  The pH is off so the first thing they grab is NaOH to adjust the pH.  ::Cringe::. I've seen a hella lot of people get frustrated that EDTA has a hard time dissolving in water.   They don't realize it is acidic and that the salt is much more soluble after a pH adjustment.  Other times people have been looking for drugs that contain groups like carboxylic acids, phenols, etc. from a biological sample. During the extraction process they'll use something like PBS w pH=7.4 and either wonder where their molecule went after they threw the PBS away, wonder why they have low extraction efficiency, or worse, don't even think about it all and report the numbers from their terrible extraction methods.  Sorry to rant about chemistry.  I understand chemists don't always understand basic biology or techniques a lot of times too, but as someone who does a ton of biological chemistry I see the worst of both worlds. I mean I understand a ton of biologists probably passed organic, gen chem, and biochemistry with flying colors in the classroom, but that knowledge seems to often go out the window when they're at the bench actually doing lab work. Adjusting buffers wrongly with the wrong acid/base and not even caring about ionic strength effects......that really gets me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That feeling you get when chemienzymatic methods synthesize in only 30 minutes what you've been trying to synthetically make for the past 5 months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now if only your boss would have listened to you in the beginning that it would have made much more sense to bite the bullet and spend money buying enzymes rather than trying to do this crap by hand and spending 5 months of failing to boot. Going from atrocious TLCs that look like a poop streak to single spots on TLC w/ enzymes. Touche mother nature, you fam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The local grocery store was charging $6.99 *per ounce* for some fucking bugs.  No thanks.  At that price, it'd cost more than a very fine Waygu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that only about 1% out of 1.25 billion people in India pay taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA request: somebody in India who is currently dealing with the currency swap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to know how chaotic it has been, especially if you have large sums of cash to trade in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in other words, the vast majority of Americans were NOT in favor of killing off the Japanese?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 09:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chapelle Show was HUUUUUUUUUUUUUUGE back in college.  Everyone kept saying 'I'M RICK JAMES BITCH!' for forever.  I'd say it was even more popular than even the Walking Dead and/or GOT at its peak.  It was literally the most watched show on TV during its time slot and Chapelle was slated to make an insane salary, which made it all the more shocking he turned all of that money down and simply walked away.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 07:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Showed this to my undergraduate researchers.  They didn't get any of it.  Man, can't believe this was over 10 years ago already.  Fuck getting old.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 07:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She'd be hipster hot by today's standards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their pork shank is one of my most favorite dishes in ALL of Baltimore.  One of our most fav. spots to go.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wicked Sisters just opened too. Their Sunday chicken dinner was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um,.....yeah.  That's exactly what Reagan youth did wrt their name.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the punk band Crass was able to spook both the MI6 and the US State Department by releasing a phony tape recording of Ronald Reagan and Margaret Thatcher discussing using Europe as a nuclear battlefield front against the USSR. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the point?  A play off of Reagan Youth?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magdalena:  http://www.magdalenarestaurant.com/

$$$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is peptidyl t-RNA after cell lysis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm following a protocol to isolate p-trna.  It is typcal lysis for for a western blot.  The only thing that confuses me, however, is whether or not the lysis should be cleared like you do for a WB.  Does the debris in a tube after spinning down the lysate contain p-trna or is it in the soluble fraction?  Should be soluble, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media completely over hyped the importance of the Latino/minority vote and wrote off the old and/or working class white vote.  Lo and behold they still matter.  A lot.  The moronic media did nothing more than encourage white people to vote the opposite of what they wanted as a 'fuck you'.  Especially with shit like 'declining importance of white vote' flashed all over outlets like CNN.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0 problems.  Took 20 minutes.  You can't expect to go vote before work, during lunch hour, or after work and for there to be no line.  Everyone is trying to do that.  I went specifically around 10:15 AM to avoid the before work and during lunch crowd.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then again, they're Hopkins students---the same ones paying ~$1400 per mo. *each* for an apartment for 4 people in the new building that opened up right on top of this place. This place will make a killing from the students, although it'll probably be impossible to find a place to sit because there will be students camped out for hours on end after buying one coffee and sitting on the computer all day while hogging space and doing their homework and BSing on the internet.  There at a lot of Hopkins kids that have no concept of money, what is considered expensive, or what being broke is like because they've been swimming in money their whole lives.  Not that it bothers me at all, they're good kids for the most part.  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should definitely set if you put it in a mould and chill it, the only thing I can't guarantee you though is how easy it will be to get out.  I've never tried it--just eaten it as is, but moulding it is worth a shot. You might have to coat the mould with some butter or non-stick spray or something.  Good luck!  And I never thought about it as a gluten free dessert, but I suppose it is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0 audits of the Housing Authority in years.  21% of all taxes goes to pay for police (which is by far and away absurd, according to the challenger at least, when you compare it to other cities).  0 city wide, full scale audit in years.  Pugh and Pratt have a business together, conflicting interest?  And people wonder where allllllllll of their money goes to provide crappy services.  The challenger sounds well educated and level headed, and has experience running a small business in the city.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My grandmother's chocolate blancmange recipe. Nothing fancy, just delicious and simple to make. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my grandmother's recipe  for chocolate blancmange.  My brother and I loved this when we were kids and still do to this day.  The recipe is very easy and straightforward, have fun making it with your own children or making it for them.  You can also make it 'fancy' by aliquoting it out in any type of mold or dish if you need to make a quick dessert for a dinner party or want to impress some guests without spending a lot of time making a dessert.  It is also fantastic with some whipped cream and berries.  Just thought I'd share this recipe since I enjoyed this so much as a kid growing up.  Hopefully my grandmother would be pleased to see that other people get enjoyment from her recipe too.  


**Ingredients**

* 2oz bitter unsweetened chocolate 

* 2 Tbl  butter

* 1/3 C cornstarch

* 3/4 C sugar

* 1/4 tsp salt

* 3 C whole milk

* 1 tsp vanilla

**Directions**

1.) Melt chocolate   butter in double boiler.  If you don't have double boiler simply use a high quality bowl to lay on top of pot with boiling water.  Make sure bowl does not touch the surface of the water or is immersed in the boiling water.   

2.) Mix together cornstarch, sugar,   salt.  Stir in about 1/4 C milk, mixing well to remove lumps of cornstarch.  

3.) Add to melted chocolate   stir thoroughly.  Add the rest of  the milk   cook over direct heat, stirring constantly in a figure 8 motion until mixture boils
  thickens. 

4.) Replace over boiling water, cover, and cook 15 minutes longer. Stir occasionally.

5.) Remove from heat. Stir in vanilla. Cool before serving.  Makes 5 servings.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strength Through Oi!? Assessing the Fitness Benefits of Punks Knucklehead Stepchild </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 02:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh 8-8 season expected.  Still need a few more pieces for a meaningful push.  The schedule hasn't even started getting difficult yet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eagles fans, is it still Wentzylvania? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they finally, finally start getting Wilmington properly developed after alllllllllllllll of these years of languish.  I don't see why Wilmington can't become say a Richmond, Va type of city.  There's great architecture in a lot of the old homes there, there simply needs to be 'things to do' to encourage people to start moving in.  That includes catering to younger families.  There is an absoluter dearth of tech industry in DE.  It would be great if Wilmington could start becoming a low tax haven to develop tech hubs that are bio and computer related.  Outside of the financial sector,  health care, and legal services, there are very little quality jobs.  Dupont is about to axe a ton of more jobs and the chemical industry is toast.  Pharma is all but gone.  Wilmington needs to strive to develop economic diversity.  It would be awesome, for example, if Wilmington provided municipal high speed internet access at a low cost like a Chattanooga, TN.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this is too late--but have you thought about checking out Mt. Vernon Marketplace?  You can walk to the The Walters so easily from there.  My favorite in there is Ful Cafe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Except for a few details in this speech, you could cut out Patrick Bateman from the 1980s and he would still be considered relevant in today's world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 04:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to burn it though...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the ferocious Dodge Charger SRT Hellcat is capable of sucking out all of the air in a 10 x 13 ft room in only 1 minute. Its fuel injectors can also fill a pint class in 6 seconds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part about this is that the LEGO version of a DC character will probably be better than any of the live action crap DC has produced in the past 5 or 6 years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you can still load 25 ug of protein, just make the samples more concentrated.  For example, if my precast gels say they can only hold 30 uL per well, at max I'd probably use 25 uL of sample, preferably only 20 uL.  I've tried using 30 uL before, even 28 uL and had spill over issues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What volume is the max the wells can hold? What volume are you loading?  I'd load at least 10% less than what is listed as the max well volume, a lot of times they can spill over.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your position on drug legalization? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Just uber it.  Especially at night.  Baltimore St. can get bad at night, and you want to stay away from 'the block'.  We literally came back from a restaurant from that area to find a guy who broke into our car trying to steal shit.  Uber might cost you nothing for that short trip...like $5-10 or something.  Saving $10 isn't worth your computer or safety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to drive *everywhere* in DE.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 05:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhh as a sugar biologist, this grinds my gears (although you're getting a totally biased opinion here).  For the longest time scientists ignored sugar biology, and many still do to this day,  because we've been taught DNA=protein= life from primary school.   What we started to recognize, however, at the turn of the century and several decades after the discovery of DNA was that there is an extra layer of complexity on top of the genetic code that's regulating life.  One such example is the glycocode - the entire set of sugar modifications on proteins and lipids that assist on regulating life.  It is now believed that the entire glycocode, in theory, is potentially many times more complex than the entire genetic code and it has also been described as 'one of the most complex entities in nature'.  

The cell membrane doesn't really look like what is in the video.  The cell membrane is absolutely covered in a dense layer of sugar. In fact, this sugar layer (aka glycocalyx) can sometimes be even as big or even bigger in terms of size than the cell itself, e.g. check out this 'halo' which is a hyaluronan coat around a chondrocyte:

http://imgur.com/a/nELHg

That's alllllllllll sugar, but you can often miss sugars under the microscope because you can't see them unless you do some specific types of special experiments to make them visually appear.  

All of the little lipids on the cell membrane that are dancing around in the video--covered in sugar.  All of the proteins on the surface that are shown in the video--covered in sugar.  It is also functionally very important.  For example, cholera toxin infects you by not even binding to a protein, it is able to make you sick by binding to the glycolipid known as GM1: 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GM1#/media/File:GM1_ganglioside.png 

Without the sugar portion, cholera can not infect. Have you ever wondered why the flu goes by the scientific name HxNy (where x and y are numbers)?  H actually stands for hemagglutinin and N stands for neuramindase.  Hemagglutin is a protein on the flu virus that recognizes and binds to a special sugar on your cells   known as sialic acid in order to infect:

[sialic acid](https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Roland_Schauer/publication/13546760/figure/fig8/AS:281848363143171@1444209294500/Fig-8-Functional-groups-of-sialic-acid-interacting-with-siglecs-The-functional-groups.png)

In order to escape the cell and infect other healthy cells, the flu virus then chops off sialic acids from the infected cell use N (neuramidase).  Want to also guess what one of the first lines of defense your body has against infection?  Your body produces what is known as mannose binding lectins (MBL).  Lectins are a special class of proteins that recognize and bind to sugars.  MBL recggnizes unnatural sugar patterns on the membranes of bacteria, fungi, protozoa, and viruses to trigger innate response.  

http://cid.oxfordjournals.org/content/41/Supplement_7/S440.full

How about the beginning of life?  You literally wouldn't even be born if it weren't for sugars on membranes that aren't shown in the video.  For example, in order for the sperm to bind to and find its way into an egg, a special sugar known as sialyl lewis X (sLeX for short) is absolutely required:

[sLex structure](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/e6/Sialyl_lewis_x.svg/1280px-Sialyl_lewis_x.svg.png)

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21852454


Development?  There's a really neat type of polymer of sugars made from sialic acids (the same sugar that the flu binds to described above) known as polysialic acid (PSA).  PSA is found at the synapses of neurons and behaves almost like a 'hydrogel'.  By regulating the amount of sugars and PSA at the ends of neurons, your body can remodel synapses and the rewiring of brain to impact learning, memory, and development:  

http://www.cell.com/trends/neurosciences/fulltext/0166-2236(96)10041-2

Finally, the video showed a lot of cell-cell/cell adhesion interactions (e.g. the selectin binding shown and the leukocyte tethering, rolling, and invasion).  Guess how that's allllllllllll regulating.  By the sugar on the surfaces of cells that are on proteins/lipids and which are not shown in the video.  Just like the sperm/egg interaction, sLeX is absolutely essential for selectin binding and is required for leukocyte tethering/rolling/invasion like what you saw in the vid. Here's a little cartoon of what is shown in the vid:
http://www.frontiersin.org/files/Articles/30245/fonc-02-00076-r2/image_m/fonc-02-00076-g006.jpg

All of the little hairy stuff shown in the cartoon on the cell that's rolling along the surface would be covered in sugar. Without it, your immune system and inflammatory response wouldn't work.  


TL;DR:  cranky sugar biology person rants about how sugars are important for life too and is upset they're not in the $5M video.  Goes on to give examples of how sugars can be important.  

::end rant::







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 03:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many negative people.  How about y'all start your own business too so we can trash it before trying it?   FWIW, no where did I catch the owner of it calling it a 'fried chicken concept' , rather that is on the writer from the Sun.  I did a little bit further digging and BRD apparently stands for baked, roasted, and fried...whatever that means.  So maybe it really is indeed a unique take on fried chicken .  Good lord, at least have an open mind.  What would you rather have there? An abandoned warehouse that used to be there or someone at least trying to start a business and someone who pays taxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but what do you do or how do you interpret the feedback when one reviewer can understand the proposal while reviewer 3 sounds like they're lost in the woods?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not so much the frustration with getting rejected, that's expected...the frustration comes with getting almost nonsensical feedback from the reviewers who either don't understand the proposal, didn't read it thoroughly, or didn't even bother with looking at other related details.  I mean being told that you have no cancer related research experience even though that's all you've published on for the past decade is nonsensical.  It is really annoying to have to waste inordinate amounts of time writing grants only to have a NIH panel reject your application because they apparently didn't even bother reading your biosketch which even listed cancer related publications.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so sick of the whole grant writing process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how we got points off of our grant and received a score of 4 for expertise because "It is suspect that the PI is an expert in cancer and cancer biology"......even though that's the only thing our lab has ever published on for the past decade and even though the NIH previously even gave us a R01 for cancer related research.  Grant writing is such a waste of time to be thrown into a mind warping meat grinder that makes no sense.  

I mean sure, we aren't Bert Volgelstein's lab or anything, but is the NIH only going to fund extraordinarily famous superstar labs now?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Frolik--a possible late bloomer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy has been around forever, so it is hard to remember that he is still only 28.  He was also once a 1st round, 10th overall pick.  Will he keep up the scoring this year? I simply don't watch enough of the Flames to see how he is looking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run a quick TLC.  If one spot (assuming you didn't have a mix of isomers or something), go run NMR.  NMR looks good, then you're OK.  Honestly,  $1000 really isn't a lot of money in biomedical research.   Every time I have to order stupid biohazard waste boxes it is $150.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burned out my HDD.  Almost lost alllllllllllllllllllllllllll of my PhD work....5 yr. worth.  Had to pay $2k for recovery. Luckily the lab covered it, but I learned a good lesson.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their shrimp w/ grits are awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a pet owner w/ two cats.  I don't understand why anyone would let their cat out in the city.  They could get hit by a car, get into a fight with rats and other feral animals, and worst of all, there are simply weirdos, psychopaths, and flatout aholes that could and will do whatever to your pet.  Smaller animals, especially peoples' pets, are stolen off the street and used for sickening things like bait to train a dog to maim/kill for illegal dog fighting.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not healthy yet.  Your core is important for almost everything hockey related, plus he probably didn't get enough training in while recovering.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like the Nicholas Cage of directing....make a whole bunch of terrible stuff and sprinkle in with a few gems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why I like the NHL way way more than the NFL and football.  Plus the NHL playoffs are the best out of any sport.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HFboards for hockey news.  Left wing lock for starting goalies.  This sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patience.  He's just getting over what was probably a nasty illness, judging by how long he was out. I'd definitely hold him since there is a good chance he is with benn and seguin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the witch hunt begins, the professor should at least have a chance to tell their side of the story.  Maybe they really did indeed catch plagiarism or thought they did.  We had students (premeds of course) threaten to sue the university and a professor because they received 0s on homeworks for turning it in late, claiming that they received 0s because they were minorities or because they were women in science.  They were ABSOLUTELY convinced that they were right and that they did nothing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what I'm looking at. Never owned any apple stuff.  The issue is that you can't plug it directly into your comp? Or it is because you can't listen to the headphones while it is charging? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benn is the perfect buy low candiate right now.  Benn owners are frustrated.  I think he is still injured or isn't 100% healthy yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 12:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bergeron, Benn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL learned that a single adult mussel can filter out sediment and pollution from 15 gallons of water in a single day. Mussel populations in the Brandywine watershed filter out as much as 25 tons of suspended pollution every year, equivalent to about 3 dump trucks full of dirt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still rocking discharge on my way to and from the science lab for work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Uber eats and all over the other food delivery services.  They if the fucking streets up and cause massive jams on major roads in the city everywhere because instead of having one deliver go out and deliver 10 deliveries you now have 10 cars driving to the restaurant to pick up food, which is almost always not ready because the kitchen is slammed so the drivers have to leave their cars outside double parked.  Yesterday there was a line of 8 fucking cars double parked behind each other on a 2 way street  with single lanes in each direction. This was during a busy time of the evening too when everyone is trying to get home.  Because here was sooooo much on coming traffic and because there was a long line of cars double parked ahead it made it impossible for traffic to go through. Uber eats and the like sound nice in theory until they clog up your neighborhood or commute with insane amounts of traffic because the drivers have no option other than to double park when they have to pick up from a restaurant in a busy area where parking can be hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 15:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, OK Putin......this, coming from the same guy and country that thinks they can rightfully take back Alaska:

http://www.npr.org/sections/parallels/2014/04/01/297835873/not-an-april-fools-joke-russians-petition-to-get-alaska-back

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 05:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flyers are stuck in mediocre purgatory hell.  The NHL rewards tankers far too much, meanwhile if you cling to a slightly above average season and make the first round of the playoffs you'll never get high quality draft picks and will constantly be stuck with mediocre season after mediocre season.. The Flyers would be better off tanking for 2-3 seasons and building up like the Oilers.  Pens, Lightning, Kings, Blackhawks ...all previously trash teams for the longest time that got the best picks to improve.  All won cups.  This will be another typical season for the flyers.  Hover around and struggle to maintain .500, barely claw their way into the playoffs, 1st round exit.  Crappy draft pick next year again.  Rinse and repeat next season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free block party in Canton. 900 expected already.  Room to sign up still.

http://www.meetup.com/BaltimoreSocial/events/234291977/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30% H2O next time might do the trick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently 70% ethanol is now a violation of your lab is above 3 stories high in a building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love when the safety people come up with new rules they tell no one about yet find you guilty of breaking them.  Apparently no one is allowed to make a batch of 70% Etoh now. Anything flammable stored in a container over 4 liters is prohibited.  I mean the other 2000 labs across the university that do biology don't have large containers of 70% etoh around the lab near the hoods or anything....oh  wait that's right, nearly every cell biology lab across the country bathes in gallons of the stuff everyday while working in the lab.  Ahhhhh safety do gooders...what can you do?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup,  I've had nothing but a HUGE amount of frustration with the Turbo2 and I've been a motorola fan for the longest time.  My original phone stopped turbo charging and would take 12 hours just to get 40% charge.  I sent it back for a refurbished phone and it stopped charging all together after only about 3 months.  I even bought 2 new power cords and tried a total of 4.  It is definitely the phone.  Such a headache for something I still have an entire year of contract on to pay off.  Judging from some internet searches and this sub, the DT2 seems to have a lot of issues with its battery and/or charging.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Skinner DTD, anyone have more details? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear if it is another concussion.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually pretty smart.  I bet she knows exactly what she's doing too + giving 0 fucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tecmo Superbowl

NHL 94, 95, 96

Streets of Rage 2

Street Fighter II championship edition

Dragon Warrior

Zelda

Ocarina of Time

Resident Evil 4

Resident Evil

General Chaos

Mickey Mania

Double Dragon 2

Earth Worm Jim

Comix Zone

Toe Jam and Earl

Golden Axe

Zombies ate my Neighbors

NBA Jam

MOrtal Kombat

TMNT Turtles in Time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well what did you expect? It's a sports bar with bar food.  Take CVP and spice it up with a new interior, that's probably what you get.  We get it, it doesn't serve locally grown, organic crap and $28 cheeseburgers from grass fed beef.  It is filling a niche in a market in the area that wasn't filled before.  I mean frazier's is there too, but it doesn't draw in the non-locals as much.  It will probably make a killing too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 14:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must read that is easy to follow:

http://www.nature.com/nprot/journal/v3/n6/full/nprot.2008.73.html

But yes, take the mean of the technicals.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, he most certainly has near genius level intellect, even though he can be toolish at times.  He's consumed an insane amount of film, music, and literature in his lifetime.  Not to mention some other things.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's wishful thinking.  If the projections for hotel revenue don't turn out as planned, guess who's on the hook for the bill?  Clark County taxpayers.  There are countless examples where the projections don't come to fruition.  See the Orlando basketball arena which caused a near default on hotel tax backed bonds. Stanford economist Roger Noll also called the LV deal for $750 million in tax dollars 'the worst he's ever seen', noting that Adelson and Davis are projecting 33% of tickets going to tourists when no other NFL team even manages 10% and also said that The idea that the thing is going to pay for itself based on a huge inflow of tourists is crazy. 

And there is absolutely NO mention of the possibility that public money will be used for maintenance and operating expenses, AFAIK.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, for the most part all of the places mentioned that SHOULDN'T have hockey are particularly successful: Ducks, Kings, Lightning all have cups.  Canada as an entire nation hasn't hoisted a cup for over 20 years.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still fail to see how this is 'OK'.  A tax increase is still an increase.  Americans from somewhere are paying more for something to fund the construction for a project of a privately owned team.  Why would it be 'outrageous' to increase taxes on hotels, gaming, and 'sinful foods' to fund schools and road repairs, yet if we increase taxes on hotel fees to pay for NFL stadiums it is OK?  It is OK to tax Americans who don't have the ability to vote?  I thought that's what caused this country to start a war for independence in the first place?   If you can approve say an increase from 12% hotel tax to 17% in a locality, it is still baffling why that 5% shouldn't be used to fund police, schools, roads, or to build parks for that locality.  And what happens if more and more people decide to stay home and not attend games, bad weather ravages tourism, or something else unforseable happens to decrease hotel revenue?  It won't be enough to cover the cost and bond holders will be responsible for all of the risk for building a stadium owned by a private entity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, I wouldn't be that pessimistic-- they'll probably get some talent too from teams that simply need salary cap relief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 19:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eagles won't make the playoffs.  They lost 2 games they should have won and they have an INSANE schedule.  Just hope they take this as a learning/rebuilding year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that doesn't seem like a lot, it still is -- the largest amount ever asked by a NFL team for a stadium.  The Las Vegas NHL owner recently also took a shot at the NFL and the raiders and said that tax payer money could be better used for schools and roads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Las Vegas' new NHL team will use an arena funded by 0 taxpayer dollars. Meanwhile, the NFL's Raiders are asking for $750 million upfront in public money to fund the construction of a new stadium in order to relocate to LV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 18:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only knock preventing Kershaw from being one of the top 3 greatest pitchers of all time is that he almost never does well in the post season. Why does he always fall apart when it matters most? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 06:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E.g. press the button the window goes all the way down.  But if it goes too far down you pull the button up and the stupid window doesn't stop where you want it to.  Then you have to hit the button again in order to get it where you want.  Why doesn't it just work like a passenger's window in a lot of cars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the point of the non-intuitive way a lot of driver's side automatic windows roll down/up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 06:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cuffs

The Boils

Oi Scouts

US Chaos

Flux of Pink Indians

Slapshot

Poxy

Violent Society

Tom and Boot Boys

Fleas and Lice

Funeral Dress
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For now the best strategy may be to do nothing. The fact that we can figure out who was behind it and even detect it means they're not doing the best job.  It would be completely unwise to reveal your cards now and reveal what the US is truly capable of on the cyber front over such a small skirmish that you can fix.  It is highly doubtful that the hacking is going to have any effect on the election outcomes anyway.  I mean I understand sending g a strong message as a deterrent to not mess with future elections, buy at the same time we need to hold projects like Nitro Zeus as close to our chest as much as possible unless it is WW3.  Russia is hacking the election, but the fundamental mistake they're making is that they don't really understand American politics.  For alllllll of the antics they're trying, nothing has been particularly effective or potent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NHL fan stashes nachos under urinal, disgusts humanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NHL fan stashes nachos under urinal, disgusts humanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you can look like an even a bigger tool than when you wore Google glass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5: How does he have scars if he has super duper healing factor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened near where I work too and we got a security alert about it.  Woman was carjacked and thrown out of her car. Once the robber realized he was trying to steal a manual transmission car he bailed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the mailbox.  Literally.  They sent it out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about that bacon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 08:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many ways to label carbohydrates, just do a little bit of research.  Nearly 100% of the time they involve taking advantage of the fact that aldohexoses like glucose have ring opened forms w/ aldhydes at the end.  You can then do reductive amination with an array of probes.  Detection can be HPLC.  If you don't have HPLC, you can use a very handy technique that is dirt cheap known as fluorophore assisted carbohydrate electrophoresis--it is like a western blot for sugars.  Label your sugar with something like 2-aminoacridone and run the gel.  You can make a standard curve of glucose on the gel and use it to quantify the amount of glucose from your sample.  There do exist other more advanced and specialized techniques, such as PAD w/ HPLC that don't even need labeling chemistries, but a HPLC that can handle it is even more specialized and rare.  Finally, there are also all sorts of commercially available, easily do-able colometric based kits available.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're awesome, when are you going to run for mayor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've only been once, but out of everything we ordered our favorite app was the tuna belly crudo.
The scallops were also amazing, but I was also looking at a lot of other peoples' sandwiches and they looked really good to. Finally, the bread pudding is out of this world if you like desserts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 07:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll add:

1157 

Gnocco

Magdalena (but maybe this is too pricey for everyone) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the city turning out the lights? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been seeing multiple blocks north of North Ave. with the street lights out.  Especially in the CV area.  I also saw a block in Fed Hill with the lights out.  I don't think it is a grid problem because this has been going on for over a week.  And it only seems to be about one to two blocks at a time, nothing really bigger.  For example, around the 28/29/30th st and St. Paul area it has been very dark recently, and it can be hard to see pedestrians while driving at night. What gives? Is this a crime reduction strategy? (just remember reading a news article a while ago that turning out the lights supposedly reduced crime) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off, American bacon is still delicious as shit.  Actually, I much prefer it over other types.  I've tried most.  Back bacon/Brit style bacon doesn't have enough fat.  It's just trendy to hate something because 'it is American', when Americans are indeed capable of producing some great food products.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flesh-eating screwworms return to U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 21:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing how uncool smoking is these days compared to the 80s and even 90s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the accuri c6 is a little different (strange from what some other people say who have used other FACS)--you can't change the gain and voltage--they're already optimized and fixed by BD.  They sell it as a way to make the C6 'as easy as possible' to operate for anyone.  

For your second point, I guess I don't really understand how titrating down will work. For example this is what I'm thinking:

If I have 1000 molecules X in sample A and 850 molecules of X in sample B and use 750 molecules of the clicking fluorophore I'll label 750 molecules in both A and B (assuming that the reaction is 100% efficient).  Even though 750 might be back in the dynamic range, I've lost the information that there was indeed a difference between sample A and B for molecule X since I'm now only detecting 750 in both of them. That's why I'm pretty sure that the clickable fluorophore needs to be in molar excess of molecule X.  Not an antibody biding, it is a pure organic chemistry reaction where the fluorophore must be not be the limiting reagent. 

It really would raise some eyebrows to reduce the emission/intensity of the signal for all samples by using the 585/40 filter for Alex 488?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Convince your PI to just buy precast gels.  The headaches of trying to track down what went wrong when you precast simple isn't worth the time and cost, because time is money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fluorescence signal over saturated in flow cytometry. Can I use a non-optimal emission filter to detect in flow cytometry in order to reduce the signal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't done a whole lot of optical/fluorescence work and have small amounts of experience working with fluorophores here.  The problem I have is that my labeling chemistry is *too* good.  I'm using alexa fluor 488 to label some cells with click chemistry.  I have a control treated with the fluorophore in order to get a background reading.  The treated sample with the clickable fluorophore labels so extremely well over the control at the proper setting (FL1-A: 488 ex 533/30 em) for alexa 488 that the fluorescence signal is off the charts and out of the dynamic range of the instrument.  If I change the setting to use FL2-A the signal is back in the dynamic range of the instrument (FLA-2 laser: 488 ex  585/40).  I'm using an accuri c6 flowcytometer.  My question is, would it be OK to report the data using the FLA2-A reading even though the emission filter is not optimal? I don't see why it wouldn't be valid as long as all of the samples use the same setting and it gets the signal back into the dynamic range of the instrument.  Is there anything wrong with this approach?

The other issue is that I really can't titrate down the fluorophore, because the goal is to click the fluorophore to as many labeled molecules as possible (fluorophore needs to be in molar excess of the molecules I'm clicking it to). Background fluorescence isn't really the problem-it's that every cell has so many clickable molecules in it that it saturates the instrument since the labeling works too well. I need to reduce the total fluoresence per cell, so I was thinking about using a different emission wavelength that wasn't optimal for alexa 488.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm originally from DE too.  How ya doing?  Anyways, what is your estimate for your GoFundMe page that you would have to reach in order drag this case on the courts for so long that your rivals would become bankrupt or would have to give up dkrsck of funds? Do they have deep pockets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Born, raised, and lived in DE for 25+ years.  DE is weiiiirdddd.  Holy S I'm so glad I left that state.  This conflict also takes place in the south , where it is even more strange.  I'm telling you man, DE people are on a different planet; it is just a weird ass state that no one really enjoys living in, no one wants to visit, and there's really nothing there.  People are so bored there they'll sue you for entertainment because of a garage on your rural property that creates 'noise'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely despised Star Wars ep.1 and 2.  Haven't seen the latest one either, but this one has my interest piqued.  

BTW, what the hell does Donnie Yen eat and drink?  Looks damn good for being 53.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you speed up to pass through a stale yellow, a cop in many states can ticket you.  I've gotten one myself.  The reasoning is that if you speed up to beat a late yellow, it means you had enough time to stop.  I tried to fight it in court and that's what the judge threw at me.  Regardless, the video shows the dashcam car going through a redlight him/herself.  See exactly at :25.  The car isn't even through the intersection and the light is red.  The car ran the red itself along w/ the BMW.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, we have a 'no douchebag rule' in fantasy baseball because one year I tried to win OBP for the week after I had 1 batter start on Monday who went 4/4.  I then tried to sit every single batter for the week (there's really no AB limits) in order to lock up 1.0000 OBP.  You might ask yourself why would I punt the other offensive categories.  It was because I was trying to lock up the division title.  I had a crap ton of closers, my opponent had 0, and all I needed was to win 4 categories.  My pitching was far superior, so I had that pretty much locked up.  In the end it worked, but my little experiment didn't fly over well w/ the rest of the league.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driver w/ dashcam ran the red light too.  Running through a late yellow can be ticketed too.  And why are so many BMW drivers aholes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is her hair dry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1976 the mayor of Montreal declared before the Olympic games that "The Olympics can no more lose money than a man can have a baby." He was wrong. Mismanagement and gross cost overruns left the city with $1.5 billion of debt that wasn't paid off until 2006. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
