<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3508</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like [this big](https://americanliterature.com/author/joseph-martin-kronheim/short-story/the-little-old-woman-who-lived-in-a-shoe) of a shoe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is "GR"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, they cannot both have their shit sandwich and eat it, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> opposition to *what FOX claimed* was the Democratic vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I really don't want to wait until 2020... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who could have know that English was so hard?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, *"rigor mortis"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is not a monolith. But generally when someone says "Russia", they mean the Kremlin. 

As far as the US government wanting to see Russia destabilized, I doubt it. Would they like to see Putin stop acting like a dick? Yes. But no-one in their right mind wants Russia to be more unstable than it currently is. 

And there you have it - you and I probably see these things/events differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, ok. Just by "Russian play" it sounded like the Russian government doing two different things, whereas I was looking at it like "Russian/pro-Putin play" vs "Not the Russian state/anti-Putin guy play" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy, Alexander Lebedev, is anti-Putin. 

Read this for example. It's behind a pay wall, but you can glean some info from the paragraphs which are visible.

http://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/russia-falling-to-dark-forces-beyond-putins-control-brv6mm7l6dj



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you share some details of those differences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a pothole if it's not as big as a pot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, they can't drink it up, i guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I was ready to castigate OP for posting old news!

/s not really, i figured it was in fact a new low. too bad it's not in the 20s yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is Hillary is doing all she can to not be ignored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>           .      -  , ? 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is the future Republicans want for ~~our country~~ their party.


FTFY.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he probably thinks that golfing = meeting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was certainly a nice, feel-good opinion piece! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Devin Nunes' own finincial ties to a Russian Winery

wat??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you, time traveller! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to need some proof that Flynn "ain't dumb". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should clarify that by "recently, you mean a year ago.

Still worth the listen though. I love how Koppel calls out O'Reilly personally for the state of journalism today and O'Reilly doesn't even bother to argue him on that point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I supect he might not have know (at the time), but Manafort sure did. And after the convention, I think Trump knew it, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she will wish it was gone and he will be glad it is still there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Deltawerks

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Delta_Works

And the [pic](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/7c/91/30/7c91300a2eecba373e0e5deba48a7297.jpg)!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thighs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love a follow-up of this story, where the reporter shows the same people this thread and asks their reopnses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, then where are my promised taco tucks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beats the middle finger "didn't buy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't want to know someone is gay. They want to think no-one is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they were failing, until The Donald came in and fixed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they are not forgotten... They are even getting coverage on NPR! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm just saying go straight for Ryan's jugular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, it's yuuuge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you ask me would I rather see the money go for our water plant, or to possibly try to control our borders and the security of our nation, the security of our nation is more important to me," Fink says.

So, in choosing between a solution for WATER which is guaranateed to work, Fink is ready to sacrifice that for a "possible try" to control our borders.

Ok, now I'm going to look at a map to see just how vulnerable this Kansas town is to threats coming from across the border. Be right back! 

EDIT: (I was fast!) Here is the map: http://i.imgur.com/QZaAZko.png

As you can see, the residents of Strong City, Kansas have very valid reasons for fearing open borders. While people in Arizona only have to worry about Mexican rapists and freeloaders, and people in Montana are more wary of Canadian serial killers and welfare drains, Strong City Kansaas is almost equidistant from BOTH Mexicao *and* Canada and must worry about threats coming from both the north and the south. 

And I'm not even going to get into how vulnerable they are to missle attacks from both North Korea AND Iceland!

This town's story needs to be upvoted. Please tell your congresscritter to access the browsing history of Strong City Kansas residents so we can target them with ads about how to survive the looming Mexican-Canadian zombie wars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the biggest, best number ever. Believe me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His browsing history is sure to have "keeping cool on a hot day", "constrictor bukakke","how to hide your lizard origins while in DC". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why this fixation on Montana? Go straight for Ryan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, this reminds me of headlines on how sure a bet Hillary was to become president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, **STATE ELECTIONS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's not auto-corrects?

Victor works for the IRS. He is one of many, but he is the main one. The go-to Victor, the one who won if you will. 

And while they, and Shirely, have the information...

And Otto is the technician running the whole show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wait? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those kids are singing, dude! they love being independent at such a young age! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed my point. A lot of users - me included - as soon as we see that the app even *has* in-app purchases, we won't even download it to try. So, we don't even give the app the chance to convince us it is worthwhile. We've already moved on. 

Like NotLawrence said - it's just the mentality that has already creeped into people's minds. The exception being apps that can build users' trust before even downloading. Like through a brand or some other kind of interaction with potential customers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people fucking hate in-app purchases. They just don't trust them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're asking if he is the one pegging Republicans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he did show up, he would 100% lie under oath. What is there to stop him? He and Russia would not give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew closing Gitmo would be so difficult?!

Obama clearly should not have ever promised to work with Republicans. It would be naive to even think that possible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Designed = natural selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it not make more sense to say that time is the first dimension?

To me, it makes no sense at all to simply tack it onto the third dimension. That's pretty much assuming a two dimensional world has no time.

And a line is not as small as you can go. You can go to one point on the line and separate it from all other points on the line. And why not? A line is simply a one line separated from all other lines on a plane.

So, if you have a single point then something is either at that point or it is not. It's purely binary (for now!). And that is time. Schrodinger's point, if you will (maybe you won't).

Consequently, time simply states whether an object is "there" or not. 

Then you add other points and have a line (and as an aside, there is no reason to assume the line is straight since a "straight line" can only be identified when it is on a plane. One a line, I'd argue the concept of "straight" does not even exist).

[[And here I take issue with your saying: *you could just as easily describe that point by its angle to the horizontal and how far it is away from some specified point*. you can only describe a point by it's angle to the horizontal if you define the horizontal first. That that's going to be completely arbitrary *if you are confined to that two-D existence*. And anyhow, I'd argue you are still using "how far and how up", just different math to get there.]]

Now on this line, one can assume that something existing on one point can (might) move to another and so you see time.

And to me that ruins the entire concept of time as a "dimension" at all. Why time? Why not colour?

Say you have a point on a line that is red. Now it is blue. How do you determine that it took time to change from red to blue? Maybe red changing to blue causes time? 

Clearly, I have too much time. So, I'll leave it at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyhow, it was a great movie. Probably the best I've enjoyed in the past year. Loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^(Look  I've got a mess on my hands  okay ? Believe me  .) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least 36! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, just when they change a flat tire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, unrealistic in the sense that plausible hypotheses were pushed to absurd limits.

Not that the hyotheses themselves were unrealistic.

At least that's what I got out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  contemporary scholars believe Little Russian sentiment endures in Ukraine even today and plays heavily upon the country's political divisions.

I believe this was the case by and large until Russia annexed Crimea. A LOT of Ukrainians who had never before thought of themselves as Ukrainian were "awakened" and now feel very, very much Ukrainian. This is not to say that before March 2014 they thought themselves Russian (certainly not!); they simply never really thought about it. So, I wouldn't say they considered themselves "little Russians" either, but the mentality of not really identifying with a nation did have a, mostly unspoken, place.

Of course this is more in central Ukraine, where I live. In the west, people certainly felt Ukrainian - Lviv, I-Frankivsk, etc. and in the east, many did feel like brothers to the Russians. But in central Ukraine, where there was never a huge nationalist fevour, but people are very much ethnic Ukrainian - mostly speaking Ukrainian at home (well, Surzhik to one degree or another, but children are speaking more literately now as schooling is by and large in Ukrainian), eating "ukrainian" food and wearing ukrainian dress on holidays and so on. But boy-oh-boy do most people in central Ukraine feel Ukrainian now. A backlash to Russia's invasion really, as many people know someone who has fought for Ukraine in the wars. Brothers, fathers and sons have all died fighting for Ukraine and people feel that. But whereas before people might have wondered why they should fight for Ukraine (the government does nothing for us!) now they realize that they do in fact have things they hold dear which are worth fighting for.

The irony here being that Putin probably started the wars in Ukraine to shore up his support at home but in fact did more than any person has in 300 years to bolster Ukrainians' own sense of identity.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a difference between Russian and Ukrainian however. "" means edge in Russian, "" in Ukrainian literally means country. 

And this is not something Ukrainians made up, as several Slavic languages use the same:

Polish - kraj

Slovak - krajina

Belarusian - 


Some will even argue that Russia's calling Ukraine "the edge" is because Ukraine always meant "the country" where Ukraine now is (like the Chinese say "middle kingdom") and when some "Ukrainians" (countrymen) emigrated to Russia before it was Russia they referred to the "country" they left as "Ukraine", because that's wat it was. And only later, once Russia eclipsed Ukraine as a power int he region, did "Ukraine" start to mean "at the edge of where we live now", simply because the term "ukraine" as country still existed and it simply gained - in the Russian language - the new meaning of edge as the memory of ukraine as "the country" waned in the minds and culture of residents of Russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's far more nuanced of course. And if you go back, of course v and na will have different nuances than they have now. 

but overall, in the context of current use today in Russian with regards to Ukraine, the words most definitely have the connotations of supporting or denegrating Ukraine's sovereignty.

And furthermore, Ukrainians who speak English take that to "the Ukraine" vs "Ukraine" as well.

As far as Alaska goes, it must be remembered that Alaska was first part of the Russian empire. So, going "na Alaska" showed you are going to Alaska, which is part of something bigger, the Russian empire. And that stuck after Alaska was sold to the US. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't, but interestingly enough, they have prepositions which do the same.

 (Na) vs  (V).

Russians will say " " when talking about something happening "in Ukraine", while Ukrainians speaking Russian will say " ".

The difference is that in the Russian language, "na" is reserved mostly for places which are not sovereign states. "V" is used for soveriegn states. (mostly, not a hard fast rule, just like in English people say "The Netherlands").

So, the Russians who say "na Ukraine" are (knowingly or not) knocking Ukraine's soveriegnty, basically putting it on the level of Alaska - a place that is part of a bigger place. They say "na Alyaska", too, by the way.

Some say, the old way of saying "The Ukraine" in English comes from learning that Russians said "na Ukraine".

Today it is a big deal, actually. Ukrainians on TV, in public peaking will alway say "v Ukraine", but sometimes older people wil say "na" simply because theyve been saying it that way thier entire lives. And if you're not picky about grammar, it's like -  why bother correcting it? 

But Russians who insist on saying "na" usually argue that this is simply "proper Russian".

Languages change and politics also has an influence on them. It's kind of interesting, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does one smile upside down?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just locker-room treason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  SIGINT

Signals intelligence (SIGINT) is intelligence-gathering by interception of signals, whether communications between people (communications intelligenceabbreviated to COMINT) or from electronic signals not directly used in communication (electronic intelligenceabbreviated to ELINT). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2+2 = 4

No it's not 2+2=5!!

    Logically, 2+2 must be close to 4.45

The Earth is a sphere! - no, the Earth is flat!

    The Earth is probably shaped like a deep dish.

The death penalty is evil! - The death penalty is justified!

    Probably should just draw and quarter people and let God decide whether or not they survive.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  OCONUS

CONUS = The 48 CONtiguous States and the District of Columbia or "the lower 48, as they're affectionately known to the Alaskans." OCONUS = Outside Continental United States. Overseas = Any country or place beyond the CONUS. Alaska, Hawaii and the U.S. territories are considered overseas under the Space-A Regulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was full of bugs.

Hahaha, I'm going to assume that was inadvertant on your part! But it was great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Herbert Bush? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the exact same problem that Trump *'pedes* have. They simply cannot admit that they were wrong - that maybe they were conned (by either Trump himself lying to them or by the Russians feeding them lies) and they will hold on to their belief until the bitter, bitter end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I had a similar conversation with many people who were quite liberal. Usually they didn't vote for Trump. But, they bought all of the rhetoric the right threw at her **with the help of the Russian government** and therefore didn't vote or voted for a third party candidate (both of the front runners of which were complete fucking morons)

FTFY.

And for the sake of an experiment, it would be interesting to ask these "liberal-but-Hillary-is-shit-so-i-didn't-vote" people what they think of the Trump-Russia scandal.

Ask them that first without giving away the catch, and see if they say "yeah, the Trump administration *must* be investigated for that. See just how adamant you can get them on that specific point. Get them to swear, break dishes, etc.

*And then*, * THEN*, point out that the allegations are that the GOP, in collusion with Russia, tried to make Hillary look bad. PRECISELY SO SHITHEADS LIKE THEM WOULD STAY AT HOME AND NOT VOTE.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except in this case we are clearly dealing with Trump trying to be president, not trying to play to his core T_D fools.

He did not present the "check" in a public setting where his rabid fans could eat it up and shout about dirty krauts.

He did it in a closed setting where really only Merkel and his and her close aides knew about it.

So, logically (and I know how dangerous it is to apply logic to Trump, but hey, whatyagonnado?), logically, I guess he really thought that this might influence her? Can that be? Let me rephrase that - can he really, honestly be that big league stupid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the news is a beauty contest

I suggest you take a look at the majority of anchors bearing in a mind a scale of "pleasing to the human eye". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, other pro-Trump people are not going to be swayed based n this articlea alone. They don't know the woman or her husband and it's easy for them to dismiss it without that emotional interest in the story.

It's basically a story to allow anti-Trump people to bask in their clearly superior smarts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does her "we" mean her husband was for Trump, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that really uncomfortable feeling you got when he said that? The feeling that made you really uneasy anout something you couldn't quite put your finger on?

That was space and time bending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me what we know about "Source E". Why do we think he is "E" and not like "Source D"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment prompted me to read the article, but I laughed at the comment there. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is who to vote for if you want to build your own roads together with your friends with no government regulations on them, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art of the deal, right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B*CH fits both branch and bitch, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Days*, you say?

What are you going to tell me next, that they worked *full, 9-5* office hour days with strict one hour lunch breaks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, November 2018. "Nov '18" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Republicans are now realizing opposing trump comes with zero consequences.

I love this.

What is market now for popcorn futures with a Nov 18 exp date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep forgetting - how many total votes were cast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, the small town was french or the beach was french? this is really confusing the heck outta me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe then they can bifurcate the partisans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grand, in fact! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just call his dick "The Dark Knight?"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Co-opt it back! 

Also, I suspect /r/themeltdown (remember that?) may soon get a second lease on life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the website is clearly bipartisan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Brutal is definitely the word to describe that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the gravity of the situation

that was not even subtle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been nice for the author of the article to delve into explaining what Appalachia actually is rather than simply repeat over and over that white, male outsiders don't get it.

Let's see how many time the author does this - calls out others' coverage of Appalachia - while avoiding any discussion of substance: 

1) 

The authors establish a region in Appalachia or the Rust Belt as ground zero for the archetypal Trump hillbilly voter while walking through what they see as paradoxes of our politics or lack thereof, before concluding with their wisdom on what should be done about us.

2) 

Currently, the pundit class is waging a self-made war over appropriate emotional response to the anticipated suffering of Trump voters and individuals like me who share their communities.

3)

What this genre looks like is pundits who are almost universally men and almost exclusively white, firing off sleazy ideas about hillbillies while doing a very poor job differentiating between Trump voters and the average sort of disadvantaged person who lives in Appalachia or the Rust Belt.

4) 

Every generation of politicians, writers, analysts, academics and economists believes it has discovered something unique or horrible or paradoxical about Appalachia

5) 

liberal compulsion [is] to hold up the disadvantaged Appalachian or Rust Belter as a stand-in for all Trump voters while arguing above his head how much sympathy were allowed to have with him eliminates any productive exchange of resistance politics among progressives. 


So, I LEARNED NOTHING ABOUT APPALCHIA FROM THIS ARTICLE. NADA. ZILCH. Furthermore, the article only very superficially delves into "the media elites obsession with the 'hillbilly problem' " and fails to address why this is wrong (I agree it likely is and wanted to know how/why) based on any "insider insights" which the author presumably could give (since the author "lives here").

Take this gem for example:

The odiousness of this genres popularity is that it **eliminates any productive discussion of actual problems** by centering the real issue its authors have with the region: namely, that a fraction of the people in this country with repressive political views who look too much like them for comfort live here.

SO WHERE IS THE PRODUCTIVE DISCUSSION? THAT'S WHY I FREAKING CLICKED TO READ YOUR ARTICLE. IN SEARCH OF IT. 

**tl;dr this article is a let down and really just a waste of time as it does not add anything to productive discussion of Appalachia. It merely whines that current media tropes are unfair.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cones of Dunshire

Wait - Koch bros do not want the AHCA to pass? Why? It's not conservative enough or it's just bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  subpoena power

yummy!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does or does not Joe Biden win 2020 if he enters it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect he is more tempted by LA and Seattle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a religious person but **AMEN** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> footsies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude is a fucking idiot if he knowingly screwed Russian oligarchs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> knock yourself out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, linky please to that poll!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone else pointed out in an other thread, what Spicer says is meant for consumption by Trump's base. The WH is just keeping those rubes engaged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, that's just SMART! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am surprised at it being okay to kiss someone's chicken in Spain if you are Arabic [sic]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many hours until this is proven a lie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> simply cuz it's interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I hadn't even gone that far. Great catch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a really weird fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It occurred to me today that this smoke and fire is like a peat bog fire.

Look up peat bog fires on wikipedia and you will see there is a hell of a lot of smoke and the fire may not be really visible at first, but it burns deep in the ground.

And they are hard to extinguish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, if all men and boy become girls, there will be no more PIV sex and soon - no babies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  squillions

hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "shit" you mean this:

http://neutralgroundnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Shitstorm-coming.png

And by "fan" you mean this: 

http://i.imgur.com/yIhpC3z.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so, you're trying to avoid them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What kind of stories on reddit do you "hide" and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what if he was being paid by some front company to push certain articles? Like he consciously had things published knowing he was going to get paid big fat sums under the table for doing so?

And what if it turns out he knew the front comapnies were run by Russians?

Think that might be what the FBI is investigating?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
