<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2778</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving game data from Origin to Steam - can it be done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 21:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, wasn't sure where best to post this.  

I recently bought the Humble Bundle, and with it Burnout Paradise. Now, I already own this on Origin, and where I am the internet download speed is painfully slow, so I want to avoid downloading again if I can. I was wondering if there was a way I could just grab the biggest files, or even the whole game install out of my Origin Games folder, and move it to Steam, allowing it to fill in the gaps of data. Can it be done, and if so, what's the best way to approach it?  
Thanks.  
EDIT: after trying all suggestions, and even doing a full re-install of steam, nothing has worked as of yet. Not sure why it's being so weird about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 22:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's plausible. The guy Jesse was going to meet was disguised as a vacuum repairman. It's a double bluff - he is a vacuum repairman and Huell gave the weed to him to plant in Jesse's roomba. Mike is there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 15:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoooly cow I'm totally going so fast right no- AWH FUCK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Break-it Brian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 21:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say anything about the engine. You're quite right, it's all level design based, but it's still a nice feature. Yes, it's not revolutionary, but it's different, and fairly (and I say this in the loosest sense) unique to the genre. That's why it's so exciting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's the whole point. I wouldn't want the game deciding when to cut the power in an apartment block, or when to raise road barriers or cause a support to buckle on a gantry. By allowing players to do these things, you change how the gameplay experience works from game to game. One time, I might walk into a building, cut the power and gun down 2 guys using an IRNV scope, another, I choose not to but instead walk outside and raise the bollards, stopping a tank getting to me. It's not just to make things pretty, and regardless of the outcome being the same, it's changing the game enough to make gameplay interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 20:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I love this new feature. Along with the improvement to the overall netcode, this will be awesome :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 20:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'scripted event' != 'player-triggered event'
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 20:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a Minecraft sword to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be the worst "novelty account" I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 19:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hit 20 years old, and got to grips with the new system I'm working on for my 2nd day on my first ever job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 19:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's the most powerful, but "Inside my heart is breaking, my makeup may be flaking, but my smile, still, stays on!" from 'The Show Must  Go On' by Queen is pretty intense. Freddie was dying, but he never sought sympathy. He always wore a brave face. The band wasn't sure he could record it because of the demanding vocals, but he took a shot of vodka, and said "I'll fucking do it, darling!", performing it all in one take without a hitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 15:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently playing **Dawnguard** and **Dragonborn** for Skyrim, I've touched on **Tomb Raider** and **Scribblenauts Unlimited**, played half of **McPixel**, and enjoyed the first 2 levels of **Dark Souls**, but I'll need to invest some more time in that game!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tagged you as Wanksy now. Wear it with pride.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 15:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did  the silly thing of buying it before I read the reviews. I thought "Ooh, a sniper game, that'll be fun". Then I saw it had been slammed by critics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 12:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Borderlands 2 DLC (Dragon Keep)
* Skyrim DLC (Dawnguard and Dragonborn)
* LEGO LOTR
* Alan Wake
* Reus (Somewhat regret this)
* Fallout 3 GOTY
* Rollercoaster Tycoon 3 Platinum
* Hitman Absolution
* Tomb Raider
* Thief 2
* Thief Deadly Shadows
* Sniper: Ghost Warrior 2 (I regret this)
* They Bleed Pixels
* Scribblenauts Unlimited
* McPixel
* Bastion  

I think most of these were on my wishlist, so mostly I've bought the games I wanted. Some I got because they were dirt cheap, some I got for cards, and some (Like Fallout 3) I got because I love them and I had them on console. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 14:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What? No way!" *- My exact words* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 20:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 22:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure that 'Large Biomes' is enabled :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 19:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thonks beb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 19:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, both forms, "spelled" and "spelt" are acceptable. "Spelt" is the irregular form, whereas "spelled" is more common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 13:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but it's spelt gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 21:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ought to correct the Bioshock Infinite entry to say "Yes" for trading cards. They've been added to it now :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steam sales start tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 14:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 14:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HSBC advert anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 13:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This map has actually been pretty fun so far. I was a bit put out when I first spawned, but it's been tough to get started (especially on hard). Right now I've got a little forest going, loads of cane, and a little farm. And yesterday I sailed 2x further than that map, and found the mainland, so all is not lost! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 02:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WILSON! WIILLSOOON! I'M SORRY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 02:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, it's 7655491680621261001.  
EDIT: This is a large biomes world. Sorry for the confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not bad. You start with one tree and some cane, and there's a bit of coal in a little cave entrance to the south east. No sheep though. That's a bit of a pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well. Shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 01:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 01:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of mine is the end of Atonement, when [SPOILERS](#s "Briony says "...And, in fact, could never have happened." And goes on to reveal that Robbie died of Septicaemia at Bray-Dunes, and that her sister is killed in the Balham bombings") That killed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 01:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, I still can't watch this film without crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 03:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at it for all of 2 minutes, saw a post about furry oppression, and nope'd so hard it would make a spider cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 03:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never used tumblr before in my life. Is it bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 01:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she has multiple "shadow babies" (I think they are called shadow assassins). One is to kill Renly, and the other is for Penrose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
