<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add me, everyone! Fartn0ise. Just started Keto and I'm about a week in and especially loving the extra energy boost!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TMI warning: For me, yes! TIFU by thinking it was a fart earlier today. WRONG! At least you're just nauseous/feeling gross!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're on Facebook, check out the Military Landlords group. Lots of good resources and support on that group including sample lease applications and agreements. Shoot me a message and I can help get you added.   

As for figuring out monthly rent, you'll want to look at comparable rental properties ("comps") in your area. Look at zillow or hotpads and search for similar sized residences in your area. For security deposit, 1 month's rent is standard. My current tenants had a so-so application so we asked them for 1.5 x monthly rent. In places where rentals are in high demand, I've seen 2 month's rent as standard as well.   

You also may want to look into using a property manager to handle all this. Cost is typically 10% of your monthly rental rate plus $500 or so for advertising your property. The benefit of having one is that he/she will handle all the research, application process, maintenance, etc on your behalf. I use one since my retail is on the opposite side of the country from our current duty station, so it will be really difficult for me to coordinate maintenance and the like. 
  
Best of luck in the Army!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 09:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For coffee, have you tried a pinch of salt? For me, I needed the sugar to cut the bitterness of coffee. Salt cuts that bitterness, and now I much prefer my coffee with a splash of half and half and a pinch of salt, vs flavored coffee creamer and sweetener.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 06:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That NASA skipped Apollo 13 because it's an unlucky number. Along the same rationale as why hotels skip the 13th floor. Imagine my surprise when I figure out the Tom Hanks movie was based on a true story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Puppy/Guardian of the Underworld Mix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
