<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to be attracting Trump defenders lately when I comment on the immigration ban in these threads.  The Trump defenders seem to like to try to draw some tenuous equivalents between this immigration ban and some action of the Obama administration.

Here's the real question, though: who benefits from this immigration ban?!  Obviously not the banned people.  But nobody else in America seems to benefit either.  What possible increase in security, or other advantage, does it convey to Americans?

The only people who seem to benefit from this ban are America's enemies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*The Washington Post* has a more detailed article behind a soft paywall.](https://out.reddit.com/t3_5qwutt?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.washingtonpost.com%2Fworld%2Feurope%2Fbrunhilde-pomsel-secretary-to-nazi-propaganda-minister-joseph-goebbels-dies-at-106%2F2017%2F01%2F29%2Fab645200-dcf6-11e6-ad42-f3375f271c9c_story.html%3Ftid%3Dhybrid_experimentrandom_1_na token=AQAAKoSOWHBQltgvLDGXuGuPp-dBZlmcgGtIKegpOoPdQgIT0u2u app_name=reddit.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brunhilde Pomsel, secretary to Nazi propaganda minister Joseph Goebbels, dies at 106 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything you say is true.  In fact, I suspect that the life-and-death nature of, for example, healthcare, may have been a factor in the otherwise-conservative John Roberts ruling in favor of the Affordable Care Act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No indeed, I don't mean that we'll automatically get through it.  I refuse to lose hope in America, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not dead yet.  This is a sad, sad time, but we'll get through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, please post the links to the stories about how foreign nationals from seven countries, legally residing in the USA, left the country and then suddenly couldn't get back in, all during the Obama administration.

Oh wait, you can't, because this current nonsense is unprecedented in the history of this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The B'l Air Which-Country-Are-You-a-Citizen-of Project?

Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea that the founders intended the Second Amendment to enable resistance to a tyrannical government is [a persistent and pernicious myth](http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2011/06/constitutional-myth-6-the-second-amendment-allows-citizens-to-threaten-government/241298/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to consider it in light of the fact that Obama blocked Iraqi immigrants for years via executive order.

You're going to need to cite a source for this seemingly hyperbolic claim.  At first glance, it appears that you have lengthened and broadened a six-month suspension in a particular Iraqi refugee program into a supposed years-long blocking of all Iraqi immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least it's some consolation that the sizable numbers of Somali cab drivers in DC won't be giving Paul Ryan's ass a ride any time soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am officially now ready to hear about **solutions** to the problem of this unconstitutional executive order.  Lawsuits fast-tracked to the Supreme Court, or House Republicans ready to support impeachment proceedings, or whatever it takes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo.  Tragically underrated comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The opponents try a corner kick. Three of our defenders touch it; can any of them clear it away from our goal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendation!  I've yet to make it to Denmark, but have been wanting to go there for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to need the address of the place in Europe with free refills of Barnaise sauce, please.  Even amidst the excellent food we got from one of the meccas of Cajun cuisine in New Orleans last year, the Barnaise sauce stood out as exceptional.  (Of course, it was the USA, so there were free refills there.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glittering prizes and endless compromises shatter the illusion of integrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blink 182 times for aging punk rockers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try sliced tomatoes and mustard once and you'll never go back to ketchup.  Also, you'll be able to show your face in certain cities where they're serious about their hot dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~the~~ a year the Steelers went to the Super Bowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  A further example of not needing a constitutional amendment to change presidential elections is the [National Popular Vote Interstate Compact.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Popular_Vote_Interstate_Compact)  Once states that hold a cumulative total of 270 electoral votes are signed up to the Compact, then presidential elections are essentially decided by the nationwide popular vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was an example from the Digest of Rules, not a rule itself.  Same principle applies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am a Steelers fan rooting for the Falcons, and I agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The referees clearly didn't feel that he established possession in the field of play and was carried into the end zone by his momentum, because if they had, Atlanta would have the ball at its own one-yard line.

(a) Player intercepts a pass with both feet inbounds in the field of play and his momentum carries him into his own end zone. Ball is put in play at spot of interception.

http://www.nfl.com/rulebook/safety2
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they didn't, because if they had, Atlanta would have the ball at its own one-yard line.

(a) Player intercepts a pass with both feet inbounds in the field of play and his momentum carries him into his own end zone. Ball is put in play at spot of interception.

http://www.nfl.com/rulebook/safety2
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Referees clearly judged him not to have possession until he was in the end zone, but the turnover should have incurred an automatic replay review.  Maybe there was one, and FOX just didn't mention it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm supporting the Falcons in this game, but yes, really looked like a safety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will repeat one of my favorite pieces of emergency management advice ever:
Do not try to outrun a tornado on foot or in your car.

Um, if anyone reading this needed to be told not to try to **outrun a tornado on foot**... there's a Life Pro Tip for you.

Seriously, though, stay safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "would", not "will"

It is interesting that, **if** the Packers win today, they would become the only 4-6 team to make it to the Super Bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 07:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, my sister was in the stands at the Dennis Byrd game.  It wasn't on TV in my area, though.

Chuck Hughes dying on the field was before my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?  No.  The Chiefs put up 389 yards on the Falcons in December in just 48 plays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how fast quantum computing could make algorithms for decision problems in P, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we can work with this.

I get the idea that the Jets really don't like the Steelers, which also seems promising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Helpful bot" just built a brick wall called karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the noun "comic" has at least one meaning that you're oblivious to: "comedian or comedienne". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps.  How do you feel about the Cowboys and Bengals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantum computing may someday allow polynomial-time algorithms for NP-complete problems, but that won't make P = NP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, there's no way that P = NP.  But it will be interesting to see if there's a proof by 2117. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 21:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, many Seahawks fans appear to hate the Steelers.

Patriots fans and Steelers fans: sistern and brethren in Seahawks disdain! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, how did Cousins do against the Steelers this year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just working from the evaluation by *Patriots fan* Aaron Schatz, who takes strength of opposing offenses into account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably can't name five better.

Broncos, Giants, Texans, Cardinals, Panthers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots fan Aaron Schatz is apparently therefore fucking nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your pick between the two times the Bengals grabbed and pulled on Steelers WRs' facemasks in the end zone in the game in Cincinnati.  No penalties of any sort assessed, neither DPI nor personal foul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're *virtual* unknowns, so no deal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate it, thanks!  2017 is the twenty-year anniversary of my Ph.D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, the Steelers defense... that's James Harrison and a bunch of virtual unknowns.  Zero All-Pro votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The disappointment of the other AFC Championship losses I remember -- Patriots, Broncos, Dolphins (I was too young for the loss to the Raiders) -- was more spread out over the game, and wasn't for the right to face the 49ers or Cowboys in the Super Bowl to see who would be the first to five Lombardi Trophy wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite Dave Barry quotes, from *Dave Barry Slept Here*:
Do you feel that people who insist upon referring to themselves as doctor simply because they hold Ph.D. degrees, which are about as rare as air molecules, tend to be self-important weenies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh.

This was the number-three most disappointing moment for me as a Steelers fan, I think, and number one at the time it happened.  I wasn't quite here yet in 1972.  Larry Brown's second Super Bowl interception became number one, and eventually Rashard Mendenhall's Super Bowl fumble followed behind it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a number, I am a free man!

Good enough to be on a Super Bowl team; not good enough, at least not yet, to *carry* a team to the Super Bowl.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 13:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You write all those words and don't mention that Dennis Gibson was the player who knocked down the pass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 11:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then once you get a Ph.D., there are two different attitudes you can take.

I am sorry to say that the more common attitude is, "I know all this stuff about total-order forward search using task-network planning, so **I must be really smart!**"

But there are also plenty of people who think, "I know all this stuff about total-order forward search using task-network planning.  Wow, there must be just as much stuff to learn about the helium line in the sun's spectrum.  And just as much stuff to learn about the journey motif in the works of Eudora Welty.  And just as much stuff to learn about how to run a recycling center.  And about how to drive a truck that picks up trash and recycling.  And how to operate a television camera at a sporting event.  So **the depths of my ignorance must be profound.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 10:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> El Tri? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 10:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some say Reche Caldwell's eyes are still wide to this day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A significant portion of what makes QBs elite has to do with choosing among the receiving options, not some sort of magic way to exploit the coverage of a particular CB on a WR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems as if you might like [this Super Bowl highlight](https://youtu.be/M4D7TVItbmE), featuring one wide receiver passing to another.  (The wide receiver who makes the catch was himself a college quarterback.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NB: If you're a **prepaid** Verizon customer, you can still watch, but if you aren't on wifi, it **does** count against your data usage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly, when that article was written, the Jets were 8-3 and the Giants were 10-1.

The 2008 Giants then finished 12-4 and had home-field advantage throughout the playoffs, but lost in the Divisional Round to the Eagles.

The 2008 Jets finished 9-7 in a year in which the AFC Wild Card teams were 12-4 and 11-5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So [Le'Veon Bell did not have a baby... **yet.**](http://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/leveon-bell-set-to-become-a-father-any-day-now/)
"Any day now."

Pregnancies, especially towards the end of the nine months, don't always go smoothly.  So we can simultaneously recognize that there may have been some complications, be happy that there appears [from Le'Veon's tweet to be good news:](https://twitter.com/L_Bell26/status/822258335198171141)
today has been a blessing (5:43 PM - 19 Jan 2017)

... and, in general, move on, because I for one feel that this is fundamentally none of my business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of reasons being provided in this thread about why an owner would vote against a team's move in that owner's self-interest.  Let me provide a different reason: because some things are right and some things are wrong, and some owners vote against things that they know are wrong.

Dan Rooney voted against the Browns' move not because of any particular self-interest, and not because of any love lost for the Browns, but because... I'll let him tell it:
But I was disturbed when I learned that Art Modell would move his Browns from Cleveland.  Not only were the Browns the natural rival of the Steelers, one of the best rivalries in sports, but their fans were among the most devoted in the NFL.  It was a sad day for Cleveland, a sad day for Pittsburgh, and a sad day for the league when the Browns traded in their orange and brown uniforms for Baltimore Ravens purple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Donnie Shell?  Oh, okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh?  Hate the Seahawks?

I have some Jerramy Stevens antipathy still, that's for sure, but no reason to hate the Seahawks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I can tell you for sure: that's no moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are exceptions in the families who have owned NFL teams for the better part of a century -- the Maras, the Rooneys, etc. -- although even in those cases, there's outside investment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a time machine every night.  I lie down, close my eyes, and wake up in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should read the part of the linked self post where it says "*Exception: Holding will be called if the defender's feet are taken away from him by the offensive player's action*". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The *Vista Wayyyyyy* video, for the uninitiated.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGb1UHsVUDo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why the question is somewhat interesting: Smith has retired and started his five-year Hall-of-Fame clock, but Fitzgerald is still planning to play in 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if a wide receiver celebrating a touchdown mimed -- *mimed*, I emphasize -- mooning the fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, you know, the Ravens, Jets, Buccaneers, and Saints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually the big news in this injury report: limited participation for him.  He had limited participation last week, but couldn't get beyond that.  They're trying again to bring him out of the concussion protocol.  If he has full participation tomorrow, that's a good sign for the Steelers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And one of them played in the NFC East. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The... St. Louis Cardinals of the NFL... is still a tough phrase to wrap our heads around for those of us who have been following the league since before 1988. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, if the reporter had called it by its proper name of "Lamar Hunt Trophy" and asked Belichick about Lamar Hunt's contributions to the history of pro football, we might have gotten a better answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch Episode I first: [1981 AFC Divisional Playoff, Chargers vs. Dolphins.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y06M_BxQBDE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rod Woodson's non-contact torn ACL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For clarification, not all of the minority coaches mentioned in the article were interviewed because of the Rooney Rule.  The Steelers had already satisfied the Rooney Rule by interviewing Ron Rivera before they decided to interview Mike Tomlin, whom they ultimately hired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the song in the bonus level of the Journey arcade video game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make the Bad Mods gleeful, or they'll make you their mare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh.  You can tell that the wallpaper previews on the downloads page on fightforla.com use the LA logo, but they've excised it from the wallpapers themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give me directions to Nickerson Field?  I hear the Steelers are playing away at the home of the Boston Patriots this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me say that while I think the Patriots are the best *team* left, I also think that they'll be *facing* the best defense left on Sunday, not fielding it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's only one way to shut some of the Patriots fans up about their "#1 scoring defense", and we have to hold this game to have any chance of that.  Hey, those of you Patriots fans who are statistically and strategically naive: you have a powerful offense, more powerful than the Steelers offense, and your defense is perfectly fine, especially against the run.  But the Patriots defense is nowhere near the best in the NFL, and it's *really* untested.  You've faced one reasonably good quarterback this year: Russell Wilson, and he led the Seahawks offense to 420 yards, 31 points, and a victory in Foxborough.

Of course, it's not the Patriots' fault that they're untested: a team can only play the schedule it's given.  There's a Patriots fan who has put together a statistical scheme for evaluating these sorts of questions: "this team has dominated a lot of inferior opposition; how good will it be when tested against stronger opposition?"  That Patriots fan is Aaron Schatz of Football Outsiders: he evaluates the Patriots as [the best team in the NFL,](http://www.footballoutsiders.com/dvoa-ratings/2017/week-19-dvoa-ratings) but also [a team with real questions about its pass defense.](http://www.footballoutsiders.com/stats/teamdef)

The Patriots are favored, and should be favored, on Sunday.  But I estimate the Steelers as only needing about one more break in their favor to defeat the Patriots.  Two big Patriots mistakes and only one big Steelers mistake, for example, is likely in my mind to lead to a Steelers victory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd be very similar.  Realize that for the winner of a three-game series to be different from the winner of the first game in that series, the loser of the first game must sweep the other two games.  That wouldn't happen very often, even with the biggest Conference Championship upsets.

In fact, presumably the three-game series would include one game at the lower seed and two games at the higher seed; when the higher seed lost its game at home in real life, it seems like a tall order for the higher seed to then win both on the road and at home.

I grabbed [this list of one writer's estimation of the ten biggest Conference Championship upsets:](http://www.commdiginews.com/sports/the-10-greatest-conference-title-game-upsets-in-nfl-history-33444/)

* 2005 AFC  Steelers 34, Broncos 17.  That Steelers team was one of the best wild-card teams in NFL history.  The Broncos could sweep two more games, but it seems unlikely.

* 2011 NFC  Giants 20, 49ers 17, OT.  Slightly more likely to change, but again, I still favor the Giants to win one of two more notional games against the 49ers.

* 1975 NFC  Cowboys 17, Vikings 14.  I mean, the Vikings were 12-2, but the 10-4 wild-card Cowboys were no slouch.

* 2007 NFC  Giants 23, Packers 20, OT.  Again, I still favor the Giants to win one of two against an aging Brett Favre.

* 2003 NFC  Panthers 14, Eagles 3.  Donovan McNabb wouldn't suddenly become uninjured in the next two contests.

* 1990 NFC  Giants 15, 49ers 13.  14-2 49ers were a better team, but the 13-3 Bill Parcells Giants, after winning with Jeff Hostetler, would still be favored to keep one of the next two games close enough with their defense to advance.

* 1985 AFC  Patriots 31, Dolphins 14.  Maybe the likeliest so far to change.  Those 1985 Patriots certainly looked horrible in Super Bowl XX.  But they did beat the Dolphins by 17.

* 1998 NFC  Falcons 30, Vikings 27, OT.  Great 15-1 Vikings team, but the 14-2 Falcons would surely be favored at home.

* 2002 NFC  Buccaneers 27, Eagles 10.  It's not like this Buccaneers team would suddenly forget how to play defense.

* 1994 AFC  Chargers 17, Steelers 13.  You should get a non-Steelers fan to evaluate whether this may indeed be the likeliest result of all to change; from my biased perspective, that's what it seems to me.  But even if you advance the Steelers to Super Bowl XXIX, they're going to have a tough time with the 49ers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I thought Dion Lewis were going to fumble twice in the AFC Championship, I'd be ecstatic.  But unfortunately, fumbling that frequently is really uncharacteristic for him: before last weekend, he had only 4 previous fumbles in his career in what I make out to be 239 previous touches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not next season for some reason, surely the season after that will also include the Wild-Card Round in this scheme.  The lure of advertising dollars will be too strong for the NFL to resist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which NFL teams were once coached by a man who had scored a goal against Italy in the (soccer) FIFA World Cup?

[Answer in link.](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aldo_Donelli) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember an old cartoon (Crow Quill?) in which Terry Bradshaw is saying to some Steelers QB, maybe let's say Kordell Stewart, something like the following: "Listen to me, kid, and I'll teach you how to win four Super Bowls."

Kordell responds: "I'd settle for just being popular in Pittsburgh."

Terry Bradshaw: "Can't help you there."

Belated edit: [FOUND IT.](http://old.post-gazette.com/crow/steelers/bradshaw.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, congratulations to "Max Huskins" who "Discovered" this, but the secret message was "SIX NAPOLEONS" in the first two episodes of the season, concealed the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of the Steelers' ineffectiveness in scoring touchdowns against the Chiefs can be blamed on the Steelers themselves, not solely attributed to the Chiefs defense.

As for the Patriots, I don't expect them to feature all of the following in the AFC Championship game: a fumbled kickoff return; a second fumble; a 15-yard defensive penalty to keep a drive alive; two interceptions; and getting beat deep on defense only to be saved by the opponents dropping a touchdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I mean, it was just a wild-card game.  I'd rather have won it, obviously, but it wasn't the Super Bowl and so it doesn't haunt me.  Even the Dennis Gibson pass defensed is closer to haunting me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Great run-blocking offensive line with great coaching from Munchak matches up perfectly with the exceptional talents of Le'Veon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, because it seems like my ears close up in those tense moments.  Feel free to post the calls from the second Larry Brown interception or the Mendenhall fumble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry -- I had a late night with lots of tension before, ultimately, triumph, as I imagine many of us did... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that sacks only became an official statistic in 1982. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off the top of my head -- I haven't watched that Super Bowl since it aired live -- the Dolphins had one of the most potent passing offenses of their time, led by Dan Marino.  So running that infrequently didn't seem surprising, especially so given the incentives for the team trailing on the scoreboard to throw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, like the Chargers, were successful in QB drafting but got injured or otherwise failed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, in his first four playoff games, he had two sacks *each game.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the other such team between 1981 and 2015 was the NY Giants who went on to win Super Bowl XXV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to happen, in my opinion.  I foresee a closely contested, well-played game, with the Patriots justifiably but not overwhelmingly favored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many passes can Roethlisberger complete to Rogers, Ayers, Coates, Heyward-Bey, Johnson, James, Grimble, Hamilton, and dare we hope, Green?  I see Belichick scheming to take away Brown and Bell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that the Steelers offense looked pretty bad this week in the red zone, and the Patriots looked generally unconvincing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Searching now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that Chris Boswell performance followed by that Chris Boswell interview on NBC, I will forever call the goalposts "THE YELLOW PIPES". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Boswell is the master of the Evil Yellow Pipes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After that Chris Boswell performance followed by that Chris Boswell interview on NBC, I will forever call the goalposts "THE YELLOW PIPES". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you play next week like you played this week, we're going to crush you.  If we play next week like we played this week, you're going to crush us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steelers will spend at least one more season as the only six-time Super Bowl champions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also one of the meanings of the phrase "backdoor pilot". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, Mt. Rainier may look pretty and hence seem harmless, but it's an active volcano. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During all three of those Super Bowls, as well as during the present season, there has been no change in the Packers ownership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff Fisher could've told you that.

Heck, Matt Millen could've told you that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in the USA: the whole season is streaming free online on the PBS website, although you have only about nineteen and a half hours left to catch the first episode of the season that way.  Also, you'll have to wait about the same amount of time for the third episode to be available to stream.

I realize that that's streaming, not downloading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Bowl XL **run** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At what point does it become more believable that cosmic rays have flipped bits and corrupted the stats?  We might be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although the Super Bowl XL run was more "despite" Tommy Maddox than "because of" Tommy Maddox.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # 'Cause he never been defeated and he won't stop now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will forever hate "turf toe". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  And by point spreads, Texans over Patriots would be the second-biggest playoff upset ever, behind Jets over Colts in Super Bowl III. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid blocked punt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/JaguarGator9, while I have you... I can't remember any postponements of playoff games before, other than the 34-minute power outage *during* Super Bowl XLVII.  That isn't quite the same as postponing kickoff.

Has any previous playoff game ever been postponed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THEY CHANGED THE SONG FOR 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when Ben Roethlisberger's **first NFL start ever** in 2004 was pushed back to Sunday night by Hurricane Jeanne?

[That turned out pretty well for the Steelers.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AvihRzjSdYc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... why did we switch to Leslie Gore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, you don't like Michael Bubl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  "Won't be using"?!  They're **already** using it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me help you out: I survived the Cliff Stoudt/Mark Malone/David Woodley/Bubby Brister era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TO FIND THE ANSWER, GO TO LUCAS OIL STADIUM, AND CHECK THE BANNERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I REMEMBER THE TIME BEFORE THOSE](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M4D7TVItbmE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago is indeed also literally on the border of Illinois. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/theonionwasright/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professor loses book; five years later, buys used copy on Amazon; it's the copy she lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, fair enough.  There weren't really any other teams I could have listed there other than Wimbledon off the top of my head, and I needed significant Internet help to come up with anyone else.  All the other examples seem to be either obscure teams ("I take it you're not a Meadowbank Thistle fan") or teams from long, long ago in a galaxy far, far away from the UK ("I take it you're not an FC De Sloterplas fan from 1994!") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And surely the best such season ever in most if not all of those categories, as punting has been steadily improving over the decades.  It's not as if the 1950s were a Golden Age of Punting or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it you're not a Wimbledon fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tell myself that I'm excited for self-driving cars to take over, but I still don't trust automatic headlights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intercontinental playoffs are already like this, and they work okay.  Bahrain-Trinidad and Tobago.  Uruguay-Australia.  Mexico-New Zealand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it's still very possible that the USA ends up having needed a 48-team World Cup to qualify this cycle.

On the other hand, I'd rather take my chances with a 32-team World Cup.  At least we have two good World Cup structures before this 48-team abomination begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, with tea you can at least visually see something about the grade of the leaves you are buying.  There's no parallel with wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way, ACLs and MCLs are ligaments, not muscles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, and people who watched *I Love the 1590s* on VH1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Chargers had gone deep into overtime in Miami. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love one of his nicknames: "The Merchant of Menace." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  And if you could challenge whenever you had a timeout, that would be six *failed* challenges, as well as infinitely many successful challenges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not OP, but: http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2017/01/08/report-steelers-asst-coach-detained-after-altercation-with-officer/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Bengals (unfortunately) have competent management.  Playoff results are dominated by the randomness of small sample size.  Many teams have come to regret firing a coach with consistent regular-season success in search of playoff magic, only to find that their regular-season success has become inconsistent or nonexistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My answer is different depending on whether I get to pick the *result* of the Super Bowl or not.

Steelers over Packers would be sweet revenge.  But with the outcome in doubt, I'd rather face the Seahawks, who appear to be merely a good team this year, as opposed to the three other great teams remaining in the NFC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
