<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7496</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idea is good but graphics may be turn-off. People went outside for pokemons because they are cute, people associate emotions from childhood with them etc. Look at ingress, many people think it is better game than pokemongo, they had even more money than you to polish and promote it and still it wasn't so popular. Some people will just like me look at this game just to check what it is and then leave it, because there is not so much to achieve/be excited for. As I wrote idea is good, but you need much more content and maybe gameplay? or something else to make people fall in love in it just like pokemongo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing concerns me. Why there are no screenshots on your page? I'd like to see what I'm going to download. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 21:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my country (Poland) the one I chose is cheaper. However it's only 3$ difference so if 550w with gold cert is better (in terms of reliability) than 650w bronze I'd take it. I don't know if it is better to have additional wats or gold efficiency.

Edit: I don't care bout 'fully modular', 'semi modular' is good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] Gaming   programming PC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I haven't build PC for few years so I got a bit rusty and my knowledge may be outdated. I have drives, monitor, mouse, kb so I need only core parts. I need PC for gaming and programming (so I prefer reliability over performance). I'll OC a bit in future.

I prefer Gigabyte over Asus cos It never let me down and I like black   red color theme ;)

I don't have cooler cos I'll have CPU box, I'll buy it in case of OC.

Is there anything bad in my build?

Thank you for your tips!

My current build:

[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/RFDft6) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/RFDft6/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4690K 3.5GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54690k) | $222.75 @ OutletPC 
**Motherboard** | [Gigabyte GA-Z97X-Gaming 3 ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-motherboard-gaz97xgaming3) | $125.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Trident X Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-2400 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f32400c10d8gtx) | $75.89 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Gigabyte GeForce GTX 970 4GB WINDFORCE Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvn970g1gaming4gd) | $359.98 @ NCIX US 
**Case** | [Corsair SPEC-03 Red ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-cc9011052ww) | $59.99 @ Newegg 
**Power Supply** | [XFX 650W 80+ Bronze Certified Semi-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/xfx-power-supply-p1650xxxb9) | $105.18 @ Amazon 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $984.78
 | Mail-in rebates | -$35.00
 | **Total** | **$949.78**
 | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2015-03-06 14:10 EST-0500 |
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lua 5.1 as target may be better, because it's more widely used, also LuaJIT is mostly compatible with this version.

I think that book from Lua's creator is easy at all, so if you want to make something easier, then maybe make something for kids. For example writing games with LVE (+ setup etc), it may be more entertaining then playing with console that usually most people are scared of and when they see it they run away (anxiety is not so good for learning ;p).

About formatting - Lot of ppl make books with LaTeX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 16:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can publish under any name that you can prove that is yours. If you have company it may be official company name, otherwise you have to use your real name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 16:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it takes you so long because you use too hard tools (If I'd use C for logic instead of Lua it'd take 10x more time). I've seen lot of hobbyist programmers making games in scripting languages in few months.

About tiles - I was not enough familiar with them because I'm WP developer for just 1 week so I didn't use them, but thanks for tip, now I see that they may be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our first WP game called "Wildagotchi: Virtual Pet" is now available on Store. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 22:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!
We made game for Windows Phone (WP8+), it's retro-style tamagotchi-like virtual pet simulator.

Link to the game: http://www.windowsphone.com/s?appid=e68449e2-e12c-49b7-b2d8-03d5d12f6c8a

Users from previous platforms like this game so I hope WP users also will like it ;)

Thank you for any feedback and downloads. Please post review/rating if you like the game, it's really helpful.

Dev info -
We are indie devs - I'm programmer, my GF made graphics for pets foods.

Nerd info ;) -
I use my own engine in which I make games mostly using Lua. It's mix of C/C++, Java , Obj-C, Lua   now also some CX/C++   C#. Previously I had games only for Android   iOS but I added support for WP so now I plan to make games for 3 platforms at once. Because engine was OpenGL-based I used angleproject to wrap DX calls and anyway performance is good enough. So if anyone here wants to port iOS/Android OpenGL-based game to WP then I may give some tips about angleproject and other porting-related things.

Kind regards,
Janusz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
