<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5644</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Web developer here. PHP is an excellent start. If you really keep at it and use your free time to learn more you'll be raking it in within 4-5 years. I was earning minimum wage as well at 28. Today I'm 32 and making about 60k a year. Was a shit ton of hard work but it paid off. Last piece of advice would be if you're doing PHP, get to know a bit of front-end as well. As long as you know the basic with FE, you're good to go. Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That my friend is the Oriental Dwarf Kingfisher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a crush on her since I saw this GIF:
http://i.imgur.com/0QWjq8Z.gifv
Didn't know who she was before because I've never watched GOT. That GIF really got me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ms. Macluskey just gained herself a follower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since this question is floating around, allow me. They land using a parachute. Have a look here https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hr5_RFTo5Ec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be a good few years. Right now the closest is slalom [wingsuit racing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w6alw-t4FeM) I'd say. Even though jetpack racing would be awesome, I can't see it being too safe right now. This is all relatively new.
EDIT: Staircase wit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 12:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know he's new yeah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men with jetpacks fly in formation with the French Air Force Acrobatic team, The Patrouille de France. Human meets machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 12:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
