<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which fictional character is most similar to you and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That if you call the suicide hotline in Iraq you will get a job offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That white people aren't allowed to wear dreadlocks because it is cultural appropriation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The need to copy and paste other people's questions for upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll feel better when it's done by someone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up to you how you define it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've initiated contact on match.com if the guy has a detailed profile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Compared to your parents when they were your age, are you more successful, less successful, or about the same? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some ways I have succeeded beyond my wildest expectations (I had a very low self-esteem 10 hears ago) and yet at the same time it still isn't enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst manager was an old guy who tried to take credit for stuff I did rather than just admit he couldn't do it. He would get stuck on some software, ask me for my help, and then robotically say "Yup that's how I would've done it" when you can see he did try multiple times because now he has all these broken formulas that you have to delete to avoid cluttering the workbook. He also tried to pull rank, stuff like calling me over the phone to tell me to come into his office when his office was literally less than 10 feet away. Anyway, when our company got bought out by another company, he spoke up for both of us and talk the bigger company into hiring us, the bigger company saw I was doing the work while he was gerting the pay, so they laid him off but not me. Since then I have had 2 raises.

My best manager would never give you an assignment he wouldn't have done himself. He sometimes made you work past 10pm, but he would be sitting there working along with you instead of just pawning stuff on you while he went home early. He would make sure you got to present the stuff you worked on, he genuinely wanted to see you get further ahead in your career. We all loved him, he is still my Facebook friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White women over the internet* they are the female version of, well, you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's fine, do what works for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Software admin - that something was my fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I once got upset enough reading Pavarotti's memoir (his parents were practically a different species from mine) that I had to put the book down for a while to cool off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a highly desirable job that you DON'T want and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have unintentionally gotten people laid off just by working a lot harder than them, to the point they weren't needed anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a question, I just applied to audition for a fancy prestigious choir and they make you put down your choral part and even if you are I or II. I think I can handle both other parts but they didn't even give me the option to select other parts.

Also in every choir I have ever auditioned for they always ask me what part I have sung previously, and sometimes they only test that. They sometimes don't even test how low I can go. Why is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents had one of those extremely toxic marriages that went bad years before they separated. In my case everyone was telling them just to split, myself included, because the environment was so toxic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think attractiveness is too objective for someone to say what rating they are. I have been described as a "ten" before but definitely there will still be people who don't find you the least bit attractive. For example, some people say Taylor Swift is hot as hell and her fame is partly due to her looks, others will say she isn't attractive at all to them.

Meanwhile, my dating life is pretty similar to Taylor Swift's without the songs lol, I've dated quite a few guys but 90% of the time I am single because the relationships were little more than flings. Probably because the relationships themselves were very shallow - some guy is into me because they find me physically attractive, I realize it and then date them for the thrill, but our personalities don't work well together at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has someone ever instantly turned you off with a single comment during a date? What was that comment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaving one choir for another in the same area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been with my non-audition choir for 2 years and I want to join a choir that is more exclusive and a little more hardcore. Plus my choir is getting boring, we perform the same songs at the same events every year. I want to join one that's harder to get into, but if I audition for a choir they will ask who I sing with, would they judge me if I mention I want to leave my current choir because it isn't exclusive enough? I feel kind of guilty about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of summer, honey bees start evicting their drones. Those are the male bees who don't work and simply mooch off the hive - they are supposed to die after having sex with a virgin queen but haven't. They get kicked out of the hive at the end of summer by their sisters when food is scares and left to starve. It made me realize that honey bees are brutal as hell.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PWSBfbAixo0 t=1s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You try to talk about a serious sibject like what is in the news and they bring it back to what they are eating or dating lives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That saturated fat was bad and transfat was good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it normal for people who do the data at your company to have mistakes in the data? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asian who does math for a living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is easy on my eyes and doesn't affect my wallet, win-win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their prime minister of Canada. Rawr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can sing both the male and female parts of songs (I am female) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Color privilege I tell ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop stars make money off being sexy and fit. Especially Kpop stars.

Look at Pavarotti and tell me that man gets much exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soprano 2 in choir, voice teacher says I am a regular soprano. Vocal range A3 to Bb5, but I can dig down to non-musical sounding lower notes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taylor Swift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read half of her memoir. Keyword being half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People will finally start saving until marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I am 28

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joffrey's, I kept reading forward going "when is he gonna die already" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy who is genuinely smart without being one of those obnoxious guys who talk about how smart they are, who can hold a conversation on topics like books, who has a very pleasant speaking voice, socially outgoing but gets along well with a shy person like me, and he has a motorcycle, and he dabbles in music, and he has a curious mind, and he is politically moderate, and he won't cheat on a girlfriend, and he is within 5 years of my own age, and he has dark brown or black hair and an olive or bronze skin tone, and bright innocent eyes,, and he likes dogs.

Well, you said perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question makes no sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go away 14 year old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Jesus can never compete with God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you more or less successful than your parents and how does that make you feel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Investing it in a stock of some new technology that I am confident will take off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think this is true. If you are talking about your own marriage then that is your individual marriage's problem and does not reflect men as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By then I wanted everything to be the way it was in the movies, wanted to have "our song" and other stupid cliches. I was 20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I went through TSA, I was wearing a short sleeved shirt and yet they kept wiping their scanner over my completely bare hands/arms when it is obvious there is nothing there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bugtrapper - a remote controlled toy that will trap that cockroach you don't want to touch, drive it out of the house, and let it go. Control it from another room with a streaming video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not one of those people who get offended by everything under the sun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I am 28 it gives me a double-take because I am usually referred to a ma'am. I do come across as younger (or maybe people just assume 28 year olds are supposed to seem older) so I dont really think much of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bounty towels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had an outdoor broom for leaves but sweeping outdoors is different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thought about the face aging, didn't even occur to me I could look down and see the skin on the back of my hands get coarser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got confused at the old picture being on the bottom and the new picture being on the top, I thought it was the reverse and was astounted by the high quality 1984 graphics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to outdo the men AND the women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Greek mythology Tiresias said women enjoyed it more.

In reality, you can probably see which sex wants to do it more, so pretty sure it is the guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IT Crowd, Sherlock, Britain's Got Talent, I Claudius, Would I Lie to You, and The Jeremy Kyle Show (that one I saw on Youtube).

We need Would I Lie to You in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was attractive, getting older now so less attractive, but answering for my younger self...

You end up being old man bait. You get a lot of unwanted attention from men old enough to be your father. You feel yourself avoiding eye contact when talking to a middle-aged stranger because if you seem approachable they will start hitting on you, some won't take no for an answer. People will assume you slept with your manager to get your job. People will be nicer to you but a lot of it is conditional. Little kids and babies will like you a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The actual prose style, the whole book used very unnecessarily flowery language.

Here is an excerpt: 

I still smart a little at the slight. When you've suffered a great deal in life, each additional pain is both unbearable and trifling. My life is like a memento mori painting from European art: there is always a grinning skull at my side to remind me of the folly of human ambition. I mock this skull. I look at it and I say, "You've got the wrong fellow. You may not believe in life, but I don't believe in death. Move on!" The skull snickers and moves ever closer, but that doesn't surprise me. The reason death sticks so closely to life isn't biological necessity -- it's envy. Life is so beautiful that death has fallen in love with it, a jealous, possessive love that grabs at what it can. But life leaps over oblivion lightly, losing only a thing or two of no importance, and gloom is but the passing shadow of a cloud. The pink boy also got the nod from the Rhodes Scholarship committee. I love him and I hope his time at Oxford was a rich experience. If Lakshmi, goddess of wealth, one day favours me bountifully, Oxford is fifth on the list of cities I would like to visit before I pass on, after Mecca, Varanasi, Jerusalem and Paris.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Falling so slow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once read a fanfic that was about Harry Potter going to Godric's Hollow, finding his dad's decaying corpse, and proceeds to have sex with it. When I realized where the fanfic was headed I actually fell out of my chair and started retching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The New Testament also a fanfic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hated Life of Pi, the book was as pretentious as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Chinese mom loves putting down other women and saying she isn't them because she is like a man. It's gotten this bad:

Her: What is a transgender?

Me: Someone who is physically one sex but thinks like another.

Her (all proud): So like me!

Me: No, you are not transgender... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump became the next president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the night though, or would you somehow end it early? Like if you are having coffee should you finish your drinks first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poisons usually don't act fast enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are on a first date with someone you met online, the date is only halfway over, and you already know you don't want to go on a second date with them. What are you supposed to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, right now I am trying online dating. Stopped talking to a guy when his hobbies were apparently giving massages and cooking for me. It was just thick with insincerity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah a Filipina roommate of mine judged the hell out of me for not knowing how to sweep properly with a broom. We used the vacuum cleaner at my house okay ;_; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gave up their seat on a metro because I was really sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animal shelter dog walker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stroke in my sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has happened to me, I had a coworker who kept taking credit for my work in meetings and eventually I stopped telling him what I was working on so he would not be able to answer. Or right after he made up some BS answer I would say "actually" and clarify what I actually did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only voted for Clinton in the primary because I am a middle-class asshole who doesn't want poor people to make $15/hr because the inflation will hurt my savings.

I didn't vote in the main election because when I updated my voter address my entire registration disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When people come up to me and start asking me about ~my culture~ because I am Asian. Strikes a nerve in me. I was born in the UK and raised in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My crazy ass tiger mom.

She once told a male secretary to do something with Photoshop. When he said he didn't know how to use Photoshop, she started yelling that he wasn't a real man because real men know their way around computer programs. She also yelled at me for not working as hard as a boy my age, and when I said she paid him and not me she started yelling that my roof over my head was my pay, the food on my table was my pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the teachers was arrested during the school year because he brought his computer somewhere to have it fixed and they found child porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw transgender refer to nontransgendered people as cisgender, or you can just say non-transgender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lower voices, I love the sound of a clear male speaking voice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animal by Sky Ferreira

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f3Z581wh85U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second kills you slowly without you realizing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got asked out without knowing I was asked out. Once I was standing with 2 guys and one of them said "we should hang out some time" and I thought he meant the 3 of us hang out as friends. I said okay, he asked for my number, and told me to meet him downstairs from the dorm. Was a date.

Another time I had a classmate tell me he had a group of friends he wanted me to meet, I wanted to make new friends so I said okay, and then he picks me up in a car with only a guy and girl making out in the back. He told me the others canceled, whoops.

Neither of these surprise dates ended in a second date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word hippopotamus comes from the Greek hippo, meaning horse, and potamos, meaning river. So a hippopotamus is a river horse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid I found a spell on some geocities website that would turn me invisible. I chanted it and walked around, and then got frustrated when people saw me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foie gras </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pillsbury </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biore for me, those self heating masks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: To log into 2 accounts on the same website at the same time, open one in Incognito mode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got driven home by the cops after walking for 7 hours in the rain. Mental breakdown when I couldn't find a job for 6 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloading music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting severely burned to the point of deformity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little Women, although I was too young to get it, I just remembered my friend and I shared a massive bucket of popcorn and my mom was complaining we weren't watching the movie. I was 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had super traditional Asian parents who wanted me to go into statistics/accounting, meanwhile the thing I loved that my teachers encouraged me to go into was writing.

I majored in creative writing, struggled to find work for 3 years, but now I do alright making 60k a year as a Tableau/Salesforce admin. Did get a novella published with a small press, working on bigger stuff. I don't regret that but I am upset with how my parents treated me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I had ADHD, would have saved so many years of self-hate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a dating app, shouldn't they avoid putting pictures of other people up without their permission? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen very young (under 20, heck under 18) girls use this on various social media platforms. Honestly it is a very teenage thing to say so if a woman over 25 says that I can understand running for the hills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real? I can't imagine any girl dating online to get laid when she can just walk into a bar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if all the girls are hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, if you were to find a relationship online, what is something in a girl's profile that will automatically make you say "nope"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immigration line. They actually told us to get there the night before and just sleep on the curb if you want them to get to you by the time the office closed (2pm or so) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone who is smart. And someone with a nice clean look to them - no visible tattoos or goatees, not really a fan of beards.

Personality-wise someone who is sincere. It makes me uncomfortable if some guy I barely know comes up to me and starts talking about what he would do for a girlfriend (neck massages and stuff) because to me it's not natural. That guy is throwing a bunch of lines at you because he think that's what ~women~ want to hear and he's reducing you to something interchangeable with anyone else who is female. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing really, she was pretty much a less sexy Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrrr a handsome Canadian he is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do what they did in movies and have the leaders of the countries fight each other to the death Hunger Games style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can decide all he wants, doesn't excuse the teacher for having sex with a student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe hell yeah they are less likely to regret it, but it does not excuse a teacher for taking advantage of a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would vote no, my company headquarters are in Utah and I like easy travel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you implying it should be younger for males because they are less likely to regret boning an older woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop caring so much about your weight. Just look at yourself naked and ask yourself if you look fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She hates other women and will constantly say women are this, women are that, but SHE isn't like that because she is one of thise rare women who are like a man.

Once we were talking about politics and she asked me what is a transgender person.

Me: Someone who is physically one gender but thinks like the other.

Her: (all proud) Like me!

Me: Um, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would wonder if he is gay, but I don't think there is anything wrong with him being gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to make friends versus reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
