<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh i need some ointment for this burn! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I wish to point out that all the sponsors and co-sponsors of this senate resolution ..... guess what party they are with .... REPUBLICAN!!! Including Rand Paul!](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/senate-joint-resolution/34/cosponsors) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Bruva! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude its a pg-13 movie at worst here in the united states and the only reason it got pg-13 because of the fact they got close to saying curse words a bunch of times and oh no sci-fi cartoon like violence and angsty depiction of teens. If this was done by a large movie company like Fox or WB it would be PG easily.

No way this deserves an R rating for something as subtle as a small head nod.

Russians in power are asshole xenophobic, racist, bigoted as fuck, homophobic drunks.

http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-36132060

http://www.nydailynews.com/news/world/leading-russian-actor-gays-burn-alive-ovens-article-1.1547713

http://www.advocate.com/world/2014/10/17/watch-scott-lively-russia-hate-sodom-documentary

http://www.advocate.com/news/world-news/2013/11/18/russian-journo-claims-gays-caused-meteor-strike

http://www.motherjones.com/mojo/2014/10/scott-lively-massachusetts-governor-sodom-russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> word of advice you want to remove any post that has any sort of text you blurred out. You want to put straight black bars instead and flatten the image and remove exif data as well. The blur images can now be easily deblured now and you can make out the numbers enough on that one apple card to get an idea of your member number. The Exif information in jpegs edited in photoshop can also keep a thumbnail of the original image before editing in the edited copy so that too. 

https://www.extremetech.com/computing/138363-the-cia-de-blurs-license-plates-from-outer-space-now-you-can-too-for-free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the thought of mind to know how you were once in need and the system was there to try to help catch you at your weakest with a safety net and save you from far worse fates that you might never have gotten out of. Payback into the system and also make sure that money is spent from your taxes to help others who were just like you in the same situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me and my fiancee left the theater talking about how realistic they made the kids. They showed how kids actually deal with. That bully that gets away with trying to break your wrist, or the clicky cheerleaders, or the jock who hates being golden boy, the kid who is taking care of a sick parent (which hit really hard for me) and isn't Asian kid stereotypical smart kid either, a black kid on the spectrum and explaining it matter of factly without it making him "special", and a gay latinx girl who has a conservative family who doesn't understand her and she doesn't understand herself. Also they showed half of them living in trailer parks and not well off either. The houses they all lived in were real lower middle class households

It had a really good almost "Goonies" vibe to it and made it just seem more realistic. 

Also god i loved how Jason just slapped the bully. He knows he is stronger than the guy and knows shame gets to people far better than straight violence. It was a great trait they put in for him to show he is good at heart.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malaysian telekom has the full episode up.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=duOFYx-Dgho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [time to read the resolution](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/senate-joint-resolution/34/text) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [time to read the resolution](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/senate-joint-resolution/34/text) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or in truth also a Kakistocracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it that in a fight it completely throws off your opponent and any sense of drive they had for the fight is broken there after. Also If i know what my goal is from the start the get go it is easier to go for that using less energy and less stress at finding an opening for the first punch or redirecting their punch. It's an offensive defense which has never failed me and if it just enraged the guy they just start going for wild windmilling punches with no direction or force behind them and are easy to then grab and redirect to the ground with basic Aikido.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Promoting a state sanctioned banning of even talking about it or mentioning the idea it exists or support groups for people to find people to understand them under fear of prison or having pro putin groups come after them to beat them up or kill them is the definition of hate we are looking at here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is subtle but if you never talked to other kids who are just coming out you wouldn't catch it i think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a scene where explaining their backgrounds to each other to help unlock the morphing grid armors, which is only unlocked when the team cares about each other, they explain there different fucked up backgrounds. Trinni explains that her family is a family that likes labels and things to fit in those labels, They want her to dress a certain way, act a certain way, have relationships they don't have to worry about. Zack then says what "boy troubles?"

Trini responds blowing that off as, "Yeahhhhhhhh boy troubles?" rolling her eyes, Zack then says," Girl Troubles?" and she looks at him and turns the corner of her lip up with a slight nod. Its very subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie was amazing. Even with cheesy product placement I really enjoyed it. Diversity Boners was had by me and my fiancee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 of those because the bill didn't gut enough protections like requiring hospital visits being paid for or doctor visits or drugs. So basically you could be paying for insurance that gave you 1 doctor visit a year and that is it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very much am a fan of Parliamentary Legislative systems. I'm also a fan of how they limit the size of political parties causing them to break up so no party has more than 30% on average, Preventing a Nazi take over again. Also the more parties you have the more likely the average of the votes becomes true centrist views on social issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when have you ever seen a ISP get cheaper because they found a new profit revenue from information they already had? This is going to just keep the price the same and get twice the money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually telling the truth. It is just funny how many young men get triggered by this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never been to cozumel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borg are my all time fav villian, its like Hellraiser in space. They almost fucked them up on voyager, they were the only thing any good on that show i felt, except the kids ... fuck those annoying ass borg kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wrastle?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Shitpost] One does not Simply shitpost Legends of Tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do believe death threats are a banable offense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you never say no homo you look at them and establish dominance, [like this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xIwps1P3ZIs)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musical episodes can be hilarious though example buffy the vampire slayer -"once more with feeling" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you were any other man i would kill you where you stand"

I agree chills at that line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In whoes eyes? Yours? Mehhh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticking dicks in time lines again barry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What ever bro you totes the [gheeeeey](https://youtu.be/YaG5SAw1n0c)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word up bro will do. Let me gets a copy of snow crash and influx  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have i kissed my share of guys? Yes yes i have. But i know i have never gotten an erection from it though and the only time i have twitched in my loins is when its raven haired Mediterranean women. Also i have never had a sex dream of guys. But if you belive in a sliding scale of sexuality as the kinsey scale i would say 0 to 5 straight to gay Im right at the 1 to 2.0

Its a guys voice that turns me off. Even transgender women the falsetto voice still sounds too masculine to me. Baily jay though sounds pretty girlish but im an old school 4channer so line trap is in everyones 34 folder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show us on the doll where i give a shit darling, you are not going to find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg really now my dear? Can you tell like that sweetcheeks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insert katty perry joke here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear m'lady im sorry you dont like the joke maybe your trigger butt hurt needs a safespace or an adult darling;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh darling you are no fun. Here have a bag of jelly red pills maybe it will make your tigger less i dont know little whiney bitchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmmm i love the triggering from you boys. Full on fabulous darling [milo impressonator to 11] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many angry triggered boys!!!! So many fantastically wonderful boys! Fabulous [does his best Milo impression] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not that im aware of. If you are grabbing my female friend's ass you either are a misogynistic redpill asshole or you're overcompensating for being so deep in the closet you cant even find the door  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never had a cold sore actually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a gender studies course as a humanities elective in college? Also I like the movie Kinsey with with Liam Neeson as Alfred Kinsey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ship was set on auto-destruct. Her way was the way the rest of the crew thought would the sane way to go. Even Worf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok bro. word. its nice to chat but like what evers, why you so triggered snowflake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not i'm talking about dumb white guys who stereotype them because white feminists make life so hard for them, you know the real dumb ass types. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> typically you go in in praying pose and slide in fast spreading your arms wide blocking their arms by spreading their arms apart since their arms are typically in boxer's stance, most people have little to no martial arts experience. You now have your chest against their's with your arms under their's and their arms wipe apart. You then want to grab one arm by wrapping it down pull their arm by the bicep down while wrapping it around and then with the other hand I go for the ass grap while holding the back of their head and then plant the wet one on their lips. This is rather fast and the entire motion is not typical for fighting for people who are trained. I'm not off balancing them so this throws them off. The kiss then comes in with the full handed ass cupping, potentially moving fingers to crack of the pants these unwelcomed advances to anyone adverse to the concept of male on male contact or unwelcome sexual advances completely shocks and freezes a person up ESPECIALLY in public areas where people are watching it happen. The laughter from the crowd also embarrasses the fuck out them and I have seen guys turn bright cherry red from this.
In order to get most guys since I'm 6 foot 5 I drop into a semi position modified horse stance spreading their legs so they cant get in for a knee or a kick. If they did i have them in such a way that i can kick in their heel causing them to fall backward on their ass and timber I go too. 6 foot 5, 400lbs dropping on someone fast hurts a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you play it up switch, just mind my hemorrhoids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked her. It makes sense that it was someone from that time period would reduce all of this technology to call out an obvious engineering solution to technology run a muck, just blow it up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sexually assault guys who sexually assault my friends. Hey if they can do it by grabbing my friends backside or try to kiss them why can't I? I'm just following by example. Karma can be a real bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know I was being sarcastic right, it was a parody of a dear penthouse letter . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fight a year is not much actually for being 33 years old about. And its turn about is fair play really. You go to enough bars with friends or electronic music events you run into all sorts of people who are asshats and want to prove something when you tell them to step off for grabbing a friend in an inappropriate way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawful means they wouldn't be damn hypocrites all the time trying to ban same sex marriage and adoption and then getting caught with male prostitutes doing Party drugs or raping 16 year old boys in hotel rooms ... if you google the news as of late you see what i mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -TLDR-: I kiss guys open mouth who are trying to fist fight me and it causes them to nope the fuck out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did Kempo, Aikido, and a few other martial arts up until I was about 25 and couldn't afford membership normally and moved out of my home state. My sensai was the one who taught me about the distracting guys this way. One day after class, i never thought it would happen to me ....

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You a top or a bottom? I got the pegs if you be the board ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you grab their cock ;) Also the open mouth / without tounge is done because it's harder to bite than closed mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i know where i am on the Kinsey Scale. I'm a solid 1 to 1.5 

Edris Elba, David Bowie (RIP), George Takei are on that if I was full blown gay list. [Also everyone is a little gay.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mY711HJK7pg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a bar with friends. It happens like once a year at most. It usually deals with me confronting someone for disrespecting a friend by them invading their personal space. Hasn't happened since I moved to Portland though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done to both drunk and nondrunk. The guys who are that aggro and that pig headed are so thrown off that if they have tried to come back at me their game is hella rattled. Easy enough to deflect or redirect them into a wall or something. But out of some 20 fights I have had to deal with only 2 in the last 15 years have tried coming back. Most are so horrifically violated by the look on their face they shiver and run off. I also go for the ass grab as well with it if they fight too much as the first thing they do then is lower their hands and try to get yours off their ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I win fist fights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I win fist fights since I was 15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslims inside FBI describe culture of suspicion   fear: 'It is cancer' Said Sam Barodi was fired after he refused to cooperate with customs agents who he believed were targeting him because of his ethnicity and religion. He   other accounts paint a stark picture of the bureau in the era of Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs suffering as a precipitate when political ambition is added to to the solution  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get lost in the time stream? because this was from 21 days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too love the white people's Morgan Freeman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why it should have a photo on it with two factor authentication and private key crypto like Estonia does.  Also then works as a passport.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Estonian_ID_card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistical fact: Cops will never pull over a man with a huge bong in his car. Why? They fear this man. They know he sees further than they and he will bind them with ancient logics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saturday Morning Breakfast Cereal [webcomic] - Important Moments in Philosophy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it like kirk gets the Kobayashi Maru and playing tic-tac-to. The only winning move is not to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were you expecting Transparent Aluminum?  sheesh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/SirPatStew/status/722251866793316353

https://twitter.com/TJ_Knight/status/844295737160749057/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is all a dream and david wakes up .... [HE BETTER FUCKING HAVE THIS HAIR!](http://i.imgur.com/z0gHYg0.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Maury says the test results says ... you are the father </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Legion gets anyone to play Charles Xavier in the show for a cameo who do you want it to be? James McAvoy or Patrick Stewart?

If both WHY HAVE YOU NOT STARTED TWEETING THE FUCK OUT IT TO BOTH OF THEM AND THE PRODUCERS OF THE SHOW?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will always be one of my favorite scenes in Star Trek and favorite scenes for Sir Patrick Stewart | Star Trek: First Contact - Captain Ahab must go hunt his Cybernetic Whale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter says Sir Patrick Stewart in drag looks a lot like Kellyanne Conway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter says Sir Patrick Stewart in drag looks a lot like Kellyanne Conway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter says Sir Patrick Stewart in drag looks a lot like Kellyanne Conway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter says Sir Patrick Stewart in drag looks a lot like Kellyanne Conway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my favorite scenes of Star Trek and Patrick Stewart | Star Trek: First Contact - Captain Ahab must go hunt is Cybernetic Whale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my favorite scenes of Patrick Stewart | Star Trek: First Contact - Captain Ahab must go hunt is Cybernetic Whale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rape Club In </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not enough love for "8-bit Philosophy" show by wisecrack. You are missing out a great way to get kids into understanding a wide range of Philosophical concepts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you enjoy causing other people pain to feel happy? Is your life that sad and depressing that the pain of others is the only way you feel happy? Do you want to talk about it? You seem very angry. No troll serious bruv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually trucks are number one cause for air issues in major metropolitan areas that don't have fracking wells. And also I have had people "Roll Coal" at me several times where they change the Mixture through modication of lifted trucks to have their fuel injector over inject fuel on purpose to create blasts of high carbon and unburnt fuel at people. Its dangerous because it is a road hazard and even for events like this its a waste since they could tune the truck to use the fuel better and get just as much torque. The only reason i know most who do it is to say fuck you environmentalists and people i'm told i should have consideration for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is the entire cabinet is dirty as fuck. I mean DIRTY! the money changing hands between everyone is so incestuous that if one of them goes down they will take others with them to save their own ass. It will spread like an HIV epidemic spreads in central Indiana when Mike Pence was Gov. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't spell republican without R A P E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me guess which party he is aligned with ..... Chaotic Evil? Aka Republicon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out though the surveillance for most of them is related to crimes of money laundering and espionage. Many of these intelligence reports are in relation i heard to information being used by New York federal prosecutor Preet Bharara who was then fired since his major big case he was working on was dealing with over paid for real estate where Russian Kremlin types would pay 40 million on a 20 million dollar property and then split the difference with the person they bought it from making 10 million or more in slush dark money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an insult to President Bartlet. That man got us through some hard times during the Bush/Dark Lord of the Oil Whitehouse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh no no they were never under surveillance, they just happen to walk into the camera lense's path when they went to talk to Russians who were under surveillance and that was before the "winning" the US election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um isn't there like a roof he can go up to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a country of immigrants and refugees. Most of the early colonies were penal colonies for petty thieves, convicts, whores, and other unwanted. This nation was founded by the people seen as the worst in their home countries and by people who wanted to breath free. 

We are a nation of rejects who banned together. Some think they are better than other people and they just don't know their own history and try to confuse the poor to think that others are to blame for them being worse off. 

you are an american my dear and never forget that. And you are bad ass! Because you are different is what makes you american and what makes you awesome. */thumbs up/* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh shit .... now i'm torn between cheap booze or cheap pot .... I DON"T KNOW WHAT TO DO!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like cultures that repress issues are only going to have them worse .... hmmmmmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snails, slow until not, but always metal as fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it funny that people who live a life of nothing but pleasure as they age start to turn more and more bitter and angry and look for anything and anyone to blame. This is also a sign of someone who is dealing with some sort of untreated form of depression or Bi-Polar disorder as well. Her risk taking behavior early on and constantly being super high energy in a manic way makes me think she is dealing with rapid switching bipolar type 1 disorder. This will lead to grandiose thinking and her fixation on nazi imagery and playing into that world shows she has lost the attention of normal people and wants to be famous and loved by people who are just as manic and delusional as she is. Anyway you can blame someone for why you feel sad and never confronting the reality is the buck stops with you about why you feel certain ways. 

"Is it I who is out of touch with reality? No it's the jews who deny me my happiness" - The Nazi Blame game 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAFT PUNK - MIX LOUIS VUITTON 2008 (remake of Daft Punk Mix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you a nazi you openly supported trump  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is some serious Yugioh level duelist level politics then if it was which i believe it was. It shows the party and the committees in charge of this are not to be trusted because the republicans are all corrupt and will help the traitor stay in power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI investigations suggests Trump Campaign aides may have coordinated Russian's release of hacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " they like me [in the nazi party] because i bring a little diversity to it" - tila tequila 

Several major players in the american nazi fuckboi party also marry asian women because they are docile and subservient. So it is typically all theredpill starter pack rejects  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the worse with unrtreated mental illnesses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we are vemomboy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we are vemomboy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Intelligence Committee chair Rep. Devin Nunes (R-CA) claimed to have evidence that President Donald Trump was surveilled after all and rushed to tell Trump. Turns out the surveillance was not on Trump himself or Trump Tower but on campaign members caught in surveillance on Russia. Oh My </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fan of this dock by OWC more. https://www.owcdigital.com/dec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the following things millennials put off doing because of the cost

1. buying homes
2. buying cars
3. getting married
4. going to the doctor
5. living a happy life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW when I realized Ashly Burch of youtube show "Hey Ash, what you playing?" is the voice actor for Alloy in Horizon Zero Dawn, Chloey Price from Life is Strange,   Tiny Tina from Borderlands 2   is a writer for season 8 on Adventure Time   talks at GDC about experimental storytelling in video games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [we all live in amerika! it's wunderbar, amerika!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rr8ljRgcJNM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And that is when Tila Tequila went full nazi.](https://www.buzzfeed.com/kateaurthur/tila-tequilas-descent-into-nazism-is-a-long-time-coming?utm_term=.xjPA3RVwE#.qsRKZ6x29) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyone's depression is the same depression but the stress everyone has is far from the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean like Speaker of the House Paul Ryan was ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Climate change research actually is very important for the study of exo-plants and finding out what is a goldilocks planet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh really? it's that simple? You do know that is is very hard to undo a tubal ligation right? It is far easier to just give out free IUD implantable birth control, and deporpovara pills for women who can't due to wegener's syndrome and copper absorption as well as the fact many women need birth control to help control their cycles and cramping. Not to mention women with Polycystic Ovary Syndrome need birth control as one of the drugs to help control the syst growth and limit it.

But by all means lets just sterilize the poor like the did in the 40s and 50s in North Carolina. EUGENICS NOW EUGENICS FOREVER!!!!! /s


asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Keith Stanfield

GET OUT!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait ... really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: be able to afford or even find birth control in the southern states if you are female or get abortion if you are raped and conceive rape baby, unless rapist comes back and sues you to prevent abortion
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: be able to afford or even find birth control in the southern states if you are female or get abortion if you are raped and conceive rape baby, unless rapist comes back and sues you to prevent abortion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because  they were told not to as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person in a position of power and is supposed to protect you and provide guidance violates that trust committed a crime still. Even if he was 18 it was still a crime because its against the law in many states for a teacher to have sex with a student period in primary education. Still corrupt as fuck teacher who is a predator and emotionally most likely never grown up either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the response, " I don't want to be right, I want you to do it before I have to tell you to." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He never asked for this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CXpuRIZzJog) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here enjoy some LOTR meme](https://youtu.be/fxaRb53UX90)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just any people, black people particularly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you forgot the /s tag 

But the fact that a evangelical pastor was disturbed by the rally shows that the people attending them are so deranged that even the traditional rank and file evangelical right are getting disturbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evolved form, evolved form. Doesn't mean it's better. Just look at spicy for example. Goes to katsukon and everything. Weeaboo evolved form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redpill alt-righter is the evolved form of american weeaboo, Weeaboo is a dark bug type pokemon that when evolved become a dark fighting type pokemon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally i think its supposed to be a universe forming. Legion has reality warping and creating powers. I'm thinking he is so over powered that he is having his mind explode into creating a new universe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well we spotted the alt-right redpill starter pack asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants holy war crusades and christian domination world wide and he thinks the cycle is every 80 years to wipe the slate clean. he is a real doomsday nut job type about having a ww2 every 80 years and wipe the slate clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Osama bin Laden was a butt hurt filthy rich trust fund kid who found Allah after getting dumped by a white girl after grad school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bankrupt the united states by starting a long unending war while ostracizing western Muslim from western culture was Osman bin ladens goal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im tired and have been studying for a chem final and running on little sleep  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not ask for money i was pointing out hypocrisy of it and seriously, shill? Lollerskates you trumpers are hilarious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All is fools gold. You will find nothing of scholarly value. Just cancer of thought, heart, and mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a fan of anonymous posting sites. You tend to have it be a circle jerk of extreme thinking with no vetting or peer review .

The value of speech on those sites would be akin to fart jokes and tourette outbursts or edge lord teens, manlets, and emotionally stunted man children posting derivative jokes ad nauseum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah its called PBS newshour. You don't listen to extremist shock jockies and expect there to be balanced debate do you? Their whole biz model is to say stuff to make inflammatory enemies and appeal to a base looking for someone to make their feelings seem justified or validate their bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those are personal pages though and they have the right to do what they want. If you want to comment go to the article comments section. Facebook pages are kinda like store fronts if they are public ones. You have to do the weeding and stuff and keep it looking like everyone is going along with the plan.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Currently the #1 post on r/The_Donald. [x-post /r/facepalm] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has my upvote and crosspost on /r/MarchAgainstTrump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4chan started banning people from all of 4chan from posting now for posting twitter links to people. I posted the twitter feed to their "stickman" asking for money on paypal via his wife since he is up for 7 federal assault charges and assaulting a police officer charge. I got banned because I DOXed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhh boy moving to Sweden is he going to have a rough time with how they support diversity and such. Also they don't fuck around when they give the ban hammer in real life for Nazi fucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amy Schumer is just like Jeff dunn, you either like them or you dont and if you don't it seems the hate come out in droves. But It happens more to Female and minority comics i notice. Rarely do they talk about joke stealing if it is someone like Robin Williams or Jay More or Denis Leary. Also its like a guy can talk about his cock or having sex but when i woman does it ... WOW no i didn't need ot hear that !!!!!! Most women I know like Amy Schumer because she does jokes that they relate to. As I guy i don't like most of her jokes because its just too crass for me. But I get them and the fact she talks about stuff like Feminine odor and biological stuff which most comics don't talk about allows other typically repressed women to talk about it.  

Ehh I just don't get the vitriolic hate. Her Comedy Central show i find funny, and staff on there is mostly women too for the writing team so i like that they can get a side of humor about being a woman not shown typically. But mehhh Mehhhhhh MEHHHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [we must go deeper!](http://i.imgur.com/ky3U2zG.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i know I saw it and I was like yup LOL but my first comment was joking because it was too obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
