<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3447</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posters calling on Muslim residents to leave immediately have resulted in a police investigation in a village in Uttar Pradesh, India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey threatens ending EU refugee deal amid diplomatic crisis with Germany and the Netherlands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine politician begins impeachment process against President Rodrigo Duterte over the thousands of deaths caused by his drug crackdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on Thursday he would honor his commitment to build a new settlement in the occupied West Bank, the first in two decades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letter bomb at IMF's Paris office addressed to the world lender's European representative blew up as a female employee opens it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson calls for 'new approach' to North Korea threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French scientists said Wednesday they had found a way to pinpoint elusive white blood cells that provide a hideout for the AIDS virus in people taking anti-HIV drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French scientists said Wednesday they had found a way to pinpoint elusive white blood cells that provide a hideout for the AIDS virus in people taking anti-HIV drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change is making people sick  Doctors say in a report called Medical Alert! Climate Change is Harming Our Health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three women have reportedly been left blind after they took part in a botched clinical trial of an unproven stem cell treatment, the patients are said to have each paid $5,000 (4,100) to participate in the procedure, which was advertised online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. has $732 billion invested in Robotics Stock  which, by way of comparison, is more than Switzerlands entire economy for the year 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check Point Discloses Vulnerability that Allowed Hackers to Take over Hundreds of Millions of WhatsApp   Telegram Accounts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul says Paul Ryan selling 'bill of goods' to Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel peace laureate Adolfo Perez Esquivel and other Argentine human rights activists are visiting a Falklands Islands cemetery, The trip come ahead of planned efforts by Argentina and Britain to identify the remains of 123 Argentine soldiers buried there after the 1982 conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A prominent Polish historian presented evidence Wednesday about Polish villagers widespread killing of Jews fleeing Nazis during World War II, touching a raw nerve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental authorities are searching for a 10-foot long crocodile that killed and apparently ate a man in southern Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reducing pollution and curbing overfishing wont prevent the severe bleaching that is killing coral at catastrophic rates, according to a study of Australias Great Barrier Reef </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government leakers are 'enemies to our state,' White House official says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can never imagine that this would happen in the 21st century. Shame, shame shame and shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States is working with India to ensure the countrys acceptance into the Nuclear Supplies Group (NSG), there are currently 48 members and the group controls the export of materials, equipment and technology that could be used to create nuclear weapons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A three-year-old girl in Pakistan has been forced into marriage in order to settle a dispute between her father and another man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eleven Philippine legislators who voted against a bill to re-introduce capital punishment lost key posts in the country's Congress on Wednesday, in an apparent follow through of a threat by the house speaker to purge obstacles to the draft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate confirms Trump intelligence nominee Coats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico wants its kids speaking English as well as Spanish within 20 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secretary of State Rex Tillerson will warn Chinas leaders that the United States is prepared to step up missile defenses and pressure on Chinese financial institutions if they fail to use their influence to restrain North Koreas nuclear and missile programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Koreans angered after ousted leader Park Geun-hye leaves dogs behind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The diplomatic spat between Turkey and the Netherlands spread online on Wednesday when a large number of Twitter accounts, many with no apparent connection to the dispute, were hijacked and replaced with anti-Nazi messages in Turkish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Earned $153m and Paid $36.5m in Taxes in 2005 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China to Trump: We dont want a trade war  but if there is one, youd lose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sign which appears to warn "beware of Jews" has been reported to police after it was posted in an area with a large orthodox Jewish population </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supercomputers may boost life expectancy by 10 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Intelligence chairman plans public hearing on Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chairman of the U.S. Senate Intelligence Committee said on Tuesday he plans to hold public hearings on possible links between President Donald Trump's campaign and Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine high-ranking U.S. Navy officers, including one former admiral, have been charged with trading classified information in exchange for travel, dinner and prostitution services from a foreign defense contractor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Navy officials charged in 'staggering' bribery scheme involving classified information, officials say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Schmeichel saves Steven Nzonzi penalty for Sevila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full time: Leicester City beats Sevilla 2 - 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Schmeichel saves Steven Nzonzi penalty for Sevila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samir Nasri headbutt Jamie Vardy: Red Card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marc Albrighton goal: Leicester City 2 Vs Sevila 0 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paulo Dybala penalty goal for Juventus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The German government has formally proposed fining Facebook and Twitter up to 50m ($53m) for failing to remove slanderous fake news and hate speech within 24 hours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The German government has formally proposed fining Facebook and Twitter up to 50m ($53m) for failing to remove slanderous fake news and hate speech within 24 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The top prosecutor in Mexicos Gulf coast state of Veracruz confirmed Tuesday that more than 250 skulls have been found in what appears to be a drug cartel mass burial ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All major crime events are now technology-based, security experts say in their newly-published study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland would "have to queue" to rejoin Europe in the event it achieved independence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Rodrigo Duterte of the Philippines defiantly rebuked human rights groups and international organizations on Tuesday, pledging to continue his deadly anti-drug crackdown despite mounting calls for a criminal investigation into his actions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British MPs have warned Twitter, Facebook and Google that they have a terrible reputation over their efforts to tackle abusive content </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a non-partisan, before I say my mind, is there any plan by the Republican for the 24 million that will be left behind? And other issues arising?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one way the use of Social Media is making a positive difference! God bless all the 200, 000 people that help make her dreams come true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The oldest plant-like fossils ever discovered suggest multicellular life began at least 1.6 billion years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A young Frenchwoman with Down's syndrome will fulfil her dream of presenting the weather on television after a Facebook campaign that was supported by more than 200,000 people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A young Frenchwoman with Down's syndrome will fulfil her dream of presenting the weather on television after a Facebook campaign that was supported by more than 200,000 people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisias coastguard yesterday confirmed it had seized 31 kilogrammes of pure cocaine valued at more than $6 million off its Mediterranean coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Admin Ups Drone Strikes, Tolerates More Civilian Deaths </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump administration is moving ahead with plans to make it easier for the CIA and the military to target terrorists with drone strikes, even if it means tolerating more civilian casualties, U.S. officials told NBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hospital stocks fall after Republican health bill seen leaving 24 million uninsured </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The German hometown of Karl Marx has voted to accept a controversial statue of the revolutionary philosopher from China  to the consternation of some of its citizens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norway's $900-bln wealth fund says real estate may lose some of its shine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh doubts surfaced on Tuesday over the financial propriety of French presidential candidate Francois Fillon with the opening of an inquiry by parliament's ethics chief into how he came to accept a gift of two bespoke suits worth 13,000 euros ($13,835) last month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thai customs seize 21 rhino horns worth $5m in major black market bust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia appears to have deployed special forces to an airbase in western Egypt near the border with Libya in recent days, U.S., Egyptian and diplomatic sources say, a move that would add to U.S. concerns about Moscow's deepening role in Libya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish Police have released striking pictures of a huge weapons haul seized from an organised crime group. It includes over 10,000 assault rifles, machine guns, pistols, revolvers, and 400 shells and grenades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian federal police on Tuesday arrested two people accused of taking bribes in return for infrastructure contracts in Rio de Janeiro, including the construction of a new subway line for the 2016 Olympic Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian-led peace talks on Syria were derailed on Tuesday as rebels backed by Turkey boycotted a third round of meetings in Kazakhstan and the Kremlin indicated there were international divisions over the process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin frustrated by lack of dialogue between Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian President Vladimir Putin is frustrated by a lack of progress in US-Russian diplomacy since Donald Trump entered the White House, his spokesman said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key members of Trumps circle under scrutiny for Russia ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FA Cup Semi-final draw: Arsenal v Manchester City, Chelsea v Spurs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outrage after Brazil football team signs goalkeeper convicted of killing girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas senator stands by comparison of Planned Parenthood to Nazis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victor Moses messing with Ashley Young as he pleases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A couple who posed as Paris attacks victims to win compensation are facing trial again over a similar claim about the Nice attack last summer. The pair were imprisoned in December after claiming 60,000 (50,000; $64,000) from a victims fund for the November 2015 Paris attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone operators outnumber any other type of Air Force pilot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer, Trump press secretary, confronted in Apple store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Russian whistleblower could have been poisoned with soup but vital evidence about his last meal was "flushed away", an inquest has been told </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.K. lawmakers reject bid to guarantee rights of EU citizens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Polish government wants to extradite a 98-year-old man living in the U.S. that it believes is a former commander of an SS-led unit during World War II responsible for the death of civilians and destruction of Polish villages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at Stanford University have developed a stretchable plastic electrode that could one day be used to bolster the flexibility of implantable electrodes in humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
