<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9815</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the fall asleep and wake up to results crew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are only five sessions total for this class and I already missed one because of the flu. 

Also I am the worst co-parent at night. I sleep like the dead, and am useless. (He's a mostly good sleeper though)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Half day at work. So neat. 
* Kid's first birthday, but I'm missing half because I have a class. 
* Playing the Mariners is going to be stressful all season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I have steered away from Nike running shoes so far! I see so many people casually wearing the Fly Knits that I had no idea they are also running shoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he also signed that Adidas contract which runs up until his first year of free agency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just going off the post about the Royals and low batting average. Is it them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man is it the Astros? Alternately I would also guess the Mariners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if we get the typical Luhnow off day move? Hoyt, Reed, and White all might be considered for a call up but who would you send down?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I feel like this is more about how great Jose Fernandez was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balanced effort in Las Vegas snaps Grizz two-game skid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. dollar drops sharply after President Trump calls it 'too strong' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an embarrassing loss for George Mason (and almost Duke!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All hail new batting coach Carlos Beltran!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros' Josh Reddick says Beltran helped swing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey it's the bee propaganda guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back where we started before that Motter HR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a high strikeout team a couple years ago to a high GIDP team now. Times have changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this isn't the MLB slowly raising the strike zone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to AstrosUmp the first was 12% called the same and the second was 26%. So maybe a little less than borderline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all very persuasive but I think I need to see Julia scarfing down grasshoppers some more before deciding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly ill be most upset if we can't get hits against Gallardo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayy I hope Altuve is getting his mojo back  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garmin unveils $139 Vivosmart 3 with rep counting, guided breathing features </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on this. My wife was a single issue pro-life voter but started to realize how narrow minded that was. And thankfully the GOP is kind of doing a good job of pushing away the college educated set. She still mostly considers herself pro-life but thinks there should be more of an emphasis on post-natal services and support. 

Her family on the other hand won't entertain arguments so long as abortion remains murder and without addressing that murder nothing else matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There probably isn't anything that they can do but I think one of Hillary's missteps in the election was assuming that people wouldn't buy the emotional (and false) argument of late stage abortions. I know she didn't want babies to be ripped from wombs, but that's a great zinger, and her answer was insufficient because people think that late stage abortion happens all the time and that democrats think it's totally cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same-Sex Marriage In North Carolina: Supreme Court LGBT Ruling Challenged With Republican Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There Is No Stopping Daniel Murphy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CC Hooks] Naturals' 12-Run Strike Sinks Hooks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fresno Grizzlies] Lost Vegas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should hire Jason Castro. I hear he's an elite pitch framer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros manager A.J. Hinch on reported Stanford interest: "a non-story" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just straight up fearmongering 

Robbers and other criminals may be less likely to commit offenses if they know they're going to get popped, they're going to federal court, they'll get five years and probably get sent off" to federal prison, Sessions told reporters. It does have an intimidating effect.

and this hyperbole

States can pass whatever laws they chose, Sessions told the attorneys general. But Im not sure were going to be a better, healthier nation if we have marijuana being sold at every corner grocery store.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a Mexican place in NYC that sprinkles them on guac. It's on my list to try. I've heard they're pretty innocuous, nothing strong enough to warrant [Julia's](http://mediadownloads.mlb.com/mlbam/mp4/2017/04/12/1275665983/1491973399242/asset_2500K.mp4) reaction here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. attorney general promises crackdown on potential surge in violent crime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa. how do you dislike Springer? He has such a goofy personality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Springer for MVP. (This one is an appropriate reaction though)

Ken Giles is the worst closer ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/Astros has descended into grasshopper madness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for your resignation speech  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's all we have though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Springer doesn't have social media but I feel like he must read r/Astros. Really responds to our cries for offense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Springer Dinger! No time to even call it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As good as the A's you mean!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd pair the Mets and Astros just to subject the Mets to Dave Hudgens again. So we can all complain together. (Plus similar color schemes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If "That's Cub" is a real thing that people try to say that definitely makes the Cubs more evil than the Mets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] after many years of a friendship that has generally been typical, you discover that your best friend is actually a projection of your imagination. Strangely, you are seemingly not as concerned about it as they are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/64s17z/wp_after_many_years_of_a_friendship_that_has/dg4rq99/

I cease to exist. Intermittently. When Imle leaves the room, I am no longer in existence. They're quite like gaps in my memory, little fractures that interrupt whatever we are doing.

Imle went to the bathroom. I poofed out of existence. And then he was instantaneously back, because I don't register time. A wonderful thing as the anxieties that I assume were implanted into my brain now seem so inconsequential.

Imle says he didn't know that I was a figment of his imagination. He seems unconcerned that we both have a memory lapse between my initial non-existence to my current.

"I was probably lonely," he says to me, before dipping out of the bedroom.

Now that Imle understands the scope of our relationship he's been avoiding me. I can of course come out of my own volition if Imle's guard is down, but I can't simply follow him around. 
There are rules that I don't fully understand, or even understand who made the rules.

The worst part is my implanted hobby is reading. How am I supposed to read books if I have no corporeal form? If I am merely the whimsical manifestation of some dropout college student.

I appear in a club. Imle has other friends, all the more reason my existence is baffling to the both of us. He nods his head at me and then moves from the small circular table to the dancefloor. I don't poof out of existence even though he becomes obscured by ecstatic bodies brushing against him. I reach out for his leftover drink and for a second my brain tingles, a short electrical sensation that sends little tingles up and down my arm, and then I'm holding onto the cold perspiring glass.

I lift it to my mouth and then drink the dregs. It's refreshing, and I'm lightheaded, but I know these are all just manifestations to seal the deal. I dash the glass onto the ground and a loud shatter startles me. I turn back to the table and Imle's glass is back where I left it.

Imle is dancing on the dancefloor, enjoying himself, and disregarding me. I clinch my fist and reach for his glass again. How many of us were there? I remembered interacting with others? I had real memories, not just the minutiae left behind by Imle to sell my existence to the both of us. Where were they?

And how could we take down Imle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cease to exist. Intermittently. When Imle leaves the room, I am no longer in existence. They're quite like gaps in my memory, little fractures that interrupt whatever we are doing.  

Imle went to the bathroom. I poofed out of existence. And then he was instantaneously back, because I don't register time. A wonderful thing as the anxieties that I assume were implanted into my brain now seem so inconsequential.  

Imle says he didn't know that I was a figment of his imagination. He seems unconcerned that we both have a memory lapse between my initial non-existence to my current.  

"I was probably lonely," he says to me, before dipping out of the bedroom.  

Now that Imle understands the scope of our relationship he's been avoiding me. I can of course come out of my own volition if Imle's guard is down, but I can't simply follow him around. There are rules that I don't fully understand, or even understand who made the rules.  

The worst part is my implanted hobby is reading. How am I supposed to read books if I have no corporeal form? If I am merely the whimsical manifestation of some dropout college student.  

I appear in a club. Imle has other friends, all the more reason my existence is baffling to the both of us. He nods his head at me and then moves from the small circular table to the dancefloor. I don't poof out of existence even though he becomes obscured by ecstatic bodies brushing against him. I reach out for his leftover drink and for a second my brain tingles, a short electrical sensation that sends little tingles up and down my arm, and then I'm holding onto the cold perspiring glass.  
I lift it to my mouth and then drink the dregs. It's refreshing, and I'm lightheaded, but I know these are all just manifestations to seal the deal. I dash the glass onto the ground and a loud shatter startles me. I turn back to the table and Imle's glass is back where I left it.  

Imle is dancing on the dancefloor, enjoying himself, and disregarding me. I clinch my fist and reach for his glass again. How many of us were there? I remembered interacting with others? I had real memories, not just the minutiae left behind by Imle to sell my existence to the both of us. Where were they?  

And how could we take down Imle?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Decent?](http://www.milb.com/player/index.jsp?sid=milb player_id=607223#/career/R/hitting/2017/ALL)

.276/.476/.600 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Springer: More Valuable Than Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Astros Might Need a First Baseman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that glue on chrome is... interesting? It looks weird on the Derby hats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly kidding because it's so low. Keuchel always makes me nervous though. I still don't have that much confidence that he can shut down other teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Case For Kawhi Leonard, MVP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I do not want to acknowledge Keuchel's BABIP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to do my taxes this week, so I might be up tonight working on them and catching this game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CC Hooks] Hooks Edge Nats for Series W </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Francis Martes pitched a solid five innings in his Grizzlies debut, allowing no runs on five hits, walking three with three strikeouts on 83 pitches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reno rally snaps Grizz three-game win streak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look Mariners I need you to commit to being bad if that's what you're going to do, at least until you face the Rangers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife has some with galaxy space stuff on it and I get some speckled dark green shit only along my calves. She doesn't even run! Just uses it for gym stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AstrosBot messed up and labeled a win a true. So it became a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've finished with all of the Empire, Robots, and Foundation books. Have you read any outside of the series books? Anything you would recommend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa this is supposed to be funny? I missed that. I picked her up after seeing her speak with Emily St. John Mandel at a night dedicated to post-apocalypta  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the In-Between Life of Vikram Lall for a college course and absolutely loved it. Your description of Nostalgia is fascinating and I didn't know/was too lazy to look it up that he had written more. Will check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sympathizer was pretty great. What books would you have preferred win this year and last?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CC Hooks] Five-Run Eighth Finishes Naturals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Tony D" secures 1,000th-career PCL win as Fresno tops Reno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evicted was so good. It firmly pushed me into the "housing is a right" camp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Case For James Harden, MVP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After one week of baseball looks like Marwin is the fWar team leader http://www.fangraphs.com/teams/astros 

Altuve should maybe ask him for advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the hype train slowed down a bit to fill out the necessary paperwork  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep forgetting to praise the company but my dog chewed on my Scosche Rhythm+ Heart Rate Monitor in such a way that the device stopped reading accurately. Contacted the company and they sent one out to me with like zero questions asked. Didn't have to send back the broken device. All I had to do was upload my original receipt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If Martes, Franklin Perez (whos probably heavier than his listed weight), and Forrest Whitley end up in a rotation with Joe Musgrove, Houston will have half a ton of pitching in just 80% of their rotation.

Can't wait to have heaviest rotation in the MLB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Comedy of Errors: The First Congressional Baseball Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does anyone have dirt on Hudgens? Maybe we can uh persuade him to quit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude Fiers the 5th starter went 6 IP and only gave up 2 Runs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weren't Harris and Peacock warming? Why keep Gustave in after that first run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? I thought Gattis was better defensively this year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This KC pitcher is already heavy breathing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twins put up like all their runs against KC in the 7th inning right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In windmill we trust  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I misremembered it slightly http://www.fangraphs.com/blogs/a-very-stupid-jose-altuve-hypothetical/ its about declining his option  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I keep thinking about is that fangraphs article about how bad Altuve would have to be before he lost value to the Astros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had a lefty heavy lineup last year so it made sense. This year I don't know. I'm just assuming we always have slow aprils  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I just remember my discomfort  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it definitely is. Retired broadcaster Brownie would make some thinly veiled sexual comments about it last year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time Julia eating on screen this season right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But really does Hudgens just collect his paycheck or does he see this continuing struggle aa a problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4/7 New album from Residente (of Calle 13) - Self titled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As briefly told by Lin-Manuel in the introduction, Residente did a DNA test and decided to travel to each country represented and write an album. It feels like a Calle 13 album. Early favorite song is:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6_PriJPSr-Q

Especially like the line 'Aqua no hay caviar, pero hay maize' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't like things that stain my fingers. But ill take your word for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Cheetos popcorn terrible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like one dude. Gurriel has been solid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we will more so see social media continue to operate the way that Obama utilized it ie indirectly and with an emphasis on photography. If you contrast what Trump accomplishes with twitter, rile up the base at the expense of the larger audience, and contrast it with Obama sneaking up on a kid who fell asleep waiting to meet him, they both set tones that are completely useless to their policy making. Social media doesn't have significant enough of an impact to overcome bias, it usually only reinforces it. 

Honestly I think most people who aspire to be president do so with some intention of maintaining their private person. At best social media use seems contrived and at worse it reveals to much and infantilizes our leaders. Where is the benefit to nation leading and policy making? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain to me what the benefit of knowing the raw and unscripted view of what our president is feeling? What policy positions or societal change have been benefited his usage of twitter? Mostly cause I don't get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Boasts of Historically Successful 13 Weeks of Presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember to put yourself in a plastic tote first!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hard is it really to fundraise for NY Marathon? I work for a non-profit that still has some spots and is willing to pay half of the $3000, but I'm worried I don't have the energy to raise $1500, and I don't want to pay that myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish Asimov was remembered more for his robot characters rather than the 3 laws of robotics. R. Daneel Olivaw is hands down my favorite literary protagonist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope you're right. I just did quick math. It was off the 4 walks last night. I'll fix it when I figure out what it should be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LAA because Trout. Anything can happen with Trout and a healthy Angels starting rotation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this keeps up the Astros-Yankees game is going to be a get to the starter or nobody scores type of series 

* 12.0 IP, 4 H, 1 R, 1 ER, 8 BB, 18K, 0.75 ERA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derek Jeter, Jeb Bush among reported potential bidders for Miami Marlins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My abuela is probably the same height as Altuve tbh. It looks like they picked stars of the team? I would've gone with Springer. more under the radar than Correa or Altuve plus he's on the SI cover.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Complaint** I'm doing a continuing ed certification for ESL instruction with mostly older/retired persons. I run from my work downtown to my class midtown, and without fail one of my classmates makes a snarky comment about my clothing. Yesterday it was my highlighter bright shorts. 

**Complaint** I haven't run in a week because of flu things and now my left knee and left foot are achey and giving me problems. 

**Confession** I have been running from my work to class but stopping in cool shops in between, but just pausing my watch as  I browse. (Usually like 1-2 shops per run) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musgrooving to a sweep tonight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the curse will be lifted when Bagwell gets inducted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey man somebody has to do your job  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa this bot is like a Reddit baby. Only 24 days old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Devo deserves a second shot at ROY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Marwin knows how to bunt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You uh want Gomez back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Beltran needs to re dye his beard blonde  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you go 4-13 (or whatever) against your division rival I think it'll be a fine comparison  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa are you teaching them against their will? Shame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least her husband is in Mexico so that'll be easy to coordinate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dope socks https://instagram.com/p/BShWRhCAcM-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Per u/SirScooby Jake was 3-6 with 2 doubles against Paxton last year. So its a good time for him to start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve is my favorite Astro. But hands down Correa is the only answer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colby Lewis is still a free agent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the Twins also beat the WBC Champion United States team. SO really who didn't see this coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard mixed reaction to whether or not Trump is a war hawk/dove, but wars are often great solutions to terrible presidencies. So I think the question becomes a) can Trump sale war in a region he previously criticized others for interfering with and b) with sentiment for Syrian refugees so low, why would going to war in their country be popular?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it was the Astros, but I'd like to hop on the wagon of saying it was against the Indians too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
