<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9272</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PIC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we should spend our life caring about politics when there are so many other things you could care about? Sorry I don't waste my life complaining about shit I can't fix like you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure if consent was involved with you though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A really good pillow, you don't realize how great they are until you sleep on one then you can never go back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bunch of drug dealers I avoided any "other stuff..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed

 I don't smoke weed but it is definitely something that is not as dangerous as we make it out to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit he has arrived  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling it will be very useful in this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they had 3 lives it would be 28-3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steelers are the true evil ones. They made the calendar with them last only to back stab the pats then go and win. Those bloody bastards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My proudest hours were when I got 5 USB's in the correct way in a row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First ... FALCONS WON'T PICK A CORNER IN THE FIRST 3 ROUNDS ... we just resigned Trufant 

ALSO we aren't picking a TE first 3   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/conspiracy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook will be dead by 2035 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samuel L. Jackson Mothafucka

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hmmm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its like the show 'Zoo' but extremely sexual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animals all begin running around in scantily clad clothing with rainbow tattoos on their cheek taping only men then running away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soul juice and spirit hacking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just possess a phone and just text people you know and creep them out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just imagining someone getting hoodies strings stuck in a big gear and being dragged around unable to breath while getting their limbs crushed before the hoodies tightens so much that their head gets cut off.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most brutal death you can imagine that hasn't already been in a movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A movie theater INSIDE OF a mall with an arcade and a phone store </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of DCTH? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To avoid getting recognized?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great acting (almost real), not enough dialogue though, I really didn't want to watch a minor (or adult) masterbate, pretty much the whole thing is extremely awkward. Also I don't like being trapped in a room for a 50-90 year movie, I hope you know I will be dead by the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went 12 years then I hit a little thing known as puberty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Car crash, super hero, spiders, woke, desert, tsunami, motorcycle, cave, worm, woke irl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I don't care I just had a copy of that written down on google docs so I could eventually use it one day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I was 13 when I had this) 

I was riding in a car through a cave in the beginning and I was talking to one of my middle school friends when a huge car accident occurred in front of us. I got out of the car and started to go try and help people. For some reason I have superpowers and I am able to save people really fast including a woman stuck under a truck. All of the sudden a bunch of giant spiders began crawling across the ceiling and me and some other people start fighting them off.

Then out of nowhere I wake up on my couch (still in the dream and I still had the powers). I walk to the door and a kid I used to know named Isaac was there. Apparently it was Halloween because he and for some reason I am wearing a costume. He tells me, "He lets ride down to Paul's (my best friend) house." I agree and we ride down there but for some reason it is nighttime and Paul is in the car. We arrived at his house about a minute after we left.

I walk inside and I am immediately teleported into another car driving through the middle of a desert somewhere, I assume Arizona. His parents explain that there is a giant monster somewhere and we needed to find it. I am in the car with Paul, his brother, his dad, mom, and a dog I had never seen in my life. We come up on a bridge and we stop the car. They tell me and for some reason the dog to get out in front of bridge. We get out and the rest head over the bridge. 

My view cuts over to what Paul is seeing and for some reason he and his brother are on motorcycles. Riding up the mountain on the other side of the bridge. All of the sudden they look over and there is a huge tsunami heading straight towards them. The road going up the mountain spirals around it so it will take a while to get up it. The tsunami is approaching on the second spiral and they are still a few meters from the top. All of the sudden it hits and his brother is unable to get out of the way and is sucked into the water. Paul dives in and is unable to find him and swimsuit back to his motorcycle.

It cuts back to me and I am exploring the desert with the dog. I the dog run off then a few minutes later I here it barking. I walk over to it and there and there is a huge cave opening. We walk in and it is really dark so I pull out a flashlight I didn't know I had. I look around for a while then I see a light coming out of another tunnel. The rest of the people in the car where there and I pull up next to them and start talking. We pull up to the end of the cave and see a giant worm monster. 

Then.... I woke up unfortunately.  

Edit: I am willing to write 5 paragraphs on reddit but refuse to write one paragraph for a project I have due tomorrow in AP... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess she had bad blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time I woke up after one of my best dreams I ever had and sat in my bed for 10 minutes straight forcing myself to memorize every single detail of it. I am so glad I did it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs more upvotes, great writing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hey, my math teacher does that to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That meteor is getting awfully close..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy stocks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can which one you are... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kool-Aid man 

OH YEA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furrys are all so annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if it was after what I ate last then Susie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably finding a swan's G-spot, though I'm equally good with ferrets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atlanta Falcons: Derek Rivers, EDGE, Youngstown State

You have my upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your job is changed to your something related to your last Google search, What is your new job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I am so confused that was a huge coincidence lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who have seen someone die, what happened, how do you cope with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldnt get rid of it right away, accidently put it on there
lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
