<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3642</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason why I write is to someday make enough money so I can play Civ 24/7 and never leave the house again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was awesome, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfffffflllflfffffbbtttt. Plbt.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered why I had such clear skin for a few days after Thanksgiving, even after eating so much food that usually makes me break out :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuffing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuffing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was something unbelievable about the stuffing my grandmother made every Thanksgiving. It wasnt just good - it was beyond amazing. Every morsel of meat and bread and vegetable was flavored to perfection. The meticulousness and love involved in the preparation process shone through with every bite. Wed eat until we were stuffed (pun intended) and still felt great afterward. Hell, we even felt invigorated, which was the last thing one would expect after Thanksgiving dinner.


Our family had been trying to get her to tell us the recipe for years. She wouldnt even give us a hint.


Since our family has always had a love for dark humor, when were around the Thanksgiving table, we liked to speculate on how she did it. My sister thought she mixed in crack cocaine. My father said she sold her soul to Satan in 1955. Even Mom, who was the least indecorous of the group, quietly said, around a mouthful of stuffing, I bet its made from the bodies of better chefs.


We all laughed. Especially Grandma. Then we had a little moment of sad silence. Grandpa had been a chef. Hed passed away over the summer. Everyone missed him. 


Dad broke the silence with a truly spectacular belch, and we all groaned and giggled and got back to eating.


Even though Id resumed packing my mouth with mashed potatoes, I still felt bad for my grandmother. Shed taken Grandpas death very hard. Even with her network of friends, family, and coworkers at the place where she volunteers, her loneliness was obvious. Seeing her smiling with us on Thanksgiving warmed my heart. It felt good to hear her laugh again, and it was obvious she was happy that we loved her stuffing as much as we did.


The Friday after last Thanksgiving, Id finished my Black Friday shopping and was bringing my nieces presents over to Grandmas. It was tradition for us to go there on Christmas morning to open our gifts. I wanted to get an early start so I wouldnt have to deal with last-minute shopping. 


When I arrived, Grandma wasnt there. I figured she was doing her volunteering, since its always busy there around the holidays. I had a key, though, and I let myself in.


Her house was as neat and perfect as ever. I left the packages in the living room, and was about to leave through the kitchen when a truly sinister thought crossed my mind. I was finally going to get that stuffing recipe.


I opened her recipe book and there, between souffle and tandoori chicken, was stuffing. I read it over and my heart sank.


It was almost completely unremarkable. The recipe looked like any ingredient list from the back of a stuffing box. There was only one thing I didnt recognize right away:  cup STC. I scratched my head for a second, then realized it was an abbreviation for salt, turmeric, and cumin. After all those years of wondering, it all came down to Grandma just being a really, really good cook. I shouldve known.


Its been almost a year since then. The familys been gearing up for another Thanksgiving. The menu is planned, the tablescape is designed, and the guests have been invited.


Yesterday, out of the blue, I got a call from my mom. Her mother, a.k.a. my grandmother, had been arrested. I couldnt believe it and asked what had happened. Mom replied that shed been caught stealing from the place where she volunteers. They had security camera footage and everything.


To say I was confused was a massive understatement. First off, how could my grandmother, the kindest, sweetest person Ive ever met, be a thief? And second, what the hell is there to steal from where she volunteers?


Mom went to the police station to deal with the situation while I stayed at home and cleaned. I couldnt stop thinking about what had happened. As far as my first concern, I chalked it up to Grandma getting old. Maybe shed gotten confused and had taken something without even knowing it didnt belong to her. That had to have been it, and it made me sad to think about. 


Mom called me an hour or so later. Shed bailed Grandma out and was waiting for it all to get processed so she could take her to the hospital to get examined. I asked Mom what the hell was going on.


She told me it was pretty much exactly what wed thought. Grandma had taken something from her volunteer place and snuck it away. The security office even rolled tapes back and caught her doing the same thing for the last eight years, all right around Thanksgiving.


What the hell did she take?, I asked, so overwhelmed with confusion that I wanted to tear my hair out.


Well, thats why Im bringing her to the hospital, Mom replied. Not just because I think she might be losing it, but because it was just waste that the place incinerates anyway.


I felt a chill start at the back of my neck and plunge down my spine. Like...medical waste?, I asked in a hollow, detached voice.


Yeah. Biohazard stuff.


I thanked Mom for calling and said to let me know if there was anything I could do to help. We hung up.


I sat there in the quiet house and put seemingly-impossible pieces together. The stuffing. The feeling of invigoration. The recipe. Everything in the room blurred and my mouth felt very, very dry.


STC wasnt salt, turmeric, and cumin. Not even close to salt, turmeric, and cumin. 


STC was stem cells. 


Grandma was a volunteer at [Planned Parenthood](http://unsettlingstories.com).







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It came after. Writing that story made me hungry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Gnocchi with hot sausage and prosciutto in a pilsner and sage sauce. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciated the attempt. Here, I'll throw my own in there.

Who says, "pfffflpfpfpftt I NEED TO SAVE THE WORLD IN 24 HOURS pfffffflllflfffffbbtttt!"

Queefer Sutherland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Egyptian protests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 03:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was the goal. There's no way I could make something that ridiculous scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Venetian cats get double the routes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was such a great idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cough.](https://unsettlingstories.com/twentyyears/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a bunch of judges around, even though they only use three per show. They shoot three episodes a day - sometimes more during theme weeks. They're always playing around together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No bother at all! Good luck with your project - I love AI stuff :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest shying away from my story, then, and checking out the thought experiment which inspired it, called [Roko's Basilisk](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Roko's_basilisk). I think you'll be able to find more usable material from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to know about this project before I entertain the possibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unaired episode of The Food Network's "Chopped!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unaired episode of The Food Network's "Chopped!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im chef Geoffrey Zakarians personal espresso maker and latte-foam artist. Yes, thats a real job. With benefits, in fact. Great health and dental.


One of the perks of my occupation, aside from hanging out with GZ and getting to eat many of my weekly meals at his outstanding restaurant, The Lambs Club, is the access I enjoy at The Food Networks studios and associated properties. 


GZ is a pretty big deal over there, which Im sure you know if youve watched the network for more than a few hours. Aside from Chopped!, which is his best-known show, hes building a new audience with the Saturday morning feature, The Kitchen. His personality fits so well with whatever hes in, though, and its just great to be a part of it.


Im totally fanboying right now. Sorry. I hope that doesnt sound disrespectful in the face of what happened.


GZ was shooting a few episodes of Chopped! with Aarn Sanchez, Marc Murphy, Alex Guarnaschelli, and Amanda Freitag. Ted Allen had just gotten there a bit late but immediately started poking fun at Aarn for a new tattoo on his hand that looked a little like a dick. (It totally did.)


I was in the backstage prep kitchen setting up Geoffreys personal Elektra Belle Epoque espresso machine. Id shown him the preliminary designs for the three lattes Id be making over the course of the days film schedule. Out of the 28, he chose *Spring*, by Pierre-Auguste Cot, *Seated Woman with a Red Kerchief*, by Anna Elizabeth Klumpke, and my favorite, *La Vrit sortant du puits arme de son martinet pour chtier l'humanit*, by Jean-Lon Grme. Id save that one for last.


The first episode of the day went well. A Nigerian-born British chef led the way throughout, and it was no surprise that he won. After it was over and they were setting up for the next show, GZ brought me a piece of the truly-outstanding bread pudding dessert thatd clinched the win. Laphroaig scotch-soaked brioche sounds wrong, but in that chefs capable hands, it was transcendental.


The four chefs waiting in the wings for the next episode were called onstage. Ted gave the rules in his inimitable style, and GZ, Amanda, and Alex sat at the judging table, trying not to laugh. If only the TV viewers knew how hard it was to maintain the air of seriousness the show tries to project.


Anyway, the appetizer round went pretty well. It was obvious the lady from Westport was going to get chopped, since she left out two basket ingredients while trying to make some weird fritters out of mussels and kale. Sure enough, when Ted lifted the cloche, her appetizer was under it. She didnt even thank the judges for the opportunity to compete.


The entree round came next, after the crew cleaned the chefs stations. I was hard at work on *Spring*, but I kept glancing up at the monitors in the prep kitchen to see what was going on.


Right as Ted announced there were only five minutes left, I heard Ted and the judges gasp. Apparently one of the the chefs had cut himself. 


Now, anyone whos watched Chopped! knows that chefs cut themselves all the time. It adds an extra element of suspense to the show as they have to wait for the EMT to bandage the wound and secure a glove, then they have to work through the pain and make sure not to get any blood on the food.


This cut was really bad. The problem was, the chef wouldnt stop. Something was very, very wrong. GZs second latte was forgotten as I stared at the live feed from the studio monitors. All the other chefs stopped what they were doing as the EMT crew tried to attend to the chef. His name was Evan.


Evan was clearly disturbed. He shouted, homemade sausage wins the round 87.2% of the time! Round one was close but this one will be a cut above! He laughed hysterically and waved the knife at any approaching EMT. One of the producers came into the prep kitchen and dialed 911.


My eyes were glued to the monitor. GZ was calling to Evan and trying to talk some sense into him. He said he was a great chef and that hed been to his restaurant before and really loved the Homard en Crote. Evan didnt acknowledge, so Aarn tried. He said something about being really proud of the work hes done and it reminded him of himself when he was younger. No response, just frenzied cooking and prepping of the meat grinder.


Alex cried.


A pan Evan had been heating was smoking hot. To everyones dismay, he yelled reduce by 25%, then carved between his index and middle fingers all the way down to his wrist. Everyone except Evan screamed. Blood poured into the pan and steam erupted from the hot surface. The odor of boiling blood filled the studio. One of the prep chefs next to me puked into the sink.


Another EMT tried to grab Evan while he was busy cutting, but Evan reacted quickly and slashed the mans shoulder. Not deep, but enough to make sure the EMT didnt try anything again.


Oh no, I heard Aarn moan. Alex shrieked. The blood steam had fogged the monitors camera, so I couldnt see anything. I stepped out from backstage and saw why they were so distraught. Evans hand was gradually disappearing into the meat grinder. 


GZ and I locked eyes and he just shook his head. I nodded. I felt bad for the guy. Horrified, but still sympathetic. 


More and more of the mans hand disappeared into the grinder. This wouldve never worked with the terrible meat grinders they had throughout the majority of the shows history. Those things wouldnt grind a sheet of paper. These were new, though, and they were powerful. As we watched, Evans arm disappeared up to the elbow as bloody confetti poured out and filled the bowl on the table.


The fire alarm sounded. Apparently some panicking intern had pulled it thinking itd get the authorities there faster. 


Form into patties and braise in blood sauce with thyme, carrots, diced shallots, and fennel pollen, Evan called out over the din of the alarm. Add chocolate and poblanos to create a pseudo-mole sauce to ingratiate Sanchez and Freitag if they are judging. Add butter for Guarnaschelli. Add veal demi-glace for Zakarian.


Evans arm had disappeared up to his shoulder. He wrenched the stump out. Pulped flesh dangled while blood spurted. His complexion was beige.


Follow the braising with a quick sear. Plate with potatoes if Murphy is judging. Marc was busy throwing up into a trashcan. 


The studio door burst open and four police officers entered the studio. Evan had dropped the knife and was busy making patties out of the meat thatd once been his hand and arm. Bone fragments may be overlooked if the flavor profile is strong enough, he yelled, and began to drop the patties into the pan of reduced blood. He then added the aromatics hed cut up before going nuts.


A scent filled the air. I was overwhelmed by the most disturbing sensation Id ever experienced; the smell was intoxicating and luscious. Everyone stopped shouting and crying and puking as their nostrils filled with the rich odor. A cop shot Evan with a taser, and Evan collapsed on the bloody floor. He convulsed for a moment, then stopped. The EMTs ran to him.


One of the producers turned off the burners and ordered all nonessential personnel to leave immediately. I looked at GZ and he pointed at his watch. I was six minutes late with his latte. Of course hed be thinking about his latte at a time like this.


I went in back and began the laborious process again. *Spring* was a no-go. I wasnt about to try to do it over, so I prepared *La Vrit sortant du puits arme de son martinet pour chtier l'humanit*. I hoped it would put GZ in a happier mood, if that was at all possible.


The $20,000 espresso machine hummed and I deftly painted the milk foam and espresso into the objet d'art we both loved. I listened as the EMTs took Evan out and the police questioned the chefs. It didnt take long. They left right when I was about to finish. 


I came out onto the set with the latte and stopped dead in my tracks. My hands trembled and part of me knew my artwork was being destroyed, but that was the least of my concerns at that moment.


Geoffrey, Aarn, Marc, Ted, Alex, and Amanda stood around Evans station. They huddled in front of the pan, each holding a fork. Each of them was cutting off small portions of the terrible sausage Evan had made and eating it. Overcome with nausea, I dropped the latte. Everyone looked at me.


Jesus Christ man, GZ complained. Was that the Grme one?


I nodded.


His expression softened. Sorry, I didnt ask if you were okay. You good?


I nodded again as he took another morsel of the sausage.


Look, I know this looks strange and we all admit well probably feel pretty bad about it tomorrow, but when else are we going to have a chance like this?


Aarn chimed in, Cmon buddy, give it a try.


The other judges joined Aarn and GZ and encouraged me over. It still smelled spectacular. GZ cut me a tiny piece and I put it in my mouth. It was the best thing Id ever tasted.


Hey, is that camera still on,? Alex asked around a mouthful of carrot and sausage.


Hmm, yeah, said Amanda, staring at the green light.


Guess its one for the blooper reel, GZ laughed. For Chopped! After Hours.


They all laughed and I backed away, not sure how to feel.


Hey, GZ interrupted, anyone want a latte?


Ted belched. Fuck yeah.


I went backstage and started to make their lattes. As I was turning the corner, Alex quipped, yeah, that guy totally wouldve won the round. If he lives, maybe we should send him a card. 

They all thought that was a superb [idea](http://unsettlingstories.com).









 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to avoid the comments because I get sad and discouraged by the abuse, but I'm often too curious to stay away. I think there's one comment that inspired/changed part of my Runners series, but I can't remember what it was. 

This wasn't a very helpful reply. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Double Dare one was pretty fucking weird. I'm thinking about doing another one in that vein. 

Edit: [Couldn't help myself](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5e53xx/an_unaired_episode_of_the_food_networks_chopped/?st=ivsc0jgl sh=86bec4cd). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but my stories are not to be published without first discussing licensing terms and payment for the work that will be used.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 03:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a fan, but not an official mouthpiece of the sub. When I asked her to credit my work the way I preferred, she was polite and quick to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good :) Let me know what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's literally the scariest movie I've ever seen in my life. I saw it when I was 12, and it had such a profound effect on me that *to this day*, 23 years later, the sight of fingerprints on a rain-streaked window makes me shudder. I cannot see a red light in the sky without a brief, but undeniable feeling like something is coming for me. 

I don't even know if it's that great a movie, to be honest. I've seen it maybe twice. But its effect has been indelible. I definitely recommend you give it a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It [came out](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5dnaet/my_last_abduction/?st=ivo02h41 sh=07c31237) a little better than I'd expected. I'm still not sure about the ending, so if I think of a better one in the future, it might get swapped out for something else. The rest of it is pretty strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Last Abduction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Last Abduction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They come for me in broad daylight.


Over the last few years, they had removed nine toes, 12 teeth, one finger, and three feet of my large intestine. There are no scars. They leave no other evidence. They take what they want and leave me with less and less each time. Every visit diminishes me.


People cant see them. Dogs can, though. Cats, too. Maybe birds. Theyll howl or hiss or fly away, but that wont deter the visit. From what Ive learned, nothing will.


My right thumb was taken four days ago. I was walking to the supermarket when I felt the telltale prickles of static electricity cascading down the back of my head and neck. Pigeons in the area began to screech. The sense of weightlessness Id grown to know and dread swept over me, and as I was lifted into the clear sky, I saw my replacement continue his walk. He always continues exactly where Id left off.


The people walking behind me didnt notice a thing.


I know the long pull skyward is an illusion; perhaps even one for my benefit. That they can instantaneously place my replacement is proof of some kind of teleportation capability, but perhaps the sensation of travel is their way of easing my mind. If so, its a strange way of doing it. Moments later, Ill feel the agony of every incision and every amputation as their machines work. Despite their best efforts, I am not, and never again will be, at ease.


After my first abduction, I was deposited where my replacement had been. The physical transition was seamless, but the mental and emotional ones were not. For those sitting in the room with me, I went from laughing at a joke to shrieking and pulling off my shoes and socks to reveal my missing pinky toe. It was my abductors first souvenir. 


At the hospital, my checkup yielded no issues. None whatsoever, in fact. I appeared to be in perfect physical health, save for the missing toe. I was unsurprised when they wouldnt believe what I claimed had happened to me. I was kept overnight for observation, then given a prescription for anti-anxiety medication and discharged. 


Ive been back to the hospital over a dozen times since. The doctors began to realize something was happening. They noticed the perfect, seamless amputations and extractions of parts of me that previous x-rays showed were quite present at the time of the scans. 


The medical professionals were at a complete loss.


As I mentioned, four days ago, my right thumb was taken. I didnt go to the hospital after I was deposited back into the kitchen of my home. 


Three days ago, I lost my left hand. I was deposited back into my shower. The stump below my wrist was clean, white, and smooth. I did not go to the hospital.


Two days ago, my penis and testicles were excised. The agony of their amputation was exquisite, hideous, and profound. The pain disappeared when I was returned. I immediately went to the hospital, where I remain. The head of the hospital made many, many calls. No more than a few hours later, I was visited at my bedside by people in black suits. They made me sign documents that Im invalidating as I type this.


Before dawn this morning, I was taken again. It was the first time I was abducted at night. It was also the first time I saw the faces of my abductors. 


To attempt to explain the sheer, incomprehensible horror of their appearance would only blunt the reality of their form. No words exist in any human language to describe the feeling that laying my eyes upon them had evoked. The word incomprehensible dwarfs the word horror, and Id never felt so frightened in my life. 


Not until mere hours ago.


When I was returned, I knew nothing had been taken. The machines that had stolen so much of me had not been used. Something new had been employed. Something worse. Something alive.


I was swapped with my replacement and found myself where Id been beforehand: my hospital bed. I began to scream with a force that caused blood vessels in my eyes to burst. Before anyone could arrive, I started to feel what had been done to me. 


They didnt question my demand that they scan me. They didnt even hesitate. And when it was over, no one spoke. No one even looked at me. Their eyes were glued to the screens. Two pairs of them began to leak tears down horrified faces. That was all the confirmation I needed.


Im typing this with the laptop Id been given to compose my last will and testament. But I have nothing to give and no one to give it to. This is more important. 


Please realize that during my most recent abduction, I saw many, many other people who had been taken. People of all ages and races from what appeared to be all over the world. And they were all undergoing the same procedure.


I dont know how much longer I have. By the looks on the faces of the hospital officials and doctors who saw the scans, I cant imagine its very long. Right now, if thousands of people around the world are experiencing what I am, things will get very bad, very soon. While I wasnt given the opportunity to see the scans, I have all the evidence I need. 


All six pairs of clawed legs are scratching at my abdomen from the inside. I can see my skin rising and falling as the pressure against it grows and whats inside gets stronger. No one, aside from doctors, hospital officials, and suited men, remains in the hospital. Everyone else has been evacuated. 


Believe my account or choose to ignore it. Its entirely your choice. I wont be around for whatever happens next, but you will. Right now, I feel more of me being taken as teeth inside me are beginning to chew. Its going to happen soon, and something tells me its going to all go very quickly from there. Spots of blood are seeping through the sheet covering my belly.


Please be [ready](http://unsettlingstories.com).











 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fuckin' starving. We have any vampire hands left over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For today's story, I'm forcing myself to write a passable abduction story. Keep your expectations low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, I shouldn't have given that away. Goodbye, 15 minutes of something-almost-resembling-the-most-miniscule-level-of-fame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've noticed that very same pronunciation a few times when  YouTube narrators have said my name. Must be a regional thing, like soda and pop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't played in years (and if I ever stop writing, you can know I took it up again), but I was a Frost DK and an Ice Mage for years. I loved the economic aspect of the game; I frequently cornered the enchanting mats market on the AH. People hated me. I raked in millions :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I'm particularly good at this, but I often fall back to ways someone would describe food. Hear me out.

I watch a lot of Food Network, so I'm used to hearing an enormous amount of descriptive terms used to describe meals or recipes. As odd as it sounds, I think that technique has sunk in. 

If I'm writing about, say, a rotting corpse, I'll be like, "hmm, how would Guy Fieri describe something gooey and bubbly and pungent?" (Please keep in mind I'm being dead serious right now.) I think doing it that way helps, because it applies some weird level of experiential knowledge to what you're trying to write, despite not necessarily having experience with, in this case, a rotting corpse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you're *so* gonna get disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pronounced "UnsettlingStories.com, tell your friends."

Jk, it's "*ee-uh*" :D

It was the automatically-generated name of my first WoW character: a Night Elf rogue. That was before I was ride-or-die Horde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all of those things! Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haaaaaay :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely feel the same way about proving that you can be better than the tropes. But there's also a part in me that wants to use a trope, do it better than anyone else, and make it my own. I don't think I've done it yet, but I want to. I will :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just [posted](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5dgphw/were_all_smiling/?st=ivmljwhg sh=6d6d2792) a story that features my most hated horror cliche as the main plot driver. And it felt good to bathe in those vile waters. :D

(My favorite trope is probably alien abduction. Scares the fuck out of me. I have yet to write a good story about it.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're All Smiling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're All Smiling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The overly-wide, grinning mouth is a horror cliche. Its a trope, albeit a successful one, thats wormed its way into scary stories from around the world. So ubiquitous is its inclusion that its taken on a legendary status; it feels like something thats always been around to scare people. Right?


In 1844, one of the first serial killers in Connecticut began a rampage. Little was known about the killer, save for their signature technique of disfiguration. While the victims were alive, they amputated their cheeks. When the bodies were eventually found, their toothy, skeletal smiles became fodder for nightmares, rumors, and legends. The killer was never captured.


Starting in 2012, local Connecticut message boards and forums started to feature messages and questions about ghosts.


Theres a town in Connecticut called Monroe. It is infested with hauntings. Two cemeteries, Union and Stepney, are sites where ghosts can be found wandering between headstones and sometimes out into the road. In November, 2012, there was an enormous uptick in the number of sightings, which precipitated the message board posts.


Those who saw the ghosts began having nightmares. 


Those who read about the ghosts began having nightmares.


The nightmares themselves were unique, save for one, shared feature: they ended with the dreamer thinking they woke up, then seeing a white, ghostly woman with devastating facial disfigurements crouching on their chests. Shell stare at them and trace her fingertips across their faces as she grins with her hideous, wide smile.


Its not unusual for cultural events to shape the content of dreams. Following the release of the movie The Exorcist, it was widely reported that people were having dreams about demonic possession. These reports of the ghostly woman are likely tied to the prevalence of the scary stories I mentioned above, along with the sightings of so-called ghosts.


I believed that for a little while.


Then I started having the dreams. My kids and wife did, too. Each night, Id watch, paralyzed, as the woman sat on my chest and touched my face. Id wake from the nightmare sweating and experiencing pain in my cheeks and chin. Soon after, the kids would start to scream.


Online searches for the identity of the 19th century serial killer have gone through the roof over the years, according to Googles list of trends. Other trends have started to show up, too.


Facial pain.


Difficulty swallowing.


Temporomandibular Joint Disorder symptoms.


Facial eczema.


Maybe its just my own paranoia, which, I admit, is growing by the day, but I can swear people around here are smiling more often. Theyre joyless smiles, but smiles nonetheless. My wife, whose stern, no-nonsense expression is legendary at the school where she teaches, now has smile lines creasing the corners of her mouth. And theyre turning redder as the days, weeks, and months go by.


My kids have always been relatively cheerful; even when theyre bored or tired, you can still see a spark of positivity in their eyes. That spark is gone. But their smiles are as wide as ever. Wider, maybe.


The local Connecticut message boards are buzzing about a find someone made regarding the serial killer from 1844. Apparently there was a chest from a Monroe church that had been given to the historical society in the 1980s. It was never opened and remained in the historical society basement for 30 years. The other day, on a whim, someone opened it.


Contained within were the musings of an old nun. Musings on positivity. On happiness. On smiles. And there were drawings of people with impossibly-wide grins. 


A knife was found, wrapped in cloth, tucked into the corner of the chest. Underneath it was a small bag filled with bloody fingernail clippings.


This morning, before dawn, I had the dream again. She was on me. For the first time, I noticed the heavy cross around her neck. She caressed my face like shed always done, but this time her fingernails began to scrape and scratch against my skin. It tickled, then it hurt. It hurt very badly. I tried to struggle, but I couldnt wake up. I couldnt get her off. The sound of a bloodcurdling scream exploded through my dream, and I woke up. The woman disappeared.


I looked at my wife in bed next to me. She was screaming as she slept. I watched as the corners of her mouth split, and with a sickening crunch, I heard her jaw dislocate. Blood poured down on the sheets as I grabbed her and tried to pull her out of bed and back into the waking world.


Down the hall, I heard my kids shriek with pain.


A half hour later, we arrived at the hospital. It was full of people bleeding from wounds on their cheeks. Some were worse than others. The place is overwhelmed, and I dont know what to do. Even as we bleed, were all [smiling](http://unsettlingstories.com).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change default starting conditions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually like playing on a huge map with island plates and no barbarians because I'm soft and weak. Is there a way to set that to default so I don't have to create a custom game all the time? Maybe I'm missing an option or something, but Civ 5 remembered your settings from the previous game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, send a DMCA takedown request. You're well within your right and it will certainly light a fire under their ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God I don't know anything about video editing because I'd make him say the word "cum" exactly 69 times.

Because I'm a 35 year-old child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for reading :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still kinda want one tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes you wonder what's going on with the police and medical examiners, doesn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide Woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide Woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyones heard of the so-called Suicide Forest in Japan, but hardly anyones familiar with the locally-named Suicide Woods in Fairfield, CT. Its probably a good thing, too; the deaths are disturbing not only by their nature, but because there have been so many of them over the years. 


Growing up, I heard scary stories about the woods behind Lake Mohegan. We all did. Rumors of devil-worshipping cults ran like wildfire through every school hallway and cafeteria. Some kid said he was fishing back there with his uncle when they discovered a dead goat by a rock face with its guts arranged in a pentagram. Another kid talked about bloodsucking demons in the trees. Our parents were always quick to dispel the more ridiculous rumors, but they couldnt deny the suicides. The suicides were facts of life in our town.


I wouldnt be writing this if I thought it was an unfortunate, but natural, phenomenon - like with the forest suicides in Japan. To be honest, Id forgotten about it all until I came back for my 30th high school reunion last spring. A few old classmates and I got to talking, and we decided to take a hike through the wooded area the following day.


Keep in mind, the place is absolutely gorgeous. Its heavily wooded, but well-maintained paths run throughout. A clear, clean river cuts through the woods, and a series of cascades and rapids terminate in a deep, tranquil pool. Kids and families would swim there frequently during the summer, despite the unpleasant stigma of suicides and hauntings hanging over the area. On a beautiful, hot summer day, its simply too pretty over there to worry about that stuff.


We headed out around 7:30 the following morning. Only one of our original six ended up actually answering the phone and still wanted to go, but that was fine with me. Todd Soto and I were pretty close in high school, so I was looking forward to spending the morning with him so we could catch up.


We walked along the scenic path around the lake and into the woods. We followed the river, and soon we reached the cascades. The rushing water was gorgeous and invigorating. Someone whod gotten up even earlier than we had was fishing off the rocks. He waved, and we greeted him in turn.


The woods quieted as we progressed further upriver. The sound of wildlife replaced the rushing water. It was a truly spectacular day. Todd told me about his business and his family while I discussed my writing career and waning popularity. All in all, we were having a great time.


Todd stopped to grab some water from his backpack, and I gazed out over the now-distant lake. I heard my friend behind me rummaging through his stuff, then he muttered, what the hell? I turned around.


A hair-thin stream of black fluid had fallen out of the tree onto Todd. Hed moved to the side, but it was on his head and neck. We both looked up, but couldnt see what had produced the stream. Well thats gross, Todd remarked, and he reached into his backpack for a handkerchief. 


I kept looking in the tree while Todd wiped himself off. He went to put the handkerchief back, then pulled his Swiss Army knife from his pocket. It was one of the really big ones that Id wanted to get for a while. I was jealous.


Hey, cool kni--, I began, but then something happened. It was very bad, and very fast.


Todd opened the knife, and with no hesitation, plunged it into the side of his neck. A brilliant fountain of blood erupted from the puncture. His mouth formed a hideous smile of calm beneficence. His knees wobbled a bit, but he didnt fall. 


I shouted his name and rushed forward, but he pushed me away. Hard. I crashed onto the dirt and scrambled to my feet. Todd was now standing directly underneath the tree thatd dripped on him. He pulled the knife across the softest parts of his neck, while gurgling, What was mine is now yours. I repay your kiss with my blood. Take it all. Swallow me.


Once more, I tried to stop him, but got pushed away again. But not by Todd. Something had descended from the tree and was dangling in front of my friend. It was long and black and streaked with gray veins and white blotches. It was no wider than a cigarette lighter, but when it struck me, its strength was enormous. I knew at least one of my ribs had cracked, and I remained on the ground, clutching my chest.


The thing spasmed and twitched before touching down on Todds gouting throat. A lime-green proboscis slid from its tip and began lapping up the blood. Todd had fallen to his knees, but he was still carving his neck ever wider. His grinning mouth moved in the same shapes of the words hed been gurgling, but nothing but blood came out. Soon that also stopped, as he severed his esophagus. Then he fell on his face.


The thing in the tree extended and pushed down into Todds wound. For minutes, I stared, too horrified to move, as it gulped my friends blood. Its veins pulsed and it swelled obscenely before turning translucent, then transparent, then invisible. I heard the leaves rustling as it retracted back, and all that was left was me and my dead friend. 


I pulled myself to my feet and ran, wincing with agony as the broken ends of my ribs rubbed against one another. I reached for my phone, but realized Id given it to Todd to hold in his backpack. I kept running until I reached the road. I flagged down a car and had them call the police.


They arrived and brought me to the station. I was questioned and I told them everything, despite knowing how insane it sounded. They asked for my phone number and home address so they could contact me if they needed anything else. Days went by. They didnt call. They didnt visit. After a week, I went online to the Connecticut Post website. I did a search for Todds name. Lo and behold, there he was, listed as another unfortunate and preventable suicide in the Lake Mohegan [woods](http://unsettlingstories.com).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love hearing that! Feel free to check my [site](http://unsettlingstories.com) for more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Devastating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think, but here's the thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was desperate after the failure of the first experiment. Losing a bit of dignity is better than failing a course, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Cmd :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maria's Extra-Credit Assignment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maria's Extra-Credit Assignment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in college, I dated a biologist named Maria. Well, a biology undergraduate. She was a lot of fun, albeit slightly odd. Being a bit odd myself, we hit it off right away. Our first date lasted almost 12 hours - the entirety of which was spent talking as we sipped terrible coffee in a 24-hour diner.


Maria told me she wanted to focus on malacology after undergrad, then started to regale me with passionate stories about the local banana slug. 


I was familiar with the banana slug. Everyone on campus was. They have an unfortunate habit of falling out of trees and landing on the heads of unsuspecting students and faculty. Being around 8 long and remarkably disgusting, having one plop on ones head is pretty close to a living nightmare. My first month on campus, one missed me by inches and splattered on the concrete. I was picking slug out from between my shoelaces for a week.


So, once Maria told me about her slug fascination, I became a little wary. It was a shame, because I liked her quite a bit. She could sense something was awry, so I admitted to being terrified of the things. All bugs, really. Instead of mocking me, which Id grown to expect after years of asking women to kill spiders and centipedes for me, she held my hand. It was the first real physical contact we had together. Right then, I knew she was special.


We dated for a few weeks and our chemistry was phenomenal. It felt good to have such a steady, positive presence in my life.


As the school year progressed, though, it became obvious Maria was struggling with her work. It wasnt that she was slacking or not studying; quite the contrary - she was studying so much that Id only see her once or twice a week. But despite all the work, she was on pace to fail her biology course - the subject most important to her.


After a miserable few days when she was positive shed get thrown out of school for poor grades and never have the opportunity to be the scientist shed wanted to be since she was a little girl, her professor gave her a lifeline: an extra credit assignment. 


The project Maria was given was simple: shed incubate banana slug eggs in different environments to learn how microclimatic variations affect hatch rate and survival beyond one day. She received permission to use several spots on campus: the wellness center, the gym, the chemistry building, the biology building, and, yes, my dorm. So strong were my feelings for Maria that I allowed her to place a shoebox breeding-ground under my bed. 


Yes, I had nightmares about slugs crawling up my bed and laying eggs in my mouth. Who wouldnt?


Unfortunately for Maria, the project didnt go well. She either hadnt prepared the shoeboxes properly or had started with bad samples in the first place, because all but one site yielded dead eggs. The wellness center location produced a few live slugs, but they died within 12 hours. 


Maria was devastated. I did my best to console her, but there wasnt much I could say. We both knew she was going to fail the course. Shed talk to the professor in the morning and see if there was any chance of redoing it. Without much hope, we went to sleep.


Maria got up early and visited the professor in his office. I waited anxiously for her to come back, and about an hour after she left, she texted me with great news. He was letting her try again. He had sympathy for experiments that went wrong.


More shoeboxes, new setups, new spots. Well, almost new. She used the spot under my bed again. I didnt have the energy to complain.


To Marias profound joy, the experiments worked. Within a space of 36 hours, the shoebox hatcheries did exactly what shed hoped. Five out of six were a success!, she exclaimed, and hugged me. Im going to pass the course!


I was so happy for her. It was a huge weight off us both, and in our excitement, one thing led to another. 


Ill spare the graphic details, so heres a summary: she went down on me, I went down on her, and because it was a special occasion, she decided to swing her leg over my head and we got to work doing some mutual fun stuff with our mouths.


Toward the end of the act, she was getting pretty into it. Shed stopped working on me and had straightened up and was grinding against my face while I held on for dear life. As she climaxed, I felt something...different.


Something, no, some things, oozed out onto my lips and tongue. And they were moving. I shrieked and pushed her away and ran my hand across my mouth. Small, wriggling banana slugs clung to my skin. I screamed again and ran into the bathroom. In the mirror, I saw tens of inch-long baby slugs in and around my mouth. I vomited with a violence I never realized could be possible.


Oh my God, Im so sorry!, she cried, as I gagged and tried to scrape the slime off my tongue with my fingernails. I didnt reply, I just looked at her. She stroked my hair in an attempt to comfort me. It wasnt working. She started to say something, then stopped. 


What?, I choked out, still retching.


She was silent for a minute, then said quietly, Its just...well, I guess its six out of six. I thought theyd all [died](http://unsettlingstories.com).



















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my inbox is a disaster of messages that haven't been replied to and questions that haven't been answered. Sorry about that. Thanks for fixing the attribution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murray pound-for-pound best QB in the league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had my cell phone number. He said himself it'd take a while. Cmon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hungry hungry basement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it. Larry and I used to have a ping-pong table set up down there. Never a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cellar door is breathing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cellar door is breathing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wed been finding paint chips and broken bits of plaster on the carpet near the cellar door. Id vacuum them up, but each morning theyd be back. At first, I thought it had to be from mice or termites burrowing into the wall. Weve had mice in the basement since we moved in, but theyd never been seen anywhere else in the house. Despite that, I looked for evidence that they couldve made the mess, but I couldnt find any. There wasnt anything out of sort whatsoever, aside from what wed find in the mornings.


Larry didnt think much of it. He mentioned something about a construction site a mile or so away where theyd been blasting out rock. Apparently the shockwaves they produce can form cracks on walls and ceilings. Just cosmetic issues, he assured me. Nothing structural. But neither of us could remember hearing any blasting - especially in the middle of the night.


My guess was whatever had been making our cellar warmer than usual over the last few weeks was to be blamed. Neither Larry nor I could figure out why that was happening, either, but we both assumed there was something with the furnace. The HVAC technician couldnt find anything wrong, but even he admitted it was strange that the basement was a full 30 degrees warmer than the temperature set on the thermostat.


So, with the working belief that the paint and plaster chips were from the expansion and contraction of the doorway, we went on caring about more important things and hoped the heat issue would fix itself.


Last week, I was getting home late after a red-eye flight back from my sisters. Larry was dead asleep when I walked in the house at 4:30am, and I was so sleep deprived I couldnt believe I hadnt killed myself driving home. After I put my stuff down and was getting ready to head upstairs, I saw something that, at the time, I was certain was the result of my exhaustion: the cellar door and the surrounding frame were moving in and out.


I shook my head to get my senses back, but the door and frame still moved in a slow, deliberate pattern. Tiny flecks of plaster fell with each contraction. I walked up to the door and put my hand on it. I still wasnt trusting my eyes and knew that touch would confirm or deny what I was seeing. As I expected, the second I touched the door, the movement stopped. I went upstairs and slept for 10 hours.


Larry was at work when I woke up. He was pulling a double that day, and I likely wouldnt see him again until the next morning. After I showered and went downstairs, I found quite a bit more plaster and paint on the floor than usual. The memory of what I thought Id seen the night before came back, and I experienced an involuntary twinge of fear. It made me feel a bit silly - almost like how Id felt when I was a little girl and still afraid of the dark. 


I brought out the vacuum and started to clean up the mess. When I was running the vacuum over the carpet right next to the cellar, I felt hot air rushing out of the cracks on the sides and bottom of the door. Not warm. Hot. I shut off the vacuum and listened. Aside from the gentle rush of hot air, there was nothing. 


I tentatively touched the doorknob, ready to pull back if it was too hot. It wasnt. It was very warm, but not hot. The fear came again as I knew I was about to open the door and go downstairs. I didnt want to. The child me wouldnt have. But Im 52 years old. This is our house, and weve lived here for 26 years. We know it inside and out. There was nothing to be afraid of. 


The fear remained. I opened the door and was hit in the face with a rush of hot, wet air.


While the temperature wasnt unendurable, it was entirely unpleasant. My plan was to rush downstairs to make sure nothing was on fire, then run back up and call the HVAC man for an emergency visit, no matter the cost. I tiptoed down the old, wooden steps and entered the basement.


The wind rushing up the stairs faded as I got closer to the bottom. All that remained was humid, oppressive air. I began sweating immediately, and I walked across the room toward the furnace. It wasnt even on. I touched it, and while warm, it wasnt close to the temperature of the room. 


Condensation was covering the tiny windows at the top of the walls. And there was an odor. It was heavy and thick and reminded me of vomit. I felt my stomach churning as my mission now became finding the source of the smell. Whatever it was, it had to go. 


It didnt take long.


On the other side of the furnace, up against the wall, was a pile of dead mice. Tens of them. Maybe 50. They were hideously decayed and dripping with dark yellow slime. I gagged so hard I felt my eyes bulge and I pulled my shirt over my nose and mouth. I couldnt believe we hadnt noticed them before, and I was miserable about the prospect of cleaning them up. But it had to be done.


I ran upstairs, grabbed a bucket, some kitchen gloves, and a bottle of bleach. Back in the stifling basement, I grabbed the vermin as quickly as I could, threw them all in the bucket, threw the gloves on top, and poured bleach over the whole area. Id come back later and scrub the remaining slime and bleach and sloughed fur off the floor. I just couldnt take any more at the moment.


I grabbed the bucket and headed back upstairs. I couldve sworn I saw the cellar doorway widening and narrowing as I went, accompanied by waxing and waning gusts of hot air on my skin. My fear and disgust were bordering on terror as I burst through the doorway into the cheery living room.


I stood in the center of the living room, watching the doorway. It wasnt moving. The bucket of dead vermin smelled incomprehensibly putrid. I went out the back door and was ready to throw the whole thing way out back where the property met the woods, when I stopped. There was smoke coming from the gloves on top of the mice. Another smell joined that of the putrefying rodents: burning rubber. I upended the bucket into the brush. I saw that the parts of the gloves that had touched the mice were bubbling and burning away. 


As soon as I got back inside, I called the HVAC guy. He said he was booked solid all day and any work after 6pm would be at double the usual rate. I told him I didnt care. I needed the furnace fixed. I needed whatever it was leaking removed. I couldnt have our home in the shape it was in anymore. 


The HVAC guy arrived around 7. I felt bad to be pulling him away from dinner with his family, so I made him a sandwich and some macaroni and cheese. He appreciated it, and brought the plate downstairs with him so he could eat while he worked. I wasnt exactly sure how anyone could eat under conditions like Id seen that afternoon, but I didnt bother arguing. I left him to his work and went next door to see my elderly neighbor.


We got to talking, and it was almost 10 by the time I realized the HVAC technician was still working. I wished Gladys a good night and went home. The techs van was still in the driveway. 


I walked inside and headed to the cellar door. Plaster and dried paint chips littered the carpet and were being blown across the room by the steady breeze coming up the staircase. Three deep cracks in the door frame and ceiling had appeared.


I called down to the technician and asked how it was going. He didnt reply. I called again, louder. Nothing. That same fear welled up in me again. I looked around. This time, the cheery living room was dark. The windows showed nothing but blackness and the distorted reflection of diffuse kitchen light and the harsh illumination from the techs lamps in the basement.


I called a third time. He didnt respond, but I jumped when a loud, splintering crack rang out right next to me as another fissure appeared in the door frame. I couldve sworn I saw the frame move right before it happened.


My fourth and final call went unanswered. For the second time that day, I knew Id go down the stairs. My 52 year-old body carried my frightened, 8 year-old mind down the steps. I felt hot, sticky air on my face. 


The moment I reached the bottom, the smell hit me. It was just like itd been with the mice, only heavier. I spoke the techs name, rather than calling it. My voice was small and weak and I realized, as I walked toward where hed been working, I was shaking. 


I reached the furnace and headed around to the other side. The smell was so strong, my eyes had started to water. But even through my bleary, tear-filled eyes, I could see the technicians clothes and shoes. They were covered in the same yellow slime and smoked weakly as whatever was burning them ate its way through. The man who owned the clothes was nowhere to be found.


I ran upstairs and called the police, fully aware that the doorway was moving in and out as I ascended the staircase, feeling cool air against my face, followed by hot air against my back. I left the house and waited with Gladys for them to arrive.


Its been five days and the technician has not been recovered. Theres been a town-wide search for him, and his wife and daughters have appeared on television begging for him to come home. Larry and I have allowed the police to search the house while we stay at a hotel. Ive refused to go back until everything is resolved. 


It wasnt the terrifying strangeness of the cellar that has kept me out of our house. It wasnt the still-missing man who came to fix our furnace. It was something else. It was the result of the chemical analysis of the substance on the HVAC mans clothes and the mice Id taken from the basement. Normally, we wouldve have been given that information, but Larrys brother is a cop. He told us what it was, and now I know Ill never set foot in that house again as long as I live.


Stomach [acid](http://unsettlingstories.com).

















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've written up a mandatory set of instructions for those who wish to use my work; if any of you guys want to treat this as a template to modify and post on your own sites or pages, feel free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://unsettlingstories.com/instructions-for-those-who-wish-to-use-my-work/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mandatory instructions for those who wish to use my work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 20:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ask if you could produce my work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are disappearing in northern Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are disappearing in northern Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the last 35 years, a lake in northern Canada has been the site of hundreds of suspected drownings. The location is in the middle of the Canadian tundra. There is nothing around. No food, no shelter. Just cold, inhospitable wilderness. 


The lake is frozen eight months out of the year. Nothing happens then. But during the thaw, when were doing our flyovers, well see clothes floating on the surface of the water. 


Like weve always done, well dispatch a team to investigate. Theyll bring back what they can recover, which will invariably be clothing and someones wallet or purse. 


So far, weve never recovered a single body. 


Had the lake been deep or veined with labyrinthine, subterranean caves, we wouldnt think twice about not being able to recover a body. Same if the lake was full of fish who were big enough to eat and digest a body. But the lakes 40 feet deep at its deepest point. Its crystal clear; we can see the bottom from our helicopter just as clearly as a boater can from its surface.


Our watchpost has turned into an international notification service for missing people. 


The Canadian government granted us the authority, along with the equipment, to research and contact anyone who might be familiar with the owners of the forms of identification. Each time contact is made, we learn the person had been reported missing. 


There doesnt appear to be any time limit on how long a person has to be missing before their clothing and IDs are found floating. Some can be missing for days, others for years. Any personal effects wed recovered then get sent back to the families or loved ones.


While the situation is bizarre, Ive never lost much sleep over it. It's all too surreal; without any bodies or signs of violence, its easy to brush the darkest aspects of it aside. But this past spring, after the thaw and during the new recoveries, different reports started coming in.


Indigenous people within a 300 mile range have started showing up in hospitals. Unexplained burns have been found on their skin. Further, the cancer rate among the indigenous population has risen by 400%. 


I havent been alone in noticing the new, blueish lights seen reflecting off low-hanging clouds. I had a hunch one night, and had our helicopter pilot fly us in the direction of the lake. Like Id expected, the flashes of blue against the clouds intensified as we got closer.


Upon our arrival at the site, hovering approximately 100 feet above the lake, blue light would shine at irregular intervals from the bottom. The pilot, a former American military engineer, said it looked like Cherenkov radiation. 


That alone wouldnt be enough for me to write this. Unexplained natural phenomena is a fact of life. It seems like the more remote you are, the more inexplicable things youll encounter. The floating clothes concern me, but dont frighten me. The flashing light fascinates me, but doesnt disturb me. But theres one last thing. 


A geological expedition recently finished a topographical study of the surrounding area for an unrelated purpose. Their data, like all state research, was made available to us. Being moderately interested in geology and geological formations, I gave it a look. Something caught my eye.


I went to our database of the photographs wed taken of the personal effects wed recovered from the lake. I was looking for ID photos. Before long, I found what I was looking for. I checked it against the geological data Id seen. Not really believing what I was looking at, I checked again with another ID photo. Same thing.


For 500 miles around the lake where people disappear, the topographical readouts show the vague, but unmistakable shapes of the faces of the missing people. And the faces are clearly [screaming](http://unsettlingstories.com).







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it gets enough popularity, it can *magically* turn into a series! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sleeping Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sleeping Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother and cousins and I used to play a game whenever we had a sleepover. It was simple: wed stay up and scare the living fuck out of each other. When we were at Erin and Kyles house, it was the scariest by far. Her house was haunted. Thats what everyone said. Even her parents knew it. Dont worry about Mr. Toombs, theyd say. Hes harmless. Then theyd laugh and go back to what they were doing.

Mr. Toombs was the man who owned the house before Erins parents. He died all alone and no one realized he was gone until many months later. Even though the house got gutted and renovated before it went on the market, we had this feeling hed died in the basement right near the furnace. The air there just felt thick and heavy  like old, sour breath.

Wed have our sleepovers a few times a month. Our parents all worked at the same factory. Whenever they had to take third shift, wed either stay at home and Erin and Kyle would come to our house or Greg and I would go over to Erin and Kyles. I never minded all the moving around until Kyle said we had to play that game. I hated it.

Kyle was the oldest and could be mean if he wanted to. He wasnt a bully; he usually knew when to back off and genuinely felt bad if he made one of us cry. But he still liked to get his way. And that meant wed have to play the sleeping game.

The first time we played the sleeping game, we were at our house. The four of us were in our sleeping bags in the living room and Kyle started to tell a really terrifying story about a skinny alien that comes through the window and cuts you up in your bed. Greg, Erin, and I hated the story, but I could tell Erin was especially horrified. She was only six. I kept telling Kyle to take it easy on his sister, but he was relentless. To Erins credit, she didnt cry, but I think that was the problem. He probably wouldve stopped if she had.

The game went like this: after the story, you werent allowed to get out of your sleeping bag. No matter how scared you were, you couldnt get up to get water, you couldnt go to the bathroom, and under no circumstances could you run upstairs to get comfort from the grownups. If you did, youd have to get an indian burn from the rest of the group.

The night of the alien story, I couldnt stop looking at the living room windows. Whenever a car went by and cast its light against the wall, Id shiver and feel my balls drawing up into my body while goosebumps rose on the back of my neck. Stupid Greg and Kyle were asleep already. Erin, whose sleeping bag was next to mine, was crying to herself.

I need to pee, she whispered. And Im too scared to get up and I dont want to get an indian burn when I get back.

I looked at Greg and Kyle. They were both completely out. Go ahead, I whispered. I wont tell anyone.

Erin gave me a tight-lipped smile and snuck out of her sleeping back and padded down the hallway. Right around when Id assumed I would hear the bathroom door close, she screamed. It was a shrill, horror-filled explosion from her tiny lungs, and the three of us, now wide awake, vaulted from our sleeping bags in her direction. We got there a couple seconds before my parents were thundering down the steps. They flipped on the lights.

Erin was in the corner of the bathroom, sobbing. Her pajama pants were soaked. Mom picked her up and held her to her chest and asked what happened.

The alien, Erin whimpered, then pointed to the shower curtain. Dad opened it. Nothing was there.

It was just a shadow, honey, Dad told her. He glared at us. Come with me, boys, he ordered, and brought us back into the living room while Mom drew a bath for Erin.

After a long lecture from my father, we agreed to not tell any more scary stories. Erin eventually came back to her sleeping bag, and with Dad snoring on the couch, we all went to sleep.

The next night, of course, brought more stories. They were much tamer, though. Greg told a dumb one about a lady who gets pulled into a grave by a killer. I told an even worse one about some teenager whose baby brothers head came off. Erin actually laughed at that one it was so bad. We got ready to go to sleep, still bound by the agreement that we couldnt get up for any reason until it was morning.

At some point in the middle of the night, Greg shook me awake. Hey, we caught Erin coming back from the bathroom. She was already rubbing her arm in discomfort from the burn her brother had given her. Greg grabbed her other one and twisted, making Erin yelp. I took her arm and just squeezed it a little. I felt bad.

Months went by and we played the sleeping game every time we were together. Everyone got caught at least once trying to sneak out. Indian burns were had by all. Erin, though, got the most. It was obvious she wasnt having any fun. To make matters worse, she looked exhausted on the mornings after we played. I brought it up to Kyle, and he thought about it for a minute, then said wed do it once a month instead of every time. I didnt argue.

We kept our little agreement to ourselves because we didnt want Erin to think we were treating her like a baby. That night, we were sleeping at their house. They had a beautifully furnished basement with a big-screen TV, a ping-pong table, and all sorts of other fun stuff. We set up our sleeping bags and played video games until well after 10pm. My aunt came down and said to turn it all off and get to sleep, so we made like we were getting ready for bed, but when the lights went off, Kyle said it was time to play the sleeping game.

I groaned, but he shot me a look and mouthed only one, to me. At least he was holding up his end of the bargain. Like we always did, anyone who needed to get up to pee or get a drink beforehand was allowed to. I went, followed by Kyle, then Erin. We all came back.

In the glow of the flashlight Kyle liked to hold under his chin when he told his stories, Kyle started to talk about a ghost. *The* ghost. Mr. Toombs. Even Greg looked uncomfortable as he stared at the slatted wooden door which served as the barrier between the furnished and unfurnished cellar. The furnace was on the other side.

Mr. Toombs waits until youre asleep, Kyle whispered, and sucks your breath into his lungs. The longer you sleep, the more he takes away. And if you sleep for too long, you wont have any air left to breathe and youllbedead.

My eyes were wide with fear and Greg just stared at the ground. Kyle, too, looked like hed successfully startled himself, especially when the furnace kicked on and we all jumped. Erin, surprisingly, had actually managed to go to sleep first, despite bawling her eyes out by the end of the story and making Kyle promise to give her his snack at lunch or else shed tell on him. I snuck her one of the Lifesaver candies Id stashed away to help her feel better. I guess itd worked.

The rest of us tried to go to sleep. Kyle caught me getting up to pee and gave me a wicked indian burn, but since he caught me while he was on his way to the bathroom himself, I was able to reciprocate. Hard. He punched me in the arm and I swatted him in the balls. I won. We tiptoed back into the basement and got in our sleeping bags. It was the worst nights sleep Id ever had; each time the furnace kicked on, I knew Id see Mr. Toombs floating above my sleeping bag ready to suck the life out of me.

Like always, my aunt came downstairs in the morning to wake us up for school. She started with gentle calls, then hollers, then shouts, then, since we always ignored her, she stomped down the stairs and threatened to haul us out of the sleeping bags.

Lets go!, she ordered, get dressed and go get your breakfast. Erin, if I have to ask you again Im gonna flush your goldfish.

Erin didnt budge.

I swear to God, Erin, Goldeens going down into the sewer with the Ninja Turtles in 321

Nothing. Concern flashed across my aunts face. Kyle, whod been sleeping next to her, shook his sister. She didnt respond. My aunt rushed across the room and pulled Erin to her. She hung limply out of the sleeping bag.

Everything went really fast for a while. The ambulance came while my aunt and uncle screamed and cried and Kyle, Greg, and I just sat there in stunned silence. My parents arrived soon after. They were also crying. We were all asked if we saw her drink any alcohol or take any medicine. None of us had. I knew Erin had been the last one to use the bathroom before bed, so I mentioned that. Someone went into the bathroom and returned with an empty bottle of sleeping pills thatd been in the medicine cabinet.

Through her tears, my aunt insisted that the bottle had been empty to begin with; that shed been saving it so she could remember which kind had worked for her so she could get it again. But there was no other explanation at the time. Erin was dead.

There was a funeral. It was terribly sad. But I went on with my life. Everyone did. I learned years later that the toxicology reports had been negative and Erins death had been ruled an accidental asphyxiation. They blamed the sleeping bag, and my aunt and uncle sued for millions.

When Greg was moving out before his first year at college, I was asked to help load the van. I didnt want to, but I helped anyway. Some of the heavier things were boxed up in the unfinished part of the cellar, by the furnace. I went down and tried not to think about poor Erin.

When I opened the door and entered the warm furnace room, I remembered that feeling I got the first time Id been in there. An image of Mr. Toombs decaying next to the furnace flashed through my head. I shivered. But then I noticed the familiar, strange heaviness in the air. I noticed the smell. It was different from the sour odor thatd reminded me of the last breath trapped inside a corpses rotting lungs. This smell was sweet. It was cloying. Like the breath of someone whod eaten a lime [Lifesaver](http://unsettlingstories.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was full of logical phallusies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another CTer? Cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well sorta but different lol Dad hurt him real bad and now we don't have to pay him to work for us anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry do you want to be friends I'm rich well my parents are but yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so sick of that excuse omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol okay big farma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you call the police he sent me a picture of his pens but I deleted it by accident.

(I'd play this character all day, every day, if it wouldn't ruin my real life.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'll do tomorrow before the parents get back haha I can't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wth I'm 13 haha I don't have dolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg stop private messaging me pictures of your thing I'm only 13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you sound poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a puppy haha two probs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a good idea :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg your so annoying do you have ades or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean he's dead but he's not gone like most of him is still on the floor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that sounds stupid lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um I don't do yard work that's Juan's job and I'm not allowed to talk to him anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay we're not all good at reading lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I bet you're pretty are you blonde too??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol can you like not read or something are you poor sorry haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you know how much ur upsetting me right now. Like do you even care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I don't WANT to have to write a letter! It's HIS fault! His dumb head and his dumb puke and all those dumb legs sticking out of his dumb face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm rich, fatty saucekin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet your mom died </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you're ugly I'm blonde so ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOP IT AND JUST STOP like wth can't you mind your business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg language lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your smart :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe you're ignoring me right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew omg orphanages have like orphans and stuff and they don't shower and use lotion tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha no all my stuff is in the house! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I WAS gonna spill the litter box right near the front door but then they'd be like why did the cat do that where's the cat Madison and I'd have to be like ummmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha ok so I don't have much of that but I have soooooo much ammonia and bleach and stuff so I'll mix that all up and try to put it on. And yeah I so wanna steal a baby (unless Kevin wants to put one in me lol omg nvm) where are there babies people don't care about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you gonna answer or just stay there and be all out of topic? I bet you're from New Jersey lololol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you, like, not interrupt what we're doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only allowed to talk to Danica at school because her mom took her phone and laptop away for sexting lol she's such a s-word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, gross? That is so from a movie I'm not a dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha she's like a mutt but a cat so like a cutt lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um no lol my hamster didn't get any vaccines those are just for people lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha helllooooooo is this thing on lol I need help with this before the parents get back _^__^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my favorite character I've ever written, btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok now my brother is all messed up and gross lol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok now my brother is all messed up and gross lol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol my brother is so gross I hate him. [I wrote about my sister a while back](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4ho869/um_can_any_of_you_guys_tell_me_whats_wrong_with/?st=ivbamqdh sh=d65e3411) and you guys were total a-word holes about it but its okay shes dead. I got in SO much trouble btw but they were too sad to hit me which is fine because I wouldve called CPS on their butts haha.


But yeah I was watching my baby brother Tommy while my parents were out of state at some election party or something and Tommy just started throwing up. Btw if any of you guys are like why is she watching her baby brother after her sister died while she was watching her you can just keep that in yourselves. My parents are weird. I think theyre swingers lol Danica taught me what that meant.


So, like, it wasnt the normal boob milk puke or anything either it was all red and stringy and ugh. Of course I started thinking about dumb dead Gina and being like how much more awful can my luck get and stuff. Gross Tommy just kept spitting up until his high chair was covered in puke. 


It. Smelled. So. Bad. O. M. G.


Anyway I started yelling at him and slapping him so hed stop but then his eye fell out and I got SO MAD because of COURSE Id get blamed for it. Then because he hates me he started to laugh and aimed his pukey mouth at me and I got some in my hair.


Of course since I have the best hair in the family I was so grossed out I ran upstairs and took a shower and left my gross brother to finish throwing up and playing with his dumb eye. I snuck into Moms cabinet and used her real expensive lotion after because it smelled real good and Tommys throw up was making the house smell bad.


While I was making sure my elbows were all nice and moist and sexy (lol) Tommy started yelling. And it wasnt his normal yell either. It was all deep and loud and vibratey like he was showing off and pretending to be a monster. Such a little creep I hate him.


You ever feel it in your stomach and butt when a real low vibration comes by and its like you gotta go to the bathroom? Well yeah it was like that. So totally nasty and inappropriate. Even though he wasnt saying anything it was like he was being so crude and just bad mannered. He reminded me SO much of Gina ugh talk about a boring funeral lol.


Like, we dont have too many people in the family and what was left of Gina was so gross that people took it away to study or something haha. I always used to make fun of her and call her a science experiment and I bet thats what she is now. Itd be funny if it still hurt for her even though shes all dead and stuff. Mom doesnt say anything about god anymore except bad words when she doesnt think Im around but I know she does and Ill tell Dad on her if shes mean about Tommys grossness.


Ugh why am I talking about Gina its making me mad. Its so not my fault but its sooooooo nice not to have to share a room anymore. Like Im in heaven lol.


I wanted to keep putting on the nice lotion but RIGHT ON CUE Tommy apparently fell out of his high chair and managed to get up the stairs because there he was, all walking on his hands backwards or something weird and drooling that stringy puke EVERYWHERE and when he got real close to Dads bearskin rug I kicked him away because no way should that get puke on it omg Id get in so much trouble.


The problem is as soon as I kicked Tommy his head sorta kinda fell off BUT NOT TOTALLY OFF SERIOUSLY its still hanging by a little bit of skin. He wont stop laughing and its super obnoxious and now places where his puke didnt even touch are starting to drip with it. Its like Tommy knew exactly how to get me in trouble and now hes doing it like just right there now he bit the cat like totally in half.


Anyways yeah you guys were total deutsche bags (lol thank Danica for that one too) but I need your help if you can control yourselves and not be mean in the comments. How can I get puke out of a carpet and get a new cat that looks like Ms. Flufferbottom and a new baby that looks like Tommy because I seriously think this ones broken. Like, how does a baby even grow extra legs? So annoying. But yeah help a pretty girl out [lol](http://unsettlingstories.com).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live and learn, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought I could fix it myself. Plus I don't like doctors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Swell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good way to screw with the reader. If you're writing something that's oppressively horrifying and miserable and dark, the reader can get desensitized to it all. Throwing in some humor might get them to relax, which will allow any coming atrocities to seem that much more jarring. 

It's like adding citrus to brighten up a rich, fatty sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about right.

Hi Vargas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 13:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll give a real response to this, since it's obvious I'm part of the reason why it was created.


First off: I'd be fine with the proposal, even though I don't think there's a way to actually do it. Like /u/EtTuTortilla said, maybe some CSS magic could hide usernames, but good luck finding someone who wants to code that.


I am 100% certain my username affects the number of votes my stories get. If people see something they consistently like or dislike, they'll upvote or downvote it without necessarily even looking at what's been posted. On NoSleep, for me at least, that translates to pretty much any story I post getting approximately 20 upvotes in the first hour.


That number is an average based only on what I've observed, so if there's some actual statistics out there, I'm sure they can tell a more accurate story. But yeah, that's what I've noticed. Better stories have gotten more, worse ones have gotten less.


What that average of 20/hour does for me is place one of my stories in the top 5 essentially by default. It's dependent on traffic, but since I usually post between 10am and 1pm EST, there's not much of that. Plus, at that time, theres little new content. A lot of the older content that's been at or near the top has reached whatever threshold Reddit's created where the number of votes it's still receiving means less than the amount of time the post has been up. So, basically, it means those posts are ready to be replaced with fresh material.


Again, depending on how busy the sub is at that time and whether any other popular "name-brand" authors like /u/ezmisery or /u/sleepyhollow_101 have posted around the same time, one of mine usually breaks into the top 2 or 3 about an hour after that. Hitting number 1, though, from what I can determine, is almost entirely based on whether or not people like the story. Theres a LOT of eyes on a number 1 story; that position means its usually on the front page when someone whos subscribed to NoSleep opens Reddit. 


If you look at your own front page, depending on how many subreddits youre subscribed to, the number of posts between the number 1 story on NoSleep and the number 2 story is 75-100. Its a LOT. To go from 2nd to 1st in any situation except when the #1 story is almost a day old requires a lot of upward pressure. More than my name alone has been able to generate, I think. Its all about how people feel about the story at that point.


THAT SAID, since my name already brought me into the top 5, it still has a higher likelihood of being read and voted on than the story of someone else who didn't get into the top 5 within the first couple hours.


Whether or not thats unfair is a gray area. A year ago, when I was still new to NoSleep, I didnt have name recognition. Any story I wrote that got to the top spots were based on the fact people enjoyed what they read and upvoted it. Even today, with the advantage I admit to having, I routinely get my stories thrown off the top by either new writers, or writers who are using an alternate account. All that shows me is despite my following, a better-liked story will usually come out on top. Its how it worked for me a year ago, and its how its working for other writers right now. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/2xcvgt/teenytiny/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, that was the inspiration. Horrible, horrible event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks! :D And I look pretty normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Oblivion that Masks Pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Oblivion that Masks Pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said Id feel better after a while; that my pain would fade along with his memory. His words echoed throughout the husk hed left. My soul had been cored out and left to rot. 


I tossed and turned, night after night, as I imagined him with the one who made him happy. My replacement. The thought of their sex didnt bother me. It was the intimacy after - the quiet bliss when I was the furthest thing from his mind. Just days following the dissolution of our multi-year couplehood, the one which whom hed spent so much of his life was on her way to being forgotten. 


I was forgotten.


I sought an oblivion to mask my pain; anything to dull the omnipresent savagery of loss. Memories of our happiness felt false. I wondered how long he hated me before he finally let me know it was over. How long was I happy while he was miserable? How much of his life had I stolen, oblivious to his diminishing love? I knew it was all in my mind. And my mind screamed as cascades of neurotransmitters reinforced my feelings of profound, hideous dejection. 


Then I had an idea. 


Part of me felt sad about how easy it was to buy heroin.


The first pet store I visited had the rats I wanted. I brought them home and fed them a solution of sugar water and heroin. They died soon after. I knew the last moment of their lives had been their best. 


While they were still warm, I removed their brains and ate them. I wanted to absorb the physical manifestation of their joy.


I know a small portion of the euphoria I experienced following my meal was from the trace amounts of heroin Id ingested. But it lasted longer than a drug high. It lasted for days. For three full days, the thought of him didnt send me into a self-destructive spiral. Quite the contrary; I felt like I was growing. I was getting over him.


At the end of the three days, the pain came back. Nightmares flooded the sleep thatd once been a respite. The fact remained: I was gradually being forgotten. I was being replaced. Someone was creating new memories with the person I love. I couldnt let that happen.


More rats, more heroin. Another respite. Two days, though. Only two. It wasnt working the way Id hoped. The root of the problem was still there. Every passing day, I was becoming less clear in his mind. The prospect being forgotten was infinitely worse than forgetting him. The former made the latter impossible.


My moment of serendipity occurred while I was throwing the dead rats down the garbage chute. 


He answered his phone when I called. To this day, I feel terrible for lying to him. He rushed over, as strong and protective as ever, to see whod hurt me. When he was sitting down, I came behind him and injected a lethal dose of heroin into the side of his neck. He punched me, hard, before his pupils contracted. Before he stopped breathing, he smiled at me.


Kate, he whispered, to think Id almost forgotten how beautiful you are. He exhaled a long, quiet breath. His eyes never left mine as he blinked once or twice, almost as if he were wondering why he didnt feel the need to inhale anymore. When he died, his smile remained.


I opened his head. It took longer than Id expected. I made sure to keep cleaning off his face. His smile urged me to go on. After an hour, I stared at the mass inside his skull that was him. His essence. His everything.


I didnt know what part did what. I just knew it was all him, so it was all important. Over the course of a few days, I consumed him as he smiled. Each morsel had the potential to be a piece that contained his memory of me. All his memories of the good times. All his memories of the beauty we experienced. The closeness. 


When his skull was empty, I felt different. I wasnt euphoric, like Id felt after the rats. I felt better. I was at peace. This was my closure. Id ensured that I wouldnt be forgotten. The one I loved was with me again. Forever. And together, we could be free to make new [memories](http://unsettlingstories.com).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here bro. Gl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here but I'm intrigued.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats a child skull i am just a young man who misses his girlfriend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats a subject3642 i am scared of the scary ground man who said mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pain is too great :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scar reminds me of the last moment she touched me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kara? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then what will I do with the Kara mask I'm making :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::sobs:: You'd be surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. We were made for each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish the bullet would take me. I miss her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only I had been more cautious and suggested the schoolyard a mile  back :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a loss to the world. Not just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wordplay. In the face of tragedy. Maybe laughter is the best medicine. 

I just tried it. I can't stop crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm lost. Devastated. I can't look at maggots crawling out of a skull without thinking of her beautiful face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was my first. My last. My everything :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kara loved coca-cola :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are...are you Kara? Kara are you coming back to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we were made for each other. I took off my promise ring for her :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::sobs:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the attempt at levity. My spirits are so low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I couldn't take any more of his callous cruelty toward the person I love so dearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I felt her bite me, I knew my world was coming to an end. She chose him over me. Each day, I ask myself why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just miss my sweet love so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is dead. How could you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you. I'm in mourning. I miss her so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sex in the Cemetery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sex in the Cemetery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I were crossing through a graveyard when she abruptly stopped and grabbed my arm. She grinned. I knew that grin.


Here? In a cemetery?, I asked. It felt a little weird. Disrespectful, too.


Mmhmm, she mewled, and pulled off her shirt.


I looked around. It was obvious we were alone. Even though itd stopped raining an hour earlier, it was still misty and cool. New England autumn was in full effect. The ground was covered in dead leaves. The place looked creepy.


Were gonna get soaked, I complained, but I started taking off my pants.


I already am, she whispered. I thought about making a joke and telling her that she shouldve brought an umbrella, but I figured it wasnt the time or place.


We did what we apparently needed to do. She seemed to enjoy it, at least. Afterward, I was trying to pick leaves and grass off and out of myself while she grabbed our clothes off the headstone.


Recognize the name?, she asked.


Whose name?


She pointed. My eyes widened.


Rudolph Jans Mendelson is fucking buried here?!, I exclaimed. She grinned.


I wish I couldve met him, she complained.


Um, you know he wouldve killed you, right? Like the others?


No, I dont think so. We wouldve gotten along just fine. Again, she grinned. I probably couldve given him a reason or two to keep me alive. She grabbed my crotch, as if I didnt get what she was talking about.


The late afternoon dimness was giving way to full dark. Fog joined the mist and it crept down the hill into the cemetery like a shroud. My girlfriend looked enthralled.


Im getting chilly, I told her. Its probably time we head back.


Hang on a minute, let me just take this all in. She pulled her phone out of her pocket and started snapping pictures of the headstone. I want everyone to see where we were.


She got a couple shots, then gave me the phone to hold. Thick, cold raindrops began to fall. Yeah, thats probably our cue to leave, I insisted, and started to walk away.


While I was pulling my sweatshirt over my head, I heard her gasp, then moan. Whats wro--, I started to say, but then felt the blood drain from my head as I saw what was causing her to make those sounds.


A hand - a cracked, skeletal hand - had burst from the ground and was gripping her ankle. I shouted and grabbed her arm, but she pulled away. Blood wept through her denim as the hand gripped ever tighter, and after a second, I heard the bone crack.


She didnt cry out, though. Her face took on an expression of intense discomfort, but she refused to shout. I didnt refuse. I yelled and kicked at the hand as profound horror forced adrenaline through my body.


Again, I tried to grab her arms. She struggled, but I held tight. I pulled as hard as I could. As I did, a hideous rotting corpse was dragged from its grave. Rudolph Jans Mendelson.


Let me go!, she finally screamed. Let me go!


I was sobbing now and expending all the effort I could to pull her away from the corpse. His misshapen head seethed with maggots and his eyes and tongue bulged out like some benthic atrocities that had never been exposed to light.


Miiiiiiiiiine, he groaned, and his other hand reached up and grabbed her back; his nails sinking into the flesh and using it to pull. Miiiiiine!


Let me go, let me go, let me go!, she continued to scream. My eyes were closed now as I pulled with singular purpose. I felt teeth sinking into my arm and my eyes flew open as I shouted with pain. 


In that moment of agony and surprise, my grip loosened. My girlfriend fell back into Mendelsons grip and he squeezed her against his rotting, pulpy body. His swollen tongue passed over her neck and face. She wasnt struggling anymore. She just watched me and watched my reaction. Mendelson squeezed harder and I heard his ribs splinter as my girlfriends body was pulled inside.


Thank you for helping me be with him, she said to me, as she was drawn deeper into his putrid carcass. I always knew wed be perfect [together](http://unsettlingstories.com).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carbonara's one of my favorites to eat *and* make. I'm a yolk-only guy, though. It'll probably bring your LDL cholesterol level up to 800, but god damn is it delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, if only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two deer walk out of a bar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One turns to the other in disgust and says, "I can't believe you blew 20 bucks in there." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus H Christ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fireflies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fireflies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theory went like this: when confused by nighttime fog, fireflies can congregate into masses of hundreds, or sometimes even thousands. The fog reduces their ability to signal properly; the distance is shortened and the light becomes too diffuse. To survive and attract mates, individual fireflies started banding together. Once a small group is formed, they signal to one another with pheromones, and that triggers simultaneous illumination. Its brighter, so even through the fog, solitary fireflies can find the group. So if you see a glowing beachball hovering over the lake on a foggy night, dont freak out. Its just fireflies trying to fuck.


I moved to the woodsy town in Vermont a couple years ago. During my first summer there, when the pea-soup fog rolled off the lake every evening, I saw those glowing orbs for the first time. That was before Id learned they were fireflies, so I didnt know what I was seeing. I watched from my porch as the ball floated across the yard at the edge of the forest. It was beautiful, but haunting.


The following morning, at the local diner, I brought up what Id seen. The waitress laughed and said they were just the local fireflies. Apparently theyre considered a minor celebrity in the area. My buddy from college, Phil, was an entomologist. Bugs were his thing. So when I got home after breakfast, I called him up. I figured hed be interested in the phenomenon.


Apparently, interested was an understatement. I guess fireflies had never been observed doing something like that anywhere else in the world. I told him hed be welcome if he wanted to make the drive up from Connecticut and stay for a few days to see them for himself. He did.


The next day, Phil arrived at dusk. Great timing. I gave him a quick tour of the place, then we brought a six pack out to the porch and waited for the fog to move in.


In a steady, slow creep, the fog poured across the lake, into the forest, and swallowed my yard. The moonlight was a dull haze above our heads, and right away we saw individual fireflies trying to locate one another with their bioluminescent shouts.


We waited and drank beer after beer as we caught up on the goings on in our respective lives over the last ten years. After a couple hours, I caught a glimpse of something glowing on the other side of the trees, right by the lake. I pointed and Phil stood up and went to the edge of the porch.


Wow, he breathed, and I could sense his genuine excitement. It was contagious. I got up and stood with him as we gazed at the orb of softly undulating light, our beers forgotten.


The mass of fireflies approached the edge of the yard, every one of its members flying in a tight, spherical pattern. I dont believe my eyes, Phil said. That behaviors never been documented in that species.


The spheres light waxed and waned, and solitary fireflies all over the yard, disoriented in the morass of fog, began to move toward the group. They incorporated themselves into the luminous mass.


The group turned back toward the forest and eventually went out of sight. 


Pretty cool, right?, I asked.


One of the coolest things Ive seen in my career, he agreed. Im going to write up a report tomorrow morning, then tomorrow night Im going to see if I can record it with my phone. Might not come out too great in the low light, though.


Worth a shot, I said. He nodded.


The next morning, I made coffee while Phil typed up his report. I could tell he was impatiently waiting for the evening, so I made a list of local stuff we could do to help the time pass more quickly for him. He finished up and we went out and had a fun, eventful day.


The sun drowned itself in the lake while we ate dinner. Individual fireflies right outside the window were already signalling, as if they wanted to do as much talking as possible before the fog made their job harder. I told Phil to go outside and leave the dishes to me. He didnt argue.


I watched from the kitchen window as Phil dragged a lawn chair out to the line where the yard met the forest. He sat with his phone and his tablet and waited while fog drifted in around him. 


He didnt need to wait long.


An orb of fireflies coalesced no more than 20 feet from my friend. I stopped washing up and stepped out onto the porch to watch Phil get his footage. He held his phone out like he was Spielberg filming his next award-winning movie. 


I dont know if this is gonna work, he called to me. Too damn dark. He put the phone on the chair and tried to record with the camera in his tablet. Thats a little better, he said. I think the camera in this thing is better in low light.


He recorded for a minute, then I saw two more orbs coming in off the lake. Perfect. The waitress told me the smaller masses would sometimes join bigger ones, so I hoped that was the case. Phil noticed them too and called out, thats so cool!


The new masses of fireflies converged on the one in the yard. The fog was dense and I was having trouble seeing Phil, but the glow of the bugs had produced a peaceful, pale-yellow haze.


I heard Phil swearing to himself. The filming wasnt going very well.


How about a picture?, I asked. That might help with the light problem. Try to take a lot of shots in a row and maybe you can animate them in the computer afterward.


Phil didnt say anything, but I saw him move the tablet down as if he were changing some settings. He held it back up, and flashes exploded through the fog as he took picture after picture.


This is gonna screw up the way their illumination looks, he shouted, but at least I can show how theyre clustered together.


Flash after flash after flash bloomed through the thick fog. Above us, the sky lit up as distant lightning announced a coming storm. Indeed, a storm had been forecasted for the early morning hours, but apparently it was ahead of schedule. You see that?


Yeah, Phil replied. Ill get inside before the rain.


He kept snapping pictures. On the outskirts of the yard, I noticed more light. There were new orbs. Lots of them, ranging from ones the size of a lemon to others the size of watermelon. Phil!, I shouted, check those out!


More orbs coalesced and moved in the direction of Phil, apparently attracted by the strobing camera. The lightning flashed again. Brighter this time. Closer. There was no accompanying thunder. 


Now there were tens of the firefly clusters, and the yard was a blur of pale yellow that threatened to compete with the camera flashes. This is fucking awesome!, Phil hollered, and almost as if in response, more lightning lit up the fog. It was almost blinding now, and I said to Phil we should probably go in. Hang on, he replied. Im almost done.


All the firefly masses formed one colossal ball the size of mid-sized car, which hovered directly above Phil. There was another burst of lightning, this time accompanied by a gust of wind so powerful it knocked me down. The mass of fireflies scattered. And Phil screamed.


I jumped back to my feet just in time to be nearly blinded by an explosion of intense light coming from where my buddy was standing. I squinted and tried to acclimate my vision. Phil kept hollering. Whats going on?!, I shouted to him. There was no reply other than hysterical gibberish. 


My eyes slowly acclimated to the light and I when I realized why Phil was screaming, I gasped and backed up to the house. A glowing firefly the size of a school bus was pinning him to the ground. He struggled and thrashed, but the insect must have weighed tons. Its wings fluttered and a hurricane-force wind pushed me against the house and flung leaves and branches from the nearby trees.


Help!, Phil shouted, over and over. I was too terrified to move. I could only watch as the hideously luminescent creature held my friend under its bulk.


A small drop of pure, white light fell from the mandible of the monstrous bug. Phils scream grew high pitched and inhuman. More of the liquid light drooled from the fireflys mouth. I smelled burning. Burning clothes. Burning grass. Burning meat. A pool of radiance formed where Phil was pinned. His screaming stopped.


The firefly lurched up and took to the air, the wind from its wings shattering windows in the house and tossing me to the ground. It was gone. The light was gone. The orbs were gone. All that remained was a puddle of horrible luminescence. 


I ran in the house and dialed 911, spoke to them for a minute, then stepped warily toward the liquid light. The stench was overwhelming. I gagged and got closer. The fog was making it difficult to see anything with proper resolution. But soon, I was only a couple feet away. It all came into focus. 


The acidic light, which was now starting to dim, had destroyed everything it had touched. Tattered, singed clothing still smoked. The skeletal remains of my friend still steamed. And gripped in his bony hand, the melting tablet still sat, its flash strobing with dying pulses as the acid ate it [away](http://unsettlingstories.com).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are multi-sentence titles allowed again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just that - a vivid imagination. That and a lot of practice. I've been ramping up my story production over the last year, and this is the result of all that effort. No stealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That issue should be fixed. I'm sorry about that. Please send me a private message if there are any other problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was ten when it happened. My tenth birthday. I was in the woods with my uncle and father and they were making sure I knew how to shoot. Before I could hunt deer, I had to show them I could hunt bottles. By that, I mean I had to hit ten bottles from ten feet away, using ten bullets. It wasnt much a test. I couldve done that when I was seven. My guess was they just wanted to do something special with the number ten. I wouldve preferred ten cakes.


Thanks to my well-placed shots, the first three bottles exploded in glittering, green shards. Against the sullen backdrop of the sun-punctured gray sky and the forest still recovering from last years fire, it looked hauntingly pretty. 


Even though Id worn my ear protection, I felt discomfort in both my ears. It wasnt the normal ringing Id encountered before, though. It was a painful buzzing, like flies were trapped by my eardrums.


I looked over and saw my dad and uncle both rubbing the area around their ears. Theyd taken out their plugs and looked uncomfortable and confused. I pulled off my own and asked what was going on. Dad shook his head and said he didnt know.


Mother of fuck!, my uncle exclaimed, prompting a burst of giggles from me and a slap upside his head from my dad. But then we saw what had caused his outburst. 


The seven remaining bottles were floating. They stood, motionless, three feet above the rocks where theyd been placed. The buzzing intensified and the three of us cringed. It was like a colony of bees had descended on the quiet forest.


Lets go, Dad said, grabbing my hand, and we started walking back the way we came. 


Then the world ended.


My father and uncle were hoisted into the air. I shrieked. Their eyes grew wide with fright and they held their rifles in deathgrips while pointing them in every direction in a futile attempt to threaten whatever was assailing them. I remember how my dad looked right before it happened. The instant before.


A one of the levitating bottles flew with impossible speed. It struck my dad in his open mouth and shattered. Glass stuck inside his devastated gums, tongue, and cheeks. My uncle, now screaming, was met with the same hideous assault. Both wailed around the glass impaling the soft tissue of their mouths while I tugged at my dads leg, trying to pull him back to Earth.


30 years later, their screams haunt me more than the sight of their blood. But blood poured. Blood gushed. In a haze of uncomprehending horror, I watched as the shards extracted themselves from the mouths of the men and began to carve. Lips were amputated. Cheeks were excised. Flesh dropped to the forest floor. The buzzing in my ears reached an unbearable level, and with a sharp cracking sound, everything went silent.


Deaf, I huddled against a large tree and sobbed. I couldnt tear my eyes away from the violence. In a noiseless, surreal nightmare, I saw the glass carve their gums down to the roots of their teeth. Their heads jerked forward in a powerful movement and teeth exploded out of their skulls and into the sky. I followed their trajectory and saw, for the first time, a patch of dull, green light behind the gathering clouds.


I looked back at my father and uncle. Theyd stopped moving their arms and legs and trunks. The violent forward motion had to have broken their necks. My uncles eyes gaped and darted in every direction, but Dads were on me. They expressed pain, but something else, too. It was comfort. Even in the bloodbath, he wanted me to know it would be okay.


It wasnt okay.


The green light intensified and I saw the outline of something - thats still the only word I can use - something - in the sky. The first thing that came to mind was Medusas head. It had a spherical center and countless, serpentine spires jutting from it at every conceivable angle. Liquid patches of light traveled between the spires, and as it descended, I felt the buzz which had deafened me vibrating my hair and fat.


It reached the treeline. It was the size of a house. My dad and uncle had their eyes on it as their ruined mouths wept. The spires stopped mere feet away from the three of us. A sliver of green shone on the two men, and they began to shake wildly.


If they hadnt been paralyzed from the tooth extraction, the shaking wouldve ensured it. They flopped like electrocuted ragdolls pinned to a corkboard; arms, legs, hips, backs - all contorting in ways that would splinter and pulverize their bones. My fathers knees bent forward, hyperextending until his toes were touching his hips. My uncles lower jaw swept back and forth. There was no conceivable way they were still alive.


With a sense of resignation, I realized I couldnt move. I was pinned in my position, helpless to do anything but stare at the carnage. I assumed I would be next.


The green light flashed red. The tattered clothing on my relatives split and fell. The glass, which had dropped to the ground after finishing with their mouths, took to the air again. It sliced through their bodies in long, deep incisions. The red light intensified, and I watched as their splintered, fragmented bones were hurled from their bodies toward the liquid light on the spire-studded object. In a final, hideous act, their eyes dropped from their boneless sockets and pulped brain matter followed them.


Two motionless bags of flesh hung in the silent forest.


If I passed out at that point, it wasnt for long.


My eyes opened to the sight of the husks of my uncle and father being prodded by one spire each. Skin flopped back and forth. Any remaining blood rained onto the floor of the abattoir nouveau below them. The light had shifted from red to something else Id never seen before. It was as if they were trapped in a beam of shadow; it wasnt perfectly black, but dark gray.


Black fluid began to drip out of their skin. It puddled in the mess of blood and organs on the ground. Their flesh wounds began to close. The dripping slowed, then stopped. The bodies started to regain their original shape.


My despondent resignation grew teeth as fresh fear suffused my small body. The skins were full again. The arms and legs moved, as if they were being tested. Eyes sprouted from the empty sockets and teeth filled their mouths. After a couple minutes, they looked exactly like they had before theyd been murdered. 


Exactly.


Everything blurred after this.


I remember them slowly descending to the ground. I remember their mouths moving as if they were talking to me, but in my deafness, I heard nothing. I remember trying to run, but being stopped; stopped and held against the chest of the thing who looked like my father. The twinkle of concern in his eyes was gone.


I was carried through the forest to our house. I remember Mom starting at the sight of my nude father and uncle entering, but then I lost consciousness. When I woke up, I was in my bed. It was the day after my birthday.


As I said above, its been 30 years. I am still deaf. Everything continued as if nothing had happened, other than a freak accident due to a combination of a misfiring shell and my shrugging off of my hearing protection right beforehand. I even told Mom about it all, and she just stroked my hair and told me it mustve been a terrible nightmare. 


There was no warmth in her eyes.


My mother, my father, and my uncle still live on the same street. I live across town. I dont see them very often. They express great sadness at this and message frequently, but I cant forget what I know happened - what I know wasnt a dream. 


Over the years, there have been clues. Every so often thered be a newspaper article about strange lights in the sky or messes of blood and organs found in the forest. Theyre things that are always explained away by auroras or animal attacks. Weird stuff, but not anything thatll make people think more than twice.


Five years ago, I was on my way to the supermarket on my bicycle when my chain fell off. I pulled over onto the sidewalk to fix it. Out of the corner of my eye, I saw another cyclist crossing the street. Then a car made an illegal turn and the cyclist had to swerve out of the way. He fell onto the ground. I looked up and realized it was Dad. He was picking himself up. A small gash had appeared on his elbow. Greasy, black liquid trickled down his arm.


He saw me and smiled. Then he looked at his arm and sighed. He lifted the bike back onto its wheels, walked up to me, and signed, your mother and I miss you. He hopped on the bike and rode away.


I just stared at tiny black drops on the [pavement](http://unsettlingstories.com). 















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I've already published one, but that was a year ago and I've grown tremendously since then. I'm putting together something new and it will hopefully be out by next month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks buddy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply; I just got my September one. For 198k visits, I got $146. Definitely not enough. I'll be moving ASAP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, when we're born, we all jump out of a bush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Data dumps are so deliciously malleable! So much potential! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, I've got 132 stories so far this year. Definitely makes my place on the other lists more an issue of quantity over quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
