<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4454</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, i've been to some 4 star hotels that were very much not what I learned were 4 star hotels as a kid in the 90's. 4 star hotels now are like decent. 

But when I go to a 4 star or 5 star hotel, i'm expecting Four Seasons, Mandarin Oriental, proper shit like that. 

Now days it's like oh we're 5 stars cuz of some rando trade magazine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Train set brought by /u/nekkonekko  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reference? I tried going thru the post history and I just couldn't figure it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just now realized how fucking old I am. Saving Private Ryan didn't come out til at least high school. And idk when this game came out. I can only assume by graffics way the hell after 2001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG! Thank you so much. Thats amazing. I swear, As soon as this situation is better. I'm donating something in the honor of you and all these wonderful people here's name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk, he'll have the book and I was able to get him 2 other things (an octonauts toy and a daniel tiger action figure type thing). And I just posted the other day. I don't want to take away chances from people who are really hard up with absolutely nothing under the tree. 

Plus I can always just do 3 kings day later even tho it'll be a little non-standard. there are 12 days of christmas afterall anyway. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to say thanks to you all. The sudden and unfortunate random change in my financial situation was really shitty. But you guys really helped out. 

Even though it was just 1 book. I'm sure he is going to love it. He's very easy to please, in this regard. (thankfully) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at Mr. Millionaire over here with a microwave and a toaster oven.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying for the warm pallet. I'm trying to up my makeup game and look like an adult. I figure it might help with my currently very lack luster job search.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 22:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wishlist for my son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's his list: Link: http://a.co/1Z2uycf

Originally everything was supposed to be super awesome this christmas but my husband got bit by a dog while delivering mail at work the first week of november. he got no pay for basically 1 month and they're still holding up the pay that he was supposed to get for the time off. They keep saying next week, next week. But its really really shitty. 

I have about 2 things for my son for christmas. But I was going to do all my shopping this week and they still haven't given him the back pay. I feel really shitty asking for anything especially since at some point we'll get this money. it just wont be til after christmas i'm suspecting. 

I wouldn't ask for anything but he really really loves christmas. He's been watching Christmas and holiday episodes of all his favorite shows since October basically. I just want him to have stuff to open on christmas. 

The list has a bunch of books and stuff, so they're no more than 5 bucks. 

I've got him a few things from 5 below like those pin art toys and slinkies, and I won a kmart giftcard for 30 bucks so I'm going to buy him a few little action figures. I was all set to buy him a huge train table but it was either train table or electric bill and electric bill won out. 

Needless to say. I just want the tree to have more than the 3 little things I was able to buy him under it. So it can sorta look like tv for him. not looking for much just really wanna see that smile. 

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up above^ 

No murder, yes thats still a hard fast rule. No killing, was never a rule. people get their words all twisted up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you should be able to use this as evidence that you're disabled. And then utilize the disability and the health insurance to assist you with losing weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SV 

I finally lost nearly 9lbs. 

I've had fitness coaches, personal trainers, nutritionists and more. And i'd basically slowly lose like half a pound every two weeks despite massive adherence to the diet. 

Most times the nutritionist would have me on some diet of 1500 or 1400 kcals a day. I'd work out 4 or 5 times a week. I was basically throwing good money after bad. 

I even started taking metformin to try and lose the weight. And it just was a bunch of crap. 

Well, i still take the metformin cuz of PCOS

but I happened upon an article in a magazine that said that for people with diabetes and insulin problems (like with PCOS), keeping your carbs under 100g's a day would really help. Especially if you haven't been seeing any results via regular diet and exercise. 

So I did my TDEE and subtracted about 7Kcals from it, for my weekly caloric goal. 

I do about 1500 kcals M - Th and 2000kcals f - sun. 

And I keep my carbs between 100 and 125g a day. 

I'm sure i could go lower but thus far this has had some great results. I'm sure it's a first week fluke, but no matter what I tried in the past i'd at max lose about 1lb in a week. 

Anyway, hope this encourages someone. 

Here's a link to something about it. I couldn't find the original article i had read: https://www.pcos.com/blog/4/how-does-a-low-carb-diet-help-to-reverse-pcos/

That article is just about how to handle pcos with low carb diets. But since I basically wasn't losing weight cuz of the hormone problems with pcos, it helps. 

I'm going to continue to search for the better article about weight loss specifically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit!!!!!!!!!!!!! Now I gotta unlearn all the super essential NY/NJ shit and learn about copperheads. Guess time to forget is lenny is black and carl is white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of those and for some reason, its sitting in the damn junk drawer. Where it is completely useless
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prediction: you win /r/giftournament  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just turnt me on to some next level shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the dreams I didn't follow are all tied up on having to make a decision about what to do since my child was disabled (autism nonverbal). 

I had to become a sahm and care for him because we didn't have and wouldn't make enough money to pay for the level of care he'd need from a babysitter. 

I regret not being able to move to Scotland and not doing a bunch of work and education related things like living on a reservation and learning the language of my forefathers. 

I'm sure I could shuffle things around, but if it doesn't work out because I have to care for someone else, I'm going to trust what my Pastor said, who's been when countless men and women as they died. 

He said not one of them ever regretted putting their personal goals aside because of their families. 

Now I'm just focused on making enough money to ensure  he does well. It's not working how I'd like, but I do what I can because it's important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz you need an amphibious vehicle or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay np. 

Yeah trying to reduce carbs to like 100g cuz of glycemic load. Too much sugars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't beans high in carbs? Not as high as rice but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool good idea. i've seen those but i never knew how it tasted. And i could def up the beans vs the rice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low Carb Substitutions for Pasta and Rice that are also not super duper expensive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We eat a lot of hispanic food. So Arroz con Gandules etc, etc. 

Also a lot of pasta. 

Also money is tight as heck. So I'm trying to find a way to eat healthy but cheapish. 

So I need some help. 

I can buy a 20lb bag of rice for about 10 bucks. 

I need a way to add bulk to my plate without over blowing my budget. 

So currently we eat a lot of Potatoes, Rice, and Pasta. 

Any good subs? That are just as filling if not better. And also lower carb? I'm trying to cut my carbs to about 100g a day in a 1700 kcal diet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But seriously Domestic Violence Shelters need things like this. They say they always need toiletries. I assume this counts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOu can send them my way if you like. I wish i had a mom to send me lots of toilet paper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he's still black. So I guess that proves that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The song is about sex. It's not christian at all. Idk why this is even in R/christianity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the lyrics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His song was horribly blasphemous. He wasn't a Christian and I believe he openly mocked us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone move onto a reservation? Supposedly my dad lived on one but no one ever told me what tribe or where and they're all dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 16:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Present </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here Are All the Hallmark Channel Christmas Movies You Need to Watch This Year | Brit + Co </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 16:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they don't nominate Frank ocean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyrics

This sounds fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But obviously when they liquidate them for the benefit of their children it would then incur some pretty punitive taxes. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would accidentally effect the retirement of disabled adult children. 

Many parents end up setting up all kinds of venues of investments to sell at a later date for the benefit of their adult disabled children who will outlive them so they can afford round the clock care givers without being subjected to the hell that are many state run options. 

I have a few friends who brought land and stocks so that when their children are 80 or 90 they'll still have additional income so they don't have to live off the pittance that Social Security offers. 

This will effect those children. 

As far as my research has gone their is no tax free saving program for disabled children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like IRAs are fine but what about people with children with disabilities? 

In order to provide them with a good standard of living you'd have to have multiple revenue streams for them to benefit from, including selling off investments that would be capital gains. 

Sure billionaires might benefit but not everyone is a billionaire and the people trying their darnedest to save a few million to last their disabled children til death would bear a decided amount of burden by having huge chunks of that money taken from them for taxes. 

Saving for your own retirement is hard as shit. But the limits for IRAs and 401ks aren't enough to save for both your own and a disabled child's old age.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't that fuck over a lot of people who invest for their retirement or children?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex feels so much better without a condom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they are. I just said I hope that isn't the case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 23:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd hope they were at least just being completely irrationally mad. 

I'm sure if my kid died in some tragedy I'd be mad enough to do a bunch of shitty things like sue companies that really didn't do anything. 

And hopefully someone sensible would slap the fuck out of me and tell me that I'm being irrational.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool. Hope you have a great time. I know it's supposed to be pretty serious study and prayer but I suspect that you'll enjoy it too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get accepted, Idk if you can use computers and stuff but if so, and it hasn't been done, do a AMA. I would love to know what being a monk and getting accepted involve. 

I always figured you just joined. I thought monks were just really religious dudes and didn't expect there to be a whole process involved. 

Also, good luck!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (And because it's still good for facepalms....)
 
 
 
     Harding referred to Newton's Principia Mathematica as a "rape manual" in her 1986 book "The Science Question in Feminism", a characterization that she later said she regretted.

I seriously have to read the reasons why she said something. I've not read the full of Principia Mathematica, probably just clips as they related to school. But from what I gathered it was just about the laws of motion and gravity and shit. 

I really want to find out how that = rape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk if this is trashy. Stupid yes. but trashy would be more him shooting up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, i didn't see that one. Should I delete?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 21:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta watch this episode again now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 21:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why people can't just remember that Science classes are based upon science. 

Okay so your black magic religion or whatever believes that lighting is because of whatever the fuck. Great, go learn about that shit in black magic religion class. Science is based upon science facts. 

When you're in an English class and reading some book that talks about dragons and shit, you don't spend a whole bunch of time talking about the science of dragons. You read the damn book and talk about grammar, and sentence structure and shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 21:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course a friend of mine told me that they have heard rumblings of similar thought in Western universities. I believe there was a feminist who wrote a paper saying that science is sexist because objective truth is male privilege.

I always thought that science and math were the two things that could unite the world together. Barring those that are upset about origin of life theories i've never saw much problem from people with science.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even science isn't safe: Students want to scrap science because it's racist and colonialist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How everyone is this election if only there were some alternative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a possibility. 

But yeah, I won't bother someone if they're having a sip of wine, or tasting their husband's beer. But some people will be getting lit while pregnant and when you mention it, they either act like this is some news to them. Or treat you like you're an idiot who clearly hasn't read how terribly good shots of vodka are for babies. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently on world news theres a whole post about Child marriages and there are some pretty hatey things about Christians in that post. Don't see those getting deleted or blocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mildly confused? they could somehow be bothered to tell you to go to another sub and that it's hate speech but not why? 

Srsly, it's like a 1 sentence explanation that would have explained that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats but honestly, one is never out of God. Once he's saved you he's saved you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you monthly payments and monthly income? 

If you're credit scores are high enough, do you think you'd be able to get a lower interest personal loan to pay off the higher interest personal loan? I'm not sure if that's a possibility in general, but if it is look into it. 

If you can find a way to sell / trade in your car and pay off the additional 4K that is of a lower interest rate than your car note at present I'd look into that. 

Also when did you have the baby? 6 months ago or more than a year? Have you adjusted your withholdings to reflect that? 

If you did have the child this year, you may get a few hundred to a few thousand in a tax return and can use that to pay off some debt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on being motivated! 

I've found a really good tool for making sure I work out. Google calendar app on Android phones (not sure about other iterations) has a goal scheduler. 

You pick your goal (exercise/walk) then what time of day you want to do it and then how many times per week. And it will set out reminders for you to do it. 

I like it a little better than just setting an appointment or reminder because it tracks how often you've completed it. And that is super fun. IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is super cute!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I've got a kid with a developmental disability. I did everything medically appropriate when pregnant, didn't drink, do drugs, smoke, no caffeine, no soft cheese, no sushi, no cold cuts. And nothing gets me more upset when some asshole drinks and does drugs while pregnant (KNOWINGLY) and has a normal kid. 

Like sure any mom who will drink while pregnant is going to give that child a shit life, and that sucks. But what the fuck with the universe man, how is that even slightly cosmically  just.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your thread is wrong. 

And it seeks to blame people and put a bunch of legalism on people for being upset. 

It's okay to be angry, and to ask why bad things happen. 

Being out of pain when you're dead is great but it doesn't alleviate the pain of today. 

If someone is dying from cancer and will leave their kids orphans, that isn't comfort. It's just a trite little musing about how they're totally sinful for being scared and in pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 02:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the promise of the world to come doesn't negate problems on earth and your post while well meaning does that disservice and is very prosperity gospel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infinite rewards and crowns for following him are all in the next life. Not here on earth. 

Jesus and the scriptures say multiple times (see 2 Timothy 3:12 and John 15:20 for examples) that you are guaranteed persecution for following Christ. 


Bad things happen because of man's fallen nature. That includes man's inhumanity to man and other evil which befalls us. 

There is no guarantee that he will deliver us from the evil that befalls us in this life. Many people have died while waiting for god to heal them. Many people have prayed for god to deliver the hem from murder or abuse and he hasn't. It's the unfortunate reality of life. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 14:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how it works. This is shoddy pop theology with little to no substance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 11:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "he said to them, The Sabbath was made for man, not man for the Sabbath." Mark 2:27

The Sabbath is to give one a break from the burdens of work. Even if not all day. 

It's not a hard fast rule any more. And besides within the Lord he gives you rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 10:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told the receptionist at my son's pediatricians office that I found it unacceptable that they still didn't have the files I'd requested ready. (I'd requested them 3 separate times over 3 months).

About 15 minutes later I got a call from the doctor saying I shouldn't be verbally abusive like that. I didn't cuss, and I didn't yell. 

It was insane

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried temp agencies. No luck and I've always been able to get work thru temp agencies. 

Shit, I'm willing to work for free which should be like a thing where they just have too many people volunteering rather than turning anyone away. 

plus I think i'm in a pretty good area, there's decent growth and a lot of big companies and small companies. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Discussion) How do stay motivated when you keep failing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example: 

I've been out of traditional work for a few years and since I've been trying to get back to proper steady work I've had no luck. 

It's been rejection after rejection. Shoot, I've even been applying to volunteer positions with not even a call back. 

At what point do you say, "fuck it clearly I'm a loser" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank all you wonderful guys and probably girls pretending your guys to avoid PMs of dickpicks, for all the wonderful gifs. I shall cherish them for at least 2 more days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to take a shower and came out not more than 10 minutes later and my son had eaten a handful of desitin. The only bonus was that his resulting diarrhea didn't give him diaper rash cuz it was full of protectorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 17:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Rufus! 

I saw that dog wandering and fed him but I couldn't get him to come inside. I had named him Rufus out of lack of options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually, if you built your own mailbox, technically you're supposed to get it approved by the postmaster or somesuch. 

https://www.usps.com/manage/mailboxes.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend just had a baby, These books should really help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is that from? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't out of the weeds yet. That guy is related to someone. could it be you? Who knows. but you must go to the next family reunion
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know how people get this kind of drama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a friend of mine ever posted some shit like that, I'd immediately defriend them and erase all record of us having known each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does have shitty tattoos but idk if a juggalo he's Canadian. Do they have many Canadian juggalos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] Gonna eat pussy tonight, guess i should tell all my friends and loved ones on facebook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 06:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> checking in~
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has norm ever done an AMA? He's so awesome. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually liked that movie. Also, I had jack shit going on in my life at the time. Ahhhhh... high school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 03:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bird by Bird  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it definitely would have helped some. But I had some stuff as auto pay that I stopped because I knew I was totally boned with my spending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! 

Yeah that brain can fucking ruin you some times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah even if it was a garnishment, it would be under a separate line item. So it's definitely not that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man. 4 Bluetooth keyboards! 

Thats hardcore. 

Tho at least they're useful. 

I brought an entire run of Jem Comics that I still haven't even cracked open.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Dave Ramsey. Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, check out a clinic or a university hospital. They sometimes offer low cost visits. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 19:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Like for some reason over the past few months I've absolutely had to buy tons of records and comic books. 

Like, fuck the insurance and the car payments. Ive got to have this damn Batman comic cuz it'll cheer me up right this minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 19:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Nah, I'm one of those weirdos that enjoys that sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well since all my bills, rent, food, car, insurance, and everything is covered by 80% of our income and we aren't on food stamps or anything like that then I don't see the problem.  

I get a few freelance gigs every now and then but not on a consistent enough basis for me to count it as income in my budget. 

I have a son who has autism who needs lots of care. I decided to stay home with him about 4 years ago because proper child care for his specific needs can be extremely expensive (like $20/hr). 

Meanwhile, after 4 years of no proper work, every time I apply to a job in my field I get, "We really liked your previous experience; however, you don't have any recent experience so we went with another candidate" This despite being in charge of Treasury management for a multimillion national company for ~3 years.

I'm currently in the process of applying to masters programs in accounting so hopefully my masters will trump my 4 years of stay at home momness. 

But even if I'm not rolling in dough, I think that if I'd normally only spend 80% of my income (and I'm not relying on food stamps to supplement my income) that I'm doing pretty well. 

Would it be better for me to be making 10k a month and spending 10k a month? 

I'm lower end of middle class I'm not in poverty. While I'd much enjoy additional income. I'd likely still have the same bills along with probably an additional expense for a caretaker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the US. 

Insurance is available for pretty cheap depending upon your situation via the exchange. 

But for that specific situation, I went to a clinic and the supermarket pharmacy does discounted generics. So it only cost me 4$ to fill the script.

Normally, I'd have gone elsewhere, but our insurance hasn't started yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said about. And no, I'm not currently employed. 

But since all my bills are covered by our income, I don't really see how it's your concern or a problem. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Those are pretty terrible. 

I studied up on Stalin for my senior thesis and I eventually got into stories of him killing millions of people. 

Now, occasionally, you'll hear some stories from any of the many genocides of the 1900s. The ones you hear most often are the good triumphing over evil or good people who endured to be good in face of evil. The oskar Schindler's and people of that nature. 

However, the thing that stuck with me most in those classes was not the "how great that there are good people in this world."

But 

How inhumane we can be to each other. Humans are not good at their core. If they were genocides wouldn't happen. But they do. They do because at our base humans can do evil to others large scale without thinking. 

Like my grandfather told me once. He was in Germany after the war and yet not one person would admit to being for the Nazis. But that can't be true. Because they could have never gotten as far as they did without at least enough of the population to be so complacent that they didn't care. 

I've thought about it. 

I hope that I'd be the kind of person smuggling people out, hiding people in my attic, fighting for good. But honestly, just based on history, it would be more than likely that I'd be either so complacent I didn't care. Or I'd have done whatever benefitted me the most. And that's the horror of it all. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 08:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am a girl, I take just as much time if not less than my husband. 

Shower, clothes, and pony tail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I was in a really bad place. I had started to deal with larger and larger bouts of depression towards the end of college. By the time I went to the therapist i was like 6 years in a pretty bad downward spiral. 

Basically if you ignore any problem for 6 years it's going to get worse and worse. 

I'm just glad that I had at least 1 friend to tell me to just check out a therapist and then have a therapist that was willing to force me to do something about the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1000. 

If I never experienced that orgasm I don't really know what I'm missing out on. But I do know what having 1000$ feels like so I'd prefer that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went on an interview I was going to be in charge of a newsletter and I was like one of the top 2 candidates. 

So they ask: "what would you do if someone doesn't have their article in by deadline" 

I went into some long spiel about tracking them down at home to make sure that they weren't sick or injured. 

When I was done there was a long break in conversation and then someone re asked the question and specified what would I do about the article. 

I felt like such an idiot. Like that beauty queen who talked about how like May 7th was the best date, when she was asked to describe her perfect (romantic) date. 

I tried to recover from that, but I think that firmly sealed the interview for the other person. And I yelled at myself the whole way home. 

Of course, I had a perfectly good answer for that question, which was that my goal would be to always have prewritten articles on standby for such occasions. But after my first answer that probably didn't matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Initially, it was that I was drinking all day and then walking to the store and rebuying a case of beer and then drinking those til it looked like I had only had maybe one or two during the day so my husband would not know. 

However, it took a lot to get me to actually quit.


When I finally put that bottle down for the last time 2 and 1/2 years ago. And got serious about being sober. It was because after about a year or so of going to therapy and AA meetings, I still kept relapsing. 

And upon telling my therapist about how I nearly drank myself to death she said, basically either I get sober or she would try and get my kid taken away. 

I wasn't a shit drunk mom or anything, there was always food, clean house, stuff was done, but I would drink myself stupid after he went to bed. And I was basically just biding time til i got up enough courage to kill myself (which was probably true but I wouldn't have admitted as such then).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 06:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Tho even in the post you link it says that there aren't any real direct public statements for it. 

Like the 1922 quote they say can be dismissed as hyperbole. 

I've considered their argument, but I'm not big into conspiracies. It takes a hell of a big conspiracy to create evidence of a mass extermination. 

I'm almost certain that it would be miles easier to cover up the mass extermination, especially under the guise of war than to create one. 

It's really sick. It annoys me almost as much as the 9/11 truthers (which come in a few forms including international Jewish conspiracy form). 


We had a Holocaust survivor come to our class (she a classmates grandmother). She talked a little about deniers. I know that it seemed very profound at the time but I've forgotten exactly what she said. But the gist of it was that for the real deniers no evidence will trump their hate. 

Which I guess is true. I hate very few people in the world, but of the person I hate the most, you could bring me mountains of evidence about what a great person they are, videos of them saving babies in burning buildings, eye witness statements, and more, and I wouldn't allow myself to believe it for any reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 06:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the sidebar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 06:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between a human and a cockroach is we can ponder these things. 

If there is ultimately no point why even try once things get to a point? 

Not saying, why don't you kill yourself now. 

But if there's no point and nothing you do matters then why even try to stop people from killing themselves. 

Not saying there aren't other reasons for not killing yourself, but why shouldn't a person kill themselves if nothing matters ultimately. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 06:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember we did a project on Holocaust denial in either middle school or high school (I'm thinking probably high school). 

We had to look up reasons why they believed it didn't happen and how they dismiss certain evidence.

So from what I remember:

1. The photos were faked by the Allied forces to make hitler look bad. 
2. The photos are actually from Allied prisons and camps. 
3. Hitler never directly said anything about the camps. 

I think there were even a few arguments against the actual places and such. 

From what do remember, my teacher said that it's actually easier for Holocaust deniers to not have to deal with proof now because there are very few first hand accounts anymore. 

It's very disturbing. 

I remember my grandfather telling me about how he had gone to Germany with the army for some time before Korea and he saw some of the camps. 
If i recall correctly he basically said that they didn't even talk about the Holocaust in America after the war like that. I think it took a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 05:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow there's a lot of these. I found out a similar story about my grandmother.

In my opinion it's worse because my grandfather told my grandmother to get rid of her affair child. 

I know that logically a woman can abandon her child just as a man can but I feel like somehow it's way more cold hearted to abandon a child that comes out of your body and then never acknowledge that she exists. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 05:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found out that my grandmother had 2 children out of wedlock. 

My uncle (the oldest of 5 siblings) she had around the time my grandfather married her. He is not my grandfather's son. 

The second she had while my grandfather was in Korea at war. 

This kid was also not my grandfather's. However, because this kid was new my grandfather told her to get rid of it before he came back from the war or he wasn't coming back to her. 

Apparently she listened and gave this daughter to the father. 

What's worse is she then never ever acknowledged this girls existence. In fact if someone hadn't slipped up and told me about it, I would have ever known. 

Which explained why the oldest uncle (let's call him Ron) wasn't named after my grandfather. 

So my uncle Ron is first born (according to official family history) followed by my Mom (who has a female variant of my grandfather's name), my other uncle (Jr.), And then my two aunts. 

It also explains why my uncle Ron is like 6ft+, is skinny without trying, and everyone else is sub 5ft 11 and has weight issues. 

I already didn't like my family (they're world class assholes). But finding out that I have an aunt who my grandmother chooses to pretend doesn't even exist, really confirmed that they are shitty people. 

I mean, my grandfather is dead now, my grandmother is in her 80s. Everyone is an adult. Even if she just told everyone she's a cousin or something, I don't think at this juncture it would make anyone too upset. 

There's no reason why she couldn't just acknowledge her daughter a little bit. I spoke to my mystery aunt on the phone one day and she really seems to want to know her mother and that side of the family. 

Even tho she's well in her 60s. I'm sure she's made peace with it. But my god, even if I gave up a kid, I would like to think that I would at least sneak and acknowledge her existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 05:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's true. 

Other than the last person basically every other person that did it, I was like how am I even going to recoup that money. 

The most someone ever screwed me out of was $700. 

I thought about taking them to court but after I did the research I realized even small claims I'd have to out up $50 to file the suit. Then I'd probably have to do a bunch of legwork or pay someone to serve them the lawsuit. And in the end even if I got the money they owed all the hours of invest in it would eat up the money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 04:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'd fucking hurl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 04:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I used to be really nice about it and would let people pay in the end. 

But now, I make them pay me half upfront. 

Some people don't like that. They hate the idea of paying in advance. 

But the few times that people stiffed me wasn't worth it. 

Like I get it. 100$ isn't a lot but, I'm not just doing the work for fun, I've got bills to pay. 

And what's worse is I often buy things for the job. So someone wants a blog post with pictures, I pay for pictures from a service. Shit isn't free. But people act like cuz it's creative, it's free shit. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 04:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time I was eating in a McDonald's in NYC near 7th Ave and 34th. 

I had to pee but when I went to the women's room it was locked so I got my then boyfriend (now husband) to check that no one was in the men's room so I could go. There was no one so I went and came out. 

Now all the bathrooms were stall bathrooms so it was weird that the women's was locked. Anyway we go back to eating and talking. 

Some more women have to go to the bathroom so they go and ask the manager why the bathroom is locked. 

The manager comes up and unlocked the door and starts yelling. 

Then he pulls out this big black lady who's in like shorts and a tee-shirt with soap all over her body. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't know. My kid can't speak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Was very much stone cold sober. Like a responsible adult who wants to give their child the best possible start in life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if nothing else matters but the present then why shouldn't people kill themselves at the first sign of trouble. 

OP said why continue to live like the future matters. 

But if there is no afterlife, if my life sucks and will likely suck til i die. Why should I even try to keep living. 

Ex. If I have Cancer,l and fighting it would put my family in financial straits. Shouldn't I just kill myself and be done with it? If nothing matters. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miles better than anything on TV now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never supported trump but I after I saw those videos about all those small businesses who either failed or almost failed because of him stiffing them I realized I couldn't even vote for him just to block Hillary. 

I really don't like Hillary but I too am an independent contractor. And even tho the guys who have stiffed me only stiffed me on small amounts like $100 or so. That shit irks me big time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know, the IRS isn't going to ask a bunch of questions when he just starts paying taxes now. 

Not saying to jot file the back taxes, but having known quite a few people who either just lived off their parents or worked under the table and didn't do anything about it. The IRS doesn't come around asking why you weren't employed for X years. 

That being said. It would be smart to get ahead of it before there is some reason for them to come around asking about back income. 

IANAL but I don't believe that hidden income has a statute of limitation. So should he for some reason get audited at a later date and those years come up you could be in the shit. I'd speak to a tax attorney regardless and see what the best course of action was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the only thing I miss about NYC. In NY making the same income I make now I qualified for Medicaid. In NC I don't. It really sucks. 

But everything else is cheaper so it's not that bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I predict that in 10 years Phelps will have some kind of terrible scandal that makes everyone hate him. 

* Will it be a doping scandal? 
* Will it be a sex scandal like Penn state? 

Who knows all we know is that it'll be so much fun for this guy.


Edit: your down voting, but it is very likely. Cosby was the most liked comedian when I was a kid, now hes a rapist asshole. Lance Armstrong was  the greatest sports  hero when I was in high school, now hes a cheater. 

My motto is wait until they're dead. Usually by then the worst has come out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This old man can take some preferred seating in my ... Uh... Nevermind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New life goal. 

1. Get famous
2. talk about some shit I want
3. get free shit. 

I heard that Korn did this with ADIDAS but when ADIDAS didn't give them free shit they stopped wearing adidas and switched to puma. I think their main problem was that not many sports companies want their brand on a song called "All day i dream about sex"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fun fact: I was a woman. I drank Dr. Pepper and now i have a dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dedicated search. and the yellow pages. 

The internet was out when i was in high school but it was still very much the AOL dialup thing and I was vehemently opposed to the internet for some dumb ass reasons. 

I remember I wanted some clothes I had seen in a marilyn manson video. Like one of those biker dresses that zippers all down the front. Well, I didn't know where to go for shit like that. I went to the mall. I looked in the yellow pages, and since most of my friends were regular teens that were into more normal stuff, they didn't know. 

So i basically just gave up. Until I happened to be sitting outside of a diner and some guy walked past me wearing platform leather boots, with a his hair cut like the guy from Orgy and  some other weird shit on. 

I basically ran up and tackled the guy and asked him where he got the clothes. Some of it he had gotten in NYC but he mentioned that he got some at some store in the town. He said he'd show me where and we went to the place together. We ended up becoming pretty good friends and I got my kick ass biker dress. 

Now i just google shit. And I have no friends. Seems like I was right about the goddamned internet. It ruined everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also significantly harder to get a drivers license in many of these non American countries. 

Like I believe germany has some minimum limits for supervised instructor driving. The best I've seen for that is NYC which requires that for drivers under 18, but they also accept a parents letter or something. 

So we are also very lax on the driving licenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking more the damage that would come from some dick texting while driving. 

Regular car smashes into a house it's gonna get slowed by the lawn and things so it won't be so bad. 

Flying car smashes into a house. It's plowing right thru your young child's 2nd floor  bedroom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah cool. I only seen the ones that put black bars and words on your gif. Thats why I asked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What fictional technology seems like it would be awesome in theory but would have some really bad unforseen consequences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 07:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

 1. Company Name: Brush with Death

 2. Logo idea/ Inspiration for idea: something involving a hairstyling grim reaper

 3. Color scheme ( if any or feeling ): something respectful of the dead. Some black and periwinkle

 4. Company's message/ description of company: A beautician for corpses to present them for funerals

 5. Other information( some clients are picky ): Something fun and quirky maybe


Might prefer ps4 but either or is fine.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you use for the editing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
