<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1320</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 45 degree angle. Hallway landing area.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP'S - Washington Poltergeist [update ] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demons In Seattle Uncovered - Poltergeist Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 09:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't point anything.  The investigators did. It makes you wonder though. What's passing my the camera, in mid-air, close rang and one time for a few seconds blots out the entire screen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 02:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> camera was pointing 45 degree angle. To capture 1/2 wall, 1/2 ceiling.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21XE0cGKdmc  same hallway with EVP. EVP at 1:57 "Awhile" (requires headphones)  and https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_xt7GiGhlrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington State Poltergeist - Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 05:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 06:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you Jamalyja.  You did me a who favor.  I like how you believe or try to suggest Ghost Adventures own the proprietary  on Ghost Investigations.  In all actuality you make my argument for me.  Where a TV show failed, other paranormal teams including some from Scotland, the UK, Maryland and Massachusetts and even Seattle succeeded and the evidence is bar none.  There's a fundamental mental difference of fan dome which u clearly are and those with a true interests in the paranormal.  8 team, each individual of each other cant be wrong. 

I'll just leave these here.

Nick Kyle(Scotland).
https://soundcloud.com/don-philips-paranormal/dark-thirty-usa-radio-clip-keith-linder-case-april-2016

coasttocoast AM
http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist

Washington Poltergeist Case and Psychic Attorney Mark Anthony on After Hours AM/Americas Most Haunted Radio
http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/


part1
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VY8f_nI6taI

Part 2
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GdSMEL2duYM

part 3
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u9YVggTNWiA

mic drop

all more recent than your post.

I report. You decide.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bothell home haunted? Parapsychologists have proven it, resident says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 23:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 01:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same house, hours earlier.
https://youtu.be/_xt7GiGhlrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 01:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/_xt7GiGhlrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The laughing baby doll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_xt7GiGhlrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 06:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did u hear the EVP'S during the page movement?
3:52;  and 4:48 
Its asking for help and says YES at 4:48
[best with headsets on] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 06:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's a 3rd voice. Did u hear the EVP's. EVP: Class A at 3:52;  4:48 hard to hear "YES"? [WEAR HEADSETS, somethings there w/them] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP Spirit Turning Bible Pages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 19:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "show me how to" at 3:52 
Another BANG at 4:00. and a 
4:48 a soft/quick "YES"
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_pJLbMwP1w4

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haunted House EVP's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 07:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ovIrMEZ-GiY

APRIL 2016. [LISTENING 1ST WITH HEAD SETS IS BEST] Poltergeist - Demons In Seattle Uncovered EVP (1) " Uuuah I thought I saw it" at 2:07 , (2) 8:28 " Uuuah I thought I saw it" and lastly on VIDEO (3) 11:26 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 21:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah too bad. 6:49 "Go" is clearly heard. Others recently discovered include. Are  6:30 "No" at the very beginning :16  "Yeah" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont edit my videos, unless its grossly long content. That's why i inserted the time_stamp. U can skip to when the word is uttered "duh" .  if I get in the habit of editing, and condensing material thats where evidence gets faked and fabricated.  U have the time stamp of when the word will appear. IMO the nothing before and after is equally important. IMO

Thanks

at least i got u to admit to a "word" being mentioned. Thats progress

count the many words here
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TeHTpVqGn-g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP "Go" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 07:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JjXkF3JDLGg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Objects thrown in House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PFBtpo9OOU8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadow Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exorcist - EVP's caught during house exorcism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 02:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exorcist - EVP's caught during house exorcism 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TeHTpVqGn-g

House Exorcism as performed by Fr Roy of the Episcopal Church. July 11th 1pm 2015. As listed on the DemonsInSeattle Ghost Adventures show. Keith and Tina. Keith specifically has always sought the attention and help of local clergy. With ample preparation and viewing of all Keith's 2012-2015 evidence. The house exorcism was finally performed. Approval was given by both Keith and house owner as originally sought and stated. The night before the exorcism some activity was present. The all too familiar thumbs, heavy foot steps, wall taps and ceiling ping noises. Noises often linked to both Demon or Poltergeist Activity. This video is one of three that covered the Exorcism. To get a full account of some of the events in this house. Individuals should seek Ghost Adventures Episode 10 "DemonsInSeattle" "Yeah" :14 seconds, :36, :37 "Yeah" 6:16 "EVP sound" 6:27.785 "EVP Sound, female voice" 30:44 "They Lie"
1:24:19 "EVP?" "Yuck!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demons in Seattle - "Shadow Baby" ONE - February 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch "Haunted House - Shadow People" on YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 02:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 00:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one uses what one learns while growing up. There is no right, no wrong.  Its all a matter of belief and faith.  Some spirits respond to being cast out. Some don't. In the end it just boils down to your belief system and what you hold dear.  I've had atheist at my house in my van pool who after seeing the events in my house now question their own atheism. Just a matter of perspective. No need for anger.  Scientists that are reluctant to explore the paranormal are foolish unto themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP's caught during House Exorcism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 23:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/TeHTpVqGn-g
"Yeah"  :14 seconds, :36, :37 "Yeah" 6:16 "EVP sound" 6:27.785 "EVP Sound, female voice" 30:44 "They Lie"
1:24:19 "EVP?" "Yuck!"

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D4LSpekDtaE
5:51 Tic , 5:52:"EVP" , 6:15 "Magic?"  Priest asks to sit down and an EVP says 7:08 "No" Priest mentions I should keep a prayer book and an EVP utters the word 9:18 "Bible" ***  10:46 "Yeah" ****   12:08 "Sigh" ??? Inconclusive EVP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP "Find Me" https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cr-zZJIlebE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [EVP FIND ME 1:14 ]   Date in video is wrong. Attempts to correct prove futile:  Poltergeists!?      In this investigation Steve Mera (Parapsychologists) and chief researcher Don Philips trek from the UK and conduct a walk through and analysis of the home. To monitor them I put up Zoom H2 devices and other cams. Whats discovered later upon review is an unknown voice and origin "FIND ME" at 1:14. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 20:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, so why keep commenting.  And why the venom? ! Kylo ?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 00:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont mind someone not believing me. To each his or her own. I think with the amount of evidence presented by me and vouched by others for some to still disbelieve is actually quite fun. Its almost equally interesting as this case. Exposes a lot.  I mean this is a paranormal forum and by it being a forum, the trolls are going to admit themselves in.  If truth staring at you in the face and u still dont believe what other reason could it be?  Esp in a community titled Paranormal. Your logic betrays you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TAKE YOUR RACISM SOMEWHERE ELSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP at 1:14 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 09:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell.  You keep responding.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadow Baby" ONE - February 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 03:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 01:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this not a paranormal community? I ask the question again. Why are you hear?  Is for answers?  Do u have something to offer in regards to ghosts? demons, spirits, entities, orbs, poltergeists? etc? You say I should leave.  I'm doing the basic of communication I'm reporting an experience that over the past few months has received ample investigation from two continents. Me go away?   I'm just getting started with the sharing of info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 00:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where's your evidence?
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RdRT3qYMi7U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Para-Skeptic

You're denying the most common sense of all which is this has been going on for four years. No team from either the east coast or the UK and Scotland is going to trek 10,000 miles for a hoax. Let alone come back again for a 2nd and 3rd time which some teams have done.

I dont know what you're relationship is to the paranormal field, and I dont care. But its obvious you dont trust or value the opinion and insight from the likes of other paranormal individuals who've came and gone from this house.  Steve Mera 30+ years paranormal and paraschological experience and background. SPS, the SSPR, Niki Unparanormal and countless others, Don Philips.

These people all independant of each other have already sustantiated my claims that this house is haunted. What perplex them now is why.

They've interviewed the previous tenants. Fr. Roy a priest has come and gone and assisted. Local news have come and seen and heard the activity. If you dont trust or believe these countless people who have nothing to gain by perpetrating a fraud or hoax then there's nothing else to talk about.

I've posted video where un-known voice phenomena takes places. I've posted video and audio of intelligent voice phenomena and you're still thinking with your arms folded.

STOP EXPECTING THE HOLY GRAIL OF EVIDENCE WHICH IS - you want to see an object levitate or fly across the room. That's not going to happen and thats not the measure of true evidence. While exciting to watch that can easily be created with the up most cheapest editing software.

I feel like Han Solo talking to Princess Leia in ESB "what do you like?"

a lot of skeptics i run and come in contact with have trust issues, benefit of the doubt issues which doesnt mean you cant be objective. But you run the risk of being overly objective which leads to blindess intellectually.

previous tenants, home owner, myself, countless paranormal teams, Priests, friends, family and others all cant be wrong. Its not an orchestrated conspiracy or concerted effort some of you think I'm trying to make by bringing u this info. I'm just sharing my experience. It matters not what you believe in to be honest.

but your not being honest with yourself.  You're taking pride in being a skeptic while at the same time hindering your own intellectual curiosity and basic common sense.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b9pVNMyUG58

EVP's caught
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IvEfxeDy3nI
:23 "Yeah"
:52, :53 something blows on the mic and at
:54 EVP voice is heard 
1:32 "Yeah"
"blah blah blah blah "semantics....I didn't fall" ??? begins at 1:47 ends at 1:53

Scientific Establishments official report upon leaving Seattle the 1st time.
https://app.box.com/s/93o3vk8o5i52225lpb686rudo9ikwfg3

"Hello" House crawl space
https://app.box.com/s/944qbngm2hyv066nic65115a7ifg89wi

Hallway/Landing area
"I hear springs"
https://app.box.com/s/6ni6ri5b070xr9bb3uuxm0ckgqdzdf1g

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u-UTd37duCQ
6:35 "Hey" is heard

Shadows
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pTzB7pWLJ3M

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbGRj3YU4YM
EVP at 18:10

tons more stuff at
https://www.facebook.com/Washington-State-Poltergiest-House-705963559540294/

Investigators Talk about their findings
http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist

https://soundcloud.com/don-philips-paranormal/dark-thirty-usa-radio-clip-keith-linder-case-april-2016

http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/


if none of this moves you then nothing will.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dan

I've posted reports from various teams on Reddit. I've shared videos, audio, interview footage and recounts from both witness and investigator. If you're still in doubt its because you chose to be in doubt.  But I believe in giving people benefit of the doubt so I will try with you one more time. Its up to you to utilize the links below. Outside of that I need not convince anyone else. I will continue to release the findings of those assisting me as well has publish the final report from S.E.P.  Until then feel free to do what ever u wish the info provided below.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b9pVNMyUG58

EVP's caught
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IvEfxeDy3nI
:23 "Yeah"
:52, :53 something blows on the mic and at
:54 EVP voice is heard 
1:32 "Yeah"
"blah blah blah blah "semantics....I didn't fall" ??? begins at 1:47 ends at 1:53

Scientific Establishments official report upon leaving Seattle the 1st time.
https://app.box.com/s/93o3vk8o5i52225lpb686rudo9ikwfg3

"Hello" House crawl space
https://app.box.com/s/944qbngm2hyv066nic65115a7ifg89wi

Hallway/Landing area
"I hear springs"
https://app.box.com/s/6ni6ri5b070xr9bb3uuxm0ckgqdzdf1g

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u-UTd37duCQ
6:35 "Hey" is heard

Shadows
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pTzB7pWLJ3M

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbGRj3YU4YM
EVP at 18:10

tons more stuff at
https://www.facebook.com/Washington-State-Poltergiest-House-705963559540294/

Investigators Talk about their findings
http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist

https://soundcloud.com/don-philips-paranormal/dark-thirty-usa-radio-clip-keith-linder-case-april-2016

http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/


if none of this moves you then nothing will.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 05:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why are you here,....why?"  

~ Khan - star trek 2 wrath of khan 1982 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 05:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow...a true troll with the curse words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es  good evps here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the only educational response you're able to muster from the video?  Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry Para you're a skeptic by choice. Bad choice at that.  Its ok to be a skeptic but to be a skeptic and deny common sense - thats not OK.  With every evidence provided there's always going to be that human element. You want this. You want that. You want your evidence all wrapped up in a little bow before you commit to simply just believing.
Well guess what its not always going to be wrapped up in a bow. The EVP in this video is a voice talking underneath both myself and Don. The beginning of the video show Steve with his back turned sitting in the kitchen. The voice is close to the mic( for lack of a better understanding) which by definition makes this video paranormal. Only three men in the house. Two of those men are in the hallway. The voice says "SLOW" at :28 seconds and " a while" at 1:57 interjecting itself into our conversation, answering my question except for the minor detail of Don and I can't hear it. The "a while" was captured later upon review of both video and audio.


Its through diligent research and diligent investigation that stuff like this gets uncovered and I'm glad i belong now to group of men and women who are diligent about discovering it.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned as I was going through this. Some, not all. Paranormal Investigators subscribe to a ratings scale of EVP. Class A EVP is for lack of a better word a top notch EVP. The vocals are clear, concise, requires little translation-almost a true real vocal.  The different classes I'm told are Class A thru C, and D. Majority of the EVP's discovered in this HOUSE are Class A or above. Don Philips has coined the term AVP. Actual Voice Phenomena. When you have an AVP you are hearing voice without need of an electronic device.  You hear it, as if a human was talking in addition the voice recorder captures it.  Im giving loose terms and definitions, as told to me by the multiple teams have ventured into my house. Go back and listen to :28 seconds.  Tell us what you hear. I wont spoil it for you as it was just written on the YouTube comments section found by someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also check out :28 seconds   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 05:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm of the same opinion. See if u still hold that opinion after you hear it.   Class A or above that opinion doesn't really apply. But I get and understand where you are coming from?

if u doubt. share the link, download it and have someone neutral hear it.

Share your results here.


0 static! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist Investigation - Demons In Seattle Uncovered NEW EVP 1:57 " a while" is heard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 03:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21XE0cGKdmc

EVP at 1:57 "Awhile"

Steve Mere and Don Philips came to the house in Bothell WA last January. Spent 6 days. Captured and are still compiling and analyzing 430+ EVPS. Many Class A. This is one recently discovered by me. I in monitoring their work, asking questions when a question arose did film some of their work as means of having a thought experiment. I believe and more EVPs are coming soon that support that belief that these spirits dont flee from investigators and researchers. The do the opposite. Many of the EVPs captured so far and confirmed as an EVP point to the fact these entities have a curiosity about the equipment used to investigate them. This video is just one example of that.  I soon will be sharing more EVP's off my devices. Devices I used as I shadowed these great researchers.  I was proven right as both voice recorder and hand held camcorder all have EVP'S on them.  I promise you no static.  HD EVP coming soon.  THIS AND WHAT STEVE AND DON AND S.E.P have and will share soon will show......the true level of activity i.e. intelligence that occupies this house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Para-skeptic

Interesting name BTW. Skeptic huh? Till the day you die?

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21XE0cGKdmc

Truck loads of EVP's are coming.

Oh man  truck loads 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
