<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8579</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 02:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was about 8 my mum was telling me a story about a rough time during her child hood that involved her dad being borderline alcoholic. At the end of the story, I proceeded to say 'I wouldn't of gone to his funeral.'
 I just remember the look of pure heartbreak on my mum's face and the tears starting to build in her eyes, I had never felt such guilt before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 02:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn how to spell and you may get more up votes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice repost, I posted this exact same post about a month ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devoted wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 10:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A devoted wife spent a lifetime taking care of her husband. He had been slipping in and out of a coma for several months, yet she stayed by his bedside every single day. When he came to his senses he motioned for her to come near.

As she say by him he said "you know what? you have been with me through all the bad times. when I got fired, when my business failed, when I got shot, when we lost the house, when my business started failing, you were always there to support me and you know what?"

"What my dear?"

"Your a fucking jinx" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 22:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my best friends mother, can confirm allergy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 13:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about my media teacher, Not to bad, but it pissed me of big time! 

So my English and media class shared the same class room which had only one display bored in the whole room. As a part of my coursework for my English class I was asked to design a display for the display board for an open evening. So for a whole day I get permission to skip classes to work on it, it took me whole day as it was pretty big. However I could not find any glue or staples and so needed up just sticking the work up with blue tack until the next day when I could hopefully, attach it up properly. 

Next day, my first class is media. Teacher comes in and gives us work to do. We set about it and as we're about half way through I start to see some of my display work landing on the desk. I look up and see my media teacher taking down all the work I spent all day putting up an arranging neatly, as well as taking down the boarder and paper back I used as a base for the board! At this point me and my friends are just starting gob smaked as they knew how long it took me! 

I proceed to tell her and all he turns around and says is "well I needed this board for my media display" bear in mind however that pretty much the whole room except one wall is covered in work from past media students as well as a whole load of media related displays! To make it work she them took some of her own media work from her bag as well as a glue stick and glued it to the board! 

I was so pissed, I told my English teacher who was also head of the English and media department, she had a word and me and some friends we're aloud to take it down and start my board again. The subject was never brought up again but I did start receiving a lot of dirty looks and snappy responses from my media teacher for the rest of the year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 01:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still in shock of him having twitter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 11:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A jar as in slightly open  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is a door not a door? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 00:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's a jar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 00:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I do find this image rather amusing (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 00:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 01:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes cut it! You will look older and your face may look less rounded plus I think it will really suit you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most common birth dates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 17:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 11:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm maybe I have Russian blood in my genes... I do like the cold  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 10:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extra ticket booked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 10:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booking my flight :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 10:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am exactly like this and constantly get asked if I'm ok at work and university, I try not to do the face by when I'm concentrating or just relaxed it's a natural thing, so annoying!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry and Ginny post hogwarts battle fanfiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 22:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to find a good one :) anyone got any recommendations? :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no over the board gestures? I guess I can do that haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god I never even thought of a present, it would probably be a good icebreaker to. Defiantly going to look into this, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great advice, Thanks :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can assure you I am not a terrible person haha I know I should stay calm and stuff but whether this actually happens is another thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pointers on meeting parents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm meeting my boyfriend (of 3 months) parents for the first time tomorrow, having a meal at his place before heading to a presentation evening for his rugby team. I guess I'm just really nervous! What the hell do I talk about? What do I do when I can tell they don't like me? In awkward moments? I really need advice here and have you got any personal experiences where things have gone ok?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's something about Rodrigo Santoro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 01:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 01:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean :')  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 00:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously haha I may give this a go :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 22:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smooth haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 21:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Compliment his majestic beard' haha made me laugh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you compliment a man? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 20:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female here, I find it awkward when trying to compliment a guy and it figured it's because I don't know how, no matter how wonderful I think they are. I always end up calling them 'nice' but I saw the post on here a couple of weeks ago saying guys don't like that so how exactly should we do it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 01:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We' e tried the swatting but that just makes her want to play more because she thinks we're playing along. I like the spray bottle idea though, I think I will try this :) thanks for your suggestion :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has toys and the one with the stick and feathers is her favourite, she does cuddle but only when she is sleepy or she thinks we aren't giving her enough attention haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat keeps biting and scratching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started a week after we got her when she was 6 weeks old and I blamed it on her age, she was just playing, teething didnt know any better, but now she is older (12 weeks) it's getting a bit too rough, in her mind she is still playing but it's not fun for us anymore. We have tried shouting and snaking her on the nose every time and for a few of my family members it had worked but she still continues to bite and scratch me and my brother.

Have any of you got any advice on how we can stop her? Any special teething toys we can get her?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hug me like a banna hugs his friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 14:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 16:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, I was one of these kids. The chances are they are probably just shy so when you have set everyone to work and no one is really paying attention to anything else around them, go up to the person and ask if they have any questions. That way they wont worry about sounding 'stupid' in front of there classmates and they will have your full attention to get a real answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Respecting him for this one - David Cameron 'A small island' speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 23:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 02:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not sleeping tonight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 03:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were you, I would way up the pros and cons of telling her and not telling her and think about both the actions and consequences of your decision. E.g. If you told her and she didn't feel the same way, how is that going to effect your relationship with her, do you really want to put that kind of strain on it? Will you be able to work past it and just carry on as before? 
Really consider every pro's and con's with care.

If you decide to tell her, great! Well done for gathering up the courage, she will admire you for that. 

Good luck :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 02:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have literally just done this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 22:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it wants you to buy Febreze :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 14:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm so sorry :( I love this little cat more than anything in the world and I have only had her 4 weeks and would be lost without her so i cant imagine a loss after 17 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Her favourite place to sleep, in my arms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 15:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 12:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I do this? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 03:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I wasn't patronising! I'm Bristish to, so please keep your comments to yourself and learn stuff before making them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 02:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am loveing all the Britishness in these comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sims 3 worlds for free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 23:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone give me the links to download the different worlds for the sims 3? e.g. sunlit tides? I would really appreciate it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sims 3 worlds for free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 23:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone give me links for the different worlds in the sims 3 e.g. Sunlit tides etc? I would really appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 02:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You freaked me the hell out but I want to hear the rest :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phases of Aaron Johnson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 04:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you just buy a magnetic bottle opener and a small double sided magnet and put them on the fridge? It eliminates the need of tools! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 03:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more with this statement! I love her!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 23:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seamus Finnegan, the things I would do to that Irish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 19:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I read Rowling's profile on him on potter more and utterly fell in love!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me to, I'm only up to 83 so far but I can't get enough of it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
