<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 08:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melo, Paul Pierce and Derrick Rose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 10:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason Witten. We would convert 100% of all third down plays! /s

To be honest I'd have to say Sean Lee. (inb4 yeah so you have a spare if he gets injured) but Sean Lee is considered by a lot of people to be one of the top LBs in the NFL, and if you have two of him? Oh boy. 

Close second is Dez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distributing some free literature.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 02:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *raises hand* 

The Cowboys are definitely my number one, but I also root for the:

Patriots - I love Brady and BB. I mostly root for them because there's a lot of Bills fans in my town and I like seeing them upset. 

Raiders - My Taekwondo master is a die hard Raiders fan, and he was a big part of my life growing up. 

Jaguars - I like /u/JaguarGator9 

Ravens - Ed Reed was one of my favorite players growing up. Same with Jamal and Ray Lewis. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 08:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know Lena Headey from Game of Thrones and I like her a lot in that. I've never seen The Sarah Connor Chronicles, what was bad about Lena in that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Christ it's absolutely unbearable in Central New York. I live on Lake Ontario about a half hour from Syracuse and you'd think we were living in rural Oklahoma.

The funny thing is I see the opposite. A lot of the people in my town that are "rednecky" are usually Bills or Steelers fans. 

We also have a worryingly large population of Raiders fans for being on the east coast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The guilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you feel guilty for trying to better yourself? 

I do. Every day. 

I try and exercise. Play guitar. Play video games. Hang out with friends. I try and do everything I used to do that used to put me in a better mood. 

But when I eventually get into a better mood and I see some of my friends, or co workers, or even my parents they all make me feel like the biggest piece of shit in the world for it. 

They say, "You're in a good mood today, I guess you're cured huh?" Or "I guess that mental breakdown at work was just for attention, I saw you on SnapChat having a good time the other night." Or (my favorite) "You only go to counseling so you get a free day off every week." 

But that's the thing. They only see the good moments. And those are few and far in between. 

They don't see me staying in bed motionless until I can get the energy to even brush my teeth. 

They don't see me struggle. 

They don't see me. 

Maybe they do, who knows. I feel like a lot of people I know are in denial about it because I never used to be this way. 

It doesn't matter. 

I'm getting help, and I'm getting the fuck out of this town once I'm better. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY! There's only one shit down corner in the NFL and that's Mo Claiborne :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That her eating disorder is going to be with her for the rest of her life. It's going to be a struggle. This might not be the last time she has to go halfway across the country for treatment. It could kill her if it gets bad enough and there are times when she wont even look at me because she's having a relapse. 

But I love her, and I'll do anything for her. We'll get through it together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 09:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me personally? 2014 when we went 12-4 and lost to the Packers. 

I specifically loved the Colts game because I didn't think our offense could go off like that. 

Runner up season is 2007. I saw the Cowboys v Bills game in Buffalo when Folk made the two field goals to win it (the first one was iced). 

But everything changed when the Giants attacked :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 08:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might be looking for this lmao

https://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/4tazs1/rnfl_roast_of_the_new_york_jets/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 08:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jackson will honestly be a player I tell my kids about. He was great. Loved watching him play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 08:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Harrison. And I think of this whenever I see his name 

https://youtu.be/kEgNKAR-L24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ. That's two different sports now where a fax machine has ruined everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. And then the Kings sign a wacky defensive minded coach and his brother that also happens to be a wacky defensive minded coach. 

So I guess they're getting the Van Gundys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 17:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has to be the 2007 season team. We went 13-3 and set the record for most pro bowl players on one team with 12(?). Good times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 02:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a Texas Sized 10-4. 

That's what I really appreciates about you. 

MENERGY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 21:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Sean Bean was the perfect Ned Stark. 

Dinklage is also probably the best choice for Tyrion as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 21:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 1 year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 01:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 - Bobby B

2 - Bronn

3 - Robb

4 - Oberyn

5 - Davos

6 - Jon Snow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That nobody is going to support you the entire time. 

What I mean is that there are people in this world that will think depression is "all in your head" and will simply dismiss your problems. 

Then there are people that understand depression and try to help you through it. 

Eventually, everyone in the second group is going to get frustrated and leave you. 

:/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wildcard VS Atlanta

Divisional VS Carolina

Conference VS Eagles

Super Bowl VS Denver

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 21:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House Brule

"Check it Out" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 06:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clippers, Knicks, Hawks. Prolly the Sixers and Timberwolves too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the NFL equivalent of Kevin Durant going to the Warriors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 07:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 05:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25% of all people that die between the ages of 16-24 die from suicide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Did you call bank?"

"I called Retirement!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even a word and I agree with ya!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 22:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly due to the fact he missed all of last year...but Orlando Scandrick is a pretty good corner. Idk if he's top 10 or 15, but he's without a doubt the best on Dallas (not that that's too hard to do).

Another one would be Doug Free. He's the "worst" of the five o linemen but he's the glue that keeps them together. 

I miss football.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 10:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Landry, Roger Staubach, Drew Pearson and Tony Dorsett clear all round 10/10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 17:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Christian Laettner missed winning a chip with the Heat by one year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 03:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aikman has every right to be in the Hall of Fame and the people that say he doesn't have no idea what they're talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 21:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ones that I feel have been forgotten are: 

Bradie James. 

Flozell Adams. 

Andre Gurode. 

Greg Ellis. 

Julius Jones (even though he wasn't spectacular) 

Terry Glenn. 

These are the guys I remember watching as a kid and I feel like I never hear their names anymore. Not even from fellow Dallas fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 20:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Wings because of Dr Cox from Scrubs. 

Clippers because of Blake Griffin. 

Yankees because I live in Central New York but I don't really watch baseball. 

As far as College sports I had family that went to SU and Michigan so I root for those two teams. Plus I'm about 30 minutes from the Dome so SU is basically my home team. 

I've been rooting for Djoker in tennis since before he was in the top ten. Probably my favorite athlete of all time. 

NASCAR is Jeff Gordon and now that he's retired I root for Kasey Kahne (met him over the summer, great guy). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 18:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had a nickel for every time I've heard Jamele Hill say "Quit trollin' dog" I'd be the owner of the Dallas Cowboys. She's awful. Almost as bad as Aisha Tyler at E3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 09:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know you. But I imagine you are walking bag of feces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad still thinks we're going to get AP somehow..it's embarrassing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 00:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rooms collarbone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 22:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't like losing THAT much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 22:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick Goings?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected it as well due to the fact that PS3 allowed it. At first you could share digital games with as many consoles as you wanted so long as your account was on them. I remember I got a bunch of my friends in middle school into the Bad Company 2 Closed Beta that way. A few years later they lowered it to 2 or 3 consoles per account. 

Considering digital downloads are more popular now than they were ~2008/2009 I shouldn't have been surprised that they stopped allowing people to do that. I remember my PS3 had more games on it that weren't mine than games that actually were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McNabb and Bledsoe. Two guys that were top QBs for their franchises for years that made it to the big game but never won it. They also put up good stats but were never considered the top QBs in the league.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 16:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say Lynch was a bust for Buffalo. He had two 1000 yard seasons and averaged 4 YPC and even had a pro bowl IIRC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 06:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I don't see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 15:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like Pat Angerer. You just want guys with cool names to do well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 06:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. First session is Thursday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 23:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night when I told him I was going to start going to counseling again due to depression and suicidal thoughts. He told me to "just get over it" and "not make a big deal out of nothing." 

Thanks Dan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised he didn't try to trip Anybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Be nice to Cruz!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 02:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Cowboys

* Patriots

* Eagles

* Packers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 06:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. I meant Pre NE v PHI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 04:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best - 49. The Butler pick is my favorite moment of any super bowl I've seen (keep in mind I don't remember any post NE v PHI) 

Worst - Ehhh I'm not sure. I enjoy every super bowl. I guess I'd have to say 48 just because it was a blowout but I still enjoyed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 03:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really excited to see what he can do. I'm not sure on his ceiling because I'm not very educated as far as how skills translate to the NBA so I have one question: 

How good of a prospect is he? I know he's apparently one of the best in the past few years but does anyone have any comparisons for me? Is he a player that a coach can build a team around around him like AD or Blake? 

EDIT: I realize now that I asked 3 questions lmao. Sorry about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 12:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady in 2008. They went 11-5 with Cassel, I wonder what would've happened if Brady never got hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only ever seen highlight reels (and the 3 Duper Bowl wins) for the Triplets. How good were they back in the day and who would they compare to now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 14:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Romo stays healthy and has an All Pro season like in 2014 OR Romo gets injured and the Dak Attack plays well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 03:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know a lot about players from before the 90's, but these are the ones I think would dominate if they played today:

Marino - It's a full on passing league now. I feel like he'd be putting up numbers similar if not better than Prime Manning. 

Deion Sanders - He would still be able to shut down any receiver in the game IMO. Think Revis with Patrick Peterson athleticism (but even better). 

Barry Sanders - Put him on an Oline like Green Bay, Washington or Dallas and he would take over seasons, let alone games.

Bo Jackson - Probably the most physically gifted player of all time, you could realistically place him anywhere and he'd kill it. 

Jerry Rice - Best footwork, hands, and IQ in a wide receiver ever. Plus he can use gloves now and doesn't have to worry about stickum /s but seriously he would do great. 

Players that have played recently that I think would do amazing:

Brian Urlacher - He had the pass coverage skills of a safety and is one of the best tacklers of all time. Place him anywhere honestly.

Watt, James Harrison, Suggs, Burfict, Suh - Place them in the 70's and people would probably die. 

I'll think of more later probably. Just got off work and I'm a little fried. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. But I would rather have Peterson. One elite tackle isn't going to turn your offense into a force. Most of the years with Minnesota Peterson was the only weapon and he STILL but up monster numbers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can buy a Wentz jersey if he wants!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obsessive Compulsive Personality Disorder. I was diagnosed my senior year of high school. When I tell people they look at my like a have six heads. I either get one of three responses,"You don't look like you have anything wrong with you." NO SHIT! It's a mental disorder you uncultured twit. Or I get,"You should hang out with me and do X, it'll cure you." No. No it won't. Or,"Huh, you're lucky, I wish I had a little voice in my head that made me work harder." NO! NO YOU FUCKING DON'T! It's torture. No matter what I do I have to do it right. Whether I'm at work, playing a video game, playing guitar or even getting ready for bed. If I even mess up a little bit I go into panic mode. I'm constantly asking questions and bothering my coworkers, I never get things done on time because I spend so long making sure every little detail is checked. I double, triple, sometimes quadruple check my work all day every day. 

It's not fun. It's not glamorous. Whenever I see someone out and about or on social media and they say something like,"I always have Oreos with my milk. it's just my OCD haha." No. Shut the fuck up. If you really had OCD or OCPD you wouldn't be laughing about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though I was only a toddler, I would've loved to see what Dallas could've done with Randy Moss. Greg Ellis was good but Moss is Moss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We call that 'Running through the Okra patch.'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 22:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dez caught it ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 05:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get that thing I sent ya?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 15:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winslow, Gonzalez, Sharpe, Witten. 

Honorable mention to Gronk. I'll bump Witten off of the list of Gronk continues his level of production because I think Gronk can end up as the best ever. Heresy I know, but the problem with Witten is that Gonzalez and Gronk (and also Gates) are highlight reel level tight ends while Witten is a master work horse. I love Witten and think he is one of the best ever, I'd definitely take him over Gates but he's more of a (for lack of a better term) Emmitt Smith / Art Monk sort of player. Not really flashy but his consistence and hard work knows no bounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 15:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. I love Fitzy to death but I would take Megatron over him any day of the week and twice on Sunday's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I'd say elite defense matters a lot more in the NFL too. Especially when it comes to playoff time. The past four years both super bowl teams had top defenses and it's usually the better defense that wins the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always use Skype!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 21:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whiskey + Coffee brings out the wildcat offense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oswego native here. Can confirm. Fuck the weather. 

40 degrees Monday. Rain all day Wednesday. 83 degrees yesterday. Windy as hell today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/d51Rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cry. A lot. I don't want to be ten again and wait two years before my dad gets custody of me. 

:(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 06:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was awful. 

https://youtu.be/umDr0mPuyQc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 19:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because Welker is white. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I was high when I said that!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 04:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How good Dez Bryant and Romo are. 

It's not a big deal and I understand it's in part because they were both injured last year but Dez led the league in TD receptions the two years before last and Romo had an MVP level season in 2014. Hopefully they come back even better this season!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 03:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome response! Thanks a bunch! :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently been getting back into playing guitar and just discovered this subreddit so I'm not exactly sure how much info in my ability I should add to ask a question like this but here it goes:

What songs should I learn on acoustic that are simple but sound complex? I've been playing a lot of Elliot Smith and Conor Oberst if that helps at all. 

Also: what's a good low budget acoustic guitar? The one I'm using is a hand me down from my sister and it plays fine but I'm looking to get a new one soon but I'm not looking to spend much more than $150. 

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot we signed Thornton. What should I expect of him this season? I know nothin about him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 22:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellowship of the Ring  Two Towers  Return of the King. 

That's not to say FOTR and TT aren't amazing, but ROTK is one of the greatest movies off all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Final Cut by Pink Floyd. The raw emotion in Waters' voice is haunting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Cowboys, Clippers and Red Wings...and I live in Syracuse... 

Dad and Uncles are Dallas fans.

I love Blake Griffin and didn't really watch too much NBA until he was drafted 

Dr Cox from Scrubs is a Red Wings fan, I chose them when I was 10 years old because of him and haven't wavered since.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 09:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paging /r/WhoWouldWin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 03:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rodgers

Brady

Brees

Big Ben

Wilson

Romo

Rivers

Eli

Ryan

Newton

I guess. I'm drunk so I could probably may have missed some of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he's using the puppy as a silencer a la Postal 2

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ehb-gbuo0Zs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that the rumor of us trading Leary and a pick to get another second comes true. There are still some studs available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After he was drafted Rapapport said he should be fully recovered by 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'M ACTUALLY SUPER EXCITED! OH MY GOD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of scouts don't see him as that great of a prospect. Not to say he's gonna be bad, but there are a lot more players that are better than him, mainly on defense. Factor in the fact that HBs are lasting fewer years than in the past and the fact that Henry is more of a "north-south" runner, nobody wanted to use a first on him. 

He'll definitely be picked today though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tears In Heaven by Eric Clapton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great song but I think Ive personally listened to it too much. I get annoyed whenever I hear it now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 03:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOW! Tunsil is dropping like an anvil in a looney tunes cartoon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 03:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/ZX2ue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 02:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME!? ARE YOU SERIOUSLY FUCKING KIDDING ME!? WHATS THE FUCKING POINT OF SIGNING MORRIS IN THE OFFSEASON IF YOU'RE JUST GOING TO FUCKING DRAFT A ZEKE!? 

COME. THE. FUCK. ON. 

I DONT CARE IF EVERY PICK AFTER THIS IS THE BEST AVAILABLE CORNER OR SAFETY IN THE DRAFT! I DONT CARE IF ZEKE ENDS UP BEING PHENOMANAL AND RAMSEY ENDS UP BEING TERRIBLE! I WILL EAT MY WORDS IF THAT ENDS UP HAPPENING BUT FOR THE TIME BEING IM FUCKING LIVID. 

GOD. FUCKING. DAMMIT. 

Edit: Now that I've taken 48 seconds to cool down I will be honest and say I am excited to see what he can do behind our line. I just really think CB is a bigger need. But if we're looking for immediate impact and trying to make our offense as efficient (or even more efficient) than 2014 I agree with the ZEKE pick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 02:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please please please draft Ramsey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how well received Madden is here. But I always pick him up out of free agency and he always turns into a monster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that happens I hope it ends up like the Joe Buck Show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 12:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically when I said "your friends all talked to her to" i meant "your friends take her to go to sleep/help with allergies/ perpetuate other drugs." The sex was when I finally decided to trip in DPH and realized its best to be used as the former. Lmao.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 08:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably in the minority but I enjoy going to shows while on opiates. I saw Oceano on 40mg of OxyContin and Cannibal Corpse on 30mg of OxyCodone plus 200MG of tramadol.

The only shitty thing was after the CC show I ate Taco Bell (Amateur mistake I know) and ended up throwing up the entire trip home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 07:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daphne is a girl that blends in with the furniture, so to speak. She's very plain on the outside. But you eventually become friends and talk to her multiple nights a week and realize she's actually interesting. You try to talk to your friends about her and realize that they've all been talking to her too, nothing serious however, she's just a very insightful girl with a lot to say about a lot of things. 

Your friends tell you there's something...different about her. But you don't care. You love talking to her anyway. She's always got great advice and accepts you for who you are. Whenever you talk to her she always seems to make your mood better. 

Eventually you fall for her and decide to hang out. Your first date is just dinner and a movie and it goes surprisingly well, you realize she's different in person. She doesn't talk as much and doesn't seem very interested, but that's not enough to give up on the future relationship yet. 

A few dates later you invite her over to your place. You turn on a movie and cuddle on the couch just enjoying each other's company. You start to think your friends were wrong. Daphne is a great girl, everyone's opinion is stupid. You start to really like her. 

You decide to take a step further and go all the way. The sex was bad and almost makes it not worth the wait, she completely changed afterward. She became verbally and mentally abusive . You're extremely disappointed and realize that even though you love being around her that a committed relationship probably won't work out. 

So you decide to break it off but still remain in contact. Once every few months you hook up again and feel great, but then you remember how she treated you and reel away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was eye strain that eventually turned into a headache. I went on break and had a glass of water and after about 45 minutes I was fine. 

As far as the OEVs being similar they were but they were a lot more noticeable today. I'm alright now though. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it normal to have open eye visuals the day after taking MDA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all. Yesterday I did about 100mg of MDA around 4 in the afternoon. I'm at work now and in the past thirty minutes I've noticed my peripheral vision is sort of cloudy/wavy. It's gotten to the point where my eyes strain when I wear my glasses. Is that to be expected? I've only done MDA a handful of times and don't remember anything like this happening before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't stop Kobe from making money after his scandal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I completely blanked on that. I'm thinking the combo would be fun for the first couple hours or so but once the body load and vasoconstriction got too much I think it would become dreadful. Probably just gonna get some bud instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao yeah, it's fun to see it live for me personally. We usually have one TV set up with the draft and the other TV with my PS4 connected. We'll probably play Madden or Rocket League and have the draft on in the backround.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
