<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4427</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US governments ethics tsar has been bombarded with requests since Trump became president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Everything that liberals embrace as progress and positive social change is viewed by Trump's supporters as proof that the world is leaving them behind. And that's a scary enough proposition, they are willing to elect a deranged orangutan to the highest office in the land." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Maher Broke Down Why Trump Voters Will Never Be Convinced with Facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 Final Fantasy Characters Who Almost Looked Completely Different </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's chaotic first 100 days summed up in 33 cartoons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can purchase a Nikon D7100, for about the same price as the D5600. It is a older, but more well rounded camera.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late night tackles Trump's first 100 days in hilariously condensed videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump doesnt talk like other presidents. Would he be a better president if he did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Fox News poll, only 36 percent of voters would re-elect President Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: Priebus made 'big push' on health care vote but came up short </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commentary: Donald Trump's lies are working brilliantly. This new poll proves it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House votes to avert government shutdown  for one week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both pretty comparable. Canon lenses tend to be a little cheaper. Nikons tend to win on "stats" like dynamic range, MP, ect. I honestly would pick the one that your friends have so you can always share lenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
