<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See you may confuse bad people with decisions of the entire conservative objective. Being a Conservative to me is about doing what works and making those things better, many things are of a value basis for us, the Liberal agenda is about being open to things just for the sake of doing whatever people want, without realizing many peoples opinions are shit. Just because someone has an opinion does not make it worth a single cent. 
Like abortion and legalizing all things for the sake of giving people a decision, I should not have to tell people not to go pick up tar off the road and eat it,  as soon as you tell someone not to do it, now everyone wants to do it cause they saw a buddy do it. Naturally when a few kids die they make it illegal, then you have a mass of dumbasses with signs saying legalize road tar for recreation, compile a lot of pseudo data to support the agenda, completely oblivious to ACTUAL science.  

Thats kind of what I think when I hear Liberal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't realize their capabilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VPN exit nodes in most countries still fall under local laws and collect all kind of user data. Its only good to get around blocks, but as far as safety, yeahhh right. If they have interest in someone, they will tag and track even VPN data, easily. Like if an exit node is in France, go read french internet laws. 

If the VPN company is American they could still totally be tracking and saving all data. If you cant trust things already set up, why do people think they can trust third party companies with privacy? Whats to say there are no set up systems designed to trick people with security? All the while thats how people have been getting caught.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a very Liberal thing to do....you know, open minded to change, total liberal thing to support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They already collect much of this data through your email being logged into google while searching along with various other examples. Soon as you buy something on a computer you will forever get promotions for similar items. Opera Add blocker works pretty well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted something on Reddit....Bam, instant Karma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably still got filmed and payed per the contract details. Kind of pointless people who are living well get paid to go out and "survive" when they could have paid people who are barely surviving to survive better, man what a world we got going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have even been pasteurized, for your safety, of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point of dressing provocative to attain sexual attention is of one spectrum, as to loving the aesthetic nature of an outfit or whatever to the other spectrum, of many. I think we should all feel empowered and comfortable to be fully nude, thats true freedom. People will dislike a modest outfit, a provocative outfit, a fully nude image, so really it comes down to this. 
What really finalizes the score, is the intention behind the photo, the thought process and the goal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my all time favorite, always makes me feel better,Reassured even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, whats my ticket number? How long do you think? Eternity? Thats ok with me, all Ive got is time. My spirit will keep me sustained until we meet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could write a thousand and more just for her, it still would not be enough. 
A thousand and more have been spoken in her name, in vain, to what avail, to what gain? 
She is a distant muse, the object of my desire, my flame. 
It is my sickness, my pacifier, for some long forgotten pain, now it dwells in images out of reach, unseen by the sane, us all much alike, the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She does date an older IT professional, so maybe you got a shot lol. Hopefully not though, sorry buddy, but I really would like time with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My muse,my flame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me that usually means I listen to what sounds good regardless of genre. Granted the majority of country I do not like, but every now and again I will hear a song that breaks that mold and sounds good. 
I mean in every single genre there are masses of stuff that sound like trash.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natural meaning not "induced" not relating to the body being intoxicated and reacting to a poisoned state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most spiritual or God like occurrence you have experienced naturally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im glad this happened, we just made a positive interaction. My mostly antisocial life littered with awkward filler comments has finally paid off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
