<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprise! You are writing the fall play! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I am new to this sub, but I recently stumbled into a playwriting situation and I need some guidance. I wrote up a sample of a play idea I had for the Tombstone Repertory Company to be used down the line. The  "head guy" loved it, and announced to the company last night my play will most likely be the fall production. I am SO excited, but this is my 1st attempt to write a play. I usually write fantasy fiction, so this is quite a step outside my comfort zone. I am more than happy to provide more details, but I just need some tips and encouragement. There is suddenly a lot of pressure for my first attempt at playwriting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 23:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is pretty easy and fast once you get a few rows in. The corrections are there in the Ravelry pattern, but I missed them at first and it frustrated me. I hope I can save someone the same fate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 21:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I need to make myself a shawl with this color! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 18:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [HERE](http://www.ravelry.com/patterns/library/festival-shawl) is the original Ravelry link by Lyn Robinson
[HERE](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1TGxkIhVoksm9B2Bve-CYi6li1EMRYKj6pBA2JaGP04k/edit?usp=sharing) is the fully corrected instructions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FO] Friday! Festival Shawl just in time for Mother's Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 18:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 01:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so sick to death of this asinine "argument". If you want to be a SAHP, make it happen. If you want to be a parent who has an out of the home job, make that work. There is not one way to be a good parent and a hard-working human. Which ever side you are on, if you have to justify your decision by tearing down the other side of the road, you are an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 00:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another thing I need to put on my crochet list. That is lovely, and thanks for posting the pattern for the squares! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 02:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so fab! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 02:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to hand write a 1st draft, then I use Dragon Naturally Speaking to dictate into Open Office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 02:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title and 1st paragraph are incredibly condescending. Although your tips are helpful, the general Redditor on this sub does not benefit from one more voice telling us it is our fault we have anxiety disorders and if we would just "suck it up" to get better. If you really want to be helpful, you could retitle and lose the "get over it" feeling of the intro to make it a little more inviting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an Arizona resident, I agree! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now cannot live without this in my life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 19:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did (amateur, community theater) stage makeup this weekend. I applied powder, then dark foundation, then more powder to set it (my favorite tip learned here on MUA) I then did a thin line of blue eyeliner on the top lids only, mascara and a metric ton of warm pink blush. I used a light touch of warm pink lipstick. This was for a more "natural" look, (little kids and men) but it might make a good base to build a more dramatic look from. Best of luck, and please post pics of some of the dancers finished looks if you can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 17:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will love that comparison! Thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 23:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and girls looked great for opening weekend! Thanks so much, ladies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tombstone Repertory Theater appreciates all the make up tips I got from this sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 23:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 05:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be my next shawl. Lovely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 03:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 04:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What up, fellow hooker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 16:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would always go out with my smoker friends and say I was on a "second-hand smoke break". I had a manager question me once about the "extra break"(restaurant job) , but he backed off when I pointed out that there were 4 people smoking and me standing around chatting and somehow only I was in the wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 02:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a big, snuggly, pile of Dragon cuteness!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 22:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really lovely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perhaps a slightly more adult after Easter gift? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 21:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 17:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am embarrassingly excited about this. My daughter's have my Jem and Kimber dolls buried in their toys somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly right. I get so excited when I get comments from posts here. When people who do such amazing work like my stuff, it's like getting invited to the cool lunch table for adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 22:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dat feel, curly sister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 19:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is just what I was thinking. Less 'airy' and more solid. Thanks for posting the pic, it looks awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 23:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 23:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Does that make it seem more solid, for lack of a better term?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been thinking about doing some pillows in the near future, and this will be in the running. Thanks for the share!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Corrected pattern] (https://docs.google.com/document/d/1TGxkIhVoksm9B2Bve-CYi6li1EMRYKj6pBA2JaGP04k/edit?usp=sharing) for the Festival Shawl by Lyn Robinson. I thought I had the most up to date corrections and wasted an hour trying to figure out where I was screwing up. I hope this saves someone that aggravation, since it is a beautiful pattern and fairly easy with the corrected instructions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WIP] Wednesday. Festival shawl. Corrected pattern in comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 05:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the way you made the fin fold in on itself. Adorbz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 05:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so lovely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 04:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it had not taken me a month, I might consider it. The thread projects are very time consuming for me compared to a yarn project of the same size. I will be making myself one, eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 03:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. It's all chains and shells. It is from one of the little project books you get at Joann for $4. If I can find the pattern online I will link it. The thread is Aunt Lydia's Peacock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 03:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! My Mom loves it so much I am starting a triangle shawl in the same color for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FO] My 1st thread crochet shawl! A gift I will hate to give away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 23:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 04:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to do a long routine of winding down, followed by self-talk to go to sleep. I have the greatest majority of my anxiety under control, but still dread bed time because getting myself to sleep is such a chore. I am a writer, and so after all my other little rituals, if I am having trouble I start to "write" stories in my head. It keeps my mind occupied enough to stay out of thought cycles, but is relaxing enough to fall asleep. Best of luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look amazing! I tried this as well for a function this last weekend and I was so impressed. Walked around all day in costume in the Arizona sun and had minimal "melting" of my makeup. Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 02:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My escape artist of a Toy Poodle got out of our yard in February and was attacked by another dog. Our neighbors saw him and called Animal Control, who took him to the vet. They saved his life, and I would give them a kidney if they asked me. Fuck that ungrateful fuck. He doesn't deserve a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 19:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I paid mine off about 2 years ago. It was a very proud and grown-up feeling, that I am glad you can now share in. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 20:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed these when I was there in February. There are little "bars" for it set up in the walkways of most of the Strip casinos and at least one service that will come to your hotel room. It was cracking us all up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 06:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazingly fabulous and I need to make one like right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 03:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live just over 20 miles from the border, our Wi-Fi is named United States Border Patrol Mobile Command </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 03:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 01:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people should calm their Tits about this. If not being able to predict a bad outcome to a seemingly positive life decision were a sign of bad parents, we would all fall in that category,  I'm sure. As far as the people saying they "wasted taxpayer money with their fun and games" do they say that about lost hikers? Victims of fire or crime?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 23:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me uncomfortable
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 01:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other guy has worked in gunfights/recreations for years and said the stupidity of people is amazing. It wasn't even the first time that happened to him, so he wasn't as shocked as my hubs was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 01:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will, he is so in love with his job, mostly because of people like you who enjoy it so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 01:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this particular show they provide their own guns, but are handed the certain amount of blanks they need for each show just before and turn in the casings after. Because they walk around on the street with their guns, they are, understandably, super careful about ammo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 01:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They stand pretty far apart and never point the guns directly at each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 00:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has only been there a few weeks. Once he has been doing it a while and has more stories maybe I can talk him into am AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 02:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had never even seen a gun in real life until my late 20's, so I have a healthy respect for them. I want to think she is just a rude tourist who thought it was a replica, but who knows. Hopefully she learned a lesson, but I doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 01:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's all for show in Tombstone, but how do you think as a grown woman that you can just grab someone's gun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 00:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They load up just before the show and walk around town empty, but it's still a real gun, not a toy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 00:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does he, it's a dream come true for us to be here and for him to be a gunslinger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 00:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He loves it! They do a demo on the show shooting an aluminum can to show the blanks are dangerous, but this was out on the street pre-show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's a real gun, ma'am. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 23:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly retail, but my husband works a gunfight show in Tombstone AZ. Yesterday while the guys were hawking for the last show of the day a woman came up to him and another gunslinger for a picture.

No big deal, happens 100 times a day. Only this woman grabbed the Marshall badge of his vest, breaking it off the pin, yanked the hat off the other guy, then pulled his gun out of the holster to pose for the picture.

Both guys freak out, along with a few bystanders. He asked the woman for the gun back, and she is like "what's the big deal?"
He informs her it is a real gun she is waving around, and although he is 99% sure it's unloaded you should always treat it like it's loaded.
She then says something like it's just blanks, and is informed even blanks can do a lot of damage or even kill at close range.

She finally gets the message and sheepishly hands the gun back. She notices the broken Marshall badge pin and turns bright red, takes the pic quickly, and rushes on her way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 05:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have a Malcolm Reynolds. Mine is an Austraulian Shepard. Cheers, fellow Browncoat dog owner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the old "crow in the woodstove" bit. Classic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 02:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thank you for your service and am so sorry you have to pay such a high price for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 23:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are actively seeking land over 4 acres here in Arizona, U.S. for a yurt. In our county an owner\builder has pretty much free reign on a rural plot 4 acres or more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 23:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sweet! Thanks for sharing and taking the time on the pattern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 22:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's beautiful! Best of luck with the signing events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a guess, they were grilling up fresh meat at that moment, and so had just butchered the victims. The remains were on a tarp, and were probably staged to be moved to a dump site after "dinner". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an excellent point. Any meat not taken before death would be suspect, meaning you could not be as efficient in using every part of the carcass as with traditional butchering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A warm welcome at a Bisbee AZ tattoo parlor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 22:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 02:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad he has you to walk him through these things! Internet hugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 02:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really the humane way to handle the situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 01:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me incredibly happy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 04:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I had a good childhood until this. Life ruiner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 04:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 6 of hearts playing card I found a few years back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 01:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many versions of this from my grooming days
I hate people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> evenings after 7 EST </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 02:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 03:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just subbed to it! So excited
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 04:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is amazing and I am so jealous right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 04:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautifully done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual Fuck is wrong with these people? How is your moral outrage worth more than a child's life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 01:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so sorry that happened. That person seems willfully ignorant about how depression works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 04:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel weird about how much I laughed at that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 23:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 23:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am actually making something for myself, for once! I cannot wait to wear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 22:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just sent an email. Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 22:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be at GenCon and also am a writer for GamingMommies.com. Both my husband and I would be thrilled to volunteer for you guys!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday WIP ripple cardigan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 17:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 16:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is beautiful! Bravo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 06:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This pattern is exactly what I was looking for! I am going to make a few to hang on my pegboard wall we are installing in our RV/Tinyhouse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 04:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to talk about your bewbs...for science! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 03:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my crafting and gaming areas are also my "Battle Stations" also, so I equate it with enjoying a hobby. It's all the meaning it has for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 03:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot thank you enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
