<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Imajica, Clive Barker** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am not reading the post, am not reading the comments, read the title and I feel the book was just ruined for me.....can people not put spoilers in their titles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What constitutes as young adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a friend of mine let me borrow a book called The Book Thief, which I haven't read so no spoilers please, he told me a little about it and I know they made a movie, so in my mind I have a semi rough idea of what the contents are. 

Now today I was in half price books and I decided to go to the YA section to look for some Redwall books, and while I'm back there what do I see? Copies of The Book Thief, and I'm a bit confused because I was telling myself "I've seen this book on top books you should read lists, my buddy suggested this book and he's not a YA reader" and so I asked him and he said it wasn't a YA book. 

So I'm assuming it's somewhat on the same level and tone as maybe Lovely Bones, a fairly serious book that isn't over the top explicit, and that's not considered YA. 

So with all the YA posts I've seen on here lately I thought I'd join the bandwagon and ask, what constitutes a book as YA, are there any that you don't consider YA that are considered YA? Or vice versa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was amazing the whole way through, I just tore through that thing.

But I like to break it down like this for the ending.

The book is essentially about a weird rich uncle who helps his nephew get stoned and laid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't figured that part out yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My little characters adventure in the yard of their previous home, so the salt elder is a high council and protective of the salt, basically rock salt that spilled in the back yard.

I'm now working on a story about these little guys and their adventures in our human world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instagram jqstringer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a lot of fantasy stuff...yet, but instagram jqstringer, though I should have the same stuff posted on here as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between my characters and mouseguard or redwall, is that my characters take place in our world, there weapons are human items, a nail, fish hooks, thumb tack, razor blade.

Though redwall and mouseguard are inspirations, these characters are a separate entity.

And yes I know they used a hook in mouseguard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to make some pretty soon, I wasn't intending too but this painting and my last one have gotten a lot of attention so I'll start making prints </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's around salt, not on it, he's the keeper of the salt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] The salt elder, watercolor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] The yellow Scaab, watercolor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] The salt elder, watercolor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instagram Jqstringer, not much fantasy stuff but I'm working on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mouseguard, Redwall, you know cute high fantasy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, the little dagger was supposed to be a thumb tack, but I don't know if it really came out that way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The yellow Scaab, watercolor, wc paper, 8x15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] The yellow Scaab, watercolor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not, I just recently picked up the first book. But even looking at that list of literary cookbooks I'm still baffled as to how these are things, but I guess people want to eat fictitious food  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading about Chuck Tingles books makes the Redwall cookbook not seem so strange at all....you've literally corrupted my entire view of books with one little post...I just...can't even.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't come across anything too terrible....yet, American Psycho was pretty rough at points, but I've got some Jack Ketchum to read and that's supposed to be pretty bad and unrelentless, I have a copy of The girl next door, so we'll see.


Also TIL that Gone baby Gone was a book.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird or "Wtf? This thing exists" type books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So recently I discovered that Redwall, yes the fantasy story about small furry animals, has a cookbook, and I was taken back to why this even existed, a cookbook on fake food that is in a fantasy novel. Do they also have a Lord of the Rings cookbook? A Wheel of Time first aid guide? To me it seemed odd and I wanted to know what kind of strange, unusual or out there books have you come across? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old man and the sea because Hemingway writes like a 5 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I buy mainly used books so sometimes they're not in the best shape, Moby Dick literally tore in half down the spine while I was reading it and I had to tie it back together. Some of the pages of 1984 fell out while I was reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 05:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like 1400 pages, get the penguin deluxe edition, penguin doesn't abridge their books. 

Also, don't let the size intimidate you, it's kinda big, but there are bigger books out there. I think the P V translation, the one with the soft blue cover, is around 1100 pages, I'm not sure how, probably spacing and different font and different translation, but that might be a good option if you want to trick yourself into a smaller book.

Also, War and Peace is freaking awesome, I'd say skip the second epilogue and just enjoy it, it's amazing and epic and sad and powerful and tragic and everything you can imagine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't this person just post about why you should read The eye of the world?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Different books, same cover art, same author, different spelling of last name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a holy grail, or just that book you never find anywhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So all my book shopping is done completely in store and usually a 2nd hand bookstore, I don't use Amazon or any other online retailer, and there are always certain books I'm always on the lookout for and just never find. I was told by a friend that Come Closer by Sara Gran was an extremely terrifying book, and yep, never seen a copy. 

Now yes,I know most bookstores will order you a copy and what not but I think for me it's the thrill of the hunt. So lately these have been the ones eluding me.

Windup bird chronicles

Voices from Chernobyl

Stormlight Archives book 2

Mort

*The eye of the world

Cutting edge (short horror stories)

The way some people die

*Redwall

What about everyone else? Any thing you just don't ever see?


Edit. found The eye of the world today 

Edit 2. found Redwall  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't they change Roland in the Dark Tower series for the t.v. show? Also tulip in preacher t.v. show, they changed her from a white girl to a black girl. I didn't see anyone get upset about that. 

I think this goes both ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What part of the chicken has the most feathers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll check it out if it isn't too heavy on the military action and develops the characters. This is the second time I've heard about this book recently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask why this is like the 10th why adults should read YA post I've seen this week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankenstein is probably my favorite book of all time.

Yellow wallpaper was good.

I've only read about a chapter but Tale of Genji is good and considered the first novel ever written and it was written by a lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like these lists to some extent because it gives me new suggestions. Since I doubt read book synopses I don't ever know what I'm getting into, so if I'm like hey I want a good horror story then I'll look up lists for horror stories, are the authors they talk about and read up on the author and find what book really sticks out for them and check that out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a whole lists of classics



http://www.listchallenges.com/centaur-editions-the-100-greatest-novels-of




Every classic I've read had stuck with me one way or another, I don't know how to explain it, it might seem boring but it's what happening behind the scenes that makes the story really stick out. Like War and Peace, it really deals with the internal struggles of the characters more than the actual war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Imajica, Clive Barker**

Me and several co workers are going to make our way through it, should be a fun journey.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to read Redwall and that's considered YA. I don't know if I actually own any YA books, nor do I browse the YA section at the bookstore. 

I think the thing comes down to people might not consider it worth reading, or maybe it's thought of as just filler. Like, what would teens know about good writing. But that being said, I haven't read any as far as I know, though couldn't Discworld be in that category? The lite fun books. 

I know some people who read only YA stuff and they compare it trashy romance novels where it's not refined in anyway it's just something to pass the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
