<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  5 - 7 seconds laps

This seems too less, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many flight of steps did go in a day?

There was a time when I'd go almost 16-18 floors in a day. But stopped that after I started running 2-4 times a week. I somehow feel that I shouldn't do both at any period of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am getting there these days. I love to drink, but don't feel like it because of how bad I feel next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  throw a couple 18:6 (or even 20:4) days per week

Will the weight lost because of this come back after you stop throwing in these couple 18:6 days per week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't remember who he was until I checked IMDb that he directed Clerks and Clerks 2. Didn't know he was an inspirational speaker as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the WiFi work inside the toilet? It never worked in current office or the previous one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  One time I injured my asshole because someone was talking in the stall next to me and I tried to shit as loud and hard as I could.

You are bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ads are coming to FB messenger very soon. How will advertisers target you without Facebook sharing your data with them?

Moreover, look at all the permissions that you gave to Messenger on your Android/iOS phone. What does that imply? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I deleted Facebook 2-3 years ago and I don't care about it. I didn't have Instagram and closed Twitter too awhile ago.

I use Whatsapp to stay in touch with folks. IMO, you shouldn't use FB Messenger, because that tracks you like crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to get off Google, but what do I do with my Gmail address? I have been using it for over 10 years now and have given it *everywhere*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good stuff, you must be so happy. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd move Skills   Abilities to the end. I'd also remove Objective, because no one really reads it, and beef up Projects and Experience part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too was part of a decent-sized e-commerce firm once and had lot of work all the time. Now, I am part of a much bigger firm, where there are more processes to follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lot of tech leads here.

And junior folks from startups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What languages do you primarily work on? I haven't worked in the gaming industry ever, so curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
