<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8593</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 21:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, I am so happy that these made you smile! Making them brings me so much joy, I'm always so pleased when they bring a little bit of that to other people. :)

And thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 21:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very true! I guess I'm super sentimental over them. Letting go would be a bit like letting go of children. I'd end up being at the factory every day, helicopter parenting! Haha.

I know, I think I keep getting stumbled upon by parents just looking for a cute toy for their child. They're so used to being able pick one up dirt cheap, they don't realise that when they try to offer me 7 for one they're being really offensive, hah. I guess it's not their fault. 

And thank you again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 21:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, thank you so much for your compliments! It always means so much more when it's coming from someone who's not necessarily my usual target audience! They definitely feel as nice as they look, I make everything out of premium minky fabric which is so soft it's like heaven melting in your hands. :)

And honestly, it's nice to meet someone who understands the price for hand-made too! I've had a few people tell me that they're overpriced, but when a rabbit alone takes 4-6 hours for me to make, and the materials alone can cost 8 for one, my actual working pay isn't much!

They're all totally handmade, yeah, and 90% of everything is actually sewn by hand too, the old fashioned way. I only really use my machine for embroidery and for sewing large areas or long straight lines. 

I did have someone recommend I take my design to a merchandiser once before! But, really, I'm reluctant to do so, as I feel like it would lose it's integrity almost. Manufacturers would use much cheaper fabrics and every design would look like an exact copy of next. Whereas when I make two of the same design, even though I use exactly the same fabrics they always turn out a little bit different due to the prints being placed differently while cutting, and all the buttons I use are mix and match. A manufacturer wouldn't be able to copy that and I feel as though that quality is the biggest part of their charm. :)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 20:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! The bunnies are 6 inches tall to the top of their heads. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 19:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I sell on etsy here: https://www.etsy.com/uk/shop/thetinyteaparty

And I do take commissions! I can pretty much try my hand at anything plush-wise, as long as it's not a human! (I'm useless at those, hah). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 18:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really does! Haha. Everyone who meets him says that! :) http://i.imgur.com/b2ZZZuQ.jpg I think I should have named him Radagast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing my big boy, Ollie! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 18:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I'm not sure I have quite enough talent to do a Boba Fett bunny! :D I do have a listing for custom bunnies though, where, if you don't quite fancy any of the premade ones, you can see pictures of some of the nice and fancier fabrics I have and mix and match them with different colours of the minky fabric to create your own unique bunny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! Crochet is such a fantastic way to deal with anxiety. I actually started crocheting to manage my depression and then the crochet led on to the sewing! I'm so happy that crocheting is working for you! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the compliments. :) Each of the bunnies are completely hand sewn with a hand sewing needle and thread and no machine, so literal blood, sweat and tears goes into them. 

I really hope you can get through your rough time and wish you all the luck in the world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm glad your bunny is helping you through the tough times! They are such theraputic creatures. I have three of my own and they help me motivated and working hard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your lovely compliments and words of support! It means so much! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe, yes! All totally by hand and of my own drafted patterns. The majority of the plushies are all completely hand sewn as well, I only ever really use my sewing machine if I have to cover a huge area or if I'm sewing a long, straight line. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thank you ever so much for your lovely compliment, and for adding my store to the wiki too! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! You should definitely give plushing a try if you're interested in it! It can be a bit of a steep learning process - especially if you've never sewn before - but I started creating these with absolutely zero experience in sewing, so it can be done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
