<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2956</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cinema Owners Association declares ban on Ae Dil Hai Mushkil in four states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 10:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was hooked once I read the sidebar here(Koo.Ka.Ka). Half the dudes on randia seem to be tamilans, so I expect it to grow pretty large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 10:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anga Neanderthalgaloda sandai poda ippa neram illai. Nethu ramar erippu postla, avanugalai nee erichatha parthen. So best you post it (with a [xpost Kuttichevuru]). Apathaan nalla eriyum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroes of Pakistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 09:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aryan problem solved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caesar, the last 26/11 hero dog, dies; Mumbai grieves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanthai Periyar's actual name is Ramasamy Naicker(Rama=Ram, Samy=God/Bhagwan, Naicker=Caste). Don't think these monkeys would have noticed the irony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Self-hatred is a mental disorder](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Self-hatred). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vetti copy pasta, the very definition of Reddit. I didn't get it because I had unsubscribed from that mokka sub a while back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enna postupa ithu, onnume puriyala. Bakchodiku ponaa, anga irukkara banian, jattiga enna pesarangannu puriyala. Anga intha subboda linka parthittu inga vantha, ingayum context puriyala. Irunthalum, intha subbai kandu pidichathula romba magilchi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 10:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleting this, one post is enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Katju professes his love for Tamil Nadu CM Jayalalithaa in sentimental Facebook post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 09:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 12:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research suggests that north-south positions on maps have psychological consequences. In general, north is associated with richer people, more expensive real estate, and higher altitude, while south is associated with poorer people, cheaper prices, and lower altitude (the "north-south bias"). When participants were presented with south-up oriented maps, this north-south bias disappeared.

Researchers posit the observed association between map-position and goodness/badness (north=good; south=bad) is caused by (i) the convention of consistently placing north at the top of maps, and (ii) a much more general association between vertical position and goodness/badness (up=good, down=bad), which has been documented in numerous contexts (e.g., power/status, profits/prices, affect/emotion, and even the divine).

[Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South-up_map_orientation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When youre a star, they let you do it, you can do anything - Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 07:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centralized authentication and billing for hotspots is not a big technical issue. Third party companies can provide the service. Both the consumer and the hotspot provider needs to have an account with the same biller. TRAI regulations can definitely help. Regulations are needed to make sure upstream internet providers, cannot restrict their consumers from providing their own paid internet services downsream, even for home connections.

The bigger issue is with the limited area a single hotspot can cover. One way out would be to encourage cablewallahs to setup hotspots along their cable routes. Most cables already carry internet traffic anyway. All they would have to do is to tap into their cable and connect routers at regular intervals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 08:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess Nawaz would be moving back to Jeddah soon.

The Pak Army has always responded with a coup, whenever they have been humiliated by an enemy or when they feel their grip on power is slipping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right through the Cold-War one side prodded and probed the other side to see how far they'll go. I think India hasn't done enough of it over the past 20 years to gauge Pak's resolve. It's better for the media to do the probing, rather than something more official (like the government releasing the footage). It makes it easier for the Pak Army to question the source. They were probably anticipating this, hence the ban on Indian channels 

Anyways, how far are you from the border? I am far, far away  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bit more info on the News18 site](http://www.news18.com/news/india/surgical-strikes-despite-days-of-doctoring-by-pakistan-heres-proof-from-across-loc-1298904.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Surat businessmen declare black money  very proudly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 09:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 05:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Praveen Swami (the defence analyst who wrote this) initially trried to play down the strikes by pointing out that these sort of Indian Army attacks across the LOC have been happening regularly for the past 20 years, implying that Modi has done nothing different. Then he wanted to know if troops actually crossed the border or if the camps were precision targeted with artillery. Now he has written this. In his defence other analysts too have pointed out that there was nothing new about cross border attacks, just that the scale was much larger this time and that India was open about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surgical strikes: Eyewitnesses in PoK describe what really happened during Army strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 04:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 10:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree with you. They are probably highly overrated  If we can keep prodding them and expose their helplessness, the Paki people would see through their bluster and they would lose the power and the respect they enjoy there. That would be a very good thing for peace in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 09:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt it. The last thing the Paki army wants is for the footage to be released. If it is, they would be forced to retaliate and put themselves in danger, instead of the apes they send over. I seriously doubt if they have the stomach for it. There is a good chance that a deal has been struck between Doval and their NSA  when they spoke to each other, about not releasing the footage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 09:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other commentators like Praveen Swami have been saying this right from the beginning. What was special this time was the scale of the operation. Hitting six points across the LOC at the same time is almost an invasion. I am really surprised by the lack of resistance from the Paki side especially when they knew a strike was probably coming. The denial from their army just shows how scared they are, of their people knowing about this humiliation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Javed Miandad calls for all-out war against India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 09:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a Punjabi born in Rourkela. Her father was in the IAS.

If we go by names, surnames or namesakes, Mira Nair is happy to be a Malayali Nair. If anyone mistakes me for a Kerala Nair, I am perfectly happy. I never deny that I am not from Kerala but the fact is I am a Punjabi from Amritsar, says filmmaker, director, writer Mira Nair

[Source](http://www.thehindu.com/todays-paper/tp-features/tp-metroplus/best-of-both-worlds/article1405520.ece) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is allying with her Punjabi katua cousins from across the border. Nair/Nayyar, like in Kuldip Nayyar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 14:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he really subtly pushing an agenda here? I am not too sure. 

What he seems to be doing here is trying to get a small a bit of the limelight that has been falling on Modi on this issue. He is trying to look magnanimous by praising Modi, at the same time he isn't enough of a gentleman to give Modi full credit. So he brought in the 'counter Paki propaganda' bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 14:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for encouraging him. Powercut in my area today and had nothing better to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 14:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And still haven't answered my question. Stop repeating yourself like a mosque loud speaker, you don't even know how to troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 13:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody can see you are asking pointless questions which have no answers, to avoid answering questions that I asked you first. Are you a Muslim and are you gay? If you are either of these or both, I don't see the reason why you are so scared of admitting it. Is it shame? Personally I don't see any shame if you are a gay Muslim. Of course your family might think differently. In which case you can always convert to secular liberalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 13:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I noticed that you were outed on /r/bakchodi as gay today morning. Is that what you are trying to disprove by making faggot comments here  There is nothing wrong in being gay dude. So what if you like shoving things up your ass. It is only going to make it as big as your mouth. Thats it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 13:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel your pain dude. It must be difficult for a medieval guy like you to adapt to the complexities of the 21 century. I mean it must be downright embarassing for you to do simple things like walking down the street with your family, when your father has an orange beard and your mother and sisters dress up like Batman.

And do me a favour. Could you please calm down and ask one of your more evolved friends to translate your comments into english before posting here. You seem to be so triggered, that you sound like you are having a meltdown, and I cannot answer your comments unless I understand them fully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 12:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be the very definition of the madrasa educated backward clown this sub has so much contempt for. My bad for mistaking you for something more advanced. Now go find excuses for your parents backwardness and your own miserable existence in the modern world, which speaks too much english than you can handle and hope for an ISIS invasion, which I suspect you crave for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 12:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at your history, you seem to be a master at non-issue shitposting. Why don't you just state the obvious, that this post offends your Islamic sensibilities? That would be a starting point for discussing what exactly Indian culture is, and hopefully the sub wouldn't be as anti-muslim in the future as it is right now. Neither this sub nor the rest of our society is ever going to change as long people like you don't state boldly who and what you are, and speak up for yourself. Dont expect some secular/liberal clown to speak for you here, which IMO is an insult to your own intelligence. If that is what you want, there is always /r/india. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Printed some t-shirts for peace, how do I send them to our Pak bros? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gets better and better. And mate, your post has made my day. I showed your post to my bedridden grandad in the evening, made him so happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I had read the Quint story. It would be nice to get confirmation from an insider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 11:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by 'the first covert op and the second well documented one' ? Was there a covert op before this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 11:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bihar and Dogra were in revenge mode

Magilchi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely Pokhran 2. That was about our standing in the world and we are enjoying the consequences now and would benefit from it for years to come. What happened today was us dealing with our longstanding mosquito problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surgical Strikes Were Filmed, Troops 'Went Deep, Returned Before Sunrise' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 12:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 11:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [4 hours, choppers and 38 kills: How India avenged the Uri attack](http://m.economictimes.com/news/defence/4-hours-choppers-and-38-kills-how-india-avenged-the-uri-attack/articleshow/54579855.cms) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 09:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jai Hind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MBA should be 'Masters in Begging for Aid' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What we need is a Kashmir to Kanyakumari canal, feeding a national water grid, just like the power grid. States like Rajasthan, Maharashtra, Telengana and TN are starved for water. They would be happy to pay a reasonable price for it, just like states pay for electricity now. Even Karnataka would approve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan Isolated. After India, More Nations Pull Out Of SAARC Summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 05:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not just a news sub.

Only people who are from the Caucasus Mountains would fail to see the humour in this you anti-Tamil Aryan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chennai-bred Tamil Tiger Gets An Ultimatum From His New Home in Rajasthan, Learn Mewari! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real drivers behind TN's recent rapid industrialization, not MNC phone or auto manufacturers. One thing the state can be truly proud of is the grass-root level, bottom up industrialization. A fact not well known outside TN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Tamil Nadus rural industry model can keep farm unrest at bay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 06:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular updates for 5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open letter to Fawad Khan   co: Take a stand like you did after Paris terror attacks for silence is not golden anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 10:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to admire this stupid woman's ability to stay in the news. Either saying something controversial or tweeting something she isn't expected to, she has mastered every trick in the book. 

She is miles ahead of Sagarika, Arundhati Roy, Nayanthara Sehgal, Kejriwal, Rakhi Sawant and Kim Kardashian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Both India and Pakistan have nuclear bombs, why is only India anxious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 08:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missing picture made Mulayam feel like Shah Jahan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 05:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OPINIONS Kejriwal  the making of an insecure leader  a personal experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [List of photovoltaic power stations](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_photovoltaic_power_stations) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adani dedicates to nation worlds largest solar power plant in TN (2nd largest according to Wikipedia) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck all Indian cults and their retarded followers. Fuck Asaram, Nityananda and every other cunt out there.

Even the middle-east and the west had no cults initially. Then it started with Moses(and the original katuas), then ambitious katua Jesus and then johnny-come-lately Mohammed who modeled himself after the original katuas.

Fortunately ambitious Indian babas/swamis/yogis (or assholes as I would call them) have not been so successful in getting enough retarded followers to form their own cults that can morph into new religions later on. Give Asaram (or one of his kind) enough followers, and he would have no qualms claiming he is God's son or his only messenger, and that his true followers should kill everybody who doesn't believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 07:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another year or two of sub $50 oil prices and Russia would implode economically, leading to social chaos. This just shows how bad Putin thinks things are going to get.

Get ready for affordable Russian 'escorts' in Delhi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cauvery water row: Woman who burnt 42 buses is only 22 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only people who went to engineering colleges would understand why the dudes jumped. Not sure why another girl jumped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'We should work together to beat mosquitoes': Kejriwal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PM Narendra Modi's assertion on Uri attack triggers speculation on India's options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did that hurt, baby? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub has always been considerate and understanding towards mental illness. Dont mistake it for bad moderation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ramkumar who killed Infosys employee Swathi, commits suicide in prison by biting a live wire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 08:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jai Italy vs Jai Myself continues... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subramanian Swamy says he would've made a better Finance Minister than Arun Jaitley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 14:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this idiot need SPG cover? Any enemy of India would only want to keep him alive, not dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naik gave 50 lacs to the Rajiv Gandhi Foundation not the Congress. Donating to RGF was a common way of bribing our non-resident-Italian during the UPA regime. RGF is the retirement fund for the Gandhi family and is administered by close relatives and family friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prices of LED bulbs drop to Rs 38 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 21:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am what you might call a kshatriya(even though the four varnas don't exactly apply in the south). So tough guy, why don't you tell us what religion, caste you are, and which city you live in. You are too ashamed of your own background to mention it here, and you talk about battlefields? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prakriti from class 8. This was written by a 13 year old girl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record,no Dalit has become a member of the Communist Politburo in 50+ years. No Dalit is allowed to enter the temple of progressive values.

[CPM talks of equality but denies dalits top posts](http://m.timesofindia.com/india/CPM-talks-of-equality-but-denies-dalits-top-posts/articleshow/46940061.cms)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest victory of Left in JNU polls also reveals their greatest weakness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government bars Zakir Naik's NGO from receiving foreign funds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should we sacrifice him for Bakrid? I mean sacrificing a pig for Bakrid is not right, but who cares. Banning him would prove we don't discriminate between goats, camels and pigs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant which city? I am not a regular beef eater, though I have no religious issues with it. I have eaten quite a few hamburgers when I was in the US, but have eaten very little beef in India. I have tasted mallu syrian chilli beef(with the coconut), a bit of beef biriyani in Hyderabad once and I was told a biriyani I had in Pondicherry once was actually beef. I found the beef in India to be one of the vilest tasting, smelling meats I've ever had. I suspect the mallus can eat it only because they mix it with ground coconut.

As far as I know beef in India is just an extremely cheap source of protein from old and unproductive, cows and buffaloes which have reached the end of their lives. So where did you eat this heavenly beef biriyani? I want some too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An actual death over this issue is appalling. This has gone far enough. TN-Karnataka is not India-Pak or India-China and even they don't have as many issues about how much water downstream countries get.

Central government should intervene now and should come out with clear, unambiguous laws about river water distribution for the whole country. Can't expect SC to decide matters amicably. Everybody knows how clueless our lordships are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 Dead In Police Firing In Bengaluru During Protests Over Cauvery Dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you have it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The importance of being Narendra Modi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15000 Pakistanis guarding 7000 Chinese working on China-Pakistan Economic Corridor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 12:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawood Ibrahim's money was not swindled, Indian government had it seized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 11:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ramlal doesn't have to wash Thakur's ass anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Call intercept reveals Dawood Ibrahim laundering money for Bollywood star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 10:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberation road: Bangladeshi freedom fighters will meet Indian soldiers who fought in 1971 war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 10:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arvind Kejriwal in Punjab: Hotel management students cater for AAP gathering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 10:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome home saar(What took you so long?), hope you stick around. This sub is open to everybody, not just our kind. If you ever feel the urge to fuck a libtard/shemale in the ass you can always have /u/gsc8, he doesn't mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will close Paks transit route to Central Asia if not allowed to trade with India: Afghan President Ashraf Ghani </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like admitting you visited Bangkok, went to a shemale bar, got your cock sucked for a while and then got thrown out because you wouldn't let them fuck you in the ass. I salute your courage for admitting you visited a shemale bar in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zakir Naik's NGO says it gave Rs 50 lakh to Rajiv Gandhi Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like gsc8 took his medication today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More info](http://www.opindia.com/2016/09/after-praying-for-relief-from-defamation-kejriwal-threatens-defamation-against-netizen/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Shri Arvind Kejriwal Ji... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/gcs8, this circle needs you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chennaiites now outsource Ganesh idol immersion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chennai youth's inspirational story: From begging on streets to studying at Cambridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 06:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he hated north indians and gujjus(sattvik, dhandho or whatever) not brahmins. But then I could be mistaken. His parrot on the other hand  obviously hates brahmins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trajectory to A0620, the nearest known black hole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is getting monotonous, in a good way. I rarely notice ISRO launches anymore. Somebody PM me if they launch Kejriwal into geosynchronous orbit, one way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter who he is. Please don't try to doxx anybody on Reddit even in jest. It is considered a big no-no, and I agree. Please edit your comment.

Gcs8 is one of the older indian redditors and is actually one of the most well informed, most interesting redditors around. Despite the hatred for him on this sub, I think he makes the sub more interesting. I cant say the same about his parrot.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize you are having a conversation with gcs8's pet parrot? He knows only a few words, he keeps repeating them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than a religious issue this is being done for political reasons. The BJP and its allies won 15 vote share in the last assembly elections. A surprisingly large portion of these votes came from dalits voting BJP for the first time. Dalits have traditionally voted for the Left and now the comrades are running scared. Kerala commies are some of the biggest goons in India and they are not going to yield ground easily. Hence the recent bomb blasts and killings against the BJP. Expect a lot of bloodshed in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clandestine conversion of a media channel into an NGO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 12:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Habib is more of a jihadi than a communist. He is not alone in this. A lot of Islamic bigots have been attacking India and Hinduism claiming they are secular/liberal.

To those of you who don't know about this guy, his primary premise is that the idea of India as a single entity is a concept forged by the Delhi Sultanate and the Mughals! Essentially he is saying India was founded by Muslim invaders, just like Americans claim America was founded by European settlers! Interestingly he describes the ancient religions of India as Buddhism, Jainism and 'Brahmanism'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why talk with those who say 'Pak zindabad', Muslim clerics ask Rajnath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half-Indian Priyanka Yoshikawa crowned Miss Japan, but not everyones impressed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 08:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would the media be covering Mother Teresa's canonisation if she wasn't Catholic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 08:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A hundred degrees and counting](http://www.thesundayindian.com/en/story/a-hundred-degrees-and-counting/14/32767/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 16:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even Protestants get the subsidy. This is not surprising considering that they don't inter-marry, and have separate churches. The divisions among different Xtians sects is far deeper than the divisions among castes. Not that they dont have casteism in Xtianity, they have a lot of that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maharashtra caste polarisation: Maratha community flexes muscle against SC/ST protection law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 15:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/india is a vote-brigaded shithole modded by self-loathing losers who try to justify their mediocrity by finding  fault with the environment they grew up in, rather than themselves or their wretched families. The voting patterns there does not represent anything, leave alone India. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My definition of conservative is some one who does not want to do something that his father never did. Most UK friends of mine have always been ready to Boom Shankar with me, though not all of them drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attack lifestyle of libtard leftist

Most libtards I know don't drink or drink a little to prove they are westernised. As far as alcohol is concerned, libtards, mullahs and conservative hindus/jains(what is the derogatory word for them?) are the same. They are either are too scared or too cuckolded by their family/community to try out new fun things, and so they just want to stop other people from having the fun that they are not having themselves.

And Togadia is a whore like Zakir Naik,  you are attributing too much intelligence to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zakir Naik approves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salute Nitish Kumar, Total Prohibition In India Next: Praveen Togadia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 09:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jain population in Gujarat 0.959. Chutiya population in Gujarat 99.041. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 07:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To show that there is nothing great about being a doctor, a engineer or a scientist. Would be popular with writers, poets, journalists, film makers and other "intellectuals". Part of the reason '3 Idiots' was so popular too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 11:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure he was wearing chappals in business class. He is very humble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kerala BJP leader favours women's entry in Sabarimala Ayyapppa shrine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 11:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top SC judge demands transparency in judicial appointments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [If anybody is wondering about Vajpayee's partner...](http://indianexpress.com/article/india/politics/mrs-kaul-delhis-most-famous-unknown-other-half-passes-away-2/)

[Also...](http://m.rediff.com/news/report/mrs-kaul-here-you-dont-know-who-i-am/20140505.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IT Blues: Why are Indian infotech firms losing steam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indonesia turns to Indian buffalo as beef alternative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 14:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnier than an overflowing septic tank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they watch 'enemy' channels? Let them go watch Chinese channels now, their 'all weather friends'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reliance Jio data plan tariffs: All you want to know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 12:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are the 10 oldest companies in India that are still going strong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 07:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bullshit. So as a non-vegetarian   Tamil if I am allowed to eat only plants on certain days if I live in Gujarat, am I allowed to insist that everybody who lives in TN should eat only fish on certain days? Any protein starved halfwit who is going to argue on moral grounds against meat beware. I dont give a fuck about your holiness, for the same reasons I dont give a fuck about the holier than thou attitude of so called liberals. And if any deluded asshole here wants to argue that vegetarianism is the Indian/Hindu way, better get ready for a lesson in Hindu history. This is not an issue about your religion(Jain or Hindus) but about the things which you think makes you special. If you think you are special by refraining from things that gives you pleasure(meat, alcohol, ganja, sex) and not by contributing to society, I am going to assume you are no different from the 'liberals' who think they are special because they are 'morally superior', for the reason that they have no way to contribute to society because they have no useful skills. On the other hand you dont want to eat meat or pussy or cock, and consider it as a personal preference and not as some holy jihad, then you have my respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With built-in trishuls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 10:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Sushma Swaraj got stuck in traffic in Washington it wouldn't be news at all. Kerry is a Pak lover, no terrorist would want to hurt him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insecurity level = Kejriwal

Take a bunch of useless guys(and a girl) and give them a small piece of the internet or anything else they don't deserve and didn't earn, and this is what happens. They know this is the only limelight they are ever going to get in their life and they would squat there forever and defend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search for 'opindia' on this sub and read Ranjan's comment in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the vote brigading and witchunting in randia during the 2014 elections. That was what made me reduce my participation drastically from being a regular poster there. For the record the mods there have always been very friendly and courteous towards me right through. But I just couldn't stand the stench there any more. I unsubscribed almost a year back and don't have a clue what is going on there now.

If they were trying to use personal info to target anybody here, me and I am sure a lot of other people here and on subs like /r/bakchodi etc, would like to know more about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Indian journalists are the modern manuvadis of the intellectual caste system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't Opindia targeted on Reddit sometime back? We need more from them on this sub. I just bookmarked opindia.com and subscribed to their RSS feed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, does sudo work well with other binaries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apt-get is probably being denied permission to create a socket because android allows net access only to processes in the aid_inet group. You might want to check what is in that group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chinese imports have hurt jobs in every developed country in the world. The second China embarks on some military misadventure either in South Asia or the South China Sea, these countries would have a reason to impose sanctions. At the most China can dump their dollar reserves, but that would hurt their exchange rate so badly that their exports would just collapse. Considering their slowing growth rate which I think would continue to fall far another decade, China has very little room for any adventurism in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want to intervene to protect a 46 billion dollar investment? India's trade deficit with China is thought to be over 60 billion dollars this year. We import seven times more than we export to China. All India has to do is impose restrictions on Chinese imports. We are not going to lose much, just some cheap phones and the cheap steel they dump on us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 11:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy actually thinks he is smarter than Pappu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert gets aggressive (surrounded by his SPG guards, no doubt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 11:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nitin Gadkari plans a highway revolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 07:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post and your's and Ranjan's comments here are some of the most informative stuff I've seen on this sub lately. If this was a couple years back /u/gcs8 would have been the first guy to add more interesting stuff to this. Unfortunately he is on drugs now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 05:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Blame game on over temple demolition](http://m.thehindu.com/news/cities/chennai/blame-game-on-over-temple-demolition/article9028579.ece) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont Maratha clans(like the Bhosales) claim they are of Rajput descent? That would make them Indo-Scythians too. It is likely bhaus have more Scythian blood than the bhaiyyas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SC would strike this down, by citing minority rights or by sending it to some committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 20:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are well informed. Now let down your lungi and go to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 12:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no Skylake support on Centos 7 yet. You have to wait for the next point release. But the latest Centos 6 point release which is more recent has Skylake support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do I Love Bollywood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why cremate them? Our medical colleges need cadavers for anatomy classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never knew about any of these sites. Thank u, government and courts for choosing interesting sites for me to visit(They have IAS officers finding interesting porn sites for us?). I run a few private servers in the cloud, so I can always go through them to visit these sites. You can also use some free VPN service like Opera. Chrome on mobile might also work, if you have Data Saver turned on in settings.

Edit: These seem to be escort services, still interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 11:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people are allowed to convert to any religion they like, why can't they be allowed to convert to any caste they like? This would put an end to all caste based discrimination because nobody would know who is what caste in a few generations. Caste based reservations can be replaced with economics based reservations to help poor dalits, OBCs and every other caste. If the lower castes are truly concerned only about the discrimination they claim they suffer, they should agree to this. If the upper castes don't agree to this, well fuck them. Then they would deserve all the reservations based discrimination they are subjected to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 11:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [`Don't invite the likes of Mani. If you must, limit them to two pegs'](
http://m.timesofindia.com/home/stoi/all-that-matters/Dont-invite-the-likes-of-Mani-If-you-must-limit-them-to-two-pegs/articleshow/8759704.cms)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when this sub was filled with pics of sexy Sikhs like Sunny Leone and Nimrat Kaur. Now all we have is this dude. How we have fallen from our glorious thurki heights.

(What happened to Da_dope/Xanadu?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MQM chief Altaf Hussain calls Pakistan cancer for entire world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect if there was any sort of systematic child abuse in our slums, our media would have sniffed it out. In spite of their bad reputation, one good thing about our sensationalist media is that they never would ignore such a big story. I remember reading a story about older street kids abusing younger kids in Mumbai, but nothing on a large scale. Having said that I am sure child abuse exists at all levels of our society, but not as blatantly as the Pak docu shows. The pigturds there are practically bragging about how they fuck young boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pakistan's Hidden Shame](https://youtu.be/xNxQhWXbDdM)

There is a lot we Indians can learn from this docu. This shows why poor kids from Pak have been ready to travel to Kashmir or Mumbai to shoot people despite knowing they are going to be killed. Feeding them some religious bullshit about 'Jannat' after death is all that is needed, considering the hell they are living in.

This is what happens when men cover up their women because of their own insecurities. Women are just property in these societies and you can get killed for lusting after them. So you go after the children and the goats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amnesty International's Jihad Problem

The rights group's pro-Taliban partner is detained on terror suspicions.

Is "jihad in self-defense . . . antithetical to human rights? Our answer is no." That was how Claudio Cordone, then Amnesty International's interim secretary-general, responded in February 2010 to criticism after the human-rights group made ex-Guantanamo detainee Moazzam Begg its poster child in protest of the alleged horrors of U.S. antiterror detention policies.

That's worth recalling now that British authorities have arrested Mr. Begg on suspicions of attending terrorist training camps and facilitating terrorism in Syria. Local police in Birmingham arrested Mr. Begg on Tuesday. He hasn't been charged, but under a British antiterror statute he can be detained for up to 14 days.

Mr. Begg, a British-Pakistani citizen, was captured in Pakistan in 2002 and transferred to Guantanamo as an enemy combatant. Soon after his release in 2005, Amnesty began sharing platforms with Mr. Begg, describing his U.K.-based Cageprisoners advocacy group as a "leading human rights organization" and inviting him to deliver the 2006 Amnesty International Annual Lecture in Belfast.

Amnesty ignored that Mr. Begg had written of his admiration for the Taliban. Nor was Amnesty bothered that, alongside his "human-rights" work, Mr. Begg was conducting fawning interviews with al Qaeda propagandists such as the late terrorist imam Anwar al-Awlaki.

In 2010, Gita Sahgal, who at the time headed Amnesty's gender unit, broke ranks by making public her opposition to promoting the views of "Britain's most famous supporter of the Taliban." Amnesty responded by suspending Ms. Sahgal, and she was eventually pushed out. "I don't see Amnesty International and other human rights organizations coming to grips with the fact that their research and campaigning have been tainted" by their association with Mr. Begg, Ms. Saghal told us this week. In a statement, Amnesty told us that its "relationship with Moazzam Begg was as a victim of human-rights violations." It added that "everyone has the right to be presumed innocent until they are charged and proven guilty in a fair trial."

That's true. Then again, if the suspicions about Mr. Begg are proved in court he would join a long list of known Gitmo recidivistsincluding Said al-Shihri, a Saudi Arabian who co-founded al Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula, Turkish terror facilitator Ibrahim Sen and dozens more who have returned to waging jihad since their release. It's a reminder of why the detention center was necessary and shouldn't be closed.

The story is also a reminder of the anti-American fervor and intellectual confusion that led Amnesty to team up with Mr. Begg. The world needs morally credible human-rights organizations. Amnesty too often isn't one of them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three years after her daughters death at Kerala priests residence, mother takes on Catholic church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW? Not Safe For Windshields? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pak-Afghan border shut in Chaman after Afghans desecrate Pakistani flag](http://tribune.com.pk/story/1166236/pak-afghan-border-shut-chaman/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan has closed one of its main border point with Afghanistan after a group of Afghans attacked the gate and burnt a Pakistani flag after Pakistan protested against the remarks made by Modi regarding Balochistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Call me a dog, but not a Pakistani </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 06:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighter jet lands in Arunachal base in first such military movement since 1962 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 13:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I taught myself HTML, how to build a website, built first affiliate programme, editing photos, etc. I also spent a lot of time going to different webmaster conventions, learning about traffic, the industry and different things I could do on my own.

Brains, boobs, blowjobs... This is my dream woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, Ranjan saar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If an aadmi can be called Tiger (Shroff)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a big fan of documentaries and I've seen her in a few BBC wildlife docus. She was one of the greatest Indian females of our times (I am saying that knowing fully well she was not human). Glad to see her being given importance on our sub.

[Machali - Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Machali_%28tigress%29)

I was trying to find a Youtube link to a BBC Natural World documentary about her, but I am on phone and 3G signal is weak. If anybody finds it please post.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bhai-zoned? Wonder if Aishwarya and Katrina call Salman Khan 'Bhai' now. He is Bollywood's most famous 'Bhai'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Union Minister VK Singh's Wife Alleges Blackmail by Nephew's Friend, Lodges FIR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 09:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Understanding Pakistans Balochistan problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 12:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a 13th century Persian poet famous for writing poetry about his boyfriend(some dude named Shams). And there is no reason for any sane person to give a fuck about what he or any other medieval faggot poet wrote, IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalists from PoK say enough is enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 03:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real story behind the GD Bakshi controversy in IIT Madras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 19:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60gb for 400rs is impossible. This is too cheap even for cable internet, leave alone 4G. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks, PM Modi: Balochi activists thank him for raising the issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 13:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 07:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there other performance improvements in this new balancer? Like better spike handling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 09:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post your spam elsewhere  This sub is not the place for Maoist-Jihadi porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using Hindi as a bridge language is a way of moving away from our colonial past. I have no doubts that within the next 100 years, not just India but the whole world would settle on a single official bridge language and that language is going to be English.

I have personally heard some northie Mumbaikars use insulting words to describe Marathis. And I support you and your party if you put those sort of trash in their place. But you should not be taking it out on some poor migrant who comes there just to make a living, as long as he behaves.

Incidentally, I know off one poor Marathi migrant who came to Chennai to make a living. We treat him like a God here now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 07:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would Raj Basha mean 'language of government'? Hindi should be the bridge language for all senior Central Government employees. All IAS trainees who want to work for the Central Government should learn hindi. By the same token, any IAS officer who wants to be part of a particular state cadre should be forced to learn the state's language. For example, if an IAS or IPS officer from outside Maharashtra wants to be a collector or DSP in Mumbai, knowing Marathi should be mandatory for him. If the people of Maha have chosen Marathi as the government language, then every senior official in the Maha government should learn Marathi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh crisis for Arvind Kejriwal as I-T dept recovers Rs 130 cr from AAP's Kartar Singh Tanwar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 06:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in school, hindi was an option and I took it since it is the obvious language to learn after tamil and english. Have never regretted the decision. I can understand about 80% of spoken hindi now, though I've forgotten how to read(lack of practice). Very useful while travelling outside TN or when talking to the huge number of migrants in Chennai or watching hindi movies. Left to themselves tamils would learn hindi for the same reasons, not because the government tells them its the 'rashtra basha' and every Indian should learn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Tamil is descended from Proto-Dravidian and Sanskrit from Indo-Iranian. Very different lineages. Having said that Tamil has absorbed a lot of words from North-Indian languages and vice-versa. It is also used in vedic rituals by Tamil brahmins, so it is not some alien language here. The opposition is really to the idea(or the ignorance) in the North, that Vedic Hinduism is the only form of Hinduism and Sanskrit is our only ancient language. Personally I am against anybody who claims their version of Hinduism, their culture, their  language or their food habits is more   important(or more Indian) than of people from other parts of the country.

The best way for the Central Government to make sure that Tamils never learn Hindi or Sanskrit is by telling them to learn it. That sounds like they are belittling Tamil culture. Lay off this issue for a few decades and people would automatically learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tamil Nadu wont impose Sanskrit and Hindi on students, minister says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 10:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That misleading flair is misleading. Mod must have glanced at the post, flaired it and went back to Pornhub. Either that or he is a paki who thinks that the bomb was planted by RAW agents and not Balochi separatists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 10:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lordships should also clarify how far you are allowed to shove a dildo up your cunt or ass. They shoud then order the government to restrict dildo sizes accordingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing more irritating on this planet than a vegetarian jihadi/crusader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I like his double role, he is the PM of India not hindus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. I don't know anything about Modi's environment policy, but I think a poor country like India needs some socialist policies, and I am all for decentralisation. I don't think Modi has done anything detrimental to the have-nots or against regional aspirations.

But I am totally against certain types of assholes, people who attack Valentine's couples in the name of Indian culture or dig up cricket pitches in the name of nationalism are on the top of my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 16:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started of neutral about Modi, but over time I have become more and more of a fan exactly because of statements like these. It's important to  be protective off your country and culture, but assholes taking advantage of nationalism and hindutva to achieve their own goals should be put down brutally. Nationalism, the economy and protecting people's rights are equally important, and this man has been delivering on all three fronts. I know some hardcore hindutvawadis here are going to be disappointed with him, but then they deserve to be disappointed. He had shown no signs of a hardcore hindutva agenda even when he was CM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 13:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are no anti-national. You are just some self-loathing dude with low self-esteem. The few self-loathing Indian redditors I know off are all mods at /r/India. Are you a mod there too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to assume this is not the first time you are sucking cock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why should Kerala have all the fun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 05:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I know how to ask for a handjob anywhere in India.

('Handjob' autocorrected to 'gandhi' on my phone(Google Indic keyboard) and I had to fix it. Does this happen on anybody else's phone?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
