<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1334</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But regardless, that is a serious piece of shit thing to do. And to think I actually liked the guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a St. Louis Cardinals pitcher anymore. He signed with the Chicago Cubs this last offseason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 05:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I had never heard of Kapvay or Intuniv. I was just going off of what my psychiatrist had told me when I started treatment a few years ago. I guess that wasn't correct though. Guess I should have double checked lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 03:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first season is on Hulu. You'll have to watch the second season elsewhere, but you can watch the first one on Hulu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 02:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they get one soon.  Michael Wacha's 8 2/3 no hitter was so crushing to see end. I feel like him, or Wainwright (if he gets back on track), could potentially throw one. I really hope one happens really soon. Yadi is way overdue to catch a no hitter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 02:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. The NL is significantly easier to pitch in than the AL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, like I said, lowering your dose might help some, or Strattera, the only non-stimulant approved by The FDA for treatment of ADHD, wouldn't make you sweat. The other thing would be if you were able to get the same effects as your adderall dose from a smaller dose of a different medicine. But you'll have to talk to your doctor about that and it'll basically be trial and error finding something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually happened before. There's been 5 no hit losses in history, but only one of them was an official no hitter by a single pitcher. Ken Johnson threw a no hitter against the Reds in 1964, but lost 1-0. Harvey Haddix also took a perfect game into the 13th inning, but his opponent was pitching a shutout, so despite throwing 12 2/3 perfect innings, he ended up losing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All stimulants are going to have similar effects as far as that goes. The reason is because your heart rate increases and your blood flows quicker. So your body heats up more. And quicker. And all stimulants cause that. The only thing would possibly be lowering your dose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will add though, in my opinion, adderall has been a complete life saver for me, and all of the pesky annoyances you have to deal with are more than worth the benefit the medicine gives you. It has been totally life changing for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had a somewhat similar experience. I didn't like having to take multiple pills when I was on IR either, but even though I'm close to underweight, my doctor didn't have any issue prescribing me XR. He just weighs me and monitors my weight each time I go in, and has said he'll take me off of Adderall completely if I drop too low. When I lived with my parents and we got in any sort of disagreement, they would say the same thing to me. It's annoying, but don't let it bother you. It's just one of those things. Just ignore it. And yes, since Adderall is a Schedule II controlled substance, it is illegal to carry it with you in anything other than the bottle you recieved it in from the pharmacy. And you can be arrested for it if your caught with the pills not in their bottle. Some people carry around the papers that come with the prescription, but that's risky. Some cops might accept that as proof, but some might not. What I would do is take the ones you need for the day with you in their bottle, and leave the rest at home in a different container. Best of luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Mormonism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took Wellbutrin for some time when the psychiatrist thought I might have depression along with my ADHD. Since Wellbutrin is supposed to help somewhat with ADHD symptoms as well as being an antidepressant, she thought it would be a good fit. Now, I never did take Wellbutrin by itself. I was always taking it along with my adderall for ADHD. But it honestly felt like the Wellbutrin was doing absolutely nothing.  I felt no effect whatsoever. It felt like I might as well have been taking nothing at all. So I wasn't a fan of Wellbutrin. Now, after an extensive interview and long, extensive testing with a Doctor of Neuropsychology, I was diagnosed with ADHD (of course), as well as depression AND anxiety. So now I take my regular Adderall as well as Celexa for my depression and anxiety. And it's a phenomenal combination. It has worked wonders for me. Much better than Wellbutrin. Anyway, so yeah. That's my experience with it. 
TL;DR: Wellbutrin did absolutely nothing for me. Felt like I might as well have been taking nothing at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 03:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think eliminating a tip would cause prices to rise that much. There are plenty of countries where typing is not expected or is even illegal. However, the restaurants still get by without completely outrageous prices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 02:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as a server waiting tables, but my first job was as a carhop at Sonic, who also rely on tips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 02:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I still tip. I'm not one of the assholes that doesn't tip. I just wish servers got paid a fair, normal wage instead of me having to tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate tipping. Employers should just pay their employees a fair, normal wage like everywhere and tipping shouldn't be a thing. It shouldn't be my responsibility to pay their employees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Seven has an extra syllable than six and doesn't work with the meter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is something that has always bugged me. I've noticed guys tend to dodge the question and not answer when asked if another guy is attractive. There is a difference between acknowledging that someone is attractive as a person and being attracted to them. Guys can tell when another guy is attractive. That does not mean they are attracted to him. Girls can tell when another girl is attractive that doesn't mean they're attracted to her. There should be nothing wrong with a guy, if asked or not, saying "yeah he's a good looking guy." This does not make him gay (which even if he is so what). Humans have the ability to recognize when another human is attractive, regardless of whether they're the same gender or not, and that shouldn't be such a problem or really have any significance whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I would guess this could possibly actually be a campaign sign for that guys opposition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I can't believe there was a real, logical answer to this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree. Although that was ruined when, in specifically Ruby and Sapphire, when they made it possible to catch a Gyrados in the wild.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never felt caffeine like other people either even before my medication. I've always wished I could, but I never have. So I don't think it's because of the stimulants. However I do believe it is because of the ADHD. Just like how our stimulant medication affects us differently than people without ADHD. Caffeine is a weak stimulant. So for normal people it works as such and keeps them awake and wired. So because of our ADHD, it doesn't have the same affect of waking us up and keeping us wired and so feels like it isn't doing much of anything. If that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today you fucked up because you're a shitty ass hole and you suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pharmacy School Tuition Assistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm looking to go to Pharmacy School once I finish prepharmacy and I was wondering if anybody knows anything about whether Walgreens (or any other Pharmacy) has any sort of program where they will provide tuition assistance for pharmacy school if I work for them as a Pharmacy Tech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like the 10th time I've seen this today. We get it. The jokes gone stale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Magikarp doesn't do anything. Don't get me wrong, I LOVE Gyrados, but as far as Magikarp goes, not a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no particular order:
1. Stunkfisk 
2. Lickilicky
3. Delibird
4. Castform
5. Magikarp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short answer: When you scratch an itch, your brain releases serotonin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buh-loan-ee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have reverence for the building but I was with a couple TBMs so I didn't like visibly show disgust. I found the entire thing completely ridiculous and such a waste of money and resources. I thought everything they have inside is just completely ridiculous and mind blowingly dumb, but like I said, I didn't show any of this on the outside, I just quietly walked through. It was somewhat interesting to see what the entire inside looks like though, since I was young enough when I stopped going that I had never seen anything except the baptismal font. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if my employer would know or not from the drug test since amphetamine always shows up, but I found out, talking on the phone to the company that did the test, that when they verify the prescription, they change the positive result to a negative result and then send it back to the employer. So my employer does not know, and as long as I have my medicine I work like a normal employee and they really have no reason that they need to know. If I ever had to go a little bit without my medicine and they brought me in to talk to me about my work performance, I might mention it just so that they understand what's going on, but otherwise, it's not really necessary that they know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cortisol is a steroid hormone released by the adrenal gland. It suppresses your immune system, increases blood sugar, and speeds up your metabolism. Caffeine triggers the release of cortisol and too much cortisol can inhibit brain function and makes you feel panicky and stressed. Cortisol is at its peak in the morning to help you wake up. So that's why they say it's better to wait until later in the morning when your cortisol levels have dropped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just wasn't compared to TV static. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More specifically, correct me if I'm wrong, but it's about a school shooting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the Kansas City temple open house as an exmo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God fucking damn that hits hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because whether he catches the ball or not, there is going to be a runner on first base. It's in the infield so Rasmus can't really take much, if any, of a lead off first. So if he doesn't catch it, he has plenty of time to pick it up and get the force out at second base. And like I said, either way there is a going to be a runner on first base, either Rasmus, who was already on first, or White, who hit the pop up. In this case, Rasmus is a much faster runner, so they elected to not catch the pop up, get the force out on Rasmus at second base, and let White, the slower runner, have first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really an answer, but based on the records at each position, I would guess Shortstop has the most errors, which would make sense. But, like I said, that's not really an answer. It's just a guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when I was a closet exmo living with my parents, I took the sacrament unworthily so many times. Felt like such a badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 01:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't target any specific bacteria. They just kill all bacteria in your body, eliminating the bad bacteria that it's supposed to kill, but also any good bacteria. Which is why people that take antibiotics for a prolonged period of time, often suffer from diarrhea and must take a probiotic (which is a bunch of healthy strains of bacteria in a pill that you swallow), because the antibiotics kill the good bacteria in your gut and throw it out of whack, causing the digestive track to not function properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm. I don't know about that. A mother can always tell. Just like how my mom can remember the exact time, exact weight, and exact height of me and my 3 siblings, even 20+ years after the fact. Never underestimate a mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
