<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject516</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](http://imgur.com/a/7wsWO) my current setup:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For piracy, it needs to be on any FW version beyond the newest one (11.0-33, IIRC). You should be able to find one relatively easy thought Nintendo has started shipping consoles with that FW on it. If you only want homebrew then any FW will do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pangu already showed off an iOS 10 jailbreak a month or so ago :) Sure, it may have been patched in the betas but at least they had a working solution not too long ago! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes a lot of sense! Thanks for chiming in :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really feasible because System Settings isn't a normal app. When the Settings open, the 3DS' home menu actually stops running. I believe this enables the 3DS to effectively shut down its normal home menu firm and rewrite its contents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> legally, contractually, whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's using the official SDK which means it's not legally allowed to be used for homebrew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this on my mobile feed and absolutely abhor it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 06:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: this is for iOS 9 ONLY!

1) Jailbreak your iOS device

2) Add http://getdelta.co to your repos

3) Download Flex 3 beta

4) Open Flex 3

5) Click the search button

6) Search for "Medusa"

7) Download "iOS 9.3.3 Enable Medusa Split Screen" and "Medusa Unified"

8) Search for and download "ForceGoodFit All Apps"

9) Go to "patches" button

10) Enable each of the patches

11) Respring


Another Note: This is what I did on my 6s+. I'm about 78% sure smaller devices need to use Upscale to switch your resolution to the iPhone 6 and also need to find and enable a patch called "Home screen rotation 6+" or something like that. Sorry I can't help ya with that part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't the *best* answer but it is one :P

I have PoGO running in landscape by enabling SplitView/Medusa through Flex. This is kind of an unintended consequence, though, because every app now can be landscape even the ones that weren't meant for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works for me by enabling the Medusa 9.3.3, ForceGoodFit, and Medusa fix crash Flex tweaks :) Still has the annoying rotate issue, though. I vaguely remember someone figuring out how to fix that tho.... :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm then I guess it might be on my end :( thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Is anyone able to get GifViewer to work on 9.3.3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hola!

So I'm trying to get [GifViewer](http://cydia.saurik.com/package/com.jerryen.gifviewer/) to work but it only shows a white screen when I go to view my saved GIFs. The tweak supposedly works according to the [Compatibility Spreadsheet] (https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1wsviKfrj_9pVWmPhVWl8ZEF4UkDHEk7SvvtnFWYaHsA/htmlview?sle=true) but alas...

Anyone know if it's actually working or if my setup just happens to be broken?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liking the look of this pop up and kinda hoping this is a "preview" of a newer UI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 20:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you mean: _**The Wii**_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, just answer the question. 

Your comment just adds *more* unnecessary cruft to the subreddit. Also, if someone in the future searches for this and finds this answer then they have to keep looking. Spreading knowledge is how you build a healthy community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 20:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, a lot of these responses are either unhelpful or intentionally lacking a real explanation.

The bootrom contains the instructions that prepare the hardware to load the operating system when the device first turns on. These instructions are in a **R**ead-**O**nly **M**emory which means they can't be altered after they were set in the factory. There are many reasons for this but it's mostly for security reasons. If one were to find an exploit in the bootrom, they would be able to have control of the device _before_ iOS even boots. Not only does that mean that it's unfixable but that also means one could patch iOS as it boots to remove a lot of security checks. Even if Apple updates the OS to include more security we could disable it because the exploit runs _before iOS even starts._ 

Hopefully that helps :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 09:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way Nintendo cares that this was found. It's a nearly 20 year old prototype of a publicly released accessory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we explain it using [another video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EOaZ830BGwU) you uploaded playing the same file.

As you said in the description: "Load a DAT file with some colors every 10/60th of a second. Audio is powered by the wavplayer library. The colors are off because NTR CFW's streaming feature is just new."

so it looks like you just converted the gc boot logo video into the format you use to play videos in smile basic. Cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely no way this is legitimate.

1. An emulator written in BASIC will be *extremely* slow.
2. There's no way the emulator can open the iso, load the boot screen, and play the video that quickly.
3. A gamecube emulator written in BASIC would have to be written from scratch. While feasible, it makes little to no sense to write one from the ground up in such a limited environment.

There are many more reasons this is fake but those three at least should be enough to disprove this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is. In regards to older/less advanced systems, video decoding tends to be more of a CPU-bound task. The GPU and the CPU both differ in how they handle tasks. The CPU (neglecting multi-core architectures for simplicity) only processes one piece of information at a time. That means if it has to do a math equation then it can only do one equation per cycle. GPUs, on the other hand, are kind of like a collection of a lot of dumbed-down CPUs all running at once. These cores are really fast but there's a catch; they're specialized and they can only do *one thing at a time.* That means if you need to grayscale an image, a CPU would go through every pixel, convert its value to the proper grayscale value, and then move on until it's done. That's pretty slow. GPUs, on the other hand, can segment the image into 100 different sections and find the grayscale value of each section in parallel. That makes the (repeatable) process _much faster._ On top of that, the hardware of each core is very specialized for specific calculations. This math could center around things like drawing polygons, generating fog, light effects, etc. Having the dedicated hardware to generate this stuff is both power-efficient and optimized for speed. This is a gross over-simplification on how everything works but it should illustrate how the hardware works at the simplest level.

So let's switch gears and talk about how this applies to the 3DS. The [GPU in the 3DS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PICA200) is specialized to do a lot of 3D-centric computations. Also, it's (sadly) single core. That means that anytime the 3DS needs to render something, it passes the data to the GPU which works like a separate 3D-optimized core. That allows the CPU to continue chugging along doing what it does best while the GPU chugs along doing what it does best.

Many modern GPUs have video decoding built-in to their instruction set but the GPU the 3DS uses was announced in 2005. According to the [Wikipedia article on h.264](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/H.264/MPEG-4_AVC), the initial standard wasn't agreed upon until late 2004. There's no way the GPU that was being worked on in 2004 has built-in hardware to decode h.264. While it was _technocally_ announced after h.264, the hardware to optimize encoding/decoding didn't show up for a few years.

And that's why the 3DS can support advanced 3D graphics but not modern video formats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao cmon yall getting ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually one of the reasons jailbreak developers don't use Safari as an attack vendor anymore. WebKit still has many vulnerabilities that are [frequently disclosed](https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvekey.cgi?keyword=WebKit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 05:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, playing video is actually a _very_ processor intensive task. It's not as simple as "show each frame and play a song," which some might think. To get the file size down as much as possible, the source frames and audio are heavily compressed. For many formats that means there are "reference frames" and each subsequent "frame" is the difference between the current frame and the reference frame. To stitch this all back together on the fly requires a lot of arithmetic that pushes the hardware. Now, imagine all of that on top of playing and syncing an audio stream at the same time. Fortunately, most computer/mobile processors nowadays have specific hardware devoted to decoding videos like h.264. This increases both the power efficiency and speed of encoding/decoding videos.

I could be wrong but I've never read about h.264 hardware in the 3DS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 11:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seriously impressed that the _first_ game I've seen actually running on Decaf is not only graphically playable but also ~60fps! Congrats!!

It's inspiring to see a current-gen console emulator being written by two people in their spare time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both, honestly. Creating an emulator involves knowing many obscure concepts such as binary reverse engineering, how a computer's motherboard functions, how to properly set up a large project, many code optimizations, a strong familiarity with assembly, graphics experience in regards to video out, audio programming experience, an understanding of how dsps work, and much more. 

Writing an emulator involves much more than what the average CS degree covers regarding hardware systems. With that being said, it also involves much more in terms of programming than what most EE degrees cover.

(Then again, I might be biased because all the EE/ECE students I've ever met think they know how to program anything because they've learned Matlab and took two semesters in C heh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great question!

There are many ways to write an emulator but they mostly involve implementing a software-based CPU, RAM, DSP, GPU, etc. at varying levels. A normal emulator tends to take short cuts when implementing each of these because it's much, much easier and takes less time. A cycle-accurate emulator aims to implement each of those subsystems perfectly with regards to keeping each of them perfectly in sync.

An example would be how a CPU reads/writes from memory. Let's look at a pretty easy system:

1. The CPU uses the Program Counter (the point in memory that the CPU is currently executing) to fetch a command.
2.  Upon reading that command, it executes the command. We'll say "Load the contents of memory address 0x3 into memory address 0x1." Thus, the CPU stores what's in memory at 0x3 into memory at 0x1.
3. The PC is incremented and thus repeat part 1.

So, a normal emulator would do this:

1. Have the CPU class read from an array of integers (the memory subsystem) at the index of the Program Counter.
2. The CPU class analyzes what the command is.
3. Once figuring out the command, the CPU executes the function by setting the integer at index 0x1 to the integer at index 0x3.
4. The CPU class increments the Program Counter, loop.

This is great but it doesn't take into account many real-world hardware issues like memory latency, how fast it takes to read from memory as compared to writing, bus speed, etc.

A cycle-accurate emulator would function similarly to how the actual hardware works:

1. Fetching the command takes 1 cycle so begin 1 cycle to read the command from memory.
2. Executing this command is supposed to take 2 cycles. Begin the second cycle.
3. First, read the contents of memory address 0x3 into a register. (A temporary cache in the CPU thats really fast). This takes a cycle.
4. Next, start the third cycle. Write the register's contents to memory address 0x1.
5. Increment the PC, loop. 

The actual hardware is timed so each moving part has a proper state for each cycle. Emulating each of these states allows the intricacies of the hardware to be nearly "cycle-accurate." It takes a lot of time and power to execute things this way, though. 

Hopefully this helped explain it a bit. It's hard to convey such advanced concepts to an unknown audience :/ Also, this wasn't the _best_ example but it allowed me to quickly describe the CPU fetch/execute cycles without going into too much detail on how the hardware works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes, some people seem to be confused by this so I'll try to break it down a bit.

This appears to be a wireless memory debugger for the 3DS. To use it, you need to have NTR booted on your console. From your computer, you're able to write or download python scripts that can connect to your 3DS and read/write memory values. 

This enables developers to debug memory values more easily, change a value in memory without recompiling (a feature most "official" IDEs support), and potentially search the memory of a game for exploit purposes.

As for the average user, this could enable a script sharing site for on-the-fly tweaks to the system. One day, there could be a gallery of tweaks for things such as "Make Ness always cause 9999 damage," "Change the home menu text to such-and-such," or potentially more CFW-based tweaks such as region free.

The only downside, imo, is that it has to be run from a computer :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The N64 has been emulated now for well over a decade and has really good compatibility but what's displayed isn't that close to what a real N64 would look like. The hardware had a lot of intricacies that lead to a lot of edge cases that game developers took advantage of. CEN64 is an emulator that is aiming for hardware accuracy by emulating the physical hardware at a low level. See [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QPN3rOhuu0) for an example of what accurate N64 emulation looks like. Compare that to [this](https://youtu.be/SyVymhB4Lto?t=99) to understand what approximated N64 emulations looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 17:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think the concept of labels helps us understand that something isn't "wrong." As in, one could think there's something wrong with them if they're asexual but they spend their lives trying to be in sexual relationships. Letting those people know that having a low/nonexistant sex having is alright means they can hopefully acknowledge and understand themselves more going forward. Idk, it's all better than "straight or gay" imo :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think you don't exhibit any romantic feelings for women, why would that make you an asshole? Honest question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 04:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I is for intersex and A is Asexual/Aromantic.

In simplest terms, intersex is when one's genitals aren't specifically male or female. This is probably what most think of when they think "hermaphrodite." Asexual/aromantic are people who either exhibit no sex drive or romance. I know it sounds *extremely* cliche at this point but asexuality is just a spectrum, not an orientation. So a guy could watch a lot of straight porn and jerk off but not necessarily care for sex in real life. Similarly, a woman could be attracted to another woman but not feel any particular romance for her. 

It's honestly very interesting if you think about it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Wow.

Let's try to work through this. 

There's a difference between someone working with IS to commit an atrocity and someone doing it in the name of IS. One implies a terrorist organization has cells throughout the world and is actively using them to coordinate attacks. The other implies there are individual terrorists around the world who want to cause harm in the name of IS. I hope that we can agree that one situation is much worse than the other.

With that noted, the Orlando shooter called 911 dispatchers saying he was about to murder in the name of IS. In the same phone call, he also claimed solidarity with al-Nusra. Al-Nusra is another organization that is actually at odds with IS. From this, we can *most likely* gleam that he wasn't directly connected to either orgs but was instead "killing in the name of."

There's *far more* at play here than just "rah rah religion!" As it stands, the Orlando massacre is far more an lgbt-related hate crime than it is an Islamic terrorist group attacking the West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 23:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty disingenuous. 

1. There's no proof this was an "attack [on the] west."
2. That attacker in France was legitimately mentally ill. He said he heard voices in his head "demand a sacrifice for Ramadan." He also had "made several stays in psychiatric hospitals." Implying this was an ISIS-related incident is spreading FUD.
3. There is absolutely 0 proof that ISIS had anything to do with Orlando and it's becoming increasingly clear that the shooter [was a closeted homophobe.](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-36525219) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 23:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summer tends to be "murder season" regardless of the location. I know the Chicago's deadliest season is summer. Summer has more violence for many reasons including: 

1. The heat makes people more tense.
2. School's out which means there are a lot more teens running around.
3. More people go out at night.
4. People stay out later because of DST.

These are just some of the reasons that crime/homicide spike during the summer. There are more hate crime-related reasons, too, like June being Pride month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 23:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> moveon.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 10:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wii/GC have a different processor than the Wii U. While they're all Broadway-based, the Wii U is multi-core and is thus an extremely different beast to emulate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 09:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're misinterpreting what chaorace wrote. I believe they meant that Cemu is progressing because the developers are able to live off donations. Since they can live off of it, they're able to quit their jobs and actually focus 40+ hours on the project. It's not that the developers are "dedicated to money," it's that they're dedicated to their pet project because money isn't a big issue atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 02:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelievable progress (again!), Cemu Team! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about Rootless, but I know that Cydia losing root status was actually a decision made by saurik. IIRC, since Cydia was a root application, it was difficult to tweak. After changing it to run as a normal app, there was a large influx of tweaks to customize the package manager :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe a Dynarec is possible on jailbroken devices. (Though, I think iOS 9 jailbroken devices don't support it due to an error of some sort in the jailbreak). 

That means sideloaded builds won't be as fast as a build running on a jailbroken device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 07:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/theydidthemath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 08:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Use it all day away from power and charge overnight, just like iPad

That's just not possible for a "Pro"-level machine. As it stands, my rMBP is supposed to last 9 hours but only lasts 2.5 when I'm developing. Unless they double the battery while also slimming the chassis down, I just don't see this happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the more tech savvy people do not llike to pay twice as much for the same hardware, don't like to pay 250$ for 32 gigs of storage and most importantly they do not like to overpay just to be put in a cage.

That's a very gross simplification. Beyond the fact that Mac OS is now [the platform of choice for devs](https://stackoverflow.com/research/developer-survey-2016), this whole argument that "tech savvy people don't buy/use iOS devices" is played out. I can't believe I have to point this out but there are over [1.4 MILLION apps in the App Store](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/App_Store_\(iOS\)#Number_of_iOS_applications). 

Anecdotally, I'm an Android engineer in the Bay Area and it's much harder to find an Android developer than an iOS dev. Not only that, but it's extremely hard to find an Android developer who truly knows what they're doing with the platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant price as for the first point, not walled garden. You're right, though, that the walled garden means a dynarec isn't possible without a jailbreak. Beyond that, though, emulators can be installed to iOS devices through sideloading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  iphones are way overpiced and the specs are pretty mid range

The first point has nothing to do with emulation and your second point is actually not really true. The iPhone's SoC has [mostly](http://www.anandtech.com/show/9686/the-apple-iphone-6s-and-iphone-6s-plus-review/6) [been](http://www.anandtech.com/show/8554/the-iphone-6-review/5) [rated](http://www.anandtech.com/show/8554/the-iphone-6-review/6) [best](http://www.anandtech.com/show/7335/the-iphone-5s-review/7) [in class](http://www.anandtech.com/show/7335/the-iphone-5s-review/5). It lacks the RAM that most Android devices have, but the n3DS can emulate systems up to the PSX with 256 megabytes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 10:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the fantastic response! That makes sense, though do you happen to know why they didn't specialize the app "OS/VM" to allow for more multitasking? I can't imagine why the AMD proc is essentially limited to running one tablet app at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 09:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> put up or shut up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would also like to know this. Unless Microsoft is using an entirely different processor/runtime environment for apps vs games, I can't imagine this would work. I'd love to be surprised, though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 02:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck, even the gold between the 6 and the 6s is different :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As already noted, JPN consoles are in Japanese and the only way to get the menu to be in English is to swap regions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 05:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To have a jailbreak, many exploits have to be used to properly disable all of Apple's security checks. If Apple were to let us run unsigned code on stock, they would essentially be removing all of those security layers. In turn, that means a malicious hack needs to target that switch and then all of the security falls apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 05:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they're good parents because they let her live without the fear of death until she was 9 years old. There's absolutely no reason we need to comprehend death at such a young age. We only have a finite number of years and it's fantastic that she went unencumbered by death for so many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 23:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've wanted their socks for awhile but the reps are all one size and tops out at a US size 9 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 09:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't inherently have to be like the PS4, just that it most likely won't use x86 in the handheld. Imagine if the game could be cross-compiled and its graphics could be downgraded for the arm processor. They could use the same file format and you can continue the game on the bus or in front of the tv.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 08:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? If the handheld was used to stream footage frok the main console, then it only needs to have a streamong protocol to work across devices. The console's games likely wont be entirely cross platform and no one should expect them to. Theres no way they could make a long lasting x86 handheld that plays console games. The handheld is bound to use ARM for battery purposes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 19:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is always a chance of brick but it's really, really small _if you read every word of the guide and don't skip steps._ The guide is largely brick-proof now but be sure to take caution with each step. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 18:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yes you should do A9LH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 01:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Imgur gained a reputation among some as "SJW"

God, I hate 2015/2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 07:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no need to bring prejudice into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Been Trill  Looks like 2014 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would a restore write the firmware back to the baseband, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 06:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 09:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree re: Malcolm X line. I get that he reviewed the music and not the visual album but that line was followed by a smash cut to Malcolm X saying:

The most disrespected person in America is the black woman. The most unprotected person in America is the black woman. The most neglected person in America is the black woman.

How can the line be corny if it directly fed into one of the most political moments of the album? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 08:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here:  https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm?hl=en
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 08:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't looked thru the full Apple catalog but the colors on this one are wrong, just a head's up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 08:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one on eBay a year ago for like ~$45, iirc. It's a large but fits like a medium </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 07:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nahh, it's usually used for a "non-blocking call," at least on mobile/PCs. An example is how your mail client has to parse through all of your mailbox the second you open it. Instead of doing this on the main/UI thread, the developer uses a second thread to load the database. Once it's ready, the UI thread merely updates the window with content. That way you can scroll/use the application without it locking up for awhile. It's also used to half work at times. As in, if two threads can be used to process two halves of an image at a time, then why not? Though, parallelized computations has largely gone out of fashion due to GPU computation frameworks like CUDA and OpenCL.

Also, just an fyi, RAM has nothing to do with this :) RAM only dictates how _much_ data can be processed at once. With less RAM you can't store as much info in memory. That translates to slow downs because the CPU has to spend more time pulling data from disk, putting it in memory, working on the data, pulling more data from disk, etc. etc. That's also why less RAM leads to slow OS'. A running application's state has to be held somewhere and if there's not enough room in memory, it gets stored on disk. So returning to that app means the CPU has to free up memory and move that state from disk back into memory. That's most of the speed increase you'll see. There are other things like how fast the memory can be read but that's mostly imperceivable, imo.

....sorry if that was unwarranted haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 06:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, don't let everyone else scare you. Multithreading in _most_ cases really isn't that bad. In mobile development you only need to use it for non-user-facing tasks like loading an image or making a network call. That's pretty simple and very rarely screws things up. Beyond apps and simple client-side applications, it can get hairy. Server-side multithreading is made especially difficult due to the severity of fucking up a web service. Fortunately, though, there are many languages and libraries to help mitigate these issues. It's still really annoying, but it's not the disaster people make it out to be.

The hard part about multithreading is that it takes patience and time to learn how to do it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 01:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine this won't happen for awhile. The Home Menu definitely uses a lot of different services compared to the average game and I'd be surprised if these were already emulated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 11:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work for Intel and actually got to play with this back in 2013, I think. It looks great in the video but it wasn't backlit. Basically, it was useless at night :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.

:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is not a problem we need solved.

I respectfully disagree. 

By framing it as removing dejected people from public transportation, then yes, it sounds bad. Framed another way, BART was not meant for half of the capacity it's experiencing and we need to solve its space issue. People who use the train as a means to sprawl out and sleep are exacerbating these issues. We need to actively work on these problems to see solutions. 

Are penalties the solution we need? No. In my opinion, BART's current testing of cars with less seats is the way to go. Note, though, that this would inadvertently lead to less people sleeping in seats.

All I'm saying is that something has to be done to help our infrastructure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard that but that sounds like a cool theory. I actually think that APE eventually turned into The Pokemon Company so that makes sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 01:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Known Limitations:

* YouTube sign in is not currently working
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 01:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did so it's definitely possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 01:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic work! Much easier to set up than Snap+ :) I bought the ad removal license to support you but it doesn't look like it did anything :/ Any ideas?

Edit: I just bought ad removal for Instagram++ as well and it worked. Looks like it might be an issue related to Youtube++. My ++ username is the same (subject516) so could you mind looking into my account when you have the chance /u/eni9889? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 07:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it definitely meets those qualifications but it definitely doesn't _feel_ like a typical JRPG, imo. The mechanics are similar and the foundation of storytelling is there but idk its pastels, comical modern storyline, and focus on American culture mirky the waters a bit. I guess it's just as much of a JRPG as Pokemon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 22:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earthbound!

I'm counting it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 01:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 02:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in summary, if you think a piece of information is related to Nintendo's marketing department then it's probably fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rad, thanks man! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any reviews on the seller? How do ya know they're 1:1? Thanks for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poorly.

From the GitHub page I just found:

 * Tap Wheel: Tap the wheel as a directional trackpad to move the mouse pointer (8 directions allowed)
* (Pressed) Select button: Mouse Left Click
* (Pressed) Rewind: Mouse Right Click
* (Pressed) Forward: Mouse Right Click
* (Pressed) Menu: In-Game Menu
* (Pressed) Play/Pause: number 6 (to enter the codes and skip the protections, i.e. Monkey Island 2)
* Hold: Esc/Skip 

 How to right click on objects:

 1) Just press Forward or Rewind on the hotspot. Be fast as the tapping will move the pointer at the same time.

or (better)

 2) Press the Select Button over the object (that equals to the Left Button) and THEN add the Forward or Rewind button. The controls have been designed to stop the Tap Wheel moving the pointer when the Select Button is pressed, so while you prepare to press Forward or Rewind, the pointer will stay in place. Use this tecniques to "anchor" the pointer to an hot spot. Compatibility
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I really can't imagine why that could be. ScummVM is just an interpreter and ran well on old click wheel iPod Video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 19:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really seems like a lot of people on Reddit are willfully ignorant as to how the US government actually functions. Thank you for introducing some reason into this witch hunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 05:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing that stops many developers from doing something:

1. Time
2. Energy
3. Resources
4. Funding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SF guy who has recently lived in Tokyo for a month checking in. Tokyo is just as expensive as a Western big city (New York, London, SF, etc) if not a little more. If you really, really plan ahead you can find decently-located hotels for ~$120 a night but I imagine that's shot during the Olympics. Food is cheaper there but only marginally. Though, you can skate by by spending ~$8 per meal at a local 7/11 or Circle K. Taxis are unbelievably expensive. The train system, while expansive and timely, are also expensive.

IMO, I wouldn't call Tokyo "reasonably priced" in regards to anything. That's just my opinion, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 21:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's recommendations? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you wanna get into it, I jailbroke my original iPhone with iPhone OS version 1.0. On top of that, I actually ported a lot of things to the iPhone before the AppStore was a thing. I ported Asteroids, Chip's Challenge, and TuxPuck (among other things). Heck, I was a pretty popular member of iTouchFans back in the day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, I must be a jailbreak elder if so many people don't know what nitoTV is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: someone arguing that "mid-range phones" are $50. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, I think you're out of luck as far as clothes go. I'm a US medium and had to buy large-extra large. XL in Japan would be XXL-XXXL and I doubt those are commonly stocked :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 12:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SF Bay Area citizen checking in. My Asian, white, and Latino friends living in SF all support Bernie. My Asian, black, and white friends in Oakland all support him, as well. 

Don't let media tell you the Bay Area is only white 18 year olds; it's extremely diverse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's perfectly legal to create and sell emulators. 

Source: Sony v. Bleem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 07:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the phantom app would be theoretically be possible but would involve a lot of work. It would mean patching the Snapchat binary with new functionality, which sounds hard. Tethering is interesting. There are multiple ways to initiate tethering so that's where it gets complicated. 

One is to enable the built-in OS-level tethering/hotspot. That's how TetherMe works. That's not gonna work.

Another way is with MyWi. I believe this is an app but it used its own bluetooth/wifi stack or something like that. This most likely won't work.

Finally, there's an app approach that can create a local server and forward the internet through a port. This is how pdanet and apps that snuck tethering in to the App Store works. This is the type of app that will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who don't know, this will only work for apps that Apple wouldn't let in the app store. So this would work for emulators, F.lux, Kodi, torrent clients, (potentially) tethering apps, etc. This won't work for tweaks or anything that needs to work outside of an app sandbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm just not as exposed to BAPE's full product line as others, but their brand is pretty "meh" to me atm. Shark hoodies are less about style and more about trends. (Though, the same could be said about HBA, Off White, Pyrex Vision, HUF, etc.) Beyond their perchance for trendy items, their bright, colorful prints don't really jive well with the current all-black or earth tones minimalism. Though, I'm sure we'll see a resurgence of crazy patterns soon as a response.

Maybe I'm just getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered on Feb 26th :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 05:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SELLING: (2) Weekend 2 tickets with shuttle passes. I'm in the Bay area (live in SF/work in OAK). 

Couldn't get time off of work :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm roughly your build; did you buy a medium or large? Also looking forward to fit pics :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CDG- Wonderwood :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
