<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It felt a lot longer than it was because of that, too. Under two hours but dragged on after, I'd say, the point where they pretend to be zombies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok you expect me to team fight from minute zero? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rod of Atos on PA? That's interesting  :x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very specific question about the Pevear translation of the Brothers Karamazov with the red cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read one of his but can't remember which.. was probably that one, though. I remember liking it but not as much as the tragedies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Adventures of Amir Hamza is new to me, though the others are all on my wish list. I really need to get around to all of these haha

What about The Pillow Book, is that a good one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this doesn't add positively to the discussion or anything but 

I can't fathom the idea of guilty pleasure reading when it can take so long to read a bad book. It's not like a bad song that's only 4 minutes or a bad movie that's only 2 hours and you can still laugh at it without feeling like you've wasted your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After trying to reread old favorites this year like Vonnegut, Harry Potter, and even Virginia Woolf, and coming out disappointed, I'm a little afraid to reread The Bell Jar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's when the novel begins but I may be wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like that last line is a sophisticated punchline but I don't get it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried Pride and Prejudice. I think what I disliked is too much dialogue all at once, as silly as that sounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antigone is one of my favorite things, honestly. My only problem with Greek plays is the chorus seems like an odd mechanic that doesn't do much other than interrupt the action.

I plan on reading all of the Bronte sisters this year, unless I get sick of them.

I've never actually considered Gullivers Travels since I know the general plot, but I guess i might as well read the whole thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I plan on doing is rereading Jane Eyre and then reading every Bronte novel in a row. Hopefully I don't get sick of them like that haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do the public servers work these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I mean, in casual/unranked/quick play. In Overwatch, that's taken just as seriously. I don't remember TF2 ever being serious about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you upset when someone leaves your team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK so I've been playing a bit of Overwatch. Something that is very bizarre to me is you're punished if you leave too many Quick Play matches, despite having a drop-in drop-out system like TF2 or many other shooters. I like to leave if I don't like the map, basically.

The even more bizarre thing for me is how the community, from what I've heard on reddit at least, really agrees with this practice. Despite having a dedicated competitive mode, they think leaving in quick play is extremely rude and that you should play just as seriously as in competitive.

This doesn't make sense to me. When I played TF2 more often, I don't remember anyone EVER saying "shit, why did that guy leave? This sucks." People just came and went, and that's how it was, and they just had fun.

Or am I remembering it wrong? Do people get annoyed when other players leave in TF2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds really fun. I wish more teachers would do something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, reading their opinion on it has me oddly excited to try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an interesting bit about it I found from an NPR article:

Moby Dick, despite its reputation as a bore, was intended to be  and actually is  one of the funniest books of all time. To save the whale from misunderstanding, all it takes is to realize that the narrator, Ishmael, is an irreverent wisecracker, forever making jokes at the expense of landlubbers, society, religion, his fellow sailors and himself. He's a terrible shipmate, falls asleep on watch in the crow's nest, is always about to tumble overboard, generally gets in the way of the killing of the whales, and is invariably more involved in his own ruminations than in the spume and storm around him. Ishmael is like Shakespeare's clowns: equal part comedian and tragedian, philosopher and cutup, always ready with the barbed aside or incisive aphorism. And all that encyclopedic stuff? It's playful  and often ironic. Give it another look and you'll see almost immediately that Melville's tongue couldn't have been more in his cheek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and as for the Dickens, it's hard to explain why I dislike him. It's not even that I dislike his writing, sentence for sentence, but knowing that he was paid by the word makes me enjoy it less. I'm always thinking in my head "well, did I really need THAT sentence or paragraph when it's kinda redundant compared to what came before it?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, The Nose and the Ivan story SOUND so interesting. I did get the impression his short stories might be very different from Dead Souls, just based on their synopsis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read Crime and Punishment, Notes, and most of Karamazov in high school and loved it. Still somehow never read any Tolstoy, though I do own Anna Karenina. As for Gogol... I tried recently to read Dead Souls, and man, was I bored. It's probably partly to do with hearing about it for years and years and building up hype. All I know is in the first chapter there is a LOT of scenery description. I read mostly for interesting characters, so I have to say that book didn't have the best first impression on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why (probably partly because of his cool name), but I've always been interested in Zola. I think he's actually going to be the next thing I check out. Ditto on Madame Bovary, always wanted to read that because I hear it's one of the first psychological novels. Part of the reason I've not read them yet is I'm never sure which translations are the "best", so I get kinda indecisive and never get around to reading them.

A lot of your other recommendations also sound like the type of thing I've considered and forgotten over the years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about Middlemarch and Dostoevsky, somehow. I do like those. Also read Shakespeare, I guess he's so obvious I forgot to mention him.

Moby-Dick is one that's always scared me because of, you know, the technical bits... but I've also heard they're intentionally inaccurate for the sake of comedy? I don't get it without having read it.

Does Origin of Species hold up today, science wise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, well yeah that makes sense. Which makes me want to just uninstall again because fighting with these "supports" is a goddamned nightmare... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wut? replying to the wrong person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So games are going to be even slower? Or am I misinterpreting that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coraline is boring to me, even if you judge it as a children's book. It's one of the few instances where I believe the movie is better than the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously, how are you supposed to carry when your own supports are contesting for your farm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound like nothing more than a complaint thread just by the title, but hear me out.

I've not played Dota for a few months. Decided to reinstall and play a bit of unranked. Usually I'll support, but this time I'm like, fuck it, I'll have some fun and carry. Then I remember the reason I don't carry: it is not at all fun to fight with *your own support* for farm.

But instead of whining about it... I want to find a way to work around it. How do I farm (and gain levels faster) if they're always in lane with me and always taking my last hits? Should I treat them like a creep and try to hit it before I know they're going to hit it, so my hit still goes last? Should I buy a quelling blade in 100% of my games as carry? Any other tips in overcoming "supports" like these that are all too common at low MMR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I think this is a step in the right direction, I agree with a lot of people who say there need to be ticks instead of straight percentage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the super obvious pre-20th century classics that I should read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For reference, I love The Odyssey, Jane Eyre, and Mark Twain in general. 

I don't really like Dickens or Austen, from what I've read of them anyhow. I doubt I'll ever touch Dickens again, however I could probably be convinced to try something else from Austen.

Don Quixote is one where I liked it at first but felt it became too repetitive. I'm going to have to give it another chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March 21st gives us two things: the arrival of Orisa and Dave Chappelle's new Netflix specials. Which one is more exciting to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tbh it's a pretty tough choice but I think I'm gonna go with Chappelle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we need this story every goddamned day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you want the truth? It's probably all off the back of Sandman. People loved that shit back then, and they've been following him ever since. I think this explains why he has great ideas but his *writing* is merely serviceable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst thing about reading in middle/high school is the teachers push ONE interpretation on to you and pretend it's the objective truth about what the author is trying to say. Reading is such a personal experience, where we can all get different kinds of value from the same novel. Required reading in school destroys this sense of wonder and the critical thinking that comes along with it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst thing about reading in middle/high school is the teachers push ONE interpretation on to you and pretend it's the objective truth about what the author is trying to say. Reading is such a personal experience, where we can all get different kinds of value from the same novel. Required reading in school *destroys* this sense of wonder and the critical thinking that comes along with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started with Small Gods. As an atheist who enjoys a good jab at religion, I thought I'd love it. Kinda bored me.

The Discworld universe is so eclectic, though, from what I've read about it, that I'm going to give him a few more chances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 74% in Kentucky... that explains why this place is so depressing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does a suicide hotline speak to an atheist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit this is entirely speculation. I don't know what happens during a suicide hotline phone call. But I'm *assuming* there's at least some hint of being part of God's plan or some bullshit like that. Do these services cater towards non-believers as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't trust these suicide lines. I imagine a lot of them are religious in nature, saying God wouldn't want you to kill yourself. Where's the suicide hotline for atheists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is important, the kill cam also takes away the spectator cam for your teammates... so when you respawn, you might be disoriented about what's been going on for the last 10 seconds. Which one is more important? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If they aren't talking, don't expect to have a good game as a healer.
 

This is my thing. I love Mercy but people rarely say anything. If they're quiet, should I just switch to someone like Soldier or Tracer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with Reinhardt is he is absolutely the most hero in the game, both to play as and to play against. Here is a game that gives you so much mobility... and then here's this roadblock of Rein's shield. You're stuck at a stand-still just to break this thing instead of being able to use your fun movement abilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a while now, across all heroes, I've had Q and E for abilities and middle mouse for ult. This makes me feel like a ninja with Zenyatta but I'm starting to suspect it's a terrible idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, a colorful and accessible shooter is also played by kids?

Who would have imagined?????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming you have a bad team, all Mercy's ult will do is get them killed again and give the enemy team more ult charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being "tilted" is not a thing. It's just an annoying buzz word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My positioning is fine. It's rare that I die. The problem is I can't deal damage so it's 5 v 6, and since you teammates can barely aim, the reality is even more grim at a 4 v 6 or worse.

 I'm really thinking Zenyatta is the far better support. Yeah he can't heal as much, but he CAN heal. It's enough to keep them alive. And if they're dumb enough to rush in 1 vs 6 as they so often are, no amount of healing is going to save them- because I refuse to chase them and die along with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communication? Like every other team game on the market, only like 10% of players even use a mic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh, I came to the same conclusion after a little bit of thought. It's just unnecessarily slow which is odd since the game is otherwise fast paced. It's like Rein is a roadblock to your fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not mad, more like upset. Why do people buy a game that is clearly labeled as team-based if they don't want to play as a team? Roadhogs and Reins are constantly rushing out 1 v 6, thinking "tank" means "invincible." People don't realize this is meant to be about teamwork instead of flanking as EVERY hero. If they wanted a deathmatch, there are other games for that and they shouldn't have bought this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 05:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever, you know what I mean. One story per season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much randomness is there? How long until the games start to feel the same?  Or does it have a lot of life in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpopular opinion: Brogue isn't that interesting and people are distracted by the pretty colors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I've heard Civ described more than once is you pick one strategy and stick to it because there isn't much reason to do otherwise. Is that true or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a slower paced PC game (probably turn-based) that takes thought and doesn't have much of a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past year, I've tried Dota and I've tried Overwatch. As much as I like these games *in theory*, I just can't do it. They stress me out too much.

I want a game that takes this amount of thought that is single player and doesn't have an obnoxious focus on a story. And something that will last me a really long time. I can't think of anything which is really depressing. 

Right now what's on my Steam wislist is basically RimWorld, Darkest Dungeon, and Age of Wonders III. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are all great tips, but honestly I think after dropping from 1820 down to 1440 that I'm going to quit for a while. I'm just not good at team games. They make me so mad and stress me out. Especially this one where I'm always raging that it's press Q to win. It doesn't seem to make any difference how well you push and coordinate because the enemy is going to pop some OP ults and take a checkpoint or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this is absolutely a casual game. Winning, more often than not, consists of building up an ult and pressing Q. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk, all I know is I've now dropped from 1820 to 1440. Fuck this stupid game, "teamwork" my ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is support a trap at lower skill rating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play almost exclusively Mercy. This used to be fun when I was new to the game. Flying around feels great and healing everyone makes me feel like I'm helping out the team.

But I've lost 300 sr the past couple days. I'm tempted to believe supporting at below gold is worthless. I can heal people all I day, not going to do anything if they refuse to aim and shoot or if they overextend and die anyhow.

Should I just say fuck supporting and play Soldier/Tracer/Sombra/really anyone who isn't a support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really understand Turf War but it sounds interesting. Is it like UT's Domination mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why in the world would I watch a parody before the original? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the game modes? One reason I like Overwatch is I'm a sucker for payload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not Fist of the North Star, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit I've only seen the first season and didn't go on to the second season because I felt it was boring. I did see a post on /r/television that says this season is really good, so I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Broadchurch ending due to low ratings or did Chibnall choose to do so so he can focus on Doctor Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point about Chibnall's Who episodes being weak doesn't worry me. Remember that some people (myself included) consider Moffat better when he did one episode per season and that he got worse when he became showrunner. I like to be optimistic and think maybe it's possible the reverse can happen, that Chibnall can turn in subpar episodes but that he could have a strong vision for the series *as a whole*.

I guess we'll see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was pretty funny, definitely the second best. It's inspired me to watch Fist of the North Star if I can ever find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unpopular opinion: Broadchurch and Doctor Who are both going to suffer in the coming years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is, if Broadchuch remains a thing and if Chibnall continues working on it. It's the same thing that happened when Moffat worked on both Sherlock and Doctor Who, the writing of both shows suffered somewhat for it.

I hope, for the sake of both Broadchuch and Doctor Who, that Chibnall has someone lined up to take over Broadchurch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word "consistent" implies they're all of the same quality.

This right here is undoubtedly, hands down, absolutely, the best #CellGames short. The others simply made me smile, this one actually had me laughing my ass off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a game mode specifically designed for this type of play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk what Legion is but with its cryptic name I'm gonna guess... another lame comic book adaptation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really played Quake as a kid, but this does look fun. How different is it from UT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you played it recently? What's it like? I don't think I've played since Halloween 2015 or somewhere around there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do have a point about CSGO. And also you inspired me to download the game again and see how it's progressed. I'm no good, but at least when I lose at UT, I know it's because I suck and not some bullshit ult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is you're not told about it until you've almost received the penalty. This would be the equivalent of having a speed limit but not telling you what it is until the cops pull you over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know games take a long time, but... I think they released this to the public too early. If it were initially released when it was more polished, I feel like there would be more hype. Once it's finished, or even once it's in beta, can they attract a large player base when it's already been out in the wild for a few years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't tell you about the xp penalty in the first place, so how can I trust them that leaving quick play games doesn't also somehow affect your ranked games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a team player. I main Mercy and she's just about the only thing I play in competitive mode. 

Quick play is, or should be, a different story. You should be allowed to experiment and have fun there, because it's a goddamned video game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UT4 has been in pre-alpha for so long that I fear it's never going to be finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tanks aren't mobile. I play this game because it's fast paced. Tanks might have a lot of HP, but they stay put in one place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TF2 and Unreal Tournament </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am desperate for UT or something like it to be popular again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried for months to get into Overwatch, thinking it would have the fast paced gameplay I like from UT. And.. it does for the most part.. but the actual shooting part is disappointing. I know its players like to tell me over and over that skill is important and I know they're probably right. That doesn't stop me from feeling like every time I lose, or even when I win, it's because someone pressed Q to use an OP ult. 

All I want is a game that's *not* press Q to win, where you can win solely based on your aim and awareness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not an explanation. Every other shooter I've played gives you more health than this one does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is everyone in this game so squishy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never played a game where I die so quickly. Not only that, I don't understand why there are even different heroes if their health is the same. Why is it a healer (Mercy) has the same health as a damage dealer (Soldier 76)? 

Maybe I wouldn't be so annoyed at this if someone could explain why one or two shots can kill you in this game. What is the logic? Do you think maybe the game is still too new and Blizzard doesn't understand the heroes need more health? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For now. If they've already got a penalty for playing a casual mode at all, I would not be surprised if they introduce more strict penalties in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I care because I like to have fun in quick play and, if this is my first penalty, for all I know they're going to ban me from searching for a match on my second penalty. Why on earth is the casual mode treated as strictly as the competitive mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain to me how you can possibly have a good match when you might be the only one from the start of the match still on your team, with five other random people that weren't there in the beginning. And when your opponents have the same scenario.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading a lot of these replies, I feel like we're in the minority. I wish the fun of gaming would make a comeback, instead of the esports internet points bullshit, but I'm not sure that's going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it makes no goddamned sense, maybe? Overwatch already has a game mode that allows its players to be competitive. Its name is, appropriately enough, competitive mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? It is also a game mode that is unranked and that allows drop-in drop-out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their idea of fun is already a dedicated game mode named competitive mode. They have no reason to be upset about me "ruining their fun in quick play" because if they want to be Super Serious, that option is *already available to them*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no expectation of a good match in quick play, though. It is never the same 6 v 6 becase of the drop-in drop-out. Winning or losing proves nothing because it's been with random people for the whole match. Because of this, quick play is meant for fun and nothing else. I know, what a shocker, fun in a video game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is only a competition because nerds have no life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would have to be an idiot to have a competitive mindset when you don't even know its mechanics. At that point, you need to say "ok, I'm not going to pretend I'm amazing or get mad if I lose, because I don't even know anything about this game. I'm just going to try out heroes and see what everything does." Only an arrogant prick would assume they're going to stomp their opponents on their first day of playing. If you seriously wanted to win when you were new to the game, there might be something wrong with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, so I was wrong about the penalty. But I stand by what I said about gaming being very serious these days. I cross-posted this on /r/pcgaming and 90% of them told me I was ruining everyone's fun by leaving quick play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite the name, it is absolutely meant to be a casual mode. Do you want to know how I know this? Because there is already something named "competitive mode." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the ironic thing is  quick play being treated just as seriously as competitive when the game has already made the distinction for us - if you want to be competitive, *there is a goddamned mode called competitive*.

This isn't like TF2 before the ranked matchmaking was introduced where, in the same match, you had everything from Timmy playing his first shooter to some nerd who has played the genre for decades. There is a clear distinction between casual mode and competitive mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is a not casual mode, what is the point of it when a competitive mode exists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game doesn't tell you this. It doesn't even tell you there IS A penalty until you've almost received one. For all I know they're going to ban me from a fucking casual game mode, since they didn't tell me about the first penalty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is not. Players are always leaving on both sides. It is never the same 6 v 6. Why would anyone possibly care about winning unranked when they're not the same opponents throughout the whole match, as well as the fact you're usually coming halfway into the match? Who fucking cares? If those two points don't clue you in that quick play is for messing around, then I don't know what to tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, that's also all I see. But at least the opinion of reddit is that it's meant to be VERY serious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Cool. It's unranked. Not everything is MLG Tournament 2017, bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Far from a casual game? A bright and colorful game that has both an unranked mode and an arcade with silly fun shit like 500% speed is not potentially casual? You don't get to decide how someone plays a video game. OW can absolutely be played casually if "next big esports stars" like you didn't ruin it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking why they are competitive in its casual mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, you're such an elitist you consider a filter only for casual play. CSGO has a filter in ranked, too, so why can't OW? is the random nature supposed to be "lol so competitive bro tests your skilz"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not ruining anyone's fun. I will quickly be replaced by someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're telling me a casual game mode is not meant to be casual? Do you clowns even listen to yourselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played a bit of TF2 and CSGO and no one ever gave a shit in their casual modes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Custom games are meant for new and interesting ways to play the game like McCree headshot only, not to play quick play the way it should be played.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did gaming become so damn serious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I leave quick play  Overwatch matches quite often because of getting maps I don't like. There's a drop-in and drop-out system where I'm replaced almost immediately by someone else, so I didn't see any harm. But you're actually punished for this after a while and the game doesn't tell you. 

I made a thread complaining about this odd design choice over on the game's reddit and about a dozen people come and say I'm ruining the game for the rest of my team. I'm sorry, what? In a casual game mode? Drop-in drop-out is old as dirt and, in any online game I've ever played, no one has ever said "man I wish these people would stop leaving so I can have a serious match."

Because I think people used to understand video games are primarily for fun. If I don't like the current map, I'm not having fun. I think a lot of people have forgotten the "fun" thing, instead choosing to believe they're practicing to be the next esports champ or some such cancerous bullshit.

I thought unranked game modes were meant to be a safe haven from this elitist mentality that games are Serious Business. But with games like OW and Dota, that's simply not the case. Their players treat unranked just as if it were as serious as a tournament.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a casual game mode. I should not be punished at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you're too young to remember, but did you know every other shooter allows you to choose maps and servers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did gaming become so damn serious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I leave quick play  Overwatch matches quite often because of getting maps I don't like. There's a drop-in and drop-out system where I'm replaced almost immediately by someone else, so I didn't see any harm. But you're actually punished for this after a while and the game doesn't tell you. 

I made a thread complaining about this odd design choice over on the game's reddit and about a dozen people come and say I'm ruining the game for the rest of my team. I'm sorry, what? In a casual game mode? Drop-in drop-out is old as dirt and, in any online game I've ever played, no one has ever said "man I wish these people would stop leaving so I can have a serious match."

Because I think people used to understand video games are primarily for fun. If I don't like the current map, I'm not having fun. I think a lot of people have forgotten the "fun" thing, instead choosing to believe they're practicing to be the next esports champ or some such cancerous bullshit.

I thought unranked game modes were meant to be a safe haven from this elitist mentality that games are Serious Business. But with games like OW and Dota, that's simply not the case. Their players treat unranked just as if it were as serious as a tournament.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to a thread I made yesterday and all the replies I received, you are playing quick play wrong. This game is serious business at all times and you should consider strategy and team comp just as much in quick play. Filthy casual. 

(??? What is wrong with this community?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are seriously forgetting this is not a job, it is a video game meant for fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck? Quick play affects your mmr??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK if people are going to be like this, we need three game modes. Give us competitive, "drop-in drop-out but people treat it seriously for some reason", and then an absolutely casual mode where leaving isn't punished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an unranked game mode. I will be replaced within seconds by someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you're not grasping that if you're thinking THAT hard about the game, you shouldn't be playing quick play. You should be in competitive. What kind of fucking loser looks at team comp in quick play? Quick play is for practice and for fun.

Wait, maybe you'll tell me that's what the arcade is for... nah, probably gonna tell me the arcade is also Serious Business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... true. I mean at least the community doesn't take it seriously. I do wish you weren't punished for leaving unranked matches. What's even the point of being unranked if you have to fight for your life just the same as in ranked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scary thing is the way they've conditioned people to accept it. Look at the rest of the replies. Fucking unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not wasting their time because someone else is going to join soon enough. This is how a drop-in and drop-out system works. Is this your first multiplayer game? How old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't seem to understand. There is never a "we" because people are always leaving. Do you even play quick play?

The reason I leave, btw, is when I get a map I don't like. I don't like playing on a few of them, so why would I subject myself to that in a mode that (you would think) doesn't punish me for leaving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a ragequit. It's a "I don't like this map, I'm gonna leave" quit.

Because it is quick play. It is not ranked. Why would this possibly count against me? (except.. oh.. it does for some bizarre reason.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously doubt anyone cares about winning in Quick Play. If you do win, who cares? It's not like you had the same 5 teammates or the same 6 opponents for the full duration of the match. What does that win really mean when it's been against a random mess of people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to say that isn't already the case? People are constantly leaving and joining. Because, you know, it's a casual game mode just for fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How am I wasting anyone's time? It's like any other multiplayer game where you drop in and drop out. You're just doing it for fun. Or are people so caught up in pretending they're the next big esports player that they forget this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait, there's leaver penalty for quick play? Is this a joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand leaving a competitive match is a shit thing to do, and so I've never done so. But I leave quick play pretty often because.. it's... quick play.....? Who gives a shit? It's drop-in, drop-out. You're never going to have the same 6 v 6 in a quick play match, so there's no emotional investment.

And yet I receive a message that said something along the lines of "If you leave, you will not receive experience. You are close to a penalty." Are you kidding me right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a good link to his earlier stuff that might impress me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the sad thing, too. Women comedians always seem to talk about their vaginas. I know it sounds sexist, but it's the truth from the comedians I've sampled. People say "women can be funny too!" I've never seen it. It's like they're too busy trying to be "edgy" instead of just telling jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, why not? Oliver isn't funny and Colbert has turned into your lame dad laughing at his own jokes. Might as well have someone who can do it better than them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still says Americas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never played it. I'm more into something like Unreal Tournament, like I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That highlights my point brilliantly about porn being amazing and not so amazing. Full-color magazines? Cool! Censorship? Not cool!

Actually... those things aren't really equal. Censorship is an order of magnitude more uncool than full-color magazines are cool. Fuck porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I've always heard it, they're ahead of everyone else in many ways and have been for decades. [Here's an article about it.](http://www.complex.com/pop-culture/2012/02/10-ways-adult-entertainment-changed-the-tech-industry) Porn is why VHS won over betamax as the home video standard, for example.

 And another one is this one: "Ever looked at porn on a dial-up connection? Brutal. Penthouse magazine was ahead of the curb in the '90s when it began distributing 2400-baud modems to its readers so they could have faster access to the companys XXX bulletin boards." 

Unfortunately, this article also says that porn is responsible for DRM  and geolocational advertisement... so it's not all stuff that your average redditor would appreciate.

And while I don't know what porn did for technology before the 1970s, I wouldn't be surprised if there's something out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with Netflix's small catalog, that's not going to happen anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did focus on objectives. That is all I did. I played support so I didn't steal farm during the laning phase (I am not about to fight with someone else over farm - doesn't matter who's in lane with me, another carry or support or whatever wacky combo 1k mmr can dream up, they're going to take my farm). I would always abandon the silly mexican standoff at mid and start doing chip damage to top or bot tower. 90% of the time, I was unpunished and could get a tower down to 75% or 50% health.

So you'll say "ok stop playing support and carry yourself out" - this does not work because people who play Dota are little babies. Like I said, if you start "stealing the farm" from the other four carries on your team, at least one of them is going to start whining and get tilted - either feeding, staying in fountain, or abandoning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you feel the impact of an actor "playing against type" works out of context? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say you've been living under a rock and you've never heard of Henry Fonda or Bryan Cranston. You don't know that they're typically portraying good guys. So if you watch Once Upon a Time in the West or Breaking Bad, you don't get the "oh shit" moment where you see these men are playing very different roles compared to most of their previous work.

Does this diminish the story, the acting? Do you need to know an actor or actress is playing against type to appreciate their rarely seen dramatic/comedic skills more than you would have without knowing about them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you feel the impact of an actor "playing against type" works out of context? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say you've been living under a rock and you've never heard of Henry Fonda or Bryan Cranston. You don't know that they're typically portraying good guys. So if you watch Once Upon a Time in the West or Breaking Bad, you don't get the "oh shit" moment where you see these men are playing very different roles compared to most of their previous work.

Does this diminish the story, the acting? Do you need to know an actor or actress is playing against type to appreciate their rarely seen dramatic/comedic skills more than you would have without knowing about them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's something interesting I heard recently that I feel is a bit related to Breaking Bad. Before Once Upon a Time in the West, Henry Fonda was largely considered as an actor who played good guys, the ones you want to win. And then in this western, suddenly he's playing against type as a murderer.

Sounds an awful lot like Breaking Bad to me, the way no one would have ever expected Hal to be a bad guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why? In what way is that congruent with Hank's character? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never understood the phrase "embarrassment of riches", but it sounds so cool. Top 5 phrases of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My games were already an hour long almost every match down **at 1k mmr** once the shrines were introduced

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno? Everyone wants to get six slotted, too afraid to push t3 towers, etc etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that day is only going to come when people stop throwing tons of money at them. Don't expect it before then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... seeing this, I'm not sad at all about quitting Dota. What a joke. Are they intentionally trolling with cosmetics these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is what I was thinking just by looking at the notes. So I guess I'm keeping the game uninstalled. My games were already an hour long almost every match down at 1k mmr once the shrines were introduced. I don't need games even LONGER than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most everything you said makes sense to me except queuing with two other people. Personally, I hate playing with the same people over and over. All they do, in my experience, is complain even more than your average teammate, since they feel "hey we're kinda close, I can vent to you." At least with strangers, it's unlikely I'll play with them again anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate playing with the same people over and over. All they do, in my experience, is complain even more than your average teammate, since they feel "hey we're kinda close, I can vent to you." At least with strangers, it's unlikely I'll play with them again anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honestly, how do you play this game at low SR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either you pick a healer to keep your idiots alive (which doesn't really do much, because they don't know how to aim) or you pick a damage dealer and none of your other teammates goes with a healer.

I don't understand how this is supposed to work.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, part of the reason I have trouble surviving as offense or defense as opposed to tank or support is that people don't usually play support unless you beg them.. or if they do, they don't seem to heal anyone. I realize this game is clearly based around teamwork, so if my team has either no healer or a poor healer, then trying to deal damage is going to be incredibly risky. 

Right now I play mostly Mercy and Zen. I'm really thinking about ditching Mercy entirely because she can't shoot while healing. Or at least, I think I'll keep her in my pocket if I notice one of my teammates has really good aim, because then the damage boost actually will do something.

As for non-support, I mean Soldier is one of the easiest, especially because of his healing, and I usually win with him... and that's about it. Everyone else seems to die too fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I play any of the offense heores when they die so quickly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I play a lot of Mercy. Part of this is that I legitimiately love playing a healer. Another part is I'm a pessimist and know my idiot teammates are going to overextend, so at least I can heal them so they can hopefully not die.

But another reason is that every other hero in this game feels so goddamned squishy. At least with her, I can use Guardian Angel to keep weaving in and out. If I play anyone else, the enemy team can sneeze at me and I die. 

I realize the logic is you balance out the mobility and firepower with being easy to kill ... but still, they die way too easily. And then there's all these bullshit ults that are a bandaid over poor aim, the most obvious example being Soldier 76's autoaim ult. What am I supposed to do to stay alive?

And getting down to the real reason I'm probably asking this, do I even need to play a healer? At low skill where I am begging my teammates to turn around, look at their surroundings, and actually shoot the goddamned Pharah in the sky, should I just play a damage hero myself, until I get to the point I can play healer with people who understand they have a mouse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing. There is no action in DBZ, just a lot of standing and talking. If you want to see Goku actually fight, you need to watch Dragon Ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do the Harry Potter games hold up today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I didn't play them, I remember hearing they were really good. Is it worth playing them today? Which ones are the best and the worst?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, sure. You can absolutely avoid most ults in most situations. But I think that's a problem. 

At low skill where people will often stumble blindly into an ult, they are the determining factor. It's 90% ult and 10% aim.

At high skill where people have fantastic game sense and can avoid ults, aim is the determination factor. It's 90% aim and 10% ult.

So considering they're largely worthless at high skill and that they're a way to compensate for poor decisions at low skill, I'd say they're all around a terrible mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've still not read more than a few of his stories in Dubliners, but oh man this letter makes me laugh every time...

 My sweet little whorish Nora
I did as you told me, you dirty little girl, and pulled myself off twice when I read your letter. I am delighted to see that you do like being fucked arseways. Yes, now I can remember that night when I fucked you for so long backwards. It was the dirtiest fucking I ever gave you, darling. My prick was stuck up in you for hours, fucking in and out under your upturned rump. I felt your fat sweaty buttocks under my belly and saw your flushed face and mad eyes. At every fuck I gave you your shameless tongue come bursting out through your lips and if I gave you a bigger stronger fuck than usual fat dirty farts came spluttering out of your backside. You had an arse full of farts that night, darling, and I fucked them out of you, big fat fellows, long windy ones, quick little merry cracks and a lot of tiny little naughty farties ending in a long gush from your hole. It is wonderful to fuck a farting woman when every fuck drives one out of her. I think I would know Noras fart anywhere. I think I could pick hers out in a roomful of farting women. It is a rather girlish noise not like the wet windy fart which I imagine fat wives have. It is sudden and dry and dirty like what a bold girl would let off in fun in a school dormitory at night. I hope Nora will let off no end of her farts in my face so that I may know their smell also.

 You say when I go back you will suck me off and you want me to lick your cunt, you little depraved blackguard. I hope you will surprise me some time when I am asleep dressed, steal over me with a whores glow in your slumbrous eyes, gently undo button after button in the fly of my trousers and gently take out your lovers fat mickey, lap it up in your moist mouth and suck away at it till it gets fatter and stiffer and comes off in your mouth. Sometime too I shall surprise you asleep, lift up your skirts and open your hot drawers gently, then lie down gently by you and begin to lick lazily round your bush. You will begin to stir uneasily then I will lick the lips of my darlings cunt. You will begin to groan and grunt and sigh and fart with lust in your sleep. Then I will lick up faster and faster like a ravenous dog until your cunt is a mass of slime and your body wriggling wildly.

 Goodnight, my little farting Nora, my dirty little fuckbird! There is one lovely word, darling, you have underlined to make me pull myself off better. Write me more about that and yourself, sweetly, dirtier, dirtier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I know is I've seen enough matches where Soldier 76 (my team or enemy team) can't aim for shit, then he gets his ult and wipes out three of the opposing team. Same deal with Pharah and Reaper, basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried the alpha a couple years ago. They released this FAR too early and will never get hype for a large playerbase because of it. It was fun for a while, especially the wall riding on the new CTF map (I don't even remember its name but there was water all around) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly doubt that's ever going to happen. Epic seems to want to push their own launcher, like Blizzard or Ubisoft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it you disliked about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never played a match where the ult isn't the reason someone wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1900 - but that has nothing to do with anything. The fact is this game doesn't require skill. It doesn't matter if you can or cannot aim your weapon because your ult is going to save the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All I want is for a twitch-based, skill-based shooter to be popular again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch tricked me at first with its faster mobility than other modern shooters, making me think this might be the game I've been wanting. But nah, not at all. I've never felt good about winning a game of Overwatch because there's not much skill required. And on the flip side, every time I've lost feels due to bullshit. Build up some obscenely OP ult that requires no strategy and then... you win? Yay?

All I want is for Unreal Tournament to be popular again. Why is that so hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All I want is for a twitch-based, skill-based shooter to be popular again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch tricked me at first with its faster mobility than other modern shooters, making me think this might be the game I've been wanting. But nah, not at all. I've never felt good about winning a game of Overwatch because there's not much skill required. And on the flip side, every time I've lost feels due to bullshit. Build up some obscenely OP ult that requires no strategy and then... you win? Yay?

All I want is for Unreal Tournament to be popular again. Why is that so hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  can play with people in my knowledge level

Dude like you are why I hate competitive games.. if you've played that many games and are "still in that skill bracket", then guess what? It's your skill bracket. Doing something a lot over and over isn't going to make you good at it. You need to actually study it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who decide to post in these threads might defend ebooks, sure. But the fact that a thread like this is posted daily and always receives a high amount of upvotes is telling that people who prefer ONLY printed books are in the majority and want that opinion to be known.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel about reading letters and journals from famous authors? Interesting or boring? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never read much of them because I can't see them being much worth my time, but booklists occasionally mention them to the point I'm curious to try some from my favorite authors.

What is the appeal? Is the writing as good? Are the correspondents' letters also included? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amusing how you can tell someone reads low brow fantasy/sci-fi when they use the term "MC" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty much exactly what I was gonna say, yeah. I love children's books for their "storytelling tone", if that makes sense. YA lit just feels like novels that publishers recognize are second-rate and have now found a way to market them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually heard specifically about the Harry Potter-Jim Dale being great. I think I'll try out the Neil Gaiman, though. I've never been able to get into the book version of Coraline compared to the movie, so maybe his silky voice can help with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... I mean, I'd agree they're not reading. They're listening (obviously). But I don't see how that is reason to discredit them. I've never touched audiobooks myself, mostly owing to the fact that I don't know which ones are good or bad. Surely some of them have better narrators than others.

Can you suggest one (or three or five) in particular that could turn someone on to them? [Here's a lit of audiobooks readily available through my library, if that helps to narrow down the choices.](https://brooklyn.overdrive.com/search?mediaType=audiobook sortBy=relevance) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've honestly never seen such a thing. People really seem to hate ebooks here. I like them both, but most people are very insistent on choosing a side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, printed books will absolutely survive. Stage theater, vinyl records, and other "outdated" forms of art are still with us. Book lovers don't need to worry. But they don't understand this, so they feel INCREDIBLY threatened by ebooks. Maybe in 10 or 20 years when printed books are still around, they'll finally say "Hey... yeah, we were being silly assholes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully you didn't type all of this out specifically for this thread, or if you did, just copy and paste for tomorrow's daily ebook vs book thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
