<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4332</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did this last year too.  They sell out usually in under 15 minutes after the email goes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 17:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that email too.  Just snagged two seats right on the 50 yard line.  Going to take my 16yo son - it will be his 2nd game ever.

Oh and I can never get those links to work in Chrome.  Opening them in IE causes the browser to crash 3-4 times before it actually works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 16:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a great show.  I didn't record any of these but I enjoyed watching them and thought I should share.

https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=queens+of+the+stone+age+mann
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree that the delivery wasn't all that great - seeing posts like this makes me realize that not everyone in this sub is 'drinking the kool-aid' if you know what I mean?

It's fun, it's whimsical, it isn't the Best Breakfast Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 16:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've referred so many scouting families to your website for camping gear that I've lost track.  Every year I ask for a gift certificate from my parents for your store.  Love the pricing and the service.  I'm going to be up in the Blairstown area for summer camp in July.  It may be time for a visit to the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 15:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junior year at university in the early 90s.  Come in out of the rain   start walking down the steps of the oldest building at school.  I was wearing old boat shoes that had no tread on them.  Slip and start to fall forward down the steps.  Grab onto the large breasts of a complete stranger walking up the steps to stabilize myself.  Say in a really loud voice 'Oh my God, you saved my life!'  Make eye contact with extremely attractive totally horrified woman.  Try to regain some composure and continue on my way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 18:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Den Leader, Fund Raising Chair   District Roundtable Commissioner?  Wow, your plate is full.

I've always tried very hard and not always successfully to limit myself to 1 or 2 roles max.  I have a pretty healthy distrust of the whole District/Council stuff so I won't bother commenting too much on that.

Anyway, when our pack struggled with volunteers in the past we tried the following with varying degrees of success:

Method One:

Set up the September pack meeting as a carnival, simple games that the kids love.  We are lucky in that the gym where we meet can be split in half.  We set up the games on one side hosted by Boy Scouts and 2 deep leadership.  On the parent side we set up a series of poster boards with the events of the year.  We then ask for people to sign up to help for 2 events.  This staffs your committees for events.  Then a registered leader takes charge of that event and has their manpower to get it done.

Method Two:

Assign the large events (camping, pinewood, blue and gold) by rank.  In our example we did the following:

Fall Campout (September) - Bear Den

Blue and Gold (February) - AoL Den

Pinewood Derby (March) - Wolf Den

Spring Campout - (May) - Webelos Den

Pack Picnic - (Early June) - Tigers

It takes a lot of the guesswork out, it removes the possibility of one person having to run the same event over and over and if you look at how it lays out it puts the Tigers in charge of an event that happens at the end of the year which gives them lots of time to get acclimated.

On a side note, hearing that the control freak is still your Treasurer is not surprising at all.  I've heard more stories of issues with that than just about any other.  At least in Cubs the parents tend to 'age out' like the kids do.  In Boy Scouts they can hang around for decades causing issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your CM opposed to them?  I know that total control freaks exist, but for the most part when people are struggling and you offer help, they accept it.  Are you willing to schedule and run these committee/parents meetings?

How about a conversation like this:

Hey CM, it sucks about us not participating in that event, I'd like to help and make sure something like that doesn't happen again.  What days of the week would work best for you to schedule a monthly meeting to go over stuff like this and plan events?
--
Anytime a parent comes up to me to register a complaint about an activity - real or imagined, the very first thing I do is ask them to help out with the solution.  It can work in reverse as well.

If asking to assist doesn't pan out, then there must be bigger issues at play.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I camped in the vicinity of Cherry Springs - at this campground [right outside of Coudersport](http://pottercountycamping.com/).  It was about 20 minutes to Cherry Springs by car.

The best bet is for you to call the park and talk to one of the rangers.  They offer a program during the year with a pretty hefty education program at night.

The park itself is split in half.  The main park has parking and a big field where astronomers can set up in a field.  When we went it was very cloudy so our views were poor.  Despite that there were 4-5 'pros' set up with rather large scopes in the field.  They were all very friendly and more than willing to talk to our kids about their gear.

On the other side of the park there is seating and an instructional area.  We did not go back for that part of the program as it rained on us.

There are tons of trails to hike.  There are a few rainy day things you can do as well.  The PA Grand Canyon is about 30 minutes from Cherry Springs.

They don't have a full blown visitors center. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tubs is a great place to spend the day:

[The Tubs](http://www.trails.com/tcatalog_trail.aspx?trailid=HGN151-029)

It would not qualify as a difficult hike by any stretch - but it's great for a a hot day in the summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what your level of rowdy is - but be aware that if you stay in a PA state park that they do not allow alcohol and the level of enforcement varies by park.  I've stayed in State Parks that are remote and despite that I had rangers sneaking around watching us at night checking to make sure we had no alcohol - and we were quiet!

Many family camp grounds have large group sites that allow for people to cut loose...just call up and ask.  Good luck and have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds great!  I will be doing this in June for some family camping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Webelos Cooking Academy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the [Webelos Cooking Academy](https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0B0Hso4Utz85pNmhXYWZxaTZsTUU usp=sharing) I mentioned in another thread.  It was written and designed by a very good friend of mine for a Wood Badge Ticket.

When we watched our oldest sons transition into Boy Scouts we were a bit stunned by how abrupt the change can be.  One of the biggest struggles we witnessed was camp cooking.  With the current program there wasn't a large focus on cooking.  Boys would cross over full of enthusiasm then do a nosedive on their first camp outs.  This program attempts to correct that issue.

Our pack has now crossed over 3 Dens into First Year Patrols using this program.  All three have had much higher retention rates than previous groups.  The SM and ASM all state that it is much easier to integrate these boys because they know their way around the camp kitchen.

If you happen to use the program please shoot me a message so I can let the author know about it.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
