<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1779</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, that's a fair point. I always forget that show when it comes to long-runners.

On that note, has it ever gone on very long hiatuses like Doctor Who? Or is it continuous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Strongly, just mentioning how you were a friend of mine to u/AwfulMonk over here.

As amusing as it is watching this become my second most popular post on Reddit ever, I do have my novel to write.

Have an upvote ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I just realized that Brain isn't in this episode. 

But he's featured prominently in the Spiritual Successor to this episode. "Shelter From the Storm" deals with the aftermath of a hurricane hitting Elwood City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep my eye out for you then. I visit there from time to time. I'm friends with u/Strongly_O_Platypus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muffy actually had a cell phone in the very first season, "Arthur, the World's Greatest Gleeper."

And there was a pretty good episode about Fern getting a cellphone and then going nuts over it.

What threw me for a loop was Buster having a *smartphone* in one of the most recent episodes. 

Heck, the Reads don't even have their green rotary phone anymore. I get technology marches on is a trope for long-running shows, but that phone was almost a member of the family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was eight at the time. Trust me, people were afraid. And I lived in California. I shudder to imagine what it was like for kids in New York or Washington D.C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fireman even jokes "How do they always manage to ask questions that stump us?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send us a postcard, if you get a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the meme about Buster wearing his earphones wrong?

https://goo.gl/images/VUOTqG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, it does not appear to be on Youtube, or else I'd post the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Grandpa Dave being diagnosed with Alzheimer's. 

"Grandpa Dave's Memory Album"

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5FoYnFizEPE

Oh, I loved the Neil Gaiman episode! Especially his little speech in the book store.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQFgqRS9OR4 t=215s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude! You're a teacher! You have a supremely important job. 

You could be Mr. Ratburn! Last season's finale sang the praises of good teachers. 

"The Last Day." Not my favorite episode by any means, but darn it if Mr. Ratburn's speech didn't put a lump in my throat. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=djlgVhPST50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really nice is that Carl actually appears in a few more episodes, which humanizes him a lot.

One episode features Buster and Arthur trying to build a model rocket, and then when they need help, they ask George, who brings Carl along, since he knows a lot more about building rockets than anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure Arthur actually releases its episodes that often anymore. Which is weird, considering all the other merchandise. It was a book series first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not actually a comment on "Rocket Power" being good or not. It just used a lot of modern talk and dated itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wouldn't be too worried about Arthur.

If PBS were to lose its federal funding (and that's a mighty big IF), most of the children's shows would be just fine. 

Sesame Street (which now airs its newest episodes on HBO) and Arthur have lots of merchandise--picture books and plush toys and video games. Arthur would be able to adjust and find a new distributor.

What would be at risk if PBS were to lose federal funding are the regional shows that are allotted the aforementioned funds in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't disagree with you about the value of the nuclear family (far from it, I find it to be the ideal), compared to other children's shows, Arthur usually does a good job about handling the issue with grace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great one to be introduced into the universe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, that's over-stated. I have no love for Trump, but I dislike misinformation.

If PBS were to lose its federal funding (and that's a mighty big IF), most of the children's shows would be just fine. Sesame Street (which now airs its newest episodes on HBO) and Arthur have lots of merchandise--picture books and plush toys and video games. Arthur would be able to adjust and find a new distributor.

What would be at risk if PBS were to lose federal funding are the regional shows that are allotted the aforementioned funds in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does seem rather crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that as if it's a bad thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with the focus on DW? 

D.W. is, to put it frankly, an obnoxious, self-important, spoiled brat, badly in need of discipline. 

She lies and throws tantrums without anything remotely resembling remorse, and she is far more prone to Aesop Amnesia. 

As a pre-schooler, her episodes are far more limited in their scope than the elementary-aged Arthur and his friends.

It's good to have more female representation and primary protagonists on shows for little girls who may not be able to easily relate to Arthur.

Did I ever say it wasn't? Female representation means squat when the character is horrible. Little girls deserve far better than D.W. to watch on television. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, that was one of my favorites growing up!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P643WRaWpKo

You want to be a writer too? I actually wrote a novel for my thesis in college.

Ever check out r/worldbuilding? It can be a lot of fun if fantasy's your thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY! You squished Buster! Hey, come out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's just it--earlier episodes of Arthur rarely used any sort of slang or modern talk (Contrasting "Rocket Power" which used the word "dude" a lot). They might not have spoken about theology like the Peanuts gang, but the dialogue was for the most part, timeless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with the decline in quality, but I do like that whatever problems modern-Arthur has (the animation is one thing, but on the whole, I think it just feels too modern--kiddy slang like "Besties" instead of "best friend" and a lot more video games and computer-oriented plotlines. A lot of the earlier episodes felt a bit more timeless), it still manages to hold its own among other children's television, especially on PBS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

The most recent "very special episode" was "Shelter From the Storm," which featured a hurricane hitting their area, and the related fall-out.

I cried three times watching it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the very best episodes of the series, and perhaps the best musical episode of any...not-usually-a-musical show.

Part 1:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xEEMuABtJmU t=231s

Part 2:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JlCm7-Y1wtk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good, if not great, episode of Arthur. I do like that it is Arthur learning the lesson, since he has a long history of thinking things are funny for far longer than anyone else. 

Heck, it's not even the first time he's made fun of a classmate for what they wear. In a season one episode, "Locked in the Library," Francine is upset at Arthur for saying that her new sweater had made her look like a marshmallow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure is. Twenty years strong and I still remember the first time I saw the first episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Second-longest running animated show in history. They're on Season 20, which sadly only had seven episodes, so they may be deciding to eventually pull the plug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arthur was a smoother transition, though I do agree that I far preferred the older animation. At least the characters (apart from Mr. Haney, who got dark brown fur instead of light beige) look more or less the same. 

Thomas the Tank Engine CGI is nearly an entire change in medium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost certainly. Arthur references shows and movies that are outside the target audience of the show all the time.

One episode, "MacFrensky" is a re-telling of Shakespeare's *Macbeth.*

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AVnK-7H5BI4

And the show's referenced Monty Python, and the Shawshank Redemption, and Beevus and Butt-head.

http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/ShoutOut/Arthur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a relatively small (for television standards) controversy about an episode featuring a child (or maybe more than one child) with lesbian parents. It wasn't commented on it that much--I think Buster sees the crowd of parents and says "That's a lot of moms."

Moral guardians and what not.

But I think Postcards From Buster's biggest weakness was that it was a spinoff that just kind of sucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I recall, Arthur's friend Adil lives in Turkey, not Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Wow, that's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually quite remarkable.

While Arthur has gone downhill in the last few years, for various reasons--a bit too much kid slang ("besties" ugh), not nearly enough focus on Arthur, WAY too much focus on D.W. and her friends, the show maintains its nearly unparalleled ability to handle mature issues for children.

Remember how they dealt with the issue of divorce with Buster?

1001 Dads:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KRPsLowm410 t=950s

They've done adoption with Binky's family. And the possibility of re-marriage and step-siblings with Rattles, of all people.

Big Brother Binky:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HW_KygOyTEA

Mix, Whip, Blend. (Quality on this one is kinda crappy, but it's the only version I could find):

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cZswZV-TDRE t=817s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make that two essays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, "The Boy With His Head In The Clouds" is a great episode:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j1KqClu2f4Y

Coupling this, Arthur is one of the best examples of a show that introduced a character who has Asperger's. And notably, the character is recurring.

When Carl Met George:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nsmjwHW40ps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, sort of. It was in response to the fear a lot of children felt following the 9/11 attacks. Arthur's writers took that fear and unease and the chance for working together for a better future and redirected it towards a problem that may be easier for children to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops. Thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Ratburn should make him write an essay on why it's wrong to lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the episodes' highlights in my opinion. Binky is *traumatized* by what he saw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Grimnoir Chronicles could be superb.

Picture this:

It's the 1930s, and for the last eighty years, people have had magic. Some have super strength, some pyrokinesis, some have rapid intelligence, etc.

Called "Magicals," or, for the more powerful, "Actives," America remains in the Great Depression while Japan has fully embraced magical powers is run by a mysterious man called the Chairman.

A man named Jake Sullivan is a private eye, a decorated war veteran, and an ex-con. After making a deal with J. Edgar Hoover, Sullivan tracks down magical crooks. On a case, he finds himself facing Deliah Jones, an old...friend. And a conspiracy that involves both the Chairman, and a group of magic users that call themselves the Grimnoir Society.

They're my all time favorite novels. There's airships and Tesla weapons, samurai and knights, ninjas and gangsters. John Moses Browning and General Black Jack Pershing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, how 'bout the ninety-four million people communism got killed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 years ago, the children's television show "Arthur" responded to the terrorist attacks of September 11, 2001 with the episode "April 9th." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a reason that the Valkyrie conspirators knew they had to kill Hitler AND Himmler.

What good is it to kill the lunatic, only to let a madman take his place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I despise Bill Nye.

Let Tim Allen squish him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that person might actually listen to his military advisors... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or all the famines of the twentieth century that were exacerbated by the communist regimes.

Edit: Credit to u/tw07255ll for correcting my spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old, childhood teddy bear. 

You can't replace sentiment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I'm afraid so and I share your sentiments here.

Good grief. Just good grief. I've seen good men get falsely accused of racism before, and let me tell you, it sucks. 

This reminds me of the Sad Puppies (a relatively loosely organized band of science fiction writers of every race and creed), and the subsequent outrage and false accusations of racism against them and some of their followers. 

Thanks for the history of Walt Disney, I wasn't aware of that.

You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang it, that was it?! That was it?! 

There's nothing that makes me angrier than phony outrage and false accusations. People condemn PewDiePie for that?! When there are others who have said far worse things and gotten off scot-free?!

Rowling should be ashamed of herself for jumping on the bandwagon like that! How many times did she get falsely accused of encouraging witchcraft or turning kids against Christianity, when her books are actually some of the most Christian-themed in modern fantasy literature. 

As an aside, one religious science fiction writer I know of said that *Deathly Hallows* may as well be subtitled: *The Passion of the Potter.*

Thanks for the video, I'm happy to know the context, though I did notice one glaring error in the video--Walt Disney was not a racist, nor was he anti-semitic. 

Per Wikipedia: 

Disney has been accused of anti-semitism,[193][z] although none of his employeesincluding the animator Art Babbitt, who disliked Disney intenselyever accused him of making anti-semitic slurs or taunts.[195] The Walt Disney Family Museum acknowledges that ethnic stereotypes common to films of the 1930s were included in some early cartoons.[aa] Disney donated regularly to Jewish charities, he was named "1955 Man of the Year" by the B'nai B'rith chapter in Beverly Hills,[196][197] and his studio employed a number of Jews, some of whom were in influential positions.[198][ab] Gabler, the first writer to gain unrestricted access to the Disney archives, concludes that the available evidence did not support accusations of anti-semitism and that Disney was "not [anti-semitic] in the conventional sense that we think of someone as being an anti-Semite". Gabler concludes that "though Walt himself, in my estimation, was not anti-Semitic, nevertheless, he willingly allied himself with people who were anti-Semitic [meaning the Motion Picture Alliance for the Preservation of American Ideals], and that reputation stuck. He was never really able to expunge it throughout his life".[199] Disney distanced himself from the Motion Picture Alliance in the 1950s.[200]

Disney has also been accused of racism because some of his productions released between the 1930s and 1950s contain racially insensitive material.[201][ac] The feature film Song of the South was criticized by contemporary film critics, the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, and others for its perpetuation of black stereotypes,[202] but Disney later campaigned successfully for an Honorary Academy Award for its star, James Baskett, the first black actor so honored.[203][ad] Gabler argues that "Walt Disney was no racist. He never, either publicly or privately, made disparaging remarks about blacks or asserted white superiority. Like most white Americans of his generation, however, he was racially insensitive."[201] Floyd Norman, the studio's first black animator who worked closely with Disney during the 1950s and 1960s, said, "Not once did I observe a hint of the racist behavior Walt Disney was often accused of after his death. His treatment of peopleand by this I mean all peoplecan only be called exemplary."[204] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....

....

....

....

....

....

....

.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got into PewDiePie. What exactly happened? Did he tell one off-color joke that got him accused of anti-semitism, or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how I feel as well. Which is why I have not bothered to read any pottermore, any other extended universe. I simply do not care. The original Harry Potter books were written from the heart, JK Rowlings baby. She was nobody before those books, and they came from the heart. She Harry came from misfortune and she fully understood that more than most writers because of her own misfortunes.

Though I don't believe I reach the full level of dislike for expanded universes that you do, I do find myself leery of them often. But I do think you have a point about Rowling. There's a level of earnestness in the books that simply isn't present elsewhere.  

I like it when authors start out by writing what they know. (If you ever want to read urban fantasy, I highly recommend the Monster Hunter International series. It's about a group of mercenaries that hunt werewolves, zombies and vampires for a living. It's written by a firearms expert).

I truly do not give one flying fuck about the egotistical, drama seeking person JK Rowling is now. Providing dumb extended universe arbitration. I could feel the passion in JK's writing.

I do think that there are some elements that are good about the Expanded Universe. For example, she did give an explanation for why Fenrir Greyback bit Remus Lupin. It was alluded to in the books, but never actually stated. But other elements seem...unnecessary. 

 It is gone now, because she was fully okay turning her art into a product.

I can understand the sentiment. My favorite comic script of all time is Calvin and Hobbes, and the creator flat-out refused to let there be much merchandise behind it. (Besides the book collections, there's a couple of rare calendars and a short study guide).

I will always love the original books. The 7 books.
I will never go onto Pottermore. I will never read the extended universe. I will never take buzzfeed quizzes to see which house I am in, or which character I am.

So will I. I love the original Harry Potter books, and the original movies. And I will buy new copies of the books.

It is the story about Harry Potter, it's not my story. I know people become so obsessed with the fandom they have to include themselves in the art. It's not my art, or my story.

I take it you don't read much in the way of fan fiction then?

I certainly have my issues with the fandom in general as well. I can't exactly condemn the people who draw themselves as Hogwarts students, but I do dislike some elements of fan art. Or rather, the common elements of fan art that are not canon, but a lot of fans treat as canon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And while there's certainly a place for that--it's not as if there wasn't a fair bit of political commentary (false imprisonment, governmental interference in education, corruption of money and power, censorship, discrimination) in the Harry Potter books--Rowling comments on a lot of things that aren't her area of expertise. 

And due to her profile, she gets a lot more attention than may be appropriate.

And, regardless of views, Twitter sucks for political commentary in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "DADDY" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, the magic is in the mystery of not knowing. Nothing's quite so wonderful as wonder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, for some reason, I never really remember the clown. 

But what about the junkyard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We only throw it away when it gets too little to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....

....

....

....

....

....
...

....

....

Can we pause the game again? Ow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it goes on like that for the entire story. And all the sequels. 

It never ceases to amaze me that this fic is so popular.

Harry is, quite frankly, an arse. To name one early example, when Ron is confused by Harry's request to be called by a different name (His offense is something along the lines of merely asking "Why, Harry?"), Harry's response to write him off as a moron who doesn't listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Miss Figg wasn't a witch. She was a Squib, a non-magical person born to wizarding parents. 

And I think it's implied she moved into the neighborhood on Dumbledore's orders to keep an eye on Harry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding on plot and foreshadowing to the characters, I do agree that Rowling doesn't do well on world-building. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24) Allegory and Parallel: The Religious Imagery of Harry Potter

As an aside, entire books have been written about this subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....

....

....

....

....

Can we pause the game for a moment? I wanna know what suppository means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secondhand Lions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that Bill Nye can be stand-offish too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually lampshaded in the movie "Big Fat Liar." Jaleel is shooting a movie for a director named Marty Wolfe, and after being called "Urkel" for the umpteenth time, he snarls "Wolfe, how many times do I have to tell you not to call me Urkel? My name is Jaleel White! Urkel is a character that I played when I was a child!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, Dr. Cox, want to play the Quiet Game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about "You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fair point, I think.

However, I feel that other films left out more important information. 

PoA left out some of the most important scenes from the book--the feud with Hermione is diluted, and the scenes in the Shrieking Shack are cut short. A not-insignificant subplot is the implied comparisons made between the friendships of the Marauders, and that of the "Golden Trio." 

Similarly, the adaptation of Half-Blood Prince left out a lot of material on the Horcruxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intense, and coupled with the single most disturbing death scene in the entire franchise, when noble Eddie, through no cause of his own (as I recall, he had very little to do with stealing the baby dinosaur), is attacked and then ripped in two by the tyrannosaurs, all the while trying to save the people who lured the tyrannosaurs to their camp in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about their shorts? *Toy Story Tale of Terror* and *Toy Story That Time Forgot* were both excellent holiday short films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so--it's been established that the parts work on their own, rather than co-relating to which body their attached to.

Potato Head was briefly a tortilla, and then a cucumber, and still had his own voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blake Clark (who I first knew as Chet Hunter on Boy Meets World) has done a great job filling in for Varney, who was apparently a personal friend of his.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's likely that GWB just misspoke. 

It's also possible that GWB read it to his children so often, or else heard his own mother read it to his children so often, that he simply mis-remembered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind if I chime in? I love the big cats and have lots of random facts about them.

The term "panther" is generally thought to refer to black jaguars, or more traditionally black leopards. Bagheera from "The Jungle Book" is probably the best known black panther.

However, the term "panther" can be used to refer to any of the five species of cat in the genus Panthera. The lion, tiger, leopard, snow leopard, and jaguar are all "panthers" in this respect.

The five species are also commonly called "Big Cats," an informal classification which also includes cheetahs and cougars in popular vernacular. Clouded leopards are occasionally grouped in here as well. Independently of this, cougars are sometimes called "panthers."

"Panther" is a term most commonly associated with melanism.

Melanism is a genetic condition that leads to an abundance of pigmentation, and is the opposite of albinism. Albinism is the complete lack of pigmentation, and must not be confused with leucism (a lack of most pigmentation--except for melanin).

Classic example of melanism include the black leopard and black jaguar. There have been very few reports of black lions or black tigers, but as far as I know, they've never been confirmed. What have been confirmed are pseudo-melanistic tigers, which have a more heavily striped coat and are actually somewhat smaller than their normal cousins. Conversely, the golden tabby tiger has been observed. As the name suggests, it has no dark stripes. It should also be noted that while the pseudo-melanistic tiger has been observed in the wild, the golden tabby tiger is strictly a captive beast, having been bred accidentally from white tigers.

Outside of anecdotal reports, African lions do not appear to exhibit melanism. However, there is at least one, potentially, partially-melanistic individual that has a leg that is noticeably darker in color than the rest of its body.

Despite **many** sightings, there has never been an authenticated account of a pure black melanistic cougar.

That said, native tribes of Mexico and the Southwestern United States, and Spanish explorers, told of "Onza." Similar to the mountain lion in most respects, it was said to be slimmer and some specimens had pale brown stripes on their legs, and most intriguingly had non-retractable claws. It was also said to be ferocious, capable of taking down fully armored conquistadors in broad daylight.

A cat was shot in 1986 matching the description of the onza and was found to be a mountain lion. So, "onza" appears to be a sufficiently rare mutation of mountain lion.

For what it's worth, cheetahs are among the only members of the cat family that have non-retractable claws, and they are the species most closely related to mountain lions. Several cryptozoologists hypothesized that the onza had been a relic of the American cheetah, which lived during the Ice Age.

As previously mentioned, melanism is the opposite of albinism. While there have been a handful of albino individuals among the Panthera species, the White Tigers and White Lions are more well-known. White tigers and lions are not albinos. White lions have the aforementioned condition, leucism, though the genes of white tigers are a bit more complicated.

Most white tigers have chocolate brown stripes and blue eyes, compared to the red eyes characteristic of albino individuals. So-called "stripeless" white tigers have been reported, and this is likely due to inbreeding. And again, the genes that cause it are similar to, but not identical to, leucism.

White Lions have a broader range of color, appearing anywhere from blond to white.

Finally, there is the King Cheetah. Similar to the pseudo-melanistic tiger, King Cheetahs have a majestic coat that features bars and stripes as opposed to the polka dot pattern characteristic of cheetahs.
When originally discovered, they were believed to be hybrids of leopards and cheetahs. Conversely, there exists a single known specimen of a spotless cheetah.
**********
While it is popularly assumed that only lions live in groups, this is not strictly true. While most cats are indeed solitary, male cheetahs have been seen to form small groups of two or three, occasionally more. Called coalitions, these groups tend to be made up of brothers of the same litter, but some coalitions include cousins or even unrelated members. As cheetahs are among the weakest of the "top" African predators, yielding their kills to lions, leopards, hyenas, and even Cape Hunting Dogs and baboons, hunting in coalitions allows them to take down larger prey.

Very recently, in the first photographic evidence of its kind, game cameras in Siberia captured a male Amur tiger assisting the female in raising the cubs. Occasional reports of male Bengal tigers raising orphaned cubs, and there have been unauthenticated reports of male leopards staying with their cubs from the Congo as well.

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2986109/Do-male-tigers-play-dad-Camera-trap-captures-rare-family-portrait-Amur-tiger-couple-three-cubs-wild.html?ITO=1490 ns_mchannel=rss ns_campaign=1490
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharptooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Air Conditioner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is interesting as a prompt, and for what it's worth, I'd like to give a little shout-out to the most badass dentist I know of: Ben Salomon.

http://www.badassoftheweek.com/index.cgi?id=587622426994

Oh, crud. The prompt is actually about BEING a dentist, not a dentist in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short and sweet, I enjoyed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, this was good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, I think Books A Million is doing a good job trying to maintain a balance between the new ways and the old.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this description is very fair, and not entirely unfounded.

Hindsight is 20/20, they probably were expecting people to keep wanting to go into stores to buy things.

I think this is still true for some things. Take bookstores for example. Although Amazon exists--to say nothing of Kindles--a lot of people still like to go to bookstores and libraries and read physical copies of books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be right back, r/WritingPrompts and r/worldbuilding are calling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stages of Hope is my single favorite fanfic, and I will love it forever.

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/6892925/1/Stages-of-Hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] "Treasure hunter? No, I'm more of a treasure protector." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in New England, and I say "alrighty-then" a lot.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell has nobody said Leland Yee yet?

A state senator from California, Yee was arrested on corruption charges.

Specifically, Yee took millions of dollars in bribes to help smuggle RPGs and machine guns through the Chinese mob, through the Ukraine, to rebels in the Philippines.  

This happened in 2014. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Chik-fil-A do this this already a couple years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By comparison, when Franklin was introduced to the Peanuts comic script, the explicit intent was for him to be seen as normal. And we got one of the friendliest, gentlest characters in the entire franchise for it.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franklin_(Peanuts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Slow clap*

*Regular clap*

*Fast clap*

*Thunderous applause* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Silver Trio fics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any good stories on Ginny, Neville and Luna? I'm not particular about when in the story it's set, though I prefer not to have slash

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't quite what you asked for, but Dudley (yes, really) actually travels back in time, and wastes very little time in going to Dumbledore, though they agree to pace things out slowly, with Dudley only revealing what he knows per school year, since his information is second-hand.

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/9662175/1/Dudley-Dursley-and-the-Sorcerer-s-Stone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm....

Harry's the leader, but doesn't want to be. I guess that means he's on guitar.

Hermione strikes me as a cellist. You can have the cello in a band.

Ron...Ron plays the French horn.

Neville rocks out on the drums, with awesome drum solos.

Ginny plays the piano. Not the keyboard, a piano.

Luna? A one-witch polka set (Polka will never die) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with me on Sirius. Though at least "Cyrus" or "Syrus" at least sound like the belong in a book about magic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was always my favorite rendition of the character. The action was stylistic and fluid, the serialization was spot-on. I loved Spectacular Spider-Man.

As happy as I am that Spidey will be in the MCU, I can't help but think that maybe he should have a Netflix series rather than movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great scene, in a superb series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I tend to think that being a man means following this philosophy:

Sometimes, the things that may or may not be true are the things a man needs to believe in the most. That people are basically good. That honor, courage, and virtue mean everything. Power and money, money and power. mean nothing. Good should always triumph over evil and that love, true love never dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You uncultured swine!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, I believe that Rowling actually gave some more details on how Time Turners work. Pottermore and what not.

The whole "You've already changed the past/stable time loop" is present in the third book, and apparent in the film, but the background info says that when they were first invented, they were abused, and apparently one witch went back far enough that it resulted in several people being "unborn."

http://harrypotter.wikia.com/wiki/Time-Turner

That said, Cursed Child was still a supremely idiotic story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three more, plus the television series that is set before XIV.

XII was the Day of the Flyers. Petrie had a day in the limelight. Cera got a new baby sister

XIII was Wisdom of Friends...less said about it the better.

Then there was the television series. 

Finally there was XIV, Journey of the Brave, featuring Reba as a friendly flyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait? Episode IX: Journey to the Big Water was the one who made you cry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name was actually spelled "Cera." As in Tri*cera*tops. 

For what it's worth, her father was eventually given the name "Topsy" in the sequel movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Substitute chemistry teacher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh him, I thought you said the Great Bambi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.rotoscopers.com/2017/03/23/disneys-live-action-the-lion-king-production-starts-in-may-donald-glover-and-james-earl-jones-join-cast/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, I was wondering, do you know the Muffin Man? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, whitetail are among several species whose population has actually increased compared to its pre-colonization levels.

We killed most of the wolves and mountain lions in the East (though if eyewitnesses are to be believed, they may have moved further into their old range than previously though), and now whitetail population is, I believe, about 16 million. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time I can remember hearing it being done for real is when people chanted "U-S-A" after Bin Laden was killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking for myself, I always found "My Old Lady" to be among the saddest episodes.

Specifically, I always found Turk's patient, the young man not a day over twenty, saddest.

JD's patient was a little old lady, who as you said is happy. She's lived her life, and by all accounts, it was one hell of a life.
Elliot's patient is sad, but we spend very little time with her. It's hard to get attached.

But Turk's patient is just a kid, and we do spend a lot of time with him, and we do get attached and it's pretty clear that he's terrified. He's young and he has his whole life ahead of him, but he's sick, and he doesn't know what happens next. You can really see this right when Turk starts to reach out to him.

The worst part is when they wheel him into surgery. He's smiling. This kid is stricken with cancer but he's smiling. He is smiling because his doctor is his friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent point, Sarah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to this, it was Passover, so Jews from all over the Roman Empire were traveling to Judea for the ceremonies.

Because of this influx of many additional travelers, the money changers were able to cheat the Jews gathered for Passover, by exchanging extremely unfair rates. They also were selling animals for temple sacrifices--essentially saying that you had to pay money in order to be forgiven.

This is part of why Jesus's outcry was "You have made my Father's house into a den of thieves!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, Hamm, look! I'm Picasso! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but sometimes even very fascinating subjects have very simplistic, uninteresting names.

Take the beginning of the universe. Scientists call it the "Big Bang." Why don't they be more descriptive, and call it the "Horrendous Space Kablooie"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was terrific! I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I get some love for Fractured Fairy Tales?

The True Story of the Three Little Pigs

The Three Little Wolves and the Big Bad Pig

The Stinky Cheese Man and Other Fairly Stupid Tales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Reading About Dragons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.deviantart.com/art/Reading-About-Dragons-455716317 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I fixed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this one even going to work? Are they making Squirrel Girl an Inhuman? 

Or maybe Thanos plays with the Infinity Gauntlet and some magic what-have-you just poofs more bizarre powers onto people lucky enough to survive the War? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
