<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject82</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drugs have been used as stimulants in warfare for a long time, it is thought that Old Norse berserkers would consume hallucinogenic mushrooms or a bunch of alcohol before battle. There is also a book I read a few years ago called [A Long Way Gone](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Long_Way_Gone) by Ishmael Beah. It's a memoir about his life as a child soldier in the civil war of Sierra Leone in the 90's. The kids were given "brown brown", "white pills", and marijuana to brainwash them and numb them to violence.

There's also a podcast by Stuff They Don't Want You To Know called [Is The Military On Drugs?](http://www.stufftheydontwantyoutoknow.com/podcasts/is-the-military-on-drugs.htm) which is discusses the practice throughout history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so it begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Menzingers - Lookers [punk rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 05:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pipeline spills 176,000 gallons of crude into creek about 150 miles from Dakota Access protest camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Lightsaber windshield wiper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's all toast to Prohibition being repealed 83 years ago today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 2 million pounds of undercooked chicken recalled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This site has them. They must have had a stockpile sitting around in a warehouse and then got burnt when they became illegal.

https://buckyforever.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can Legally Purchase Buckyballs in the U.S. Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grinch flicks cigarette on parade float, setting it on fire on the way to Huntsville Christmas Parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is exactly what I was thinking. Also there's that new property tax bill which was just passed so all the rates will be even higher. Slick move, Chicago, slick move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
