<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  W. Anderson

I bet you saved a lot of time by shortening 'Wes' to 'W." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares what he thought? He was an asshole and not a very good reviewer, because he was bad at objectivity. Seen [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c5bWkv0eV3M). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the first couple issues of Crossed so I kinda know what I'm getting into, but I'd rather see just about any number of beloved human characters die before an animal one (I know I sound like every other person on the internet by saying that).

But yeah, that last page in the first issue of Crossed kinda fucked me up because I was already having a really shitty day, I don't know if I could handle that but with dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the traffic so bad? Like I get that it takes longer to get places, but there was insane traffic on the most random fucking roads.

Like I was stopped for about 20 minutes on Division. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry! I thought my 4 hours was bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm scared to read it. The description makes it seem like a hyper-violent Homeward Bound which seems awesome, but I don't want to see cute animals die horrible, brutal deaths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shitting at work and the music plays in the bathroom, and the song White Christmas was playing when I read this comment, and it even sorta synced the words when I got there.

Huh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why has there never been an Iron Giant comic?

Never mind the movie's perfect leave it be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Olivia Wilde is my dream pick for Catwoman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New player, I've got a few questions about guns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 05:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (question)

The single shot battle rifles seem to be the best, as they seem to have higher DPSes and greater accuracy. Is that the case, or am I missing something?

Also, how do I craft decent guns? I have a bunch of blueprints but all the guns I can make are way worse than what I'm currently using. Is there a 'special ingredient" to increase the damage, accuracy, RoF, etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading Moby-Dick makes you tough.

Only sorta kinda kidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he put his whole name in the post, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought I installed Battlefield 4 but I'm playing World of Tanks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay the title is a bad joke, but I swear, this game is dominated by tanks. Admittedly, I just got the game last week, but I played a lot of BF3 and it wasn't like this. I feel like I win most mano a mano fights, but then a tank comes along and fucks my shit up. Even with the Engineer class, I'm powerless to the might of the Abrams.

I realize that its a tank vs man and the tank should usually come out on top, but there doesn't seem to be any alternative to death, pretty much ever.

Is there something I should be doing to increase my survivability, or is everyone doomed when they encounter an enemy tank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I never got to watch it without knowing the twist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 36 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I was thinking, what's the Blair Witch Project without found footage? Then I thought, potentially good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be such a sad movie, if it followed the source material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this comment made me cum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go into not with low expectations, you'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not always like that though.

Source: I met my girlfriend on tinder while messing with people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but that has nothing to do with the comic being a money grab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, if you consider doing your job a money grab. I guess we could call the original Fight Club a money grab as well, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doolittle wasn't their first album yo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question wasn't "what movies have a dark ending" Jesus Christ people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except it was written after the first, intended to be a sequel, has a continuity, and was published with permission of the author, unlike the TKaM "sequel". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had to assume those movies ended badly? It flat out shows you what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh weird I always heard it was. I'll probably skip that one then.

Thank you so much for all the recommendations! And I will check out Weapon X. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the guy you responded to, but did you think it was scary at all? I can kind of get that being the reason you like it, but that's about it.

Legitimate question for you since you know about the subject. It seemed like it was barely about witches, and more about paranoia and the [devil](#spoiler). The witches only did a few things, and [the goat](#spoiler) seemed to be the main antagonist. If I'm not wrong (which I could be, I'm not the one with extensive knowledge on witchcraft), why did the movie resonate with you so much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> durr hurr if he didn't like this horror movie he must only like jump scare movies

Don't act like you know shit about me. When I say I'm huge on horror, it means I know a little something about horror. My favorite horror movies are the old Universal Monsters movies and the Thing, along with others a fan of Boring Atmosphere and Pretension: The Movie probably haven't heard of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha awesome, I'm glad you love it, its my favorite too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm using Marvel Unlimited and buying what I can't get from there. Unfortunately my local library only has like five comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Age of Apocalypse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I really want to read those FF runs, but for some reason I don't like reading them more than once in a while. I get burnt out quick which is weird because they're a lot of fun.

Anyway, thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol fuck off

The Witch (I'm not going to spell it with the double V's because I'm not an idiot) was bullshit on so many levels. I'm huge on horror and a pretty big movie buff so I'm not one of those people complaining just because it was boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going through Marvel's history. Need help with suggestions and reading order. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting a long process of reading a lot of characters I haven't read much of over the years, and I'm also trying to read most of the events in order. I know there's the FAQ but, in order to keep the cost low(er) and save some time, I'm probably only gonna read one or two arcs for most characters, so I'm trying to get a feel for the best of the best. I need suggestions for:

- Spider-Man

- Beta Ray Bill

- Hulk

- Silver Surfer

- Nick Fury

- Vision and Scarlet Witch

- Rocket Raccoon

- Valkyrie

- Daredevil

- Avengers

- Black Panther

- Agents of Atlas

- Polaris

- D-Man

- She Hulk

- West Coast Avengers

- Thunderbolts

Aside from that, I'm also looking for:

- Best Claremont X-Men stories

- Best stories with or about Dr. Doom

- Good stories that feature Colossus and Nightcrawler being buds

- And Cyclop's story arc/evolution through the years

Already in my reading list:

- Pretty much all the large scale events (and a lot of their companion stories because I'm a masochist)

- Epic Collection Vol. 1 for FF, Iron Fist, and Power Man and Iron Fist

- Remender's Uncanny X-Force

- X-Men Legacy: Legion

- Frank Miller's Daredevil

- Superior Foes of Spider-Man

- Hickman's Fantastic Four

- Deadpool and Cable

- Marvel Zombies

-Planet Hulk and WWH

- Hawkeye by Matt Fraction

- Pretty much all Moon Knight

- Invincible Iron Man: My Monsters (it was a dollar)

- Tom King's Vision (got the second half left)

- Punisher: War Journal

- Old Man Logan

- Dr. Strange   Dr. Doom: Triumph   Torment

I plan on reading everything in the order that it was published with a few exceptions like  [this](http://i.imgur.com/N7OXfyI.jpg).

I know this probably seems kinda daunting but if you have any suggestions I would love to hear them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way that movie's plot could have been enjoyable to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Bounty Killer? Its on Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm doing is going through the Marvel universe's biggest/best/most important moments, and hitting characters I like along the way. So I'm starting with the original Fantastic Four and Spider-Man runs, and then slowly moving forward, hitting some early Avengers when that time comes, etc.

I already have a decent understanding of a lot of Marvel but I've never known a lot about the in-universe history, and I want to rectify that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna have to make another post for it. I think there's at least 20 characters and runs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it okay to ask for suggested reading order/runs here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a whole slew of characters and events I want to read and I could use some help on picking the best parts of each, but I don't know if I'm allowed to do that here. I trust you guys more than /r/comicbooks (I like that sub but this is more specialized) and /r/comicbooksuggest. I totally get if that's not allowed here, but I didn't see anything in the rules.

Also I realize the irony of this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 10:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is so perfect holy crud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I don't remember the context. Just reverse image search it if you wanna know more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://theheartisanorganthatpumpblood.files.wordpress.com/2008/05/n1.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks sort of like Del Mundo's art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem fun.

But not really. I was being facetious before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 05:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment inspired me to become an EMT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Read Watchmen. Yeah it has pictures but it's a real book. Yeah there are superheroes but it's more than that."

Then you read it.

And then you decide you want more, so you look for more books in the series, but those are shit, so you look to other series. And then you discover more comics you like. And slowly but surely, you build a collection and hide it in your closet.

And if you're me, you spend a third of your rent money on books because it's black Friday and instocktrades has some bitchin deals and you have no self control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's not even what that means even kind of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooooh, that does make sense. Thanks for the clarification, and I will check those out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not judging I was looking at Walmart.com last night haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 10:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read nazi as nat-zee automatically.

Good stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 08:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pumped for this until I saw the cast. None of those, barring maybe Angelina Jolie and Javier Bardem, are good for those roles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 07:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 07:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that even mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is potentially one of the worst things I've ever read. I think I could go on for an hour about why I hate this, but I will not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a spoiler. That's kind of the premise of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I've heard of those! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't pick one off of it so I'll just say Sufjan Steven's Songs for Christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls, I need your help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I buy a dress that isn't shitty or super expensive? I want to get my girlfriend one because that's what she said she wants but I know fuckall about buying clothes, especially for girls.

Online is preferred but I can go to stores too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay don't get too overhyped for Saga because that will ruin it. It's my favorite comic but don't let it get too overexaggerated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't fucking understand why Marvel isn't giving King's Vision an omnibus. It seemed to be one of everyone's top picks for the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 03:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Polaris and Gambit did go out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 03:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I'm not even referencing something, my first name is Gage and you're not far off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this my name is Gage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 02:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they would do Apocalypse Now so much.

Also Heat, Charlie Bartlett, and Metropolis.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relatively new to movie collecting, and I've got some questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 10:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been buying DVDs forever, but I never considered it collecting until recently. Now I realize it's a bit more complicated than I expected. So, a few questions.

Is there a good way to know what movies have "special editions" of some sort? Most of my favorite recent movies have been by A24 like Green Room and Ex Machina, which I thought didn't have special editions but apparently Ex Machina has a steelbook. I would never have known if I hadn't accidentally stumbled upon it.

While on the topic of steelbooks, what's the point? I got the It Follows steelbook and it seemed like it was just a different case. I'm fine with that but I don't get why people like them so much, for the price, if they don't have any special extras or anything. I'm probably missing something there but the steelbook website didn't have much to say.

Is Criterion *always* the best edition?

Does anyone set up cooler movies so the cover is facing outward, to display the art? If so, can I get some pictures as a reference?

I've noticed a lot of newer movies have slipcovers that just look like the regular cover. What is the point?

Also it seems like most new movies have like barely any special features? The Nice Guys, Bone Tomahawk, and the Lobster are three off the top of my head. That's no fun, yo.

Other than Criterion and Steelbook, are there any other 'brands' I should be on the lookout for?

Thanks for your time, and sorry if these are dumb/common questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 10:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay cool, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 09:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say Royal Tenenbaums has the visual flair and a romantic subplot of the two you've seen (and it's also my favorite). The Life Aquatic is probably up your alley too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 09:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any way to get those Best Buy Elite deals without spending $1500? Ex Machina, It Follows, and Independence Dayfor $4 each. Yes please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 07:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that song was a meme tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 06:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steinbeck because every reason.

The only faults in his writings (IMO) are the way women were almost universally portrayed in a very negative way, and the way he wrote about religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only things we're missing are fingerless gloves and the yellow tinted Guy Fawkes mask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mortal Kombat is so bad it's good, with some parts that are actually legitimately good.

Mortal Kombat: Annihilation (?) is so bad it goes past being 'so bad it's good' and back to being bad. Like that movie isn't even fun to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is bullshit I demand a different cover.

I mean Mercury's from Portland, I don't care if she hasn't been an Avenger whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin brutal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or we could stop being pedantic little shits and use whichever we want to say. It's not like the point isn't made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait who are the four? I've only seen a few episodes of each series so far, but I know there's DD, Punisher, Electra, Cage, and Jessica Jones, and we have Iron Fist coming. So...who isn't making the cut? Please don't answer this with spoilers for any of the shows, as I plan on watching them soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 10:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did anyone justify this story (other than making loadsemony off that sweet, sweet movie fan crowd)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MRAxGWmzAxc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see that I'm upset it isn't real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of art, is Rebels just like Clone Wars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it not phonetic? I've always read it like Kull-en </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is almost a week old but I figured I'd say something in case you're still on the fence. I've only read the 15th issue but that seems like a good place to start, and I'm gonna pick up #16 next time I go in.

Personally, I like it because it has a lot of variety in characters, and the characters I like are done right. The art is really good, and I think the artist just changed, so you're in the clear there. Right now they're fighting the Hand and spoiler, I guess? The Hulk. Deadpool is pretty alright, it is Duggan writing, so mostly jokey character, but not the meme character he has become under other writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait why was this music playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean no-holds barred? Disney wasn't the edgy Nazi people always make him out to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a list of releases that have stuff like this? I'm tempted to try and look through mine but I'm scared that I'll just end up ripping apart the packaging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 04:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the words though

I'm not being snarky I'm just actually curious for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 04:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He draws the best She-Hulk, in my opinion.

And that's all I know about him. This thread is confusing and I didn't know comic books were so political. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 03:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no one else is gonna mention how the top two panels kinda looks like just one panel where half of Batman's face is covered by shadow but also super fucked up and small? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write something in, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Frog Man one killed me and I didn't even know of his existence.

Also

 married a robot ha ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking kidding me? What a shitty week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they didn't vote, do we really care? It would be their own fault if they didn't get what they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty common style of clothing over there, so to say it looks like Kim Jong In is like saying she looks like a middle aged woman because of her hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me preface this by saying that I sure as hell don't agree with the other guy. There is an intolerable amount of racism within the police force, and that's not to say all cops are bad, yadda yadda yadda.

However, it isn't unreasonable to dislike BLM. They've pulled some unacceptable stuff, and there are better ways of handling the problem.

However,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice idea but that isn't how the human mind works. People generally want people to like them, despite political ideals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol like I'd waste money on a film class, I form my own opinions.

There might be better ones, but I saw that first and its what got me into his movies, so its my favorite.

So you can get the last word, and I can look like an idiot? Okay sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait you can do it with bots? Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As with everything else, Dr. Doom is the best in this category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Seven Samurai

 boring vanilla choice

Do you even know what you're saying? That's not a mainstream movie and boring is almost laughably wrong.

And maybe I didn't feel the need to start a completely pointless argument? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And having Kurosawa, FF Coppolla, and Carpenter is boring?

I don't get why you'd criticize my list if you submit that limiting it to 5 is dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same thing you're doin mate. I'm waiting on a job interview so I don't have much to take up my time anyway.

Really, if the joke's on me, then the joke's on both of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
