<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4639</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loophole, bitches! Can't throw it anymore now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt the beeping had a rhythm. Like

Beep...beepadeep...beepadeep.......badeep...


I miss beep. #BeepIsLove </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol all praise beep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...I think it finally stopped.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The refs are so in charge of the league they can even fuck with the almighty ad break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google, you really shouldn't use "OK Google" in your ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exclusively on NFL Network means no channel wants that shitfest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He who destroys has been destroyed. 

All is lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Something Hallas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green 18 is because #18 is Szechuan green beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shitty drop by that random dude standing near security outside of the end zone. See it's not all Rodgers fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOYER THE ~~DESTROYER~~ OVERTHROWER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also we won't pay you, but you get to meet Jamie Foxx  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over under on the time in the game when we see a packers player has pooped himself at 7 minutes into the 3rd quarter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really digging the gloss on the numbers/stripes on the packers uniforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's absolutely what he was doing.  It just looked funny to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this the other day. Found it funny (not in a troll way). Luck doing an angry shake-fist. (Credit to /u/Fusir/) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [At the very end of the sack](https://gfycat.com/AffectionateVillainousAmericantoad)

I'm not here to hate on Luck or praise Luck or anything circlejerk Luck. I just thought that was a funny reaction to a play and you might enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the "smartest" head coach in the NFL just basically said Microsoft Surfaces were trash. Huge fucking PR hit.

Even if slight, if MS could get the slightest dig in on a big stage that Macs are just as unreliable... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, did fox just try to save microsoft's ass by mentioning his ipad breaking down? After the Belichick smackdown... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary just proposed a "middle out" solution to solving the national debt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clip pls, anyone?

Edit : Please keep this thread civil.  This is not meant to start or be a political discussion. I just thought it was funny.  Keep to the sub rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely same reaction both my friend and I had. Both in tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks a bit larger than the Saturn from the series "what would the other planets look like if they were as close as the moon." [Here](https://youtu.be/usYC_Z36rHw)

I'm no mathematician, but if Saturn were closer than the moon, it would certainly fuck up our oceans. Probably at some point (relatively quickly)our orbit would decay and we'd get splattered on Saturn. I don't see how any of the inner planets would survive, either smashing thrm or screwing their orbits and flinging them out of the system. The extra gravity would probably eventually draw Jupiter closer to the inner system. Which would in turn have a slight effect on Neptune/Uranus, the loss of mass in the outer system possibly sending Pluto out of the system also. 

That's vaguely what would happen if Saturn was teleported to that orbit, at least. But you could also interpret that picture as, "there's obvious human civilization with Saturn in the background", which would mean we've ways been in orbit with Saturn (likely as its moon). Which would probably mean mercury, Venus, and probably Mars never became planets, and over a span of time we probably don't need to worry about all that outer planets stuff might happen.

Edit: Seeing from the other answers that I mostly got this right, hooray! Forgot about gravitational effects on continents tho... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thought so. Seemed like others were blaming the PT. Even the title on the imgur page... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt it the car/truck in the far right that starts this? The PT was passing on the left, far right causes middle to swerve which causes the pt to swerve, eventually hitting thr truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gfycat.com/AffectionateVillainousAmericantoad

Credit to /u/Fusir/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man you are amazing! Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 05:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear mighty giffers maybe 45 mins ago was the play where luck got sacked, but there was a facemask. In the live feed, after being tackled luck makes an old man yelling at clouds gestures. Any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 05:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell are they chanting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 05:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So like 2 drives ago maybe, when luck was sacked and there was a facemask, and after getting sacked he went to indicate facmask but made an angry man yells at clouds gesture. Any chance I could get a gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great response and definitely the vibe I was feeling. It's (97) well intentioned but seemed to be poorly targeted and/or overly aggressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love my quarterback :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing from that article, is it mentions it's a 2.5% tax, and what I knew before is that's on gross receipts.

So I tried to imagine the "worst case" for something like Umqua. I tried to find their actual financial reports but of course those aren't easy, although I did find their "revenue" is close to $50m per year.

So then I thought, $50m revenue, let's say they only actually take in $100k as net.  Well, 2.5% of that would only be $2500. That doesn't seem like something that would make or break Umqua dairy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you (and everyone so far) who's replied and kept it civil. Go Bend! 

You mentioned it may help small businesses, which I'm for. But it's the more regional businesses I'm concerned about. Wilco etc. The ads (not that I necessarily believe them) say those are the businesses that'll probably get hurt most. And then Safeway or some other nationwide takes over. That's something I hope doesn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to read this more thoroughly in the morning, tho bearing in mind the comment below.

Edit: But thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] I would like input on 97. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, please no trolls. I'm looking for a reasoned response either way.

I went to the site with the summary/arguments for and against 97.

I thought it sounded pretty okay. I liked there were ways to avoid paying the tax, by doing green things or whatever . I don't recall exact numbers on how much of that stuff they'd have to do to get the break. And it closed an apparent gap, which, I'm all for (reasonable) taxes for.

But two things gave me pause.

1) Can't recall exact numbers, but I think they're trying to close a $900m gap? That's like, a lot. But...the site said the measure would generate a revenue, again don't recall, but I do remember thinking it was a *lot* bigger than the gap. Like a more reasonable tax could close the gap.

2) When it mentions companies like wilco umqua etc. I'm still pissed that Rays had to close because of Safeway. A nationwide company can more easily absorb those kinds of losses. 

But. How much of an actual hit would those companies take? I guess I'm asking would the net profit to tax ratio be that terrible for those semi-local companies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, interesting, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least in my state, all that matters is the national requirement to have a bachelor's degree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that is a business by business decision, and not something that automatically rules you out from the beginning.  But there may be specific state rules that apply? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real estate appraiser.  For all you youngins out there who just graduated college and are working a shitty cafe job and don't know what to do, I highly recommend looking into this.  

[I wrote a lot and answered a bunch of questions about it here](https://www.reddit.com/r/savedyouaclick/comments/4xit32/the_25_most_promising_jobs_for_millennials_list/d6g6cxp) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he kicked the field goal almost the second he was in range I was impressed. A lot of coaches would keep wasting the clock going for the TD first even when two scores are needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wait I remember during the Bengals game people were asking why weren't the helmets white/black striped. And lots of replies said helmets can't change during the season. So waddup with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Idiotic. And the special teams coach was the head coach, of course he has more variations ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously who ices an inside kick?!  So they'll just pull some other formation you aren't 100% prepared for?! So stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go Retardgers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... 1-4? So week 6? The sidebar is fucking with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha haha kill me now*


*Note: applicable through most of the season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate being so easily exploited, but yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here hear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His only game so far, last week, was pretty studly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every goddamn week Phil Simms will guess an injury, and immediately say "you hate to guess an injury..."

Then why do you do it every goddamn week, Phil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bosa ain't hurt. Just wanted to show he's awesome then fuck the chargers bc of the offseason bs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thursday night for a fail team that's likely leaving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend works Sundays, comes over for primetime games. We watched the 49ers last home game. I pointed out to him how empty the stands were, and see how (in)frequently mention it. I told him to pay attention tonight to how often they show other colors in the stands etc.

Edit lol okay the only blue is the stands. Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...does that account for all the missing matter that dark matter is supposed to account for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thanks for all the work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 06:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only think of a brute force analysis, but thinking some of you have better search/parsing/etc?

And um, any time all four championship teams did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Game Thread] The Undefeated - A Conversation with The President: Sports, Race   Achievement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 04:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So um there isn't really a good place to talk about this thread?  Thought I'd do a game thread for it? 


Player | Time of possession
---|---
Obama | 78%


**8:02** - Obama delivers an eloquent and well argued defense of the importance of getting out to vote.  Emphasizes that regardless of the party you choose, you should get out to vote for the one that best represents your ideals.

**8:05** - Nhawndie Shaw asks a tough question regarding the recent death of Michael Brown.

**8:11** - Obama mentions task force(s?) created to work on this. Emphasizes independent inquiries. Better education.  Emphasis on "protecting and serving."  Vote local, Obama can't get involved in every town's problem.

**8:14** - It's over.  No one cares?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure of a good way to research this - If the Cardinals   Panthers both end up with a losing record, would that be the first time *both* Championship game teams from the previous year ended with losing records? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So **if** we do a town pallete, right now it's based on the idea that we settle in desert. If we end up somewhere else, these ideas may get scrapped.  

But these two images are from a flower called a Desert Rose and they would more or less be an idea of the pallete.  [1](http://i.enkivillage.com/PQDSeHm0g9uXEpNsPhr1iQn5AjM=/800x0//images/8c168bceed35c49b4952bba2c926f57f.jpg) [2](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/6a/16/86/6a16860db685cfdaf0360bc32972d5f4.jpg)

So reds/pinks (wool (probably not as a primary material), clays, etc) and tans (sandstone, wool, clays, etc) for the primary colors, with some white/black accents. 

Again, that's only a possibility even if we settle in the desert, but we're looking for feedback. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like *far* from being the oldest coach too isn't he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait kubiak had a heart attack on the field like 2-3 years ago right? Is this related? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait why am I not saying this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game thread. I've seen more action repairing tony romos back. 

I'll be here all week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm here to drink liquor and look optimistically at the chargers season, and I'm all outta looking optimistically at the chargers season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 21:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last season backup on titans I think, chargers most of his career. Think he did a year or two in Seattle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first taste was "uh it's really cold guacamole?" But then it quickly grew on me. Also super easy to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made it. It's delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The redzone channel guy said "Charlie Whitehurst will be attempting a hail Mary. Insert joke here."

Love the recognition clipboard Jesus gets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha the clipboard Jesus joke about throwing the hail Mary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fedorowicz? 

M'tightend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marcus Maryoto! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whitehurst makes 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Next Rev] Rev 18 Feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 04:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you like? What did you hate? What would you like to see more of? What do you want to see less of? 

Note (the following is *possible* but nothing set in stone yet) 

We may be heading towards a desert, possibly mesa.  We may also be keeping an eye out for other interesting terrains in general.  

A portal isn't a primary concern, but if we find one it may be worth trading for better area later? (Portals are nice, but elytra/new boats/horses/rails make everything pretty accessible.)

There are some ideas of going back to a "town palette" - i.e. all builds ~~use~~ incorporate a certain range of blocks.  

___________

Leave your thoughts here!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must be it. They align almost perfectly with where it was in the region when comparing it with google maps.

Thanks! That's awesome!

Edit: I guess why I considered it odd is I probably don't see weather diversions often because of the weather.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a height that would leave contrails?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but what little I know is, flight paths are typically chosen in arcs/straight lines. Changing course by as much as a cardinal direction seems like a shitty flight path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly unlikely. I could still see the aircraft leaving the contrail, and it was a perfect rounded turn.  I should clarify, it was eventually a 90 degree turn but had a smooth curve to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I saw a contrail that had made a 90 degree turn (could still see the plane leaving the trail, it wasn't wind). Is there any way to find out what happened? Because that seems like a rare thing to happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some place where I can check flight paths over my area at a certain time? I'm not really into aviation, that just seemed odd to me. 

It was at about 9:45 AM in Central Oregon, the flight seemed to be heading west (possibly SF-Boise?). The turn had it heading (roughly) in the direction of Portland, Oregon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [What If] Trade Rivers to the Cardinals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 08:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pros: Rivers and Fitzgerald may get a ring?

Cons:Lose one of my all time favorite chargers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally put the Cardinals over under at 11. I can see them getting a td-fg from turnovers. But no way is Drew Stanton going over that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them. There will never be another punt in the NFL because they will all be used in this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dig em but like someone else said, gold trim around the numbers would be nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. But football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stadium is so empty, the crowd could fit between Sam Bradford's eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The three Jamie Foxx's all support the 49ers based on tie colors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If enough bricks are thrown at you to build a castle, isn't it likely you're the villain?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way my friend and I described them last night was - McAdoo looks like east coast pedophile, Zimmer looks like Midwest pedophile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer the version from an email to this year's "why your team sucks" - if the chargers had a dedicated fanbase they'd be the Cleveland browns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eagles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll probably see a lot of these same people complaining about McCoy playing too conservative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rivers really does run like a hybrid of roethlisberger and Manning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need a two birds majority?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are there defenses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, time to put the second layer of stain on my coffee table... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw cmon they're both awesome with shitty front offices around them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to start hot coming out of the half... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which fanbase will be happier with a win vs which fanbase would prefer the higher draft pick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of how this game goes, beers will push through </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the fire in Gordon, like he took last season personal.

That being said, no more getting flipped pls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Brees/Rivers shootout? 

What could be better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have applied the first coat of stain to my used coffee table that I'm fixing up. Just have a few hours to wait til the next coat. 

I fear applying that second coat would be a far more valuable use of my time than watching this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit the ravens rb lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn Steve Smith is still a beast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Announcers said they both arrived Friday which is later that normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't there a game later this season in Mexico city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looked like the ref wanted to throw a flag, realized how many had already been thrown this game, and kept it in his pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 16:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is terrible. But...it's football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 02:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His arm was hit during the pass attempt, how can that be intentional grounding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 01:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the only top 25 team not playing on a proper TV network? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an Aaron Rodgers hater, but in that state farm commercial, he looks like he's never given a speech like that ever. Clay Matthews I can believe. But Rodgers has never given a locker room speech like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 16:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my job involves lots of driving, and these are great when on the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, I have to watch John Wick for the 20th time, how ever will I deal with that... 

:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> btw, changing my movie to Basquiat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that'sthejoke.gif  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central Oregon. From now til late next June, mostly 50 or colder with plenty of gloom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Born there and college there but central Oregon now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went with gin and tonic, which breaks a several year streak of bourbon and football. But it's my summer drink, and today looks like the last day of summer in my area... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They made some deal where only like 1/2 the games are simulcast on another network. Basic drug dealer technique, give you a tase to get you hooked, then make you start paying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm here to drink liquor and watch football, and I still have plenty of liquor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twist: all of those points come on a single play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So tostitos advocates keeping a black man trapped in your pantry during a party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It screwed with me bad this week. On Tuesday I woke up and thought "there was Thursday night football last night, it's Friday! Awesome!"

Was not fun to remember I watched Monday night football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember - the Bengals, at home, are in white. The visiting Dolphins are in orange. 

Because logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. Generally I just feel like if you're presenting a dish for others to see, including the recipe would be obvious. I'm sure I could Google a random duck au poivre but maybe this looked particularly excellent and I wanted to make exactly that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a long time lurker, why does it seem very rare for recipes to be attached? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real estate appraiser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you miss the pregame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey NFL, you're exploiting a tragedy at this point, not honoring it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Tin Pan Theater showed the election results last election.  Maybe they'll be doing something? Not a bar exactly, but they do serve beer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they gonna win thanks to bullshit?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for running a quick play and not letting us waste a challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BIG MAN WITH BALL!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with the bolts. I was still nervous til the end last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still the first quarter guys. No reason to be throwing in the towel already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, San Diego is further south than Indy. How about we take your spot until Rivers retires? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up at 7 am today. 3 hours until football sucks. How do you east coasters deal with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck kinda haircut was that dudes behind elway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this comment is very underrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 09:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That graphic of most wins was so depressing. 8 to 10 seasons and BB will have the most all time wins. No way he's retiring until then. I was hoping he'd be gone soon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the Texans approach the week like they'd be playing Brady? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 14:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it end before she finishes?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I just turned off this episode about 20 minutes in and that'll be the end of that for me. 

This episode started with a family I know nothing about. Great? Then it cuts to someone we know...and the series's millionth flashback. Then back to normal times and then another flashback.  That's when I turned it off. 

For me, how this show was originally pitched, "before the breakout," sounded great. They gave up on that after 4 episodes and now it's just stupid people doing stupid things, with a million flashbacks to try to get you to care about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shouldn't "ok" (emphasis on lowercase) be "ok" by now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 07:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still see places that either write out "okay" or use "OK."  Why not deem "ok" acceptable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 07:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...so why was he taken so high...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 07:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're a Panthers fan I'll admit I was totally wrong about Cam. I thought, "Oh yeah, another running quarterback, that always works..."

His first season proved me so so wrong and I've grown to love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 06:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to admit before the season, I really only knew 2 things about the Eagles - 

1) Their new head coach was the guy who "masterminded" the season of the Chiefs when no wide receivers caught a touchdown.

2) They drafted a guy from North Dakota State?

Gotta say, impressed how well groomed he looks and the play calling tonight looked pretty inventive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The facts don't lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like...a bit less red headed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would submit that certain coaches may choose to kick the field goal and then kickoff normally and etc etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the word milquetoast, and agree he is that. 

Not compatibility, not charisma...but like...how well two people get along.  They don't have good...whatever.  

Edit: Chemistry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna repost a comment from the game thread just because I appreciated it so much - 

I really like the Eagles play calling to kill the clock.

They know the other D is tired and dejected. They aren't giving easy up the gut runs. They're still spreading the runs to the outside mostly, making them more tired and more dejected.

I feel like with a lot of other coaches (ahem), there would be a lot more time left on the clock right now when it was time to punt.

Edit: AND THEY DIDN'T EVEN PUNT! HOLY SHIT I LOVE THE EAGLES COACH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first saw him last week, my first thought was, "Why is Gruden with some dude who looks like he should be covering college games?"

In the game thread tonight someone told me who he was and he used to be a college commentator. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he left ESPN so that isn't happening any time soon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Carson Wentz is the good Andy Dalton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you imagine SVP in the booth with Green? Those could be fun broadcasts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever the new guy with Gruden is should be replaced immediately.  He has the personality of mayonnaise. They have no ...what's the word... compatibility? Tirico wasn't a pure "straightman" in the comedy routine that is Jon Gruden. He had personality too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the Eagles play calling to kill the clock.

They know the other D is tired and dejected.  They aren't giving easy up the gut runs.  They're still spreading the runs to the outside mostly, making them more tired and more dejected. 

I feel like with a lot of other coaches (*ahem*), there would be a lot more time left on the clock right now when it was time to punt.

Edit: AND THEY DIDN'T EVEN PUNT! HOLY SHIT I LOVE THE EAGLES COACH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE DUKE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Aaaaand there's another Bears player doing something kinda okay I guess?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which division would they be put in?

NFC North...maybe they could squeak a wild card.  AFC North, probably still miss the playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kinda hoping for a resurgence from RG3. And I know McCown won't win a Super Bowl, but he can at least keep you in games mostly. So yeah to lose both is why I could see Browns being worse. But I predicted the Bears to be the #1 pick next year at the start of the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bears. At this point. Maybe magic strikes a mostly-unknown first time starter with no gametape. Hoyer is a known quantity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh I'm not surprised. Just decided to randomly hate on North Dakota </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we going to have to wait like 20 minutes after the game before the post game thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New CBA bc of salary cap reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Rex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bears remembered how to Bears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In North Dakota you shouldn't drink and drive. Not because of safety, but because you'll be sober by the time you get home from the bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really should have set up a camera in the one bar in North Dakota to get some fan reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I would expect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait? Did the NFL have a female official on the field this entire time and they didn't make a gigantic deal of bringing it up every 3 minutes?  

What alternate reality did I somehow get teleported to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was ESPN I'd be fuming about how much I paid for these matchups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for 6-10 games a season before injury </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some random hand injury that happened at some point. Not sure if they know the exact hit that caused it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cutler gets injured

hoyer comes in

hoyer looks great for 5 games

bears go back to cutler

hoyer gets a big contract in cleveland

cleveland remembers hoyer sucks

tfw brian hoyer is josh mccown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Bank Stadium is a really nice facility, but why is no one talking about the fact that Jay Cutler didn't have to go thru a sports bar to get to the locker room? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step it up, Soldier Field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
