<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9525</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This compendium is a a greedy child of the ti5 compendium and the winter battle pass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 21:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still have that problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, good sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is vulkan api doing okay with Dota now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got it as soon as it was released. It flickered a lot and crashed the game. Is that fixed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Core Omni isn't a first phase pick which opens up the possibility of dispelling/purging heroes. And he comes online way before they get enough farm for a diffusal. He's a pocket pick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try drafting him into a early game death push kind of line up. You get a bkb way before the enemy can even begin to build a diffusal. You get physical damage immunity. You get heal bombs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't core Omniknight played more often? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a good base strength and decent growth now (22+2.8). Decent agi (+1.75). Purification is a 360 pure damage nuke on a low cool down, Repel is extremely annoying, Armlet is great on strength heroes. Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TI6 cursor pack bugged? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cursor disappear every time I push A or hover the cursor over an enemy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 06:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, then he's kagami  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More aptly, miracle is Aomine Daiki of Dota 2 right now. Get over it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 06:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, did you realize game of thrones season 6 episode 8 was named Alohadance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 06:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When jungling early in the game, box select all the eidolons and choose the one who's taking damage from the group of portraits on the bottom you get when you select multiple units. Easier to pick out the dying eidolon than selecting individually (learnt it from limmp, actually)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 06:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witch doctor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is valve's problem with custom animations for spells? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 10:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DC's new sf set had an amazing animation for the shadowraze. It's gone.  Why, Volvo, why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 05:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never get Dagon unless you're REALLY ahead and it's early enough in the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 05:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orchid is pretty unnecessary on a roaming SUPPORT bh. What I prefer to that is going full aura mode. There's a lot of magic damage, get pipe. There's a lot of physical damage, get assault. You need push, get vlad's. You benefit from all of those items because more survivability --- more tracks --- more track gold --- you've successfully fucked bitches to get money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 05:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think io is a really good ban right now because now io isn't played like that dedicated-to-one-and-only-one-carry way. He's a roaming ambulance+attack speed buff now. And that can be really disrupting in the laning stage. And bounty hunter is just a infuriating little cunt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 05:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't necessarily have to be far away from fights. Even though the ice blast radius is smaller the closer you are, you can be more precise. And what helps with the lack of a large aoe is the application of the debuff on everyone in it's path. Get another burst damage potential support and/or carries and you're set even if you're close to a team fight. Watch kuro's aa games. He's always pretty close to the fights. And almost always clips at least 3 people with his ult even if he only hits one of the enemies. The aoe gold after a kill doesn't hurt with the aghs rush either. Try it out. GLHF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 10:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 10:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I'm only talking (jokingly) about how all players near him get worse. Not talking about secret's failure since the roster change. That can be attributed to a number of different things like lack or team chemistry or compatibility, adjusting to a new environment etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 10:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a different time, mate. Puppey was drafting then, they had a stable mid in w33 and pie was on steroids as lion. Or have you forgotten that game where eternal envy was safe on a cliff and he decided to jump between 3 enemy heroes with next to no mana?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 09:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pit Lord to be envy Lord? (atrophy aura since he atrophies everyone's game play)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 09:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Rtz has vengeful's swap. Swaps teams a lot and feeds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 09:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah. It's like cm aura. It is 2x as effective on himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That too, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
