<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4368</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King of the Hill has humour that I believe transcends comedy at times. There's so much at play for this gag that at first I may have only laughed a little, but the more I watch it, the more layers I see, the funnier it becomes. King of the Hill is a classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 hours? Dude a camera does it I like 1/2 a second.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuclear weapons don't explode. A nuclear warhead is nothing more than a small fission device atop a munition. It's actually quite tiny the actual device - it's a remotely detonated atom splitter. To activate the device, a free neutron is forced through an atom, where a chain reaction for the atom to recoup it's lost structure is triggered, which is essentially just a giant, rapid implosion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask a serious question? How do swatters give the address?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I paid a lot more than I needed to for my car and she gets dirty from time to time. It's best to clean it off properly when I'm ready to do it. Smashing your greasy dickbeaters into my clearcoat and digging shit into the urethane is fucked up... And it's happened to me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video game expert here. What we have is the "hard mode" controller for Soul Blade. Instead of mashing buttons like everyone else does, you take turns spinning the wheel to fight the enemy. Landed on Red? Spin kick. Yellow? Grapple. Blue? Main menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed so hard my girlfriend woke up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What it's like flying United. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know downies could use Reddit. Actually, that's unfair to people with Down Syndrome - the ones I've met at least know how to spell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been on there for years. I remember watching this with my first roommate and that was 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed there would be something out there that helps with the process, but when I learned about how it was done I was surprised at how simplistic the approach was but how tedious it was. Essentially you just paint the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that he used the headlights to blind the perps, used the seatbelts to constrain them and used the windshield wipers to fill out the paperwork.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really crazy is my pops was one of the first people to get Internet access at home. Back then, circa 1991, the internet just consisted of DOS based ASCII templates that people hosted and connected to. My dad would download all the best DOS games off of it. Nowadays, 2017, my dad doesn't have the forethought to research something on Facebook without posting it first. What's even crazier is that, while I don't think my dad is dumb guy for believing the things he posts, the actual kernal of truth most of the crap he posts about stem from are normally better suited for sharing than the altRight, info wars crap my dad floods his feed with. I remember my dad used to preach internet safety and protocol now he just doesn't seem to practice it anymore.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the people asking: I did this in school. What we used was Photoshop; basically you dont change the picture, you simply select what region you want colored and you put an opaque colored filter over top of the selection. 38 seconds x 24 frames per second = 912 frames colorized. Could do it in a week I suppose. That's my guess. As far as I can tell, there's no software out there that will automatically colorize B W motion picture... But I've been wrong more than I've been right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
