<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about as convincing as when the first President Bush said it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so we got Trump.  Great job, Debbie!

I'll agree, DWS was powerful enough to destroy our changes of retaining a Democrat in the White House.  I hope you're happy with that.

As for now, she's a washed out pol who's name is synonymous with "corruption."  That's not power, it's infamy.  Do you understand the difference?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh..Yes.  Being able to sit down with a member of the opposite/same sex without viewing that person as a potential sexual partner is very healthy, in or out of a relationship.

If you can't see that, I suggest you look to the health of your own relationship, because it may be even sicker than Pence's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's why DWS is a minor washed out minor rep from Florida trying to skim off whatever she can from the residue of her underhanded and illegal deals, while Bernie is a rising star in the Senate guiding actual policy.

That's some knowledge she has. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the modern Republican party.  They have no interest in working with others or in considering new ideas.  They are ideologically repressive and backward.

Is this really what America wants or needs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't understand the meaning of any of the words you typed, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comes from the former DNC chair who went on air and stated point blank that the Democratic primary system was designed to make sure grass roots efforts weren't able to affect the outcome.

Wasserman's belief that we're so stupid we'd forget everything she ever did or said is insulting while her own stupidity in hitching her horse (and the DNC) to a wagon filled with garbage is merely sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment would have been funner if your username had been /u/NorwegianWood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR:  Won't somebody think of the poor victimized corporations and stop these meddlesome regulations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in other words, you support endangering the lives of women, controlling their bodies against their will, and making them subservient to men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm solidly in support of you guys eating your own, but for the record the modern conservative ideology is drawn from greed, fear, and ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's hope Trump provides as much guidance and sanity to his goal of gutting sensible regulations and worker protections as he did with Trumpcare.

Other than that, the opinion in the article is filled with nothing more than propaganda, lies, and euphemisms for "break the Unions."  Not worth the time spent to upload it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember this.  Huckabee chose Russia over America.  He cares more for his political ambition than he does for the integrity of our nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never ceases to amaze me how you Trumpsters can complain day in and day out about political correctness, then squeal like stuck pigs when someone calls you out on posting bullshit from a rag owned by your idiot leader's son-in-law.  

Why should you be given the right to speech without repercussion?  

Why are you demanding a safe-space that wraps around you wherever you go for whatever you say and think?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this is a silly question, but did the victim ask who was knocking?

I understand that there are some rough neighborhoods out there but opening a door with a gun in your hand is pretty provocative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering that a cop generally needs a search warrant to enter your home, which means that there is a reasonable suspicion of wrongdoing in the first place, I see this as probably being a reasonable decision.

On the other hand, if the cop is in your home without a warrant, and therefore already in violation of the Constitution unless there is probable cause to suspect an immediate need to enter to stop a felony, then it would be one illegal action after another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The poor little multi-millionaire victim!  He was discriminated against so much while pulling in one of the largest salaries in Hollywood in the 90s.  How did he ever make it?

When you think about it, the comparison to being paid millions every week for a half hour sitcom with having all your possessions stripped from you before being sent to work and starve at concentration camps before being brutally gassed to death is uncanny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not even pro-birth.  They certainly don't want to pay for prenatal healthcare or subsidize housing and food for pregnant women to help ensure a healthy gestation period.  

They're actually pro-control over women.  They don't want women to be able to decide when to have sex because that would put men at a disadvantage.  That's why they're also against birth control and support "slut-shaming" tactics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical Trumpster.  Not understanding that no one implied making a choice between people and food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the "conservative" ethic in a nutshell.  This coward would never have done that to someone who could have kicked the shit out of him.  He only did this because he's a bully.  Just like Trump and all the other sniveling little cowards who have no problem picking on the weak and poor but piss themselves with fear in a fair fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand this might be beyond the grasp of some people, but when the only candidates on the ballot are corrupt, a corrupt candidate will win.

If your argument is that we need corrupt politicians to win elections, I think we're trying to achieve different results for this country.

And the question of whether Bernie could have won the primary in a fair fight will never be known because Hillary and her cronies used unethical and illegal means to ensure he never stood a chance.  If you're okay with that, there's not much else to discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there weren't enough "adults" willing to buy Hillary's center-right nonsense to elect the DNC corruption enhanced candidate.

People like yourself can bury your heads in the sand and pretend everything will be fine "next time," or you can search for the root of the problem.  

As a hint, the root of the problem in 2016 wasn't the fact that someone had the audacity to run against Hillary in the "open" primary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that knowledge that I'm about to be down-voted into oblivion, I'm going to step up and say that this is a big deal and does matter greatly because it points to what Democrats did wrong in the last election.  If we learn from our mistakes and root out the corruption in our party, we can start winning elections again.

Wasserman and Brazile are corrupt politicians who used the DNC apparatus to prop up a failing candidate who couldn't win in the general election.  They did so illegally and unethically.  Knowing this, we should make sure they and their cronies are kept far away from the levers of power in the party during future elections.  A properly contested primary will give us the best hope of getting the best candidate to challenge the cancer that sits in the white house now.

Or we can chant "Who cares?" in the hopes that everyone forgets what caused us to lose in 2016.  Then we can set ourselves up to lose again in 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  Just a 40 hour work week, unemployment insurance, potable water, public education, mass transit, after school programs, a social safety net, etc.  Nothing to make their lives better at all. /s

Of course Republicans have been doing their best since 1981 to destroy all of that and have succeeded to a large extent.  Congratulations on your success at making life miserable for millions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give you credit for stating the real purpose behind the anti-choice movement: slut shaming and regaining power over women.  That's all small men have, I guess.

Congratulations on being so blatant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another professional victim gets her own story in the paper and plenty of media attention so she can demand that everyone else be quiet and allow her to be a public asshole.

I'm guessing this same individual complains daily about "PC culture" without ever understanding how ironic that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
