<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject525</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For people who have been long term sufferers it's definitely not enough in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you came close but didn't do it, I'd call that bravery, the bravery to say "I can face life, just give me a minute"

Edit: that's what they told me anyway   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed that I started making a lot fewer jokes when recovering from depression. I was often told I was really funny and my sense of humour helped cheer people up. When I started recovering I didn't feel like making jokes anymore. Little did I know my sense of humour was me coping with depression... I thought it was part of who I was..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now this is a cool concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think one of the strongest things about Zap was that it was instant, whereas arrows had travel time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say I blame you. You definitely know more about the game than I do being at Master Rank, but completely polarized matchups  and a couple of deck archetypes that are completely unhealthy to the game are not what I came to Shadowverse for, I may as well have stuck to Hearthstone for that.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're about to get laid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen such moral integrity from anyone else. I definitely appreciate that about TB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but uh.. phrasing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a social etiquette thing that needs to catch on more. Right now too many people say "I've got time" or "Give me the short version" but they need to realise often it's not about the story being long, but rather the person's lack of desire to tell it for whatever reason, which should be respected.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How dimwitted people can be" = "How people can be so dimwitted"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else getting a loud audio glitch in combat where one harsh sound plays repeatedly, drowning out all other audio? (On PC)

Edit: Here's the community fix by Kaldaien: http://steamcommunity.com/app/429660/discussions/0/142261352640205850/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my favorite shitposts on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone can deny the power creep at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
