<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF - Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was. a terrible idea.

You can read about how I got to this point [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/68kifc/wtf/).

She was my mom. Nothing could break the bond. Even if she had made a terrible mistake years ago, it was nothing we couldnt overcome together.

Right?

When she got home, I told her right away that we needed to talk. If she suspected what I had found, her expression betrayed nothing. 

I wasnt sure what to say. Finally, I told her, I found this, and produced the VHS tape.

Her expression started to crack, and she gave a few gasping sobs.

I think.

I was going to tell her how things would be okay, that we could work through it. Of course, there was anger swirling around in the back of my mind  there had been all day  but I refused to accept what I saw as real. 

I tried reasoning with myself, justifying evidence, doing everything I could to get around the reality of having watched my dads final cannibalistic moments.

So I never really dealt with what I saw.

Bad idea.

I woke up a while ago on the floor. I dont know where this room is, or what happened between then and now.

But Im in a chain-link cage, Im naked, and Im pretty sure Im underground.

Not good. 

I still refused to accept what was happening. So I called for my mom. I was naked, terrified, and the top of my head throbbed like it had been hit pretty hard. In retrospect, it was one of the lowest points of my life. I was naked and afraid, and I was calling out for the last person I was with. In that moment, I needed my mother more than anything. 

*Im flashing back to being six years old. My dad had been gone less than a year. It was my mom who taught me to ride a two-wheeler. I started getting pretty good, but I fell. Hard. I cried and cried for her, and somehow she knew to find me a block away. She picked me up and cradled me, giving that soothing sh sh sh tone that only mothers can give. In that moment, I felt like everything would be okay again, for the first time since my dad disappeared.*

The memory stood in such painful contrast to where I was now. The only thing that my brain could grasp is that my mom would make this better, and absolutely nothing else would.

Then I saw the camera.

It all fell apart in that moment, and I stopped calling for my mom in mid-yell. The camera, an old, VHS dinosaur of a machine, was sitting on a tripod and pointed directly at me. I deflated when I realized that it was at the exact angle the previous camera must have been, all those years ago. 

She was making another video.

All illusion ended in an instant. What I saw was real, my dads fate had been real, and what was about to happen to me was very, very real. 

The only tool I have with me is my laptop. And nearly every website is blocked.

All of the evidence points to the fact that someone found what I wrote, and, for some reason, wants me to keep writing. 

This is a game.

I dont understand why my mother is doing this to me. I dont know if its possible to escape. Is that part of the game? To find a way out? Or is the idea simply to engineer suffering?

It turns out that we dont really know the people in our lives, not even the closest ones. Our inner thoughts are so personal that only a tiny fraction actually bridges the gap to the rest of humanity.

I wrote before about how everyone has a million tiny connections that link us all.

I dont believe that anymore.

Things are about to get very, very bad. When I close my eyes, all I can see is the video of my fathers last torturous days (weeks? months?) 

And then I open my eyes, and I cant escape the fact that Im here.

Theres no point in asking for help. I have no idea where I am. There are no windows in this room, and the floor is dirt, so Im likely underground. Based on the elaborate preparation, its pretty obvious that this computer was only left to me after someone made sure there was no way that I could use it to ask for help.

I write someone because its still to hard for me to say the truth. Because beyond all the fear and hurt, the feeling thats coming through the strongest is sadness. 

Even if I survive this, what will I have left? My mom is basically my only family. I was just about start a new life, which means that I have already left the last one behind.

Theres one more thing.

Im not alone in this cell. Theres an man in here with me whom Ive never met. Hes naked and unconscious. 

I dont think hes here to help me escape. Because I saw the video, and I know why there are two people in this cell. 

Im not looking forward to what comes next. Or how long it will take. But I suppose its part of the grand plan to take all of you along for the ride, so youll know soon enough.

Though I have been thinking about it. Ive been unable to stop my brain from trying to process it all. I believe now that the design of this cage is to draw out the inevitable change, to allow the watcher to savor each step. And the steps will all be there. Anyone suffering long enough will abandon, one by one, the most precious things they believe. Its inevitable.

Its what binds us as humans.

Theres one edge I have though. Just one.

I saw the first video. I know what to expect, what were about to go through.

That will give me a certain advantage.

[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/68zna0/wtf_part_3/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF - Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
