<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2527</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 08:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is pretty much dedicated for discussions about typography, all our are doing is whining about op posting this. I have seen this before and I still think this is a good post because this struck up a constructive conversation in comments.  But our are not making any constructive comments here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 08:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, some people like helvetica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has such a natural and candid laugh you can't do anything but laugh with her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the ESO crownstore model. If they need to have one, things like cosmetic items, not so vital mount upgrades and ok potions are things to sell there.  No pay to win stuff but completely optional things that doesn't have any real impact on your game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like clubbing time to time. But the reason I don't usually go to clubs is the shitty music. The clubs in my town all play the same top40 lists over and over again and it just doesn't fit my taste of music. But if I'm drunk enough I will dance to everything.

I prefer pub night with good friends and good beer. Nice drunk, so that I feel good, won't throw up (much) and will remember everything the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. No idea why, I really like old classic movies so I think I picked it up from there. But my pocket watch was really cheap so it didn't last long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the same. And it didn't help that I have always been really into things like biology, physics, astronomy so I talked alot about those and acted like I was smartest person in the room. These days I'm scared that I sound verysmart when I talk about things I know alot of / am passionate about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is nice to hear, Regis is one of my favorite characters!

I think Milva would be harder to do. She is such a vivid and emotional character that I don't think they would be able to created her well unless she was major character  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I have not played the dlc's yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy as long as he at least *once* answers my question before I even finish the question. 

Did they do his return well? I mean [Spoilers](/s "I have hard time believing even high vampire could regerate from being turned into pile of ash and molten glass") so, without spoiling much, did they handle that well?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Malukah's version](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eOR2QYy670k) is good way to compare the two, she sings both english and polish verses back to back

And I must agree, polish (ingame) version sounds much better. I always thought the english lyrics were bit... clumsy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Roche, or is there really difference between Polish and English versions of Geralts horse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was on point. Game-Dandelion was just a shade of Book-Dandelion. I haven't played Blood and Wine yet but I heard Regis is in it and I'm worried they did same to him. I did like Zoltan in W2, I think they captured him pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Dandelion. I think the games continue his "Half a century of poetry" which is his memoirs he started writing after the battle at the bridge in Bapism of Fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every artist borrows ideas and people would respect you more if you were open and honest.

This is what I was kinda disagreeing with. I got the feeling that you were asking op to credit Olly Moss if he took inspiration form his work.

But I probably just misunderstood your comment, sorry about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graphic designer here. Flat landscapes have been around since the 50's. Oldest posters to use double exposure I have seen were from 70's. It is nothing new to use these together, Olly Moss just popularized them in the gaming community and tbh even though I *love* Olly Moss' work, he shouldn't get credit for "inventing" it either since it has been around forever.

But you can see that these posters have been inspired by the style which many people do, including Moss. But getting inspired by someone elses work is part of design, and often certain themes bring up same ideas on people.

EDIT: Also that flat landscape art is pretty much inspired by chinese paper cutout art which has been around forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wolf looks amazing, like the worn look. I especially like the fact that the background it could be either snow, or ash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do that in most rpg's but as a big fan of the books, I tend to play "book-Geralt". Rather than thinking what would I do I think what would Geralt from the books do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he only killed one person that didn't fight back (woman in a house he stabbed from behind) Geralt says that other have defensive wounds/fought back IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wouldnt want to meet anyone who let a killer like that go IRL. 

Definetly. But this is a game and when I play, I don't play as "me" I play as Geralt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I don't think the witcher in this quest fitted that. When compared to characters like Bonhart who was more of a monster than a human. But then again it is possible that you and I just see/play Geralt as different kind of witcher.

EDIT: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But she doesn't deserve the same fate as the cat school witcher. What I mean is that the prospect of good and bad in witcher universe is kinda loose. Especially from eyes of witcher who kills monsters who are threat to humans but yet doesn't work as a bounty hunter and sword for hire.

I think Geralt lives by a code he came up with that he doesn't kill sentinent monsters. I think this counts humans, unless as self defence or if they are threat to him or people he cares about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point! This kinda reminded me of *Witcher 2 spoilers* [Spoiler](/s "the part in witcher 2 where Letho and Geralt fight and he could have easily killed Geralt, but didn't because that wasn't his job and they were almost friends at some point. It kinda showed the relationship witchers have. Altought its different since they already knew eachother") 

But you make good case about witchers getting bad name from him, but it seems like most people already have that image of witchers (which is probably why they didnt pay him and tried to kill him), so the cat school witcher only matched their expectations.

I really like reading other peoples opinions on this because it shows how different everyone plays Geralt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's so black and white in world of witcher. I mean Ciri killed innocent people when she ran with the rats as Falka. She also robbed people and used drugs. But that didn't make her a bad person, did it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you completely. (At least my) Geralt isn't some vigilante that runs around killing criminals, he is a monster hunter. Also what was done was done, it's not like Geralt had a reason to avenge the people in the village and risk his life fighting another witcher, which would not be easy thing to do. 

Also the witcher had just risked his life saving those villagers. Put himself in danger and got cheated again, this time by village that obviously could afford to pay him more than 12 gold. Ofc it wasn't right to kill those people but like you said, it's not black and white </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people seem to think it was right choise to kill him. But (my) Geralt isn't some vigilante that hunts down and kills criminals. He is a Witcher and imo like he says in the quest, it's not his job to judge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they obviously had money, they just tried to cheat the Witcher  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about painting but I do graphic design. With this I would first shade the head same way as the mane. Also I'm not 100% sure about the background. The gradient is nice, but somehow I feel the relation of colors or something is kinda off. Hard to put a finger on it.

Also I don't know how hard it's to do but it would be kinda cool if you added snowflakes and embers. Like snow falling down and embers rising up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good point! This was actually pretty hard choise in the game, really no "right" answer (one thing I like about this game) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geralt talks alot about being neutral in the books but in reality he isn't. For example he helped Yarpen Zigrin and the others to fight Scoia'tael after making big deal of not being a sword for hire and being "neutral" in the war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True its not completely relatable but Shani was scared to go near him even though he was loosing blood and he almost attacked Philippa. Potions probably doesn't put witchers in frenzy (also probably depends on both witcher and potion) but I think the combination of being "high" on potions, adrenalin after fight and anger could cause frenzy.

I thought the cat school witcher didn't actually mean to kill bunch of innocent people. Especially when he stopped at the child so he wasn't completely "evil" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the story was called lesser of two evils or something similiar. Important part in his story that there is no lesser evil. 

"If I'm to choose between one evil and another, I'd rather not choose at all"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why it reminded me more of the scene where Geralt went on blind rage while chasing after Rience. Blaviken was different, but didnt  Renfri say that it was just a bluff? That they weren't going to kill the townsfolk? I'm not sure I'm remembering it right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went there with a full beard and she say "When did you decide to stop shaving?" which I thought was nice touch since in books Geralt pretty much hates his beard and shaves it as often as he can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers]Just finished "Where the Cat and the Wolf play..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definetly one of my favourite sidequests. I loved the fact that the cat school witcher noticed that I was wearing feline armor and a wolf medallion. Too bad the quest was so short, thats the only bad thing about it. Ended up sparing the witcher because he regretted what he did and the rage he was in reminded me of the part of the books where Geralt fights Rience and his men and after Rience gets away (because of Philippa) Geralt was in a blind rage because of the elixirs so I'd imagine the other witcher was going trough similiar (he was also wounded like Geralt). And also Blaviken.

This game keeps suprising me with it's well written contracts. Some of them have actual stories instead of being same repeatable quest again and again. Which choise did you choose?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, I just find it funny when imgur especially tries to say some of the giffers in HQG are "theirs" while most post them in multiple platforms (ones that aren't crazy meta gifs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the irony in that /u/iH8myPP is one of the giffers who imgur thinks in "their" giffer. Someone on Imgur once tried to convince me that s/he and /u/EditingAndLayout are "imgurians" and that reddit just reposts their gifs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None, only free DLC's from steam (except the alterative outfit ones) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leo Bonhart. One of my favorite villains ever. He didn't have any grand plans or delusions of world domination. He was just a crazy sadist that wanted to torture Ciri and see her fight in arenas and probably kill her in some point in some fucked up way. Scary as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat it with a knife! Problem solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I can't wait for Season of Storms to be translated... Its been 3 years goddammit! I need my fix! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have played all TES games since morrowind and I have 900 hours to eso in past 2 years. Of course it is not for everyone but I think its unfair to say its "rotten" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they did fairly good job, except the legs. Why do they spread in every direction instead of going downwards like one in Morrowind and Skyrim? That is the only part that looks weird to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't say things like that without providing some pictures.

[Finnish ones are just awful, they all look like this with different colors](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/fi/thumb/c/c9/Noiturit.jpg/1200px-Noiturit.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 11:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tower of Swallow especially jumps around with the time. It isn't as bad in other books but especially ToS kinda uses it to confuse the reader so he/she doesn't know what is happening at the same time. Only timeframe to use to tie everything together is the september equinox (not sure if translated the name of the day right) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A song of fire and ice is next on my reading list . Haven't started them yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triss' favourite game is Roach? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Aaand of course I forgot to bring something to grill on this fire...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I've heard that there are things kinda "missing" in english translations. Not sure how accurate the finnish ones are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I myself read books first and I'm just finishin up The Witcher 3. The books are my favorite series and I have been reading mainly fantasy novels since I was a kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Are you reading them for the first time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because even if its meta and dickbutts, it isn't low quality content. It's amazing how much work they put on the images. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have managed to avoid all dlc related spoilers so far but *IS REGIS IN BLOOD AND WINE!?* That is great news, he is one of my favorites!

EDIT: Had minor spoiler in the comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been playing for 2 years and I've seen it go from good game to great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why wouldn't you just take some piece of pipe or make the cannon out of wood and just wrap one coke can on top of it? Seems like really hard way to do it by wrapping tons of cans around each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Alfred Hitchcock having a dinner with MGM lion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This application is just *ahead of it's time* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PERSON CORRECTS GRAMMAR [GONE GRAMMATICAL] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Personally I don't think it is OK to be a as arrogant as she is no matter what your origins.
 
 
 
 Also, selective kindness is not much of a virtue. 

I completely agree, and I'm not making excuses. I'm just saying that there is more to her character than "being a bitch" and that she does have empathy *and* sympathy for the people she cares about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, I just can't "turn off" the books in my head. For example I hated Emhyr's character because of what he was in books, altought he is nothing like him in the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is somewhat addressed in the game and Avallac'h wasn't turned into a "good guy" just like that? That's good to hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's an elitist, she has no empathy or even sympathy for anyone she deems 'beneath' her. 

I wouldn't say that. She just sees herself as "better" than others because she came from suffering before becoming a sorcerer. She is also very kind to people who she cares about, for example Dandelion.

Triss on the other hand often shows tremendous amounts of compassion for her friends and fellow mages

Yet she completely manipulated Geralt after he lost his memory and played crucial role on the events on Thanedd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is actually very good point! I can't remember if it was in one of the books or the game that she said she doesn't "waste" her charm on people who's opinions doesn't matter to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why everyone says that. She isn't bitchy in the game IMO. She can be kinda cold but Geralt did sneak out of her window after few weeks when they first were together.

Also [this](http://imgur.com/a/AynNA). But then again I'm a book fan first so my image of Yen is probably different than the one from games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Triss hotter than Yen? In what universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No... [Jesus christ it's Jason Bourne](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xYG89rB6c5k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been playing it for 2 years and I really like it. To me it is good mix of solo content and group stuff. I am in 2 guilds so I haven't had any problem with the social aspect even thought I don't have any friends who play it. Also I love the Elder Scrolls setting. I didn't approach the game as ES game but the fact that I'm already familiar with the world and lore helped me. Also it keeps getting better with new updates.

But then again it is the only MMO I have enjoyed so don't know how much my opinion counts. For example I played Guild Wars 2 for around 30 hours and didn't really care for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it heavy? The one without the led eyes might be lighter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if what I get is shit I might just order from there. That would make a neat keychain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get that? I ordered one from ebay just few days ago, it was some chinese seller and cost like 5 euros so I have no idea what I'm gonna get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many "Doing Landry" jokes she gets in tinder every day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I still get 2 xp from completing the quest but enemies are higher level? At least that's something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure Emhyr just wants her to be his heir, not his wife. They ignored that plot from the books completely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they? I still have low leveled quests in my journal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they just left her out because it would be way too hard to explain the whole "Emhyr is her dad and wants to marry her and father her a child because of her Elder Blood and the crown of Cintra" 

BUT it should be mentioned that I have not finished the game yet. In "Isle of Mists" quest atm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well 2 things

* Make the potion system same as Witcher 2. I love that I had to prepare for fight instead of chugging potions mid fight

* Make quests level to you. I hate the fact that when I got to Skellige most quests were too low level and getting 5xp when completing them was kinda meh. I mean leveling up is not the main thing in the game, but still I would like to get xp from quests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they were thinking that book-Dandelion wouldn't work as a small side character. They had to pump up his personality. I personally disagree, but they kinda did this with Triss too. 

It is harder to represent character as accurately as in book, especially a side character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go check out alcasthq.com, one of the top PvE players in the world. He is part of the top guild in the world (Hodor) and makes wonderfull builds. Most of them are made for end game PvE (trials) but also work in solo content like Vet Maelstorm arena. 

I would look into his mag sorc build that has amazing sustain and single target damage and nice AoE.

Mag DK that has awesome AoE damage and you can wipe out lots of mobs in seconds. Also DK's have good shields too. 

Then there are Mag NB that does great single target damage, has huge resource pools and ability to self heal trough siphoning abilities.

Mag templars (or stamplar) have the best heals which helps you on tough situations but it lacks shields like NB and has okay damage.

Right now magicka based characters are probably the best in meta. Especially for PvE. Stam sorcs are also great, but I think for solo content you should go with mag because you can run destro and resto (with resto passives its really easy to get more magicka when you run out)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha Well I'm not russian but definitely will give it a look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone asks me whats the best house and there is only one correct answer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man that looks so great. I have yet to play the dlc's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second tier Feline armor is my definet favorite!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was lvl 8 when that lvl20 Leshen jumped on me and fucked me up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read all the books before playing any of the games. I really love the books even thought I'm not a huge fan of the games (except 3 is amazing, 2 first were bit meh. Amazing writing but the gameplay was bit meh to me). I really need to buy the books for me, definitely my favourite saga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried other buttons on my mouse but it didn't work. The middle utton is fine but for some reason it doesn't work in game. The game doesn't recognize the middle button, can't even bind any keys on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually read english books regulary (currently reading lotr in English) so my English is pretty good. 

Never heard of Max Frei, what kind of books he writes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "See? She's his lobster" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats one great thing about Morrowind, where as Oblivion is your basic high-fantasy, Skyrim is vikings, Morrowind will always feel kinda alien. I don't think I have ever played a game that had world that felt as weird and different like morrowind.

I also like to think that reason why elder scrolls games are inconsistent is that they are like stories, instead of you actually living the events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they said they added Seyda Neen because they knew that if it wasn't there, morrowind fans would complain. Since it was made for people who played the original morrowind, they decided to add it since its pretty iconic location.

I can forgive them little bit inaccuracy, its not like the other elder scrolls games have been exactly consistent with lore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaalll riiiight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fact: Phones go to cases. Phones. Cases. Battlestar Galactica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I might looks into it! I'm also kinda weird in a way, I have worked in a print shop and done layout design etc. and I'm kinda passionate about that stuff. So I really like good quality print. I know it sounds kinda stupid but thats one reason I like reading actual books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He even learned Rivian accent just so it would sound more legit. He choose it because it sounded good and apparently people don't like Rivians (I think it was mentioned in Last Wish that people don't like Rivians?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in fairly small city with small library that doesn't have many english books. They didn't even have LOTR trilogy in english so I bought my own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crime shows like this are my guilty pleasure shows. I mean I love british and scandinavian crime shows that usually makes more sense than American shows (latest I watched was Broadchurch). I can just put them on and watch them without thinking much.

That includes Bones, NCIS, Mentalist, House (it's basicly a crime show but with diseases instead of murderers) etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really like reading from screen. Plus I spend alot time on computer during the day so its nice to look read something that doesn't have a backlight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the Morrowind DLC is going to be awesome, I think you can get the Morrowind DLC and the main game for bundled up price. 

Also the download asks for 80GB of free space (if I remember correctly) but the game takes under 50GB. The download itself is between 50-70GB.

Bad things about MMO's is that they take alot of space so it kinda sucks if you have small hard drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i've been thinking about getting books in english but the cost is just so high when ordering from US or UK. Also I don't really care for buying expensive books without knowing I will like it which is why I prefer library before I buy the book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finnish so the books are probably split because of the size. Some finnish words and expressions are quite longer than english ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dlc's aren't actually needed to enjoy the game. The base game has alot of things to do and the dlc's just mostly add some more quests (you have plenty of those in the areas of all 3 alliances) and some new gear sets/style that you can pretty easily buy with ingame gold. Also it is pretty big download, I think first time download is around 60-80gb so it isn't *that* much more than some single player games

So if that is what is pushing you away you should definetly try out the game!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
