<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 12:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I remember hearing this and watching the video week after week on JTV Saturday. Has 9 years really gone by so fast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 12:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MORE DAMBUSTERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Peake looks like the kind of guy who'd look good in any hat you give him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can do this the same way a Sherlockian/Holmesian can pick out certain things from the collected works at will.

We read, re-read, are passionate about the subject matter and know what stands out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 12:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You'll have to settle for this.](http://questionablecontent.net/view.php?comic=2350) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What would Jimbo say about this?](http://questionablecontent.net/view.php?comic=1526) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MASH S7E11 "Point Of View" is an intriguing one. The premise is that viewers get to see a wounded soldier being treated at the 4077th through his eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...you know what? I would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My base of operations on Spectacle Island was built to mimic the layout of the House of Tomorrow.

[The blueprint for my base, Fort Baychimo.](https://imgur.com/a/l56Fu) Try it for yourself. It's surprisingly good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think my supervisor is a fuckboy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He walks around all day wearing his "Ass Manager" badge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 03:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny. At this angle, it looks like [A Bit of Fry and Laurie.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hNoS2BU6bbQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, Smith and Ross were ashamed to be associated with Trott thanks to his usual racist antics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, Jack Black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaaand there's the sentence that'll launch a thousand Rule 34 images. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have yet to come across the YouTube channel that does not pronounce any Pokmon name wrong.

If I had a dollar for every time a YouTuber mispronounced a Pokmon name, I'd have enough to buy the equipment to start a YouTube channel focused on Pokmon facts and proper pronunciation.

And I apologise for the condescension. This really grinds my Giaru. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **H**oles,

**O**il

**L**eaks,

**D**ents and

**E**ngine

**N**oise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We dreamed of showcasing the most unexpected apocalypse Pokemon...and we succeeded." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need any help, get in contact with Cephei_Delta from the Pokemon subreddit who does some [fantastic work which includes instructions and piece lists.](http://bricksafe.com/pages/Cephei_Delta/pokemocs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you thought about using an online LEGO builder to create instructions on how to build this and what pieces are needed and uploading that information to a website like Bricksafe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-Institute: Cabot's Lab Coat

Institute: Any of the Lab Coats

However, the problem with the coats is that you can's equip any armour over them. Including armour into this question, I'd have to say anything with the "Sharp" Legendary prefix and the Inquisitor's Cowl from Far Harbor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 15:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Push-ups, sit-ups and plenty of juice.

But, yeah; radiant quests and settlement building with the Idiot Savant perk, coupled with any perks, clothing and chems that enhance and boost Intelligence for that sweet, sweet experience.

And one other thing; this is the character I've been playing with since I started back in November of last year, so I've got 10 months (amounting to 8 days of total playtime) under my belt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 14:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level 256 with all relevant damage-enhancing perks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Random drop from a bloodworm in Dry Rock Gulch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 12:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else think the chorus is reminiscent of "Livin' On A Prayer"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this legendary weapon. Renamed it accordingly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 08:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I couldn't resist. R.I.P.](https://imgur.com/a/cQ0qv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 00:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mega Mr. Stake, anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a place without serious lexical parsing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman mythology in 3 words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck's plagiarism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's no submarine; that's a helicarrier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ross, Trott and Smith need to visit The Creatures' office in America if only to sample their homemade mead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm...as much as I want to say my parents copy of Pink Floyd's "Dark Side", I think I'm going to say my rare promotional copy of The Who's "Eminence Front". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 05:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading only the words that are fully capitalised makes for some interesting interpretation.


ALMIGHTY FIRST SPAWN DESPAIR

FEET ETERNAL

CRUSHED ONLY

COWER DESPAIR

BURNS NOTHING

MINOR GEK CONQUER WORLDS

GAVE GLORIOUS RISE FIRST SPAWN SPRANG FORTH RECOILED FEAR

SCOURGE OUTER EDGE TREMBLE ALMIGHTY

GREW WEAKLING PORWIGLE MIGHTY

OPPOSED FIRST SPAWN FLAME

MINOR GEK GREW STRONG

OPPOSERS DESCENDED WAR GREAT TOO MIGHTY

BRED PLOTTED MULTITUDE CYCLES

HOLY SPRANG FORTH PUREST PORWIGLES BEGAT FIRST SPAWN TIDE BLOOD ATTACK

DAWN EMPIRE FIRST SPAWN BIRTHED SHADOW FOLLY

FOOLISHLY SINGED FLESH LASER SHADOWS FIRST SPAWN

SPILLING BLOOD WHITE METAL RIGHTFUL STARS

SPILLED THEIR OWN PUTRID BLOOD SENTINEL MACHINES SILENT GLORIOUS GEK ASCENT RIGHTFUL DESTRUCTION

VAST PRECIOUS MINERAL ORE POWER UNIVERSAL RULE CREDULOUS FEEBLE CONQUEST DENIED

REFUSED PROFIT JEWEL FATE DIRE WILL ABHORRENT STRIKE

KORVAX PRIME VAST SUDDEN MIGHTY PUNISH RIGHTFUL ASCENDANCY OF THE GEK

FEASTED DEBRIS KORVAX PRIME RICH DESPAIR

FEAR FIRST SPAWN ANGUISH CONSUMED WORLDS FOREVER MORE

NOT BENEVOLENT MERCIFUL SLAVERY SAVED THE WORTHLESS

BECAME OURS BECAME OURS BECAME OURS

FIGHT KORVAX WEAKNESS ELECTRONIC CHAINS

MIGHTY BRINK ETERNAL EMPIRE ENDLESS TIME ENDLESS

ELECTRONIC REBELLION PUT DOWN ATLAS SUPERSTITION DESPAIR VAIN THEY ARE CONQUERED NO MERCY

VAST KNOWABLE CONQUERED FOR ALL TIME
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every day that I think to myself "This will be a productive day!" turns out to be the least productive day I have all week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the same thing happened with Funhaus and Chyna.

^And ^me ^and ^Christopher ^Lee. ^And ^David ^Carradine. ^And ^Charles ^Tingwell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do. O7 (It's a salute.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I summon /u/Cephei_Delta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 07:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not wooden needles, but BONE needles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 07:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **UPLOAD ALL DISCOVERIES OPTION!** I don't know how many thousands of units I have tied up in discoveries because I just can't bear the tedium of having to upload them one by one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pffh. Guide? What do you take me for? Some kind of casual?

^I ^have ^a ^crippling ^obsession ^with ^game ^guides. ^Help ^me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Those who forget history are doomed to repeat it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In which case, there sure are a lot of amnesiacs on this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God. Fucking. Damn it.

It's always the way, isn't it? You go into a cave, wander around for a bit aaaaaaaand you're in Blackreach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bedroom Philosopher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fire" as in the song by Arthur Brown? Because that song has NO guitars in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to look at what Jeph says under the comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/iVlkZVAw8Gc?t=11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "It wasn't a chicken!" is never funny.

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...but...that's just Los Santos. The state of San Andreas encompasses Los Santos, San Fierro and Las Venturas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I pay Smith 5,000 to eat horseshit when I can get Dave England of Jackass fame to do [the same thing for US$200?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=37mb7p97QJ8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just let you cream?

...I know what you said. Don't judge me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would argue that the entirety of Pink Floyd's "The Dark Side Of The Moon" would be relevant regardless of time. 

From the Wikipedia article: "Each side of the album is a continuous piece of music. The five tracks on each side reflect various stages of human life, beginning and ending with a heartbeat, exploring the nature of the human experience, and (according to Waters) "empathy".

* "Speak to Me" and "Breathe" together stress the mundane and futile elements of life that accompany the ever-present threat of madness, and the importance of living one's own life  "Don't be afraid to care".

* By shifting the scene to an airport, the synthesizer-driven instrumental "On the Run" evokes the stress and anxiety of modern travel, in particular Wright's fear of flying.

* "Time" examines the manner in which its passage can control one's life and offers a stark warning to those who remain focused on mundane aspects; it is followed by a retreat into solitude and withdrawal in "Breathe (Reprise)". 

* The first side of the album ends with Wright and vocalist Clare Torry's soulful metaphor for death, "The Great Gig in the Sky".

* Opening with the sound of cash registers and loose change, the first track on side two, "Money", mocks greed and consumerism using tongue-in-cheek lyrics and cash-related sound effects (ironically, "Money" has been the most commercially successful track from the album, with several cover versions produced by other bands).

* "Us and Them" addresses the isolation of the depressed with the symbolism of conflict and the use of simple dichotomies to describe personal relationships.

* "Any Colour You Like" concerns the lack of choice one has in a human society.

* "Brain Damage" looks at a mental illness resulting from the elevation of fame and success above the needs of the self; in particular, the line "and if the band you're in starts playing different tunes" reflects the mental breakdown of former bandmate Syd Barrett.

* The album ends with "Eclipse", which espouses the concepts of alterity and unity, while forcing the listener to recognise the common traits shared by humanity." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYONE has a lookalike. I've met seven of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm...

*looks over at the 11 years of MASH*

...yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are people even finding these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A random encounter with a rogue robot called Lady Liberty. After destroying her, her creator comes out of hiding and chastises you with "You maniac! You blew her up! Damn you! God damn you to hell!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Promising. Very, very promising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [BOOM?!?](https://imgur.com/a/SkkGE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I would like is irrefutable visual evidence of one star with 8 or 9 planets around it. That's all I ask. That way, I can hop from cluster to cluster knowing that my search is not in vain. If you can serve up said evidence, I would be eternally grateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your encouragement is much appreciated, fellow star-strider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damage among vapor donut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to find the appropriate system to claim, first. Any evidence to further prove the existence of systems with 8 or 9 planets would be greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Personal End-Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has a journey they wish to travel, a goal to complete. For me, in NMS anyway, my goal is to find an 8 or 9 planet system which I can call my own and settle down in. Now, Ive yet to come across such a system; the maximum Ive seen so far is 6 planets, but I am assured of systems with more thanks to /u/jive495 and [their comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/NoMansSkyTheGame/comments/4yiyiz/how_many_planets_can_a_system_have/d6odrfx?context=3) on an earlier question I had.


You may be wondering why Im searching for such a system. The answer is simple: Im looking for a system which I can name in parallel to our own system. Not the names verbatim, you understand, but the counterpart names of the Greek and Roman mythological deities which our system and planets are named after. Ive always thought this would be a cool thing to do, and now NMS appears to cater to this. The names that the system and planets are to take are:


* The **Iliosar** System, from the Greek word **Ilios**, meaning star, just like **Solar** comes from **Sol**, the Latin word for star.


* The closest planet to the star of the system will be **Hermes**, the Greek counterpart to the Roman **Mercury**, God of Commerce.


* After Hermes comes **Aphrodite**, the Greek counterpart of the Roman **Venus**, Goddess of Love.


* Then we have **Gaierra**, which is a unique case as **Earth** is the only planet not named after a deity, so the best choice is to name this planet with a fusion of both respective relevant deities, those being the Greek **Gaia** and the Roman **Terra**, both Goddesses of the Earth.


* Next up, we have **Ares**, the Greek counterpart to the Roman **Mars**, God of War.


* Following Ares, we have **Zeus**, the Greek counterpart to the Roman **Jupiter**, King of the Gods.


* Then we have **Cronus**, the Greek counterpart to the Roman **Saturn**, Titan of Capitol.


* After Cronus comes **Caelus**, the Roman (yes, ROMAN) counterpart to the Greek **Uranus**, God of the Sky.


* Up next is the predictable Greek **Poseidon**, taking the place of its Roman counterpart **Neptune**, God of the Sea.


* Finally (and optionally), we have **Dis Pater**, the Roman counterpart of the Greek deity **Pluto**, Ruler of the Underworld. Yes, **Pluto** is Greek, not Roman, as is widely believed. **Pluto** is the Latinized form of the Greek **Plouton**, from which it is believed that **Dis Pater** is translated from. Look it up.


If and when I achieve this goal, I will let you all know, so that you may attempt to find it if you so wish.

And one more thing: should you find any of my previous discoveries from my meandering through the galaxy, you'll know they're mine if you scan them and it says "Discovered by **ByteBasher**", as **ByteBasher** is my PS4 username. Feel free to add me if you want.


See you among the stars, travellers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried re-creating the famous 'Akira' movie poster using the game's Capture Mode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 07:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eddie Izzard had a [good skit](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M5X-9brvoq0) about performance-debilitating drugs in the Olympics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you didn't try the Shazam app. Identified it in under 5 **seconds**. The song is "Let Me Go" by Diego Miranda   Braudt feat. Kevin Brauer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 04:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're more right than you know.](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a5/Goanna-Spirit_of_Place.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else getting a 'Lost In Blue' vibe from this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 07:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, she's not wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you have a v3 Pass, the v2 becomes redundant, as the v3 can unlock v2 doors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 03:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AtlasPass v3 can be found in colonial outposts on Korvax planets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bourne VS Desh in The Bourne Ultimatum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you call among you the little mouse, the mouse that surfs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
