<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as it's not bugged down by micro transactions or something similar I'll deffo remain with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyday I feel as if my girlfriend is going to break up with me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently got a girlfriend , but because it's my life I get really scared she will have enough of me and call it off. I have absolutely no evidence for this, it's completely unfounded. I overreact to the tiniest things, like if she doesn't text me first or how long I get to talk to her. For example today we were on the phone before she said she had to go in the shower my mind just flipped. 

I'm sick and tired of feeling like this. Anyone relate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 09:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it's one of the only games I've bought in the last year or so that actually has 50 worth of content. Always finding new classes and things to do,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only game Ive bought in about a year that I think has enough content to justify the price. I adore this game and don't get why everybody is so negative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garden Warfare 2 has taken over my life since it came out. Probably my game of the year so far. Also really enjoying the wolf among us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 19:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toy Story 3 and the last Harry Potter film twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is crafting relied upon heavily given the time period? Hate how every game now days thinks I want to craft. I tolerated it in the other far crys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So how is Far Cry Primal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 21:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally have some money saved for a game and fancied a good single player experience. For some context I loved Far Cry 3 to bits but didn't like FC4 due to it just being so uninspired. Has a lot changed or should I get a different single player game instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 21:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not since the patch. The official avalanche forums have loads of threads of people saying its fine and others saying its unbearable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the patch end of December fix it for you? Mines been running fine since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I overthink way too much shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats going on in y'all heads when you don't text back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 09:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been dating this girl for a few weeks now and its going swimmingly. I have an anxiety disorder and think through things a bit more than other people. Normally we send a morning text to each other but this morning I haven't had a reply. shes been on facebook on her phone and tweeted out today but I haven't had a reply, my anxiety heightens the feeling and I just jump to conclusions that being she doesn't want to be with me. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats going through y'all heads when you don't text back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 09:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 12:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 06:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems your definitely in the majority now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 08:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He IS Grump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 14:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rambling: Leo Wins, Epic Rap Battle, Vidya Geamz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 13:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLANTS Vs. ZOMBIES: GARDEN WARFARE 2 - Kicking Some Grass - Jim Sterling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 11:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 09:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget he is also in The Human Centipede 3: Full Sequence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 11:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it available on the other platforms now though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 15:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The games only been out a day. bullshitty witty is what we will call you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 15:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hopefully the game grows on you

HA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 12:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yep done that a few times to no avail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocket League says servers are down, but then says theres people in the playlist... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 13:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask what the Xbox one did to disappoint you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be worth getting a PlayStation 4 just for the exclusives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 11:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got an Xbox one this generation because that's where my friends all were. However I miss me those PlayStation exclusives, R C, The last of us, uncharted etc. Would it be worth it to get a ps4 as a 'back up' console or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would a Ps4 be worth it just for the exclusives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 04:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to Jared last year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 01:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we give the guy a break? He's a video editor for a free internet show. I barley noticed the stammering yesterday, I assume they had a conversation about it at Grump HQ and decided to upload it anyway. We will never know the full story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 22:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how do you suggest we don't except it? Buy a ps4 :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. We just need someone to explain what's going on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 22:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason I can play rocket leauge online perfectly but not odd world? What a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 21:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 days in a row is unacceptable. This is a fucking joke, losing more and more respect each day/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 11:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP but I'm not a big fan of racing games but Forza Horizion looks chill to play. Do you think I could get into it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 00:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About what time and when? I never see it on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to watch legally in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 20:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A blu Ray release hasn't come over here and I can never find the show on tv. I want to support the crew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 10:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved chapter 1 but I just can't get into chapter 2 for some reason/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the need for such a specific list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 11:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does ranked play work? I've heard something about being sorted into leagues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 11:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really interesting. Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 01:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played for 40 minutes, perfect performance. No problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocket League is live in the UK!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 01:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 23:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is one of the most bullshit things I've ever heard of. Its approaching breaking trade laws. Super disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 23:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck you'll be lucky if it does. Hasn't gone live in any other regions yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Sorry guys we didn't forsee that we were going to make soooo much dlc, we are just going to need more money!' They should have picked a price and stuck with it, I have the season pass but could see people being put off buying it when people who bought it before are getting the exact same content for less.

Edit: they haven't even announced what the new dlc is, so why should people have to pay more for already existing content and content that hasn't even been shown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But on the Xbox store it says the game releases at midnight in each countries time zone so surely that's when it should release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's Hong Kong and Aussie gamers who have said the game isn't released yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the only problem is them upping the price, in a way it seems that people who haven't got the season pass are getting punished for not buying earlier. The season pass has been out for ages and is a product you can't just raise the price of a product you made. I don't see that as fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 20:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but that's disgusting. I don't get how people can say wait a few hours. If the game it says it will be ready at midnight then it should be ready at midnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming up same for me to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only time to play this game was tonight, I'm at a work trip for the next few weeks and was looking forward to cracking 6 hours into this tonight but because of this release schedule I cant. Also the Xbox store says its 12:01 GMT if that's not the case then I'm sorry but that's a company lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's not fair.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a hit sucky for people who have waited until midnight tbh,  I was hoping to play a bit this evening as I won't be able to play again until the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Rocket League will be a hit on Xbox one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 12:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this be as successful as garden warfare or cod? Or after a few months be forgotten like titanfall? No cross play means there won't be as many players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill buy season 1 and wait till season 2 becomes available. Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah! Thanks! Better quality than I've been watching. I'll buy season 1 on iTunes to i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best way for someone from the UK to legally watch this show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have Disney xd at home but due to some unsavoury sites I have really gotten into this show. I really want to support the creators, are there season DVDs for sale? I can only find one with the first 6 episodes and I can't find that for sale over here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 14:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope this becomes the new mouse mat thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 13:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck, I work in a movie theatre and if I saw that when on a screen check I would have kicked them right out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's just an audience thing. UK here no one laughed other than me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloody hell, which planet did you come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today has been a good day. Change that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 23:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Christian I think discipline is great and Lent allows me to fast something I do quite a bit (to play games) and use that time praying and seeking God instead. It has catholic roots but other denominations picked it up to, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my worry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long do you think Rocket Leagues appeal will last? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to give up video games for lent and have shot myself in the foot forgetting about Rocket Leagues release. Without the cross play feature that the other versions have do you think people will be playing this game for a long time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dropped my phone and now have big black line across screen, is this as simple as a screen replacement or will I have to shell out more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 11:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 22:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved and still love the game to this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 16:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to do the minutemen quests to continue with the story, I forget which one it was but it forces you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pip Boy Edition Holders - 4 months on was it worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 16:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I walked past a Cex (a British second hand games and technology retailer) the other day which had Pip Boys for 50 with game, I know the one that I got is just gathering dust in the corner of my room. Anyone happy with their purchase and actually still use it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 14:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I was trying to overcomplicate the matter. Thanks much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuck on Unravel trial Level 2 [Possible Minor Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 14:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've just got to the bit where you fly the kite and I always fall to my death, from what I can see I can't see any indication off the game to jumps off and swing to something else. Little help?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 14:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that makes sense, I was in shock when it said I had 10 hours left! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why wont the Lord heal me? [Slightly NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 22:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For years I have continually pleaded with the Lord to help me never look at porn again but I always fall. I listened to someone's testimony today where they did the exact same thing and from that point on they didn't want to? Why do I feel that sometimes the Lord loves others more than me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is resident evil zero good? Or should I go with revelations 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the resident evil games enough, is resident evil zero worth fill price because I've never played it. Or should I go with revelations 2? Would I need to play revelations 1 before it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the Rocket League community will die down, theres a lot of people on this sub who are excited for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 12:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luigi Mansion okay if you haven't played the first one?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me fall in love with the 3ds again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 11:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IPhone is disabled please connect to iTunes... I don't own a computer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 11:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I use a tablet for all my online tomfoolery and can't download iTunes to it. My iPhone has locked me out because my nephew was messing with it, is there anything I can do or am I boned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the first game with a double jump and why was it implemented? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 17:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been thinking about the double jumps mechanic in many platforming games and its such a buzzard concept I knew I had to ask this question. Did the devs accidentally programme a jumps too high and say 'Ah fuck it, give them two'. Why would you need your character to jumps again in the air? It doesn't require additional skill as I can see it just means you can make higher/longer jumps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Spoilers : Does Life is Strangest choices actually effect the story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive completed episode 1 of LiS and am wondering if my actions actually have consequences or is it like The Walking Dead which makes you feel as if what you do matters even though whatever you do the same outcome happens?

Edit: Autocorrect ruined my title.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My week off has consisted of... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 12:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 09:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently brought my snes and just got **Super Star Wars** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the pal version of Super Star Wars have level passwords? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 09:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the copy I brought someone wrote what appears to be passwords in the notes section of the manual, but I can't find anywhere to put them. Are they level passwords? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha should of elaborated, that's if someone else is doing that thing with me. I guess that's different... I settled down to watch a movie earlier, lasted 5 minutes, tried to buckle down and do some work, lasted even less eventually tried to sleep but just couldn't. Its an odd cycle. Sorry for confusion, its late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have an awful attention span... anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 01:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly, awful. I can't go 10 minutes without getting distracted by something or getting bored. Anyone else have that problem? What are some ways to combat this?

Edit: Originally said my attention span was an hour. This is a mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 18:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Owns the game before sad to say it's not my cup of tea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't let me send an email. Apparently my message exceeds 5kb, when it doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm locked out of my account, due to a password reset form and the email doesn't come through. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitch is making me reset my password but the email hasn't come through I cannot get through to any twitch page because of this, I saw this was a problem months ago, is it still happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LF: Jane, Cherries, Videos or accounts. Kimberley Marvel and Helena Strong, any big cuties. Have: Valery, Plump Princess videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 17:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 17:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Kimberley you got? I Have quite a bit of Valery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save the money on fixing up you house, Sri picked you! Pming you now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets hope we dont pick the same person :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 14:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still in the competition but just so you know Just Cause 2 is not nessacary playing before 3 at all. Anyway, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 14:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope hope hope this comes out and isn't another crowd funding disaster. I didn't give to it but I hope you guys haven't been screwed over who did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a Just Cause 2 code to give away. Comment below why you should get the code and I'll randomise and pick a winner in a few hours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 14:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rocket League Out Now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie do you regret not seeing on the big screen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 16:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw Mad Max : Fury Road and damn I missed out on such a great ride not seeing it till now. I loved it anyway and will definitely see it in a theatre if it sees a re-release locally. The action and colours deserve to be seen on big screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 23:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ilovegta6 he was playing gta v </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 13:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still get Christmas attire until January 4th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 13:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own both Just Cause and Halo, Halos single player really leaves something to be desired. Just cause is single player only and is great, its personally my game of the year. The story is standard but alot of the missions are mega fin. Its up to you , though Halo does have great multiplayer (no splitscreen though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 13:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Yes! Yes! Huge Rare fan and I was so excited for rare replay, people were talking about starting up the online communities again and it was great... alas it never happened. I am 100% down to clown with this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 02:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I really like this album, and I mean really like it. Love the idea, love the tunes and damn you guys have some pipes on you. This album has kept me amused as I've been ill over the holidays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 13:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the problem, I am an uncle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 01:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the complaints were due to a lack of content and a season pass which is near enough the same price as the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 01:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just realised that one day I will probably be uncle knobhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My auntie keeps getting me shirts that are too small every Christmas, after I always remind her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 01:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 00:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know how the fuck it got the budget for a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Christmas my parents got me 140 to get a "big present" help me Reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 00:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Games don't install when on instant on... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 22:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merry Christmas you filthy animals! I got Halo 5 today so will be playing that. Multiplayer wise I also own GTA, Titanfall, Rare Replay to name a few. Also down for speaking in party chat while playing single player games. Gamertag - Specialunitt - 20/M/UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting . How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 15:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Titanfall! This is good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 15:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will I be able to follow it without playing the others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Halo 5's multiplayer strong enough for it to be the only bit I play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 14:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 16:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 15:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kings Quest Chapter 1 is one of my favourite games of the last year. I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait? Jirard has an album? What? Wait? What? Is this him singing? It's all come about so quick
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 17:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not always but 99% of the time there's a liar reveal bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 08:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody I know loves chicken run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 07:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The snowman.

The snowman and the snow dog I just didn't get into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 23:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Titanfall is my favourite online shooter of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 18:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally loved it but I do get if people don't like it, there is ALOT of recycled content in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 15:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 14:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Grumpcade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 00:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about a minute or two to tell someone on staff versus an hour and half of annoyance. I know what I'd rather do, also I work at a theatre and if you ask for a free ticket after a bad experience you will probably get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 00:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who didn't like the end of the movie, I've never thought about it that way! Will rewatch soon with that in mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 23:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The patch is out, if it didn't download during instant on you will have a nudge to download it when you next start the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 18:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it felt like a news helicopter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 14:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theatre I work at does autistic showings, I thought this was something everywhere does. Guess not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patch has made my loading screens longer... Xbone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 12:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had a problem with loading in this game it's always been about 10-15 seconds but I've just waited a solid minute for a challenge to restart after patching it...

Edit: also the slowdown is way more apparent now, normally it was just with explosions but now I'm getting framerate drops from just flying. Avalanche have you broke my game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 11:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather miss a minute of the movie or be distracted all the way through? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 00:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did like it! I just want to see a bit more :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 19:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh I just feel like the whole sequel trilogy is going to rehash the original trilogy. The  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 19:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she was legitimately distracting you could have asked an usher to do something. I work as a theatre usher and we love telling people to be quiet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 09:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love the fuck out of it. Would you rather have her not be a Skywalker? Don't you think it's just a little too safe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 09:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it's a red herring, it'd be way to obvious that she could be Lukes daughter and also they'd just set up the I am your father scene from ESB. I really hope she isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 09:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not, that would be the laziest writing. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 01:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh, which is a shame as you weren't trying to be funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 23:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no. I hope not, I see TFA as a nice homage to IV but episode 8 really needs to be its own story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 23:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there was enough new in the film to warrant it. People complained that the prequels didn't have enough parrells to the OT. While it did feel at times like we were retreading old ground the story still moved along, it's not the exact same plot. You have Kylo Ren, Finn and others which are similar yes but different characters. I just hope they don't do a I am you father thing in episode 8  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it just the Jedi that have been shown to be myth status? I'm sure Rey mentions how Han could also be legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Regarding the myth status of the Jedi.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 22:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? Why? It's been 30 years in universe how has Luke Skywalker become mere myth? How can people not remember the events of both Death Stars blowing up. How have people forgot that Alderaan has completely gone. How do they explain these things if they don't know about the Jedi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 21:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep even for children it's really dumb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theatre I work at has banned costumes, I know of a few worldwide that have. Find out first :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 19:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a movie theatre, I saw it early because every film for the past year has been spoiled due to people talking about it as their leaving the theatre. I wasn't going to let that happen for Star Wars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 19:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like to expand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 19:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the movie, had a massive grin on my face the whole time. I can live with this being similar to A new hope, I just hope that in the next episode they don't reveal Luke to be Rey's father. It'd be way too obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the movie but I would have loved the next movie to be about finding Luke. It would have given me a clear objective to look forward to in the next film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry. TFA has got me back into Star Wars and as a result I'm getting some EU Books for Christmas. Stories are still stories, canon or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say that people who haven't seen the others could enjoy it? Or are all 6 movies mandatory. Just wondering how they went with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 15:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kings Quest chapter 2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 12:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed some of the best platformers ever made my friend! The ps2 was excellent and just may be my favourite console of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 02:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now the Star Wars Holiday Special </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 23:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited as shit for Star Wars and I think a new Indy movie would get the same amount of excitement out of me. I like Kingdom, it's fun. I prefer it to temple of doom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 22:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume they would release a new one in April. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 22:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were 4 months late releasing their calendar this year. The 2015 calendar goes from April to April 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 21:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm constantly taking breaks, other commitments get in the way to watch everyday. If the series is a longer series like Galaxy I'll normally wait for the series to end and watch the series on a day where I'm doing nothing, however series like Dog Island now I will try my best to watch everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 21:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the best Christmas present I could ever have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't meant to be released 4 days ago, it got through some cracks the official release is today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings Quest Chapter 2: Avaliable now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 16:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chapter 1 may just be one of my favourite games of the year and the second chapter is no dissapointment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 14:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject1260nitt,

Have loads of online games, but am way more into single player. Up for a party chat one time though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 13:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried downloading it within the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 15:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just cause 3
Batman Arkham Knight
Kings Quest Episode 1
The Witcher 3
Rare Replay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, didn't mention that I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When dogs cry when you leave them alone in the house, do they think you're ever coming back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dogsit for my brother a lot, and was just wondering when she cries when he goes in holiday, is it because she thinks he's abandoned him? She's alright after a day or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 17:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally no, I'd wait the extra few seconds until I'm out the cinema  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you get to see the film spoils free. Cinema worker here too but I have the 17th off but working every day from 18th - 24th gonna be brutal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't really get that frame of logic, can't people wait until they leave the theatre to talk about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usher here, we don't have a clipboard we have a little piece of card. What they're doing is probably a screen check. At my cinema I work at We are instructed to go into the screen and check the audience for disruptive people/ kids/ anyone recording and also check that the audio is still syncing properly on the movie and that the movie is the correct aspect ratio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 21:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newly getting into Star Wars properly, what does this viewing order accomplish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day one Xbox one owner of the game here. The slowdowns aren't as bad as the media said they were. 60+ hours in and the game keeps a constant framerate, I've also never been in a loading screen for more than a few seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 15:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have destiny and Roxie email me your pp account :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me happy at the end of an awful day. I loved chapter 1 to bits. Happy I'm not working tommorow :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 17:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you have to do is let it in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars Clone Wars vs Star Wars The Clone Wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 14:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the newer series is canon, and apparently very good. Should I ignore the 2003 series and go straight to the newer one or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 13:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if I think it's worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 01:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Birthday man! Have a great day, we love you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 11:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about being strategic to make the most money.

So it is about making money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 11:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a league I can get behind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres a Dr Dolittle 5?!

That means theres a Dr Dolittle 4! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it. It's not about a talking kangaroo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 14:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I'm down if the grumps want to update the heads, these are great. Having a new coat of paint on the channel is never a bad thing as long as it keeps the original feel and flavour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 00:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a relief, praying for his healing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 23:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the victim dead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 17:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just cause 3 comes with Just cause 2 :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 10:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is fun as fuck, doesn't surprise me at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here we are December! And you know what I want for Christmas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need my complete Jake and Amir Blu Ray VHS set. I really do.  If I don't get it for Christmas this year I'll stick a paper clip in my drink, die, and sue the pants off of you coy coy divas. I swear to God you micey micey bastards, taking art from my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 15:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would it work for PC players then? They can cross play with everyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 12:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will buy this as soon as it goes on sale. I've heard enough good things off of people who have it on PC. I hope the cross play is retained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's to stop Isis bombing us now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 10:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So how do you rebuild settlements and towns to blow up again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 10:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard this was a feature and haven't experienced it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The longer you play the more the issues occur. Currently on 20 hours and the whole game stammers along. Don't try to cover actual issues. I have the game on Xbox one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
