<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7831</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 15:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She did. I teased her about expecting money or weed to be in there :) ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 15:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's strange. It happens really loudly and wakes us up, but stops the moment we move, before we can really get a chance to ascertain it's position.

I'm going to open the wall soon and see what I see.

And dude, you are going to freak Leah out with that creepy nightmare stuff and your theories.  That's the last thing I need to deal with.  Once I find out what's in the wall this will all be settled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I can totally hear them scratching. It's very annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Message Sent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From: David B. [mailto:xxxx@xxxxxxxx.com] 

Sent: Friday, June 03, 2015 12:29 PM

To: Sandra B.

Subject: We've arrived!

____________________________________________

Hey Sandy!


I want to make sure you have my new email address.  I'm using this one now since I left that job in Atlanta.

So, Leah and I arrived safely yesterday and we're getting all setup here.  The move was pretty easy, it only took one small U-haul truck.  It was weird to think that all of my possessions fit in the one big rolling box, but I guess I always was a bit of a free spirit.

I have to say, it is really strange being back here, the house hasn't really changed at all.  How many years did mom live in a house with both of our rooms almost completely intact?  Feeling a bit sad about that now, thinking about her passing our childhood bedrooms every day to get to the bathroom.  I guess when you're a parent you never really let go.  You'd know better than I (PS: how are the kids?).

I want to thank you for dealing with the estate paperwork, that was a huge load off and I am much more suited toward dealing with the house and her stuff.  Not to mention I need to thank you again, and again for agreeing to let us live here. I never thought that Leah and I would own a home together, and least of all our old house.  It means a lot that you'd give up the sale profit for now so that we could try to start a family here.

Anyway, I was thinking of you today.  I ran out to grab some cleaning supplies and when I got back you won't believe what was sitting on the kitchen table.  My old nightmare box!  Remember you brought that wooden box back from Salem when Grandma and Grandpa took you there for Halloween?  I think that was the first gift you ever got me. We were what like 8 and 12?

I was so happy that day.  Remember how I always used to wake you up every time I had a nightmare?  Then one night you suggested that I should "put" the nightmare in that box and close it instead of crawling into bed with you?  Totally worked, I would do it every night picturing the images in my nightmare being shut into and trapped into that box.  You learned those parenting skills pretty early with me :)

Anyway, Leah found it in my old bedroom   was checking it out.  I think she was hoping there was some money or some weed in there or something.  She thought it was pretty cute when I told her what it actually was, and it was quite a stroll down childhood memory lane.

Oh hey, I wanted to ask you.  Did mom say anything about rodents or problems in the house before she passed?  We both got woken up last night by this crazy scratching sound that seemed like it was coming from the walls.  Leah is really freaked out by rats, and I really hope that's not it.  I could deal with a squirrel or something, but if it's rats I might need to keep that quiet and take care of it without her knowing. She'll definitely freak out.

Ok, I feel like I'm rambling now.  
I just wanted to touch base   let you know that we're taking care of things here.  I'll be in touch soon.

Ciao!

[[Part Two](https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4waf6r/message_sent_part_two/)]

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was in northwestern PA on the edge of the Allagheny national forest.  I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl with a Bright Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sooooo psyched!  Today was the big day and I just can't help but share it with someone!  I can't tell anyone else, so I'm totally sending it to the anonymous interwebs instead!  Please please please leave replies! You're gonna be the only people who know.

Today was my sweet sixteen.  We had a great party, all of my besties were there, and even though my Dad was totally being ridiculous and emotional we managed to have an awesome time.  Amy, Sandra and Divan we're totally styling, dressed to the hilt and crazy happy with the snacks and drinks (virgin of course, thanks to Dad). We hung out, ran around, dipped in the pool and partied like all day, it was soooo fun.  Oh yeah, and mom totally splurged and bought me an awesome dress, I was beyond hot, and all the boys that came were totally bugging out.

Anyway, that was really cool, but it was nothing compared to the gift I got myself after the party.  I'm getting goosebumps again just thinking about it.

I know this sounds totally uppity, but I'm special.  I was just born that way and I can tell that lots of people see it.  They crowd around me, want to be near me like all the time.  There's just something I've always had. I'm different.  And special people have to take care of themselves.  I read that in this book that my mom has.  Mostly it's filled with silly hippie junk, but there was this thing about a goose that lays golden eggs, and if the goose doesn't take care of itself, it can't make any more.  Totally hit me, and I started planning my gift to myself.  Gotta make sure I take care of that goose!

So after my party, after my mom and dad went to bed and my friends left I got ready.  I went makeup crazy first and totally smeared my face.  There was no way anyone would recognize me, I totally looked like some freaky clown, that like got caught in a rainstorm or something.  I covered my hair with a black beach hat, got dressed in my black dance leotard grabbed my shoulder bag   headed out.

Sneaking out was easy just like always, but I had to walk like 2 miles cuz I wanted to get far away from my house.  I'm special but I'm not stupid or crazy! LOL!

This is where the fun started!  It's so silly, and I know I'm a bit old for it, but I started playing eenie-meenie with the houses.  Feeling so silly, but kinda cool too.  I landed my little finger on a small ranch house, which looked perfect.  I wanted to do this by chance, leave it up to the universe ya know, but this place was dark and small, and there was probably only one or two people who lived there.

There were no cars driving around at all which was perfect. It was really easy to get behind the house without anyone seeing me, and boom! Totally found a window cracked open!!! This was soooo meant to be.

I lifted myself and climbed into the window that was over the kitchen sink.  No sound at all, I was a total ninja.  My ballet shoes made no noise at all, as I walked around the house like i was taking a tour.  I was pretending that I was gonna buy the place, thinking about all the crappy cupboards and carpet like my Mom did when before we bought our house.  Too bad those totally hot dudes from house hunters weren't there. LOL!

I was solid, not scared at all and messed around looking at pictures, the food in the fridge and the magazines and stuff piled up near the couch in the living room.  I was pretty sure this was a single dude and when I got into the bedroom I was totally right.  One dude, like 30 something, kinda fit but a bit redneck. He was asleep, snoring like a freight train, face down on his bed.  His back had no gross hair or anything, but it was all pimply. Kinda disgusting.

I opened up my bag and grabbed the ice pick (my grandfather would have freaked out, it used to be his before he croaked.) Then I took a second to breath and be really ready.  I wanted to really take it all in and make sure I enjoyed my gift here.  This was like the only time I was ever gonna do this and I had to make sure I remembered it! Right?

"Happy birthday to me." I whisper-sang and then I leaned on the ball of the ice pick, pushing into the guy's back.  I swear! I almost totally blacked out, it was such a RUSH!!!

Dude sounded like a fish gasping and trying to turn over, and I knew I did it just right, just like in that youtube video I saw.. I got the pick right in his lung! (Of course, I'm awesome. applause, applause..)

I pulled out the pick and let him turn over.  His eyes were all like "what what? Who who?"

"Awww. You're a little owl with those eyes" I said. (ha! I was sooo cool, just so me right then.)

I put on my pouty face and then I went like totally angry-crazy!  I stabbed and stabbed and stabbed, like all over.  He flopped like a fish and I got him in the belly, in the chest, in the arms sometimes, and I even aimed for his cock once but that wasn't that fun really.

Blood started shooting out of some of the hole (but not others which was weird) but I just kept going and going.  It was so Hot!  I totally get how dudes love plunging into girls now.  I don't think any of my friends will ever understand it like I do now.  

Then it all stopped. The dude went still, I got really tired and then we just cuddled for a while.  I curled up all tired and put my arms around him and it was like total bliss.  I soaked it all in and sighed.

So this was the one! The biggest ever pressie to me! I got a present that like NOONE ever gets.  Did something totally cool and totally unique, and I will alway always always have this memory.

When I'm like 50 and chillin' on a yacht with like Hollywood stars I'll have this with me.  I am like super awesome, super powerful and nobody can ever ever take this away.

Anyway.. I'm 16 now! Totally gonna take on the world! Wish me a happy birthday, it was an awesome one!








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! fixing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She rode me home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time in my life where I had wanted nothing more than to leave this harsh world.  I was 15 years old and was utterly and completely alone in the world.  My grandmother cared for me and though she did her very best, but was simply not equipped for properly caring for me.  I had no true friends, only acquaintances that were sometimes friendly, but mostly kept me around to fill the role of a whipping post.

I was overweight, unattractive, too sloppy to be grouped with the popular or athletic kids in my High School.  I was too dull and quiet to be seen as interesting with the geek crowd, and I was far too much of a social pariah to be popular with the girls in my neighborhood.  In short I had nothing going for me, and chose to just embrace it, and find comfort in solitude.

I had always been in poor physical shape (I like to blame my Italian grandmother who considered pasta and cheese to be the mainstay of every meal) but as slow as I was, I began to take to long walks through the woods on the outskirts of our town.  These were deep, lush woods heightened in color and thickness by the moist Pennsylvania air.  I always found the wet rock faces, and rich moss to be very soothing for me as I explored the winding creeks, riverbeds and complex weaving game trails of what I always called the "dark forest".

Over the year of 1992 I had explored these game lands fully time and time again to the point where I could walk the trails in my own mind before going to sleep, which I did often to assist with my insomnia at the time.  There was no corner of that area that i did not know intimately.  Because of this I was very surprised when one day I pushed through some brambles at the eastern edge of the fishing hole, to find a small clearing which I did not recognize whatsoever.

The clearing was only maybe nine feet across and thickly surrounded by thick Maples almost completely blocking light from entering the refuge inside.  I immediately felt an intense love of this spot, along with a strange growing uneasiness about how encapsulated it truly felt. I was at once both a moth who had finally embraced a flame, and a butterfly suddenly ensnared under a glass dome.

My reverie was quickly dispersed as I fell backward hard onto my tailbone, the instant my mind recognized the shape of a young woman sitting and sobbing at the center of the small clearing.

"Ma fuh." I so eloquently uttered as I fell, sounding like a mentally challenged cartoon character.  

At this, the waify towheaded young woman looked up, eyes teared over and examined me as I both backed away and attempted to regain my composure and my footing.  She looked at me pleadingly through her obvious pain, questioning and hope beginning to light her face.

She was my height and maybe 90 pounds soaking wet, wearing a simple thin white dress, and apparently nothing else.  Her hair was light and blonde almost to the point of being white, and her features beyond fair.  She was barefoot and bare legged, though there was not a trace of dirt or grime on her alabaster limbs.  To every extent she was delicate and beautiful save for one very odd feature which did not ruin her appearance, so much as accentuate her other perfections.  Her eyebrows were thick and as black as could be, and flared wildly across her brow seeming to extend into, and jut out past her hairline, pointing outward from her temples.

"Haallo" her small intricate drawn out voice was subtle and enchanting.

"Hello".  This was the extent of my charm, and ability to deal with this unusual encounter.

Her eyes rolled slightly upward and her lips began to curl slightly into a smile, as she slowly reached out a thin hand toward me, inviting me toward her.

At this point, I was at my feet but feeling a bit apprehensive.  My eyes darted around, as if this was some trick being played upon me, and I was being lured into a trap to be beaten by some of the more aggressive kids in my school.  I could hear and feel my heart pound and then pause, and the hair on my arms stand on end. 

In the end, this trepidation turned quickly into cautious excitement.

As likely seems clear, I had never been very popular with the female gender and certainly had never been an object of their interest.  But here, suddenly, there was only me and the lovely creature, and she was in some kind of trouble or pain, and was reaching out to me.  I cannot say that I was lured by any sort of expectation, but I was certainly intrigued, enchanted an steeled myself to not allow this strange opportunity to pass unfulfilled.

I swallowed hard, and stepped toward her, slowly reaching out my hand so as not to scare her, and gently took her hand in mind.  This connection was overwhelming, and the warmth of her hand in mine was like nothing I had felt before.  My heart swelled at the feeling of that warm (no that feverishly hot) appendage in my palm.

"Are you ok" I inquired caringly.

She only smiled, and raised her other hand to caress my cheek, and then my neck.  The heat from her hands was overwhelming, and the touch was all encompassing.  Her right hand continued to explore my neck, pull on my ears, push soft and then hard upon my chest as I consciously tried to let go of the shame I had for my own body and fully be in this moment.

Things progressed so quickly. It was a delicious blur of heat, exploration and passion as we kissed, caressed, undressed bit by bit, our bodies responding, and before I could think for a moment, for the first time ever I was making love.  I was making love to a beautiful young woman in these woods that were my refuge without shame or fear or anything other than ecstasy.

She had pushed me to the ground in the center of the clearing, and was riding me slowly and then faster as our passion increased.  I swooned as she bit her lip staring upward at the sky and blood began to trickle from her thin lips.

This sight pushed me to the edge, and I could not stop myself from immediate expenditure.  As my head cocked back and eyes began to roll I was startled as she quickly jumped off of me and put her cupped right hand between her legs, scooping the fluids now amassed there.  She then quickly spat the blood from her mouth into this same hand and shouted something indeterminable as she flung the collection of fluids onto the ground above my head.

What happened then, I am at a loss to accurately describe.  In a blur of motion and overwhelming sensual impact of sound, light and even smell, the trees about us fell away, the ground breathed and moved beneath my back, the sky darkened and lightened assaulting my eyes, and the pressure of gravity upon my body, which I had never felt or considered before pulled at me and then released it's grip slightly but noticeably.

At once I felt as if I was in a confused dream.  Around us were plains of searing crimson brush like no other vegetation I had ever seen.  Small lights like fireflies migrated through the air and even through our bodies in the thousands as I took in the strange collection of shrieks, clicking noises and piping in the distance.  The ground beneath me was wavering and gelatinous but I was not pressed into it as my body felt lighter and almost frictionless against it.  As I tried to turn over i found that the push I made upon the earth (or what I still choose to call earth regardless of the obvious change in environment) was enough to send my body reeling upward toward the enormous leaf shaped wisps a hundred feet above our heads.

Her quick but gentle hand caught my pant leg and she effortlessly pulled me back toward the ground and she secured my position with both hands.  She then rose them to my face, holding it gently and whispered to me, peering directly into my eyes.

"I am home, and I thank"

I flinched as she dug her fingernails into my lip, slapped her hands together and then smacked me hard, directly on the forehead with a great cracking noise, that sent me falling backward onto the hard ground.

The hard ground.  The trees.  The stones. The thick moist air of the Pennsylvania forest, in that small clearing, where I visit time and time again, for the hope, for the chance of seeing my lost love, who I helped to return home, but will never, ever forget.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 02:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  Up until the point where the action comes in is actually a completely true story. This probably led to the lead-up vacation story, because i based it on one of my vacations :)

I was trying to follow the ""write-what-you-know" advice and perhaps was a bit too dedicated to that split.

I truly appreciate the read and feedback! Thanks so very much, I'm excited to continue to this excellent subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love a critique please!

Workshop Post:
https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleepworkshops/comments/4vzpfq/please_critique_my_first_nosleep_story/

Actual post:
https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4vzdnv/the_intended/

Thanks all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Critique my First NoSleep Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 19:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that writing this is pointless.  I know that it will likely be of no help whatsoever.  At this point I'm left decided between trying and not, doing something or just accepting the fact that I will never find solace in sleep, or in a dark room for the rest of my days, marked as they are.

I'm going to try.  I'm going to convince myself right here and now that maybe, by the grace of some higher power that If I share this story with someone it may relieve some of the burden that I have carried for the past two years.  Perhaps writing this down and putting this out to the world will exorcise the fear and horror from my subconscious and bring this darkness into the light.  Perhaps the onus of the scarred mark on my chest will feel a bit lighter, more surreal in the light of day.

Sharing this with you now, is a tribute to hope and nothing more.

+++

It was a dream come true.  After years of scrimping and saving my wife Rebecca and I had finally reached a point where we could take our first vacation in several years.  We were ecstatic to arrive in Madrid in the spring time, check into our hostel and begin to eat our way through the city.  Our plan was to tour the entire country of Spain over 14 days beginning and ending in Madrid.

Our lives had always been defined by chaos.  We managed small businesses, were heavily involved in the lives or our two children, took part in community organizations, read, crafted and generally drove ourselves through life, experiencing everything we could at every turn.  On this trip we decided to spend out time without a plan, to take each thing as it came, to drive through the countryside and do whatever caught our fancy in the moment.  Finally we would spend some time not pushing ourselves and just seeing where the world may take us.

Our trip was immediately marked by both wonderful and tricky situations.  On our first night in Madrid both of our cellphones were stolen by a young thief.  The skill at which this young man asked for directions and set his paper map upon our outdoor dining table was without measure, and it took hours for us to realize that both of our cell phones had been on the table and were now missing.  Shortly thereafter we found an old egyptian temple that had been moved from Egypt stone by stone and placed in park in the city.  This was an astounding place, so out of character for the city, but historic and wonderful.

Our trip went on like this for a week as we drove the small rental car up north to Bilbao and visited the Guggenheim, further east near France to experience the wonderful outdoor restaurants and exceptional food, and then south toward Valencia.  At each turn we randomly and freely found incredible experiences, places to be, things to see and quite often wonderful meals and Spanish wines to consume.

Wonder after wonder, we were enchanted again as we drove from Valencia toward the beaches of Malaga to see off in the distance some very interesting ruins.  I remember my wife looking over at me inquiringly and then both of us smiling knowingly as we took the closest exit and made our way up the hill toward this destination.  We quickly found ourselves navigating very narrow, ancient stone lined streets through a quaint little village and were overwhelmed by the historicity of this town.  Parking the car on a small dirt lot we hiked the remaining half a mile up the hillside overlooking the village and explored the minimal remains of a moorish castle that stood at the top of the hill.  

I remember the sun shining at the very edge of the only remaining complete wall of the castle, pulsing as it started to fall behind the corner of this magnificent structure.  The grounds in front of the wall, which would have been the interior of the castle were broken stone leading close to the edge of the cliff where sat a single almond tree, gripping the dirt of the cliff's edge for fear of falling over.  The strangest thing about the ruin was that the wall that did stand complete, had a very large entrance where you would imagine thick wooden doors to be hung.  The doors were likely long ago destroyed and in their place was hung thick canvas, darkened by the dust and arid weather of the Spanish climate.  This hanging seemed very out of place, and my wife and I pondered and talked about why someone might hang this in the entrance of these ruins.  We could come up with no good reason, but continued to poke around and enjoy the environment, and the view from the hilltop.

When we finally decided to get back on the road, we headed down into the village below and started heading towards the car.  It was at this point we started noticing that on several roads through the village were hung streamers, and on other roads there were large wooden blockades painted blue.  

Rebecca turned to me, "Wait, there's something happening here today.  Let's stay."

The sound of a small engine entered my consciousness as a small old gentleman rode up to us on a scooter.  His small dog sat upon the floor of the dusty vehicle between his feet and the back was a bundle of buckets strapped with bungee cord.  The man parked, smiled at us with a wide grin and took a bucket and trundled over to us with a very welcoming look.

Rebecca and I spoke no Spanish and this man did not know English, but through a series of clumsy gestures and sounds we understood that today was a festival day.  As we attempted to communicate about the festival he fed us delicious fresh figs that he had picked from the fields outside the village.  They were warm from the hot sun that day and were a wonderful treat.

We were then lead over the barriers and into the main street where the occupants of the village gathered, and were astounded when a large bull was lead by a rope into the street with us and let loose.  We anxiously laughed and ran through the streets with the collection of european youths as the bull snorted and charged, turned and bucked for near to an hour.  This was an exceptional experience and we were giddy with falling upon this random happening.  

As the sun began to set, the bull was pulled back into a fenced area and the crowd began to disperse, as did we.  As we walked away from the main street we heard a single gunshot, and realized that this was likely how this festival ended, with the killing of the animal.  We tried not to judge, but that shot set a darkness over the event that we did not expect.

Before we reached the car, we once again ran into the small man who we had met earlier.  He offered us each one more fresh fig and bowed low as if to say goodbye.  Unable to refuse one last taste of these exotic fruit, we savored them on our tongues.  Almost as instantly my world went dark, and I only remember wondering why the ground in front of me was lurching toward my face.

+++

When my eyes opened once more, my mind struggled to assemble the image of the castle upon the hill which we had visited earlier.  I turned and searched my surroundings to find that I was gagged and bound in place, tightly tied to the Almond tree on the cliff's edge, inches from my wife.  We had been stripped completely naked and I felt the warm night air upon my body as I took in the scene before us.

We were facing the curtained opening of the ruin's wall, and between us and the opening were three men, two in black robes on either side of the doorway, and one in a crimson robe directly between us and the canvas curtain in the doorway.  The two men in black robes each had buckets near to them, and were chanting in low tones as they cautiously tossed figs between our tree and the opening as if marking a walkway with rose petals.

I cannot say what I felt in this moment.  I recall the whimpers and sounds of struggling around me but I have no concept of whether they came from me, Rebecca or both of us.  There was only thick and heavy panic and pulling at our binds as I tried to comprehend what was happening before us.  

The man in Crimson approached us, his face in the shadow of his hood, and the small knife in his hand catching the glint of the moonlight as it was lifted towards my wife.  The shriek that left my body as he cut into my wife between her breasts will haunt me forever.  It was an unearthly sound that was so unnatural streaming from my vocal cords and being warped and tangled by the gag in my mouth.  My eyes teared instantly and I gripped my eyelids shut as I heard my love cry and then moan through her gag.  When her sobbing began to subside I opened my eyes to see the small symbol letting blood upon her chest, and the man in Crimson beginning the same work upon my body.   

I am not a proud man, but I can simply report that I was able to remain calm and silent as the man drew the knife upon my chest, cutting a small circle and two horns between upon my solar plexus.  I was likely less fearful due to the fact that I had first seen the extent of this actions upon my wife before I, a fact of which I am certainly not proud.

This work completed, the man in Crimson dropped his knife upon the stone at his feet, slowly turned away from us toward the opening, and shouted something indistinguishable as he raised his arms high in the air with much fervor.  We saw no-one very close to the opening but at that moment the canvas burst into intense flames, and as the smoke cleared we could see the multitude of stars though the opening.

These were not our stars.

I have no proof, no description, no understanding of how or why I felt this so intensely in that moment. I can only state, as a fact that the night sky through this doorway was not ours.  They were misaligned, skewed, shifting and corrupt.  Just seeing this small swath of ill omened stars turned my stomach and I began to fear that I would choke on my own vomit, held by the rag in my mouth. 

Thunder began to shake the mountain top.  The wind began to howl and the smell of ozone filled my nostrils, as I began to notice that stars were being blacked out in the doorway before us.  One after another, beginning at the ground, blackness overtook layer upon layer of starlight, and a shape began to take form.  I could begin to make out the shape of a large lumbering oval backed beast approaching from the other side of the door as the chanting of the robed men began to rise.

For a moment rain blasted the hilltop on one quick sweep.  The wind spun, the thunder increased in volume and intensity,  The ruins became chaos as branches and dust flew through the air in confusion.  I struggled to pull my wrists from the binds, as I trained my mind to be ready to free Rebecca and not become lost in fear and immediate escape.

The ominous pitch dark shape of an other-worldly Bull began to emerge from the gate and into the ruins.  It's slick black coat seemed to be covered in sweat, or oil, or some organic fluid as it bucked and snorted and fought the air as if it was somehow constrained. The man in crimson was chanting louder and louder, hands raised as if encapsulating the animal as it slowly approached him and us.

I had never been religious, or believed in anything outside of what I could see hear and prove at this point of my life.  But at this point I was faced with the unexplainable.  I was faced with a madness and a horror that made me lose every preconceived notion I had ever have about the sanity or trust in the natural order of our world.  

I prayed.
I pleaded. I begged.  I gave myself up.  I let myself go. I in that moment accepted the complete loss of myself, without holding back.

There was only immediate darkness for me.  And then there was immeasurable light.

Looking back afterwards I realize that at that very moment, what had actually occurred was that lightning had struck the tree to which Rebecca and I were tied.  There was darkness, then light and then freedom.  In the chaos of the moment, as the tree split and fell behind us, I was able to fully free and ungag  myself and Rebecca.  In the confusion I saw that man in Crimson turn toward us enraged, and at that moment saw the bull break free of it's invisible fetters, charge and impale him upon it's midnight black horns.  Blood poured from the already crimson robes as the two men in black, Rebecca and I each ran down the sandy path of the hill.

We never looked back up at the ruins, there was only running for us.  Naked, bleeding, and tearing full speed through the fig fields, Rebecca and I looked only forward until exhaustion overtook us completely.  I have no concept for how many hours passed as we ran, for how we stayed together though the mad flight, or how we found ourselves sinking into delirious sleep in the fields close to the main road together.

I only know that we awoke at sunrise, torn up by a multitude of lacerations from the trees, completely naked and with a darkness in our souls that we had never had thought possible.

As you must imagine, we reached the road and found assistance, avoided the authorities and eventually found ourselves back home, mostly unharmed outside of the marks upon our breasts, and the unbeknownst horror in our hearts which we have never yet shared with anyone.

There is only one thing for us now.  We are marked.  We carry the seal upon our bodies, every passing day and each sleepless night.  

We know, you see.

We know that this mark is clear, that regardless of where, of when, and of what door that beast may find travel in the future, we are the intended.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Intended </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that writing this is pointless.  I know that it will likely be of no help whatsoever.  At this point I'm left decided between trying and not, doing something or just accepting the fact that I will never find solace in sleep, or in a dark room for the rest of my days, marked as they are.

I'm going to try.  I'm going to convince myself right here and now that maybe, by the grace of some higher power that If I share this story with someone it may relieve some of the burden that I have carried for the past two years.  Perhaps writing this down and putting this out to the world will exorcise the fear and horror from my subconscious and bring this darkness into the light.  Perhaps the onus of the scarred mark on my chest will feel a bit lighter, more surreal in the light of day.

Sharing this with you now, is a tribute to hope and nothing more.

+++

It was a dream come true.  After years of scrimping and saving my wife Rebecca and I had finally reached a point where we could take our first vacation in several years.  We were ecstatic to arrive in Madrid in the spring time, check into our hostel and begin to eat our way through the city.  Our plan was to tour the entire country of Spain over 14 days beginning and ending in Madrid.

Our lives had always been defined by chaos.  We managed small businesses, were heavily involved in the lives or our two children, took part in community organizations, read, crafted and generally drove ourselves through life, experiencing everything we could at every turn.  On this trip we decided to spend our time without a plan, to take each thing as it came, to drive through the countryside and do whatever caught our fancy in the moment.  Finally we would spend some time not pushing ourselves and just seeing where the world may take us.

Our trip was immediately marked by both wonderful and tricky situations.  On our first night in Madrid both of our cellphones were stolen by a young thief.  The skill at which this young man asked for directions and set his paper map upon our outdoor dining table was without measure, and it took hours for us to realize that both of our cell phones had been on the table and were now missing.  Shortly thereafter we found an old Egyptian temple that had been moved from Egypt stone by stone and placed in park in the city.  This was an astounding place, so out of character for the city, but historic and wonderful.

Our trip went on like this for a week as we drove the small rental car up north to Bilbao and visited the Guggenheim, further east near France to experience the wonderful outdoor restaurants and exceptional food, and then south toward Valencia.  At each turn we randomly and freely found incredible experiences, places to be, things to see and quite often wonderful meals and Spanish wines to consume.

Wonder after wonder, we were enchanted again as we drove from Valencia toward the beaches of Malaga to see off in the distance some very interesting ruins.  I remember my wife looking over at me inquiringly and then both of us smiling knowingly as we took the closest exit and made our way up the hill toward this destination.  We quickly found ourselves navigating very narrow, ancient stone lined streets through a quaint little village and were overwhelmed by the historicity of this town.  Parking the car on a small dirt lot we hiked the remaining half a mile up the hillside overlooking the village and explored the minimal remains of a Moorish castle that stood at the top of the hill.  

I remember the sun shining at the very edge of the only remaining complete wall of the castle, pulsing as it started to fall behind the corner of this magnificent structure.  The grounds in front of the wall, which would have been the interior of the castle were broken stone leading close to the edge of the cliff where sat a single almond tree, gripping the dirt of the cliff's edge for fear of falling over.  The strangest thing about the ruin was that the wall that did stand complete, had a very large entrance where you would imagine thick wooden doors to be hung.  The doors were likely long ago destroyed and in their place was hung thick canvas, darkened by the dust and arid weather of the Spanish climate.  This hanging seemed very out of place, and my wife and I pondered and talked about why someone might hang this in the entrance of these ruins.  We could come up with no good reason, but continued to poke around and enjoy the environment, and the view from the hilltop.

When we finally decided to get back on the road, we headed down into the village below and started heading towards the car.  It was at this point we started noticing that on several roads through the village were hung streamers, and on other roads there were large wooden blockades painted blue.  

Rebecca turned to me, "Wait, there's something happening here today.  Let's stay."

The sound of a small engine entered my consciousness as a small old gentleman rode up to us on a scooter.  His small dog sat upon the floor of the dusty vehicle between his feet and the back was a bundle of buckets strapped with bungee cord.  The man parked, smiled at us with a wide grin and took a bucket and trundled over to us with a very welcoming look.

Rebecca and I spoke no Spanish and this man did not know English, but through a series of clumsy gestures and sounds we understood that today was a festival day.  As we attempted to communicate about the festival he fed us delicious fresh figs that he had picked from the fields outside the village.  They were warm from the hot sun that day and were a wonderful treat.

We were then lead over the barriers and into the main street where the occupants of the village gathered, and were astounded when a large bull was lead by a rope into the street with us and let loose.  We anxiously laughed and ran through the streets with the collection of European youths as the bull snorted and charged, turned and bucked for near to an hour.  This was an exceptional experience and we were giddy with falling upon this random happening.  

As the sun began to set, the bull was pulled back into a fenced area and the crowd began to disperse, as did we.  As we walked away from the main street we heard a single gunshot, and realized that this was likely how this festival ended, with the killing of the animal.  We tried not to judge, but that shot set a darkness over the event that we did not expect.

Before we reached the car, we once again ran into the small man who we had met earlier.  He offered us each one more fresh fig and bowed low as if to say goodbye.  Unable to refuse one last taste of these exotic fruit, we savored them on our tongues.  Almost as instantly my world went dark, and I only remember wondering why the ground in front of me was lurching toward my face.

+++

When my eyes opened once more, my mind struggled to assemble the image of the castle upon the hill which we had visited earlier.  I turned and searched my surroundings to find that I was gagged and bound in place, tightly tied to the Almond tree on the cliff's edge, inches from my wife.  We had been stripped completely naked and I felt the warm night air upon my body as I took in the scene before us.

We were facing the curtained opening of the ruin's wall, and between us and the opening were three men, two in black robes on either side of the doorway, and one in a crimson robe directly between us and the canvas curtain in the doorway.  The two men in black robes each had buckets near to them, and were chanting in low tones as they cautiously tossed figs between our tree and the opening as if marking a walkway with rose petals.

I cannot say what I felt in this moment.  I recall the whimpers and sounds of struggling around me but I have no concept of whether they came from me, Rebecca or both of us.  There was only thick and heavy panic and pulling at our binds as I tried to comprehend what was happening before us.  

The man in Crimson approached us, his face in the shadow of his hood, and the small knife in his hand catching the glint of the moonlight as it was lifted towards my wife.  The shriek that left my body as he cut into my wife between her breasts will haunt me forever.  It was an unearthly sound that was so unnatural streaming from my vocal cords and being warped and tangled by the gag in my mouth.  My eyes teared instantly and I gripped my eyelids shut as I heard my love cry and then moan through her gag.  When her sobbing began to subside I opened my eyes to see the small symbol letting blood upon her chest, and the man in Crimson beginning the same work upon my body.   

I am not a proud man, but I can simply report that I was able to remain calm and silent as the man drew the knife upon my chest, cutting a small circle and two horns between upon my solar plexus.  I was likely less fearful due to the fact that I had first seen the extent of this actions upon my wife before I, a fact of which I am certainly not proud.

This work completed, the man in Crimson dropped his knife upon the stone at his feet, slowly turned away from us toward the opening, and shouted something indistinguishable as he raised his arms high in the air with much fervor.  We saw no-one very close to the opening but at that moment the canvas burst into intense flames, and as the smoke cleared we could see the multitude of stars though the opening.

These were not our stars.

I have no proof, no description, no understanding of how or why I felt this so intensely in that moment. I can only state, as a fact that the night sky through this doorway was not ours.  They were misaligned, skewed, shifting and corrupt.  Just seeing this small swath of ill omened stars turned my stomach and I began to fear that I would choke on my own vomit, held by the rag in my mouth. 

Thunder began to shake the mountain top.  The wind began to howl and the smell of ozone filled my nostrils, as I began to notice that stars were being blacked out in the doorway before us.  One after another, beginning at the ground, blackness overtook layer upon layer of starlight, and a shape began to take form.  I could begin to make out the shape of a large lumbering oval backed beast approaching from the other side of the door as the chanting of the robed men began to rise.

For a moment rain blasted the hilltop on one quick sweep.  The wind spun, the thunder increased in volume and intensity,  The ruins became chaos as branches and dust flew through the air in confusion.  I struggled to pull my wrists from the binds, as I trained my mind to be ready to free Rebecca and not become lost in fear and immediate escape.

The ominous pitch dark shape of an other-worldly Bull began to emerge from the gate and into the ruins.  It's slick black coat seemed to be covered in sweat, or oil, or some organic fluid as it bucked and snorted and fought the air as if it was somehow constrained. The man in crimson was chanting louder and louder, hands raised as if encapsulating the animal as it slowly approached him and us.

I had never been religious, or believed in anything outside of what I could see hear and prove at this point of my life.  But at this point I was faced with the unexplained.  I was faced with a madness and a horror that made me lose every preconceived notion I had ever have about the sanity or trust in the natural order of our world.  

I prayed.
I pleaded. I begged.  I gave myself up.  I let myself go. I in that moment accepted the complete loss of myself, without holding back.

There was only immediate darkness for me.  And then there was immeasurable light.

Looking back afterwards I realize that at that very moment, what had actually occurred was that lightning had struck the tree to which Rebecca and I were tied.  There was darkness, then light and then freedom.  In the chaos of the moment, as the tree split and fell behind us, I was able to fully free and un-gag  myself and Rebecca.  In the confusion I saw that man in Crimson turn toward us enraged, and at that moment saw the bull break free of it's invisible fetters, charge and impale him upon it's midnight black horns.  Blood poured from the already crimson robes as the two men in black, Rebecca and I each ran down the sandy path of the hill.

We never looked back up at the ruins, there was only running for us.  Naked, bleeding, and tearing full speed through the fig fields, Rebecca and I looked only forward until exhaustion overtook us completely.  I have no concept for how many hours passed as we ran, for how we stayed together though the mad flight, or how we found ourselves sinking into delirious sleep in the fields close to the main road together.

I only know that we awoke at sunrise, torn up by a multitude of lacerations from the trees, completely naked and with a darkness in our souls that we had never had thought possible.

As you must imagine, we reached the road and found assistance, avoided the authorities and eventually found ourselves back home, mostly unharmed outside of the marks upon our breasts, and the unbeknownst horror in our hearts which we have never yet shared with anyone.

There is only one thing for us now.  We are marked.  We carry the seal upon our bodies, every passing day and each sleepless night.  

We know, you see.

We know that this mark is clear, that regardless of where, of when, and of what door that beast may find travel in the future, we are the intended.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a fecking VECTREX!
oh yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree 100%.
Best. Game. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 20:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gallon of liquid latex meets the quilt that my wife's dead grandmother made her. 

This night was not nearly as hot as I expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thelesis Oasis in Philadelphia needs your help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 21:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh, shit.
Sorry.... should have looked more closely at that puppy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 21:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the occult sense, this symbol represents the convergence of earth and heaven.

The bottom triangle represents the "fire" of prayer and is often red in color, while the upper triangle (pointing downward, and often blue) represents the divine influence (mana) raining down upon the world.

This is of course a specific esoteric interpretation aside from other traditional significance (Star of David, etc.).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it ALL goes to Mumbai from here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love girls in crutches.  
Am a I ridiculous misogynist?  I promise I don't generally like seeing ladies hurt..... but.... mmmm.... crutches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
