<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7426</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * **N. Wastes:** I'll kick off with the remaining settlements. They do not predate the war and have been developed on the bones of razed Ageis cities. I may or may not keep these where they are. I've been toying around with giving this regions the ol' "Wild West" feel but what I've been tossing around has felt half-baked. The cornerstone of this region is the ruined capital where a bunch of old malicious magics linger due to the war ending confluence of forces centralized on the city. The Ageis are keeping an eye on the ruined capital as well but have been covert about it. The ruined capital is also one of the cornerstones of the zealous Golden Temple religion practiced by conservative Manous (the more liberal alternative is the Living Church introduced by the Trellen). According to the Golden Temple, the Manous God Emperor (from the Golden War) will be reincarnated and return to claim the throne and dominion over the world. Very doomsday cult that operates on a large scale and pours a lot of money into the Manous government to ensure it doesn't go anywhere. But I digress. I think most people just want to turn their back on the region lest it open up old wounds. Now only adventure seekers, bandits etc roam the northern region and the communities existing up there are little more than self-governed pit stops and halfway houses for those who have left or been exiled from the southern nations.

* **Ballutte:** Right off the bat, this nation is a work in progress both in terms of culture and geography. Your note about settling in the rain forest resonated with me because I've been tossing around expanding the rain forest to the north of the nation further south and making it more prominent and integrated. However, that screws up the geography a little bit and puts a warm region too far south for my liking (though I am not a rain forest expert). Like I said, it's being workshopped.

* **Dworu:** Pretty much spot on. As a side note, they are also one of the few nations that isn't riding the anti-magic kick. But like I mentioned earlier, they are still unable to draw magic from within themselves. The Dworu have built a culture around ritual bloodletting where magic casting is done in pairs. One member of the pair (usually a large man with great fortitude and constitution) will let their blood which allows their partner to tap into their life force and perform acts of magic. It's a refinement on the sacrificial magics used by both the Dworu and Manous during the Golden War. Mage-pairs are usually paired for life and the pairing is made when a person's potential as a mage is discovered. The role of the bloodletter comes with its own social status and they are highly respected - especially if they live a long and notable life.

* **Vorcae (pronounced Vorkash):** Beastly as in part man, part beast. I've been toying around with how exactly I want this to be and I'm currently circling tall (8-9 ft) satyr-esque humanoids with a large rack (of antlers, that is). They are human enough to be familiar, but beastly enough to easily be labeled as others. Their allegiances belong to the Manous and Trellen, in the sense that they are fine as long as they stay where they are. Both allied nations have an unhealthy romanticist and patronizing attitude towards the Vorcae because they are exotic (think romantic/exotic attitudes towards Africans in post-emancipation United States mixed with the current American attitudes of "look the poor ethnic people...let's put on the appearance of helping them without getting our hands dirty by tweeting a hashtag or whatever"). Some of the western-most Manous cities are less racist towards them but the Golden Temple has made a hostile stance against the Vorcae that has made honest attempts at integration and true allegiance difficult. The Vorcae have been pushing north into No Man's Land but not too aggressively as one of their primary focuses has been growing their settlements in their bay region.

* **Manous:** The Manous' heartland has always been where it is now (save for when their central government was temporarily relocated to the ruined capital near the end of the Golden War). During the war, the Dworu occupied much of the land the Vorcae dwell in, pushing the Manous east. They then occupied and enslaved the Trellen (leading to the aforementioned refugees fleeing both south and east). After conquering the Trellen, the Manous marched north and conquored the Ageis (who were geographically remote). It was the Dworu, in liaison with refugee Ageis and the fractured remains of the Ageis military, who called down the meteor on what is now the ruined capital. Lots of people died, an entire race of magical beings was sacrificed, the Vorcae were created, and the Manous slunk back to their homeland where the Trellen groomed them for economic dependence. The Golden Temple church is the last vestige of the (self proclaimed) God Emperor but definitely sticks out like a sore thumb and wears its antiquity like a badge of honor. The Golden Temple gets money via donations from its members, which is then funneled back into the Manous government to further the advances and agendas of the church. Until semi recently this practice was unimpeded. However, the animism-based religion of the Trellen (the Living Church) has slowly been integrating itself as an alternative and has spread all the way to the western reaches of the Manous nation.

* **Trellen:**  Oofda, this has been a lot of writing but it's been fun. I'm following you on your comparison, though I don't know enough about historic global cultures to say for sure. The Trellen are crafty and have been watchdogs over the Manous following the war. Rather than seeking vengeance against their once-enslavers, they are killing them with "kindness" and culture. The Trellen rule through economy, though the Kon Hapi are a strong contender for this. The Trellen, also aware of the Golden Temple and all their hootenanny, have been an effective roadblock in northern expansion, choosing instead to colonize the islands off the eastern coast of the main continent. Like the Ageis, the Trellen are also keeping an eye on this region, mostly to ensure their borders are secure against any raids or attacks from the ungoverned cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, second follow-up since you've added on since my last check-in. Thanks for pushing my boundaries on this - it's been super helpful!

* **Roak Ald:** Ex-refugees who fled from the Golden Manus Empire's expansion and enslavement. The initial refugee group was not huge - think maybe two to three ships of around 60 people on each ship. Mostly able bodied men and some women with very few children. By the time they land on the island, grapple with the initial struggle to survive (breaking down the boats for shelter) and regroup into a sustainable lifestyle, the initial refugee group has become pretty invested in the communities they've fostered. Additionally, very few people knew about the refugees departing (and those who did probably died in the war) so they've been pretty invisible as a nation. With no communication between them and the mainland, it's like the war may as well have not ended. By the time contact was reestablished, the Roak Ald had little to no interest in reintegrating with a global society that had reintegrated the nation that had driven these ex-refugees into exile in the first place.

* **Kon Hapi:** Fear ye not, xenophobia is still alive and well, thriving as much as the blossoming caste system. I would hesitate to say the Kon Hapi pulled a 180 so much as the wealthy ruling class saw an opportunity to make more money, increase their global presence, and seemingly do a good deed in accepting refugees during the Golden War. Make no mistake about it, the refugees and their descendants have not risen in Kon Hapi society. They have been relegated to piss poor labor jobs or straight up begging in the streets. To add to the stereotypical orientalism of it all (because I'll call it when I see it), I've been toying around with the Kon Hapi controlling one of the larger drug economies in the world. Again, it comes down to money and power.

* **Ageis:** I suppose now is as good a time as any to mention that nation names are still being work shopped. I'm using them more for their feel and as placeholders. That being said, I think your biggest point about the Ageis was who their enemies were and how their cities and borders are situated. If we are drilling down, the Ageis' biggest enemy is themselves. As a nation, they have built a post-war society solely around growing military power and being self sustaining. You mentioned a lack of ports. The don't "need" (desire) them. The sense of security they feel is both in part because of the mountains, but also because the rest of the world has been ignoring them while the Ageis have been hiding and licking their wounds. This is to the point of most of the modern world not really knowing much about the Ageis except for what is written in history books. Without downplaying the enslavement and genocide of the Ageis during the Golden War, they are like a child who had all four appendages broken by a playground bully and has been amassing a metric f***ton of nukes to get back at said bully - even after the bully has reformed and become a productive member of society. So everyone knows they are there, but the Ageis have fallen out of sight and out of mind because no one has seen them for hundreds of years. Regarding self-sustainability: the Ageis are really adept farmers and have become quite industrious as well. That region of the world is pretty resource rich, negating their need for trade.

* **Asarii:** Literal aliens. While your comment about them being magicians is somewhat relevant, the magic they wield is drawn from inner, inate power rather than external sources (spirits, the land, magical beings like the Ed'Argo). I won't dive into magic right now, but following the Golden War, magic became taboo due to the near apocalypse that occurred because of it, as well as its use in Manous military treachery. So following the war we have magic aliens who literally come in peace except no one wants them. They are a by-product of a last-ditch effort that no one wanted to deal with. The Ageis, seeing their magical utility, form a temporary alliance with them to cross the mountains, swamp and lake to where they currently reside. Once the Ageis got settled, however, they became intensely hostile to the Asarii and began a witch hunt to either kill or drive out both the Asarii and Ageis who used magic. (Again, they hopped on the no-magic train because it was used for the systematic genocide of their nation.) The Asarii fled north past the strait and set up camp, figuring out how to make the best out of a really crappy and unexpected situation. Thanks for the feedback on their location as well. I'll probably migrate their nation center closer to the coast then expand their major cities out along the steppes following the rivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a follow-up broken down by point:

* **Regarding Scale:** I don't have this set in stone yet, but I have a general idea that I'll try to convey here. If you look back on the map at the Manous capital, I have been working under the assumption that it would take about 2 of a day's travel on horseback at a moderate pace to travel to the city to the south/southeast by the river. Like I said, I have yet to translate that into actual numbers.

* **Regarding the North-Central Desert:** This desert was created as the result of two factors happening in quick succession. I realize this may have been lost in the imgur album because the images got reordered after I had written the descriptions. The first factor is the massive amounts of magic that was drained from this region at the end of the Golden War to summon a meteor down on what is now the Ruined Capital. Additionally, a large amount of magic was used by protect the same city from the meteor (which is why it still stands). Not only was the land sapped of its natural magics, but the Dworu and Ageis bound and sacrificed the Ed'Argo (elemental beings/caretakers of natural magics) in order to summon and contain the meteor without destroying the entire world. It was pretty apocalyptic stuff and has permanently scarred the region because the Ed'Argo are no longer around to work on restoring magic to that land.

* **NE Frontier Wastes:** I'll admit to a bit of laziness here and you caught me in it. You might have been able to infer this from the descriptions in the imgur album, but my most fleshed out nations/regions are the Manous/Trellen/Vorcae trifecta as well as the Ageis.  Because of this, the land north of Ballutte is a little under-developed. I intended this wasteland to be the result of two factors - proximity to the equator (which is north of the map) and lack of fresh water in the region. Because the region is so arid, a lot of the topsoil (mostly sand) is picked up by the coastal winds and blown south where it "fouls" the land. I think over time the whole region will experience natural desertification that will only be impeded by the mountains.  As far as previous settlements in that region, I have no doubt the Ageis and later the occupying Manous sailed eastward. However, like settling there now is a financial and resource drain on the Trellen and Ballute, it was certainly so for the Ageis and Manous and likely abandoned. Since the Golden War put a large hold on expansion and drew most citizens of warring nations back to the main continent, any attempt at colonization was abandoned. Lastly, I wanted a "final frontier" on my map and this was the region. Without going into too many details, there is another continent far to the northeast of Ul Uren and the NE Wastes would be the closest landing point for them on discovery voyages. If I write anything in that region (I don't have anything planned) there will probably be some foreigners on the northeastern shore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a bundle! If you end up using it, I'd be pumped to see how you repurposed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! We should get a NaNo group going in this sub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll xpost it there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post: Looking for Geography Feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post: Looking for Geography Feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello fellow world builders! In prep for NaNoWriMo, I've been hard at work laying the foundation for a world that has been kicking around in my headspace for a few years now. I finally bunkered down on Inkarnate (say what you want - it's easy to work on at work) and have what I would consider the closest draft to my vision of this world.

I am looking for feedback on geography first and foremost. Comments on the placement of each nation's capitals is also welcome if you have strong opinions. The rest of the cities are placeholders and will likely move around. The album has more description in it to help you get a sense of the world.

Edit: Fixed the order of the images in the album (you might have to click through), updated main map image with distance scale and compass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geography Feedback: Ul Uren   Surrounding Islands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tips! Not sure if he would be open to leather clubs....at least not yet. It's been a slow, gentle push on my end to open him up to going to some of the dive and low key gay bars in Milwaukee.  Also thanks for the links to some gear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This is a pretty low stakes thing - it's not like our happiness is on the line lol. I just want to spice things up a bit because we have the rest of our lives together, so why not try out something new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice: Discovering leatherplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ordered two pairs of these...they look super comfy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Don't worry...I'm eager for them to grow back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM's welcome :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for going into this a little bit more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you care to elaborate more on plate tectonics regardless? This post is really motivating me (can't wait to get home tonight to take a whack at it) and I would love to have some additional insight into something I know almost nothing about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real.....they really need to add more color schemes and terrain variations. Everything is so grimdark.....but it's a better end result than my potato drawing skillz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would generally tend to agree with you. I'm treating most of the names as placeholders just to tack down my train of thought at that moment. Thanks for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some solid feedback regarding the desert and it's something I'm definitely still workshopping. The desert terrain color in Inkarnate was an easy and identifiable method for me to codify that region and I just rolled with it. With where I'm at in the rest of my world building (everything else has been localized around Stormwatch and Chalk Beach) I haven't had to make and real hard and fast decisions with that region.

Edit: names are still being workshopped as well. I'm sure you can relate, but they are one of those things where you throw a million things at the board until you find something perfect and it sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://inkarnate.com/

I did this all on Inkarnate. It's still in (indefinite) beta but the tools they have are pretty nice and easy to use once you get your feet wet. I wish everything was a vector, but hey, you get what you get with free tools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! When I was about half way through making the map I had the same realization about the shape of the geography! One of my biggest pet peeves are city names that are all fluff and no substance. I grew up in a rural area where all the towns were named after either a geographic landmark, the founder, or their some aspect of their history. I find this to be a more realistic way of naming cities and towns and I agree - it conveys flavor that "Thollulagazlah, Capitol of Chacharalamadamadingdong" doesn't quite give. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I forgot to touch on Dustfall. This settlement post-dates the creation of the desert and is one of the few "inhabitable" areas in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
