<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4489</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mystery Of Fallen Creek Orphanage Part 2; Ending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First Part: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zfcoq/the_mystery_of_fallen_creek_orphanage_part_1/

(This part is dedicated to Gorey58, a great Reddit user.) 

As the days pass, I'm getting less and less sleep... My eyes are heavy with weariness, and it is becoming harder to focus in school. I find myself falling asleep in all my classes. Now I am afraid of falling asleep when I ride my bike back to the orphanage. The noises occur every night. The other boys try to sleep as best as they can. The creepy noises are freaking everyone out. We've heard footsteps of little children playing, and laughing. Other times you can hear crying, and scratching behind our dorm room door. The boys and I have huddled our bunk beds together as far away from the door. We've also barricaded it and placed metal cans around it in case whatever is outside decides to come in. We've told the girls to do the same thing as well. I do not how long I am going to last in this place. I seem to have a connection with all of the creepiness going on. We try to sleep by blocking the sounds out with cotton or something that we can plug into our ears, at least it gives some sort of relief. As the day went by, it was time to go to bed again.I walked towards my dorm room as the lights were getting turned off. 

As usual, I was the last one who got there. All the other boys were already in their bunk beds. I made sure the door was nice and locked and proceeded to my bed which was not that far away from the door. Normally, when I go to sleep, I try to sleep as fast as possible. This time, I couldn't make myself sleep. I kept thinking about a lot of memories that were passing through my mind. I tried to ignore the chill, creepy laughter that had just started outside the dorm-room door. 

When I want to move away from the noise, and chaos, I end up zoning out. As I was laying on the top bunk, my mind drifted away to my memories, I felt the noises lessen, as I started to remember my past. I saw the face of my Great Aunt, smiling, her white-crested teeth showing. The sunshine from the window was casting an aurora on her making her seem like she was glowing. My Great aunt was the best. Ever since my parents had died, I have been with her. I hardly remember my parents, it was like they just vanished, gone. All I knew was that I was put in the care of my Great Aunt. I forgot to mention her name. Her real name is Margareaux Gilbert but she likes to be called Aunt Maggie. I have been with her for 13 years. She took care of me, and taught me everything. The scented aroma of her cooking still makes my mouth water. Aunt Maggie was also a great teacher. She homeschooled me in the classroom that she made as part of her 2 story, humble house in a quiet neighborhood outside of town. It was very peaceful there. I remember the pictures of her husband, Donald Gilbert, a veteran who died while he was fighting in the army. 

I recollected Aunt Maggie's sullen expression when she returned home from a checkup at the hospital one day. She came and wrapped me in a hug as her eyes filled with tears. I asked her what was wrong. She didn't answer. That night, she made a whole table filled with all of my favorite dishes. She played games with me. She hugged me more. I told her that I loved her,( I don't know, it just came out automatically), Aunt Maggie smiled and told me that I will never be alone. I did not get what that meant at that time. Aunt Maggie came in that night to my room. She sat at the bed for a few minutes and just rubbed my forehead. She told me she will miss me. I was confused, but her soft, gentle, hand soothed me to sleep.

 The next day, I woke up extra early to make Aunt Maggie a surprise breakfast. I wanted to show her how much I appreciated everything she's done for me. I fixed the breakfast, and brought it in a tray to Aunt Maggie's room door. I called her name twice, no answer. I opened the door to the bed where I saw the sight that made me drop my tray. Aunt Maggie was lying there, the blood drained from her face, her pupils were red, and there was blood dripping from her mouth. The white sheets of the bed were shaded a dark, bloody, red. Aunt Maggie had veins sticking out of her arms and face, almost as if her body tensed up from the inside. Her once peaceful face, was now a sight of horror. Her eyes stared upward into darkness, and her whole body was a pale, gray, color. I will never forget that sight. I called the police, and soon a whole group of trucks, police cars, and ambulances surrounded the house. I sat on the stairway of the porch watching them take Aunt Maggie's lifeless body away on a stretcher. 

The doctor came up and sat next to me. He asked if me if I noticed anything wrong with my aunt when she returned home that day. I told him that Aunt Maggie did seem depressed that night. I told him everything that happened. He told me the autopsy report that they just conducted. My aunt had a disease (the name was too long to write down) that messed with the internal organs of her body. Her bodily functions just stopped working, and sort of exploded. It caused blood ruptures to spread everywhere,(that explained the red pupils). The doctor told me that the disease had a very painful process as it destroyed the body. The thought left me in more tears. The doctor sadly patted my back as he went away.  

The health officials brought me to the orphanage the next day. Before that, I was in the hospital for tests to make sure that I did not contain the disease. When I was taken to the orphanage, it was the most gloomiest day of my life. I remember that day so vividly. The sun was blocked out by the stormy clouds that were closing in. The officials brought me through the front gates to the grumpy old head mistress. She looked at all my files, and thanked the officials for coming. And from that day on, the orphanage became my new home. 

My mind returned back to reality when I was startled by a loud scream that echoed through my eardrums. All the other boys were awaken by the shriek. We then heard our names being called out by voices behind the dorm room door. I got out of bed and ran to the door. The boys were close behind me. I slowly unlocked the door and opened it. Behind it was.......nothing. Just the chill air of the creepy orphanage that greeted me. I turned to look back at the boys. Their faces had a petrified look filled with fear. I told them to stay put. Surprisingly, they listened. They all returned to their bunk beds...all except for Jimmy. I've mentioned Jimmy before. He was my so-called "acquaintance" who actually talked to me. He knew many secrets about this orphanage. No one knows Jimmy's background, or where he was even born. Everyone's files are kept in the head mistress' main office. 

Anyways, Jimmy asked me where I was going. I told him that I'm going to figure out what's wrong with this place. Why all the creepy children's voices started when I arrived here, there must be some connection. Jimmy stared at me and smiled. He replied, "Well, looks like you'll need some help than." Before I could tell him that this may get him into trouble too, he raced back to his lower bunk in the corner and pulled out a bag from under the bed. He took something that looked like a photograph and stared at it for a few seconds. He then put it back in his bag and slid it under the bed. "Let's Go!" he said silently as he walked past me through the dorm room door. 

To be honest, I've never seen the hallways of the orphanage late at night before. We always stayed in our dorm room, and no one dared to go out at night especially since the creepy noises had started. (If you're wondering, we have a bathroom in our room, so we did not have to go out of the room in case of an emergency). Jimmy and I made our way slowly to the end of the hallway. For some reason, they didn't have security cameras at this end of the corridor, so we were fine for now. The dark, gloomy, corridor had many doors leading to many places. There were barely any lights except for the dim rays that seeped through the windows from the full moon outside. Jimmy spotted a vent system that was just a few inches from the ground. It looked big enough for us to fit through(how convenient). Jimmy broke open the loose hinges that held it up in place, and told me to follow him. He told me that this vent lead to the main offices. I wondered how he knew that, but that thought quickly slipped away when I heard a chill scream echo through the vents. The scream was coming from our right inside the vent. Jimmy told me to stick behind him, and we crawled our way towards the direction of the sound. 

The screaming had stopped when we reached the end of the vent. We peered through the vent openings to see what room we arrived at. It was the head mistress' office. Jimmy tore open the vent to reveal the interior of the room. There was no one inside. It was not very well maintained either. There were papers everywhere, and everything looked disorganized. The ceiling was crumbling, and there was what looked to be dried bits of blood on the wall. It looked like it had been stained with blood for years. I proceeded to examine the files on a desk in the center of the room. I went through all the cabinets while Jimmy stood watch. I finally managed to find a small box inside a cabinet. 

I opened the dusty lid of the old box, and proceeded through its contents. Inside, were many files of the orphans that used to live in this orphanage. It contained their names, a small portrait of them, and their bio data. Most of them were from the 1980s. This orphanage was pretty old. I saw Jimmy slip a piece of paper into his pocket. It was just something I noticed. I didn't really ask him why, because I didn't care. As I read more of the files, I realized that all of this kids died at a young age. The reports said that it was because of a disease from the plague that went through the village. These were the kids that were buried in the mass graveyard next door. 

There were pictures of kids and villagers being treated from the disease. The kids looked messed up. Some were missing hands, others had no eyes. Some kids looked like zombies because their bones showed in places where they had no skin. Many of them had lumps all over their small bodies, and others were missing hair, legs, or teeth. It was horrifying looking at the pictures. These were just orphans. I suddenly spotted one of the nurses helping out in the pictures. The nurse looked familiar...she looked like my aunt Maggie, no, it was my aunt Maggie. I 
recognized the same facial appearance. It was definitely her. No wonder she had the disease. It probably spread to her when she was a nurse helping out at the time. The accounts of the disease said that it could kill a person before they realized that they had it. "Why didn't Aunt Maggie tell me?" I yelled out loud. Jimmy asked me what I was talking about. I told him about the files. "She probably wanted you to not worry," he said. A sense of sadness formed inside me. I suddenly missed Aunt Maggie, and I felt more alone than I already was. 

As I stared at the pictures some more, a question arose in my head. Why were this kids missing body parts? The disease killed you from the inside out. It just messed with your organs. There was something suspicious going on. I started looking around some more, trying to see what I could find. I ended up finding nothing. I was just about to give up when I spotted something in the corner of the room. There was a handhold in the wall. I walked up to it, and felt the hold. There was something in it, almost like a button. I pushed on it. Nothing happened. "Well, I said, "looks like there's--, I didn't finished my sentence because the wall behind suddenly fell, revealing a hidden staircase.

"You got to be kidding me," I said, as I walked up to the once hidden staircase. Jimmy had a pained expression on his face, but at the same time a happy one. Before we went down the staircase, Jimmy made sure that we didn't wake anyone up. Then, we proceeded into the darkness. I had found a flashlight somewhere in the office. It still worked, so I used it to guide ourselves down the ominous staircase that spiraled down into who knows where. As we continued the walk down, the air stank of something rotting. The strong odor made me want to vomit. Weirdly, Jimmy was silent as we walked, and I couldn't tell what expression he had because of the darkness. Finally, the staircase came to an end. It lead into a tunnel that stretched into even more darkness. I kept the flashlight shown ahead as we stepped through the wet puddles of what looked like blood and water mixed together. The stench was even worse here. I couldn't hold it in, I vomited out next to me, spilling the digested liquid of my lunch. "You ok there bud,?" Jimmy asked. He grabbed the flashlight and guided me along. Why did he not feel sick? He wasn't bothered by it at all. 

The tunnel led into a room that was filled with coffins, bloody tables, bones, and bodies of skeletons. "What in hell is this place?" I said, as my voice echoed of the brick walls. There were writings written in a blood that read, HELP US, and ITS THEM, which were written in many areas. I told Jimmy to shine the flashlight at the tables.  I caught a glimpse of his face. It was a sullen, depressed, look almost like he's seen this place before. My attention shifted to the tables. I looked in horror as I saw what were on the tables. They were lined with.... torture devices.

Not only that, but there were needles, and other painful looking devices. There were bloody papers strewn across the floor and the tables. I picked one up. It had a child's face with an x marked over the picture. It was similar to the files of the orphans back in the office. I read the papers thoroughly. I realized what was going on in here. When the villagers were living in this area, there was a plague that went over that ended up killing many  adults. It was the same disease that my aunt had which was the cause of the deaths. The children weren't affected, so they built this orphanage to keep them there. However, there was something horrible going on the orphanage that no one knew about. The children were secretly being abused sexually, and also experimented on. Some of them were little kids, others were older. Almost all of them were tortured, here in this chamber, to death. That explains why there were torture devices. Very little survived, and of the orphans that made it out, they were treated by the nurses that remained here. That also explains the photo of my aunt with these tortured children. The people who ran this abuse operation targeted the nurses and....killed them. The reason why they weren't caught, was because everyone assumed that the nurses died from the disease that was spread from the plague.

 Somehow my aunt remained hidden from her pursuers for all these years. I sat in a shocked silence, as the truth seeped into me. I cried in bitter resentment towards the people who had done these things to the innocent children, and no one couldn't do anything about it. I heard something drop behind me. The flashlight that was supposed to be in Jimmy's hand rolled over to a side of the wall of the room. The light illuminated a name that was written in blood. The name sent shockwaves down my spine. It was the name of our head mistress. 

Under the name, it said, IT WAS HER FAULT. I suddenly heard something call out to me from the darkness. The room became filled with many loud voices of children echoing out to me. There was no sign of Jimmy either. The voices whispered thank you all around me. It kept echoing until all was silent. Something inside me told me to get out of here. I had to put an end to this. My heart raced as I ran towards the staircase. I didn't know where Jimmy was, but I knew what I had to do....

24 HOURS LATER...............................

The children of the orphanage stood together and watched as the cops handcuffed our head mistress and took her way in the police car. It turns out that she had known all about Fallen Creek's secret. Her father was the head of the organization to abuse and experiment on these children for a private company. They started this orphanage to make sure no one was suspicious. The plague benefited their plan as well. I was still having trouble processing all this information. Maybe I was fated to help find the mystery behind this orphanage. I surveyed the construction workers who entered our orphanage. They were excavating the torture chamber for more skeletons, and evidence. There were also new plans being made to refurnish the interior and exterior of the new orphanage to actually benefit the children. The children will have a proper home, where they are free to play, live, and grow without any difficulties. We will also get new security, because the old ones were fired for not keeping proper watch on the orphanage. They just went to the security shed outside the orphanage to drink, and sleep. There will also be a separate room in the orphanage for the staff, and security to stay in. How did I know all of this? Well, I overhead the engineers  talking about it. 

Anyway, I decided to go take a last look at my dorm room because we were going leave. The police are escorting all the children of the orphanage to a hospital wing just outside of town, while the orphanage was being constructed on. As I was walking past the pictures of the orphans on the wall, I noticed a familiar face in one of the pictures. There was a boy standing in the crowd of some orphans. As I peered closely, I realized that it was Jimmy. The date was from the 1900s. I stared in awe as I figured out that Jimmy was one of the orphans that had died. Another thought also came into my head. What if the ghosts of these children were helping me out? What if they wanted me to solve this mystery once and for all? Maybe that's why they were yelling and screaming because they wanted me to find them, to free them from their misery. I ran to my dorm room to find a piece of paper on Jimmy's bed. I slowly picked up the piece of paper that read: Thank You, You freed all of us, and for that we are grateful. The horrors that happened here are a reminder of our numbered lives. It is part of the pain we suffered. You will not be forgotten-Jimmy. 

That's why Jimmy knew all the secrets of this place, I thought, as I made my way to the police escorts outside. The children were being filed in to big police trucks. As I got in, I asked the other boys if they remembered Jimmy, but all of them denied me. They said that they never even heard of him before. The policeman started the truck, and followed the other trucks out past the gates of the orphanage. I stared at the letter written by Jimmy, and I took one last look at the gates of FALLEN CREEK ORPHANAGE. To my amaze, standing at the gate was Jimmy, waving goodbye to me as we drove away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] Mystery Of Fallen Creek Orphanage Part 2, Ending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are the best discoverer the world has ever seen. Your intelligence helped you discover creatures that man presumed fake. One day, you receive news of an unknown creature located in a small unheard-of island. You decide to head there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, I would have been freaking the heck out if I saw that dude. Glad you were safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
