<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7382</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the crashes that happened throughout Tamriel can now be found in MOL and HRC. vMOL is literally impossible on Xbox now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that's hilarious. So are you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooooo you must embrace the massage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 03:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They updated the craglorn trials so they reset all leaderboards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the update last Tuesday the overall leaderboards reset, the weeklies didn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got my beautiful kitten from Fulton AS a month ago! She's incredible. If you're on the fence about a companion, don't be! Get one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL I knew you were better than that. Was shaking my head like wth is this guy thinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare those numbers to say- 3 aether 2 kena 5 tbs with VMA front Aether destro back and you'll find that 5 aether on a dps isn't all that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops yeah you are correct. There's a flat bonus that scales depending on item quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I believe it's 8%. You'd only want 3 PC for the minor slayer and crit buff. The 5pc is more geared towards a support role in trials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 PC aether should be on a healer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea of Celestial Slayer- achieved after completing all craglorn trials on HM. Saw someone post that idea last time this thread popped up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 04:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I raise my glass to you. You've said it better than I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uuh, not entirely. You spend say 15 bucks for a month, get 1500 crowns and access to dlcs, craft bag, xp gains, gold gains. So you're getting more than 15$ worth of product. You can't use crowns to buy another month but if you amass enough crowns you can outright buy the DLCs. The craft bag is exceptional by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my stam sorc is dot heavy in PVP. Dual axes, hurricane, blade clock, tendon. Slashes, bloodthirst, poison inject, and arrow barrage, flawless DB, steel tornado. It's awesome.... Catch a ton of people off guard by the rolling dot ticks. In 1vx situations it performs quite well with barrage, hurri and steel tornado. It's inherently tanky as you have major resistances up always, minors too with bound arms, and bloodthirst keeping your health topped off. 
  
VMA axes are critical for the build to really shine.
  
5 hundings impen, 5 VO, 2 VMA. Could run this with agility/endurance and skoria instead of VO but the speed and sustain from vicious in Zerg fights is pretty exceptional  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internet diet high in fiber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VMOL
...
That's pretty much it at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah not really, I just hunt skyshards. I do feel gimped on fighters guild leveling which is why I recommend focusing on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orsinium public delves is the quickest, but you'll miss out on fighters guild xp. I like to find alliance based grind spots online til about lvl 15-20ish, focusing on undead kills. Then head over to orsinium public dungeons. This is great for alt characters, since you'll be low on skill points. Orsinium spots are also great for champ point grinding.
  
Also keep in mind there is a huge bonus on the activity finder once a day, get a group of four THEN start queue. And do all of the normal/vet dungeons for skill points and undaunted xp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 19:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not do both? Level up a redguard or khajiit stam dk. It's as easy as making a full set of training gear (or have someone do it) and grinding for a few hours. Now you have 2 toons! Love variety. Quickest I've ground one up was ~6hrs. Helps to use exp bonuses like scrolls, ambrosias, esoplus, grind with 1 other person, and get married.
  
Having the right race for what you're building is like setting up a good foundation for your home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you can't really heal your way through VMA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha just 2 manned this yesterday. No reason for anyone to be picky about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know for sure VO and major expedition stack currently on console. It's a lot of fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi it's me your brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it was attached to yo rod muthalicka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry cat got my lickitung </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so amped up right meow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 22:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is true- it seems OP is running a pvp set. Don't use TBS in pvp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 22:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alaviri dragon guard set- found in hel ra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On console- older trials drop it. Got a few dragon impen yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's my main source of income right meow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are all fairly easy once you get the hang of it. With that being said it feels like stamsorc is prime. Stamdk and stam NB are comparable in my opinion. Haven't tried stamplar yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blessed thistle, dragon thorn, water hyacinth/wormwood. That's the drink right thurr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 00:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete all you quests. You can have one. Go into audio settings turn down pretty much everything. Go into interface and turn down all quest indicators. 
  
When you're ready, grab the mael quest, walk up to the portal, and restart your game. 
  
This has brought me some luck, although it may seem more superstitious. Idk how well this works on PC, but on Xbox it helps... A little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 04:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this. Isn't that what the achievement is called anyways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I totally believe you... /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every class has access to evasion... So it's balanced. Get good kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [question] Having trouble inputting month/date information with Xbox menu cursor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As title says I'm having trouble with the menu cursor. The problem is when I have to input month/date info via scrolling through numbers and years...it won't scroll whatsoever, stays at the top numbers (ex: 01,02,03...and: 16,17,18 for year) 
  
Any suggestions? I'm trying to buy something this should be way easier, amirite?
  
Apologies if I am in wrong subreddit, or going about this in a weird way. Google/Bing weren't coming up with anything pertinent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharpened is very op, especially right now. Crit chance is fairly easy to raise up, armor pen isn't easy to raise without weapons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 15:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tested out non VMA weps on my stamblade in a bloodspawn test the other night. Comparable numbers at 35k/45secs. 2 things to consider- BS is a short fight, VMA would have pulled thru by a larger margin had the fight been longer. Stamblade also has surprise attack, other classes have to rely on flurry and wep dots to stay competitive. Just food for thought! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JFC I never said vMOL. I said 'healing springs' which apparently is your trigger. Chill the fuck out. I was in vMOL last night and understand what you're saying, but at this point I feel like you just want to argue based on all these wild assumptions of yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what, never mind. I'm sorry I aggravated you. You pissed me off with your elitist attitude and general demeanor. You're an asshole, but there are many assholes out there. We both play eso and for that, I think you're pretty cool. As a final farewell- fuck you.  
  
Best,
A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see that, wanna post a link? I get the vibe that you're full of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I said was healing springs. There are many cases where, if you want to live, you need to be in healing springs. You took that and ran with it ridiculously far. And you were being a dick about it. Bow/bow just doesn't work. Read through the comments throughout your thread and that illustrates why this is the case. Like you said, you need to be x far away for bow to be on par with wrecking blow. That's outside of healing springs, you're a liability in most end game trial content for that reason. You're a liability because your dps is shit. You're also toxic to be around so fuck it you're a liability in that regard. Thank you, good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm top 100 all time VMA. I've completed vSO on 3 toons. I have a 42 sec bloodspawn time. I know my shit and you have no room to assume otherwise. In a not-so-polite-way-of-saying, fuck you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hel ra citadel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two completely different games...right? Doesn't change the fact that you will either die since you're not getting healed across the room all by yourself, or you wouldn't be in the group to begin with since you're a bow main in this situation, and no one wants that. 
  
And I really appreciate you starting this convo with all this shade you're throwing at me for no reason. You must not have very many friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears you're not well versed in this game if you think bow dps is viable in pve. Have fun at the back of the room spamming lethal and dying like a scrub. 

Nice assumption about normal trials, dickface.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find it by googling - 'salvation set eso' 
  
Crazy how powerful search engines are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Healing springs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if quick cloak works on them tbh. It shouuuulllllddddd, but it doesn't feel like it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 01:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the flavor that's caked on the griddle. Source: I sit at the bar a lot and watch it cake on after I order a Texas phillycheesteak  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 16:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows what you're talking about and if they did they really shouldn't post about it online I reckon. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 16:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah get all divines, the thief, and all medium </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 02:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so cool. I'm getting the heebus-jeebus just thinking about how I stood at that same spot when I was a wee-lad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hircines veneer? I think it is. Also comes in jewlery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 01:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So take away their signs, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gratitudes intensifies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be salty too if you ran sanctum 80 times and only have 1 divines vicious ophidian drop, and 15-20 prosperous or training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you suck at math. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you don't have to run 2h with a stam NB- you have surprise attack and ambush. The only thing missing is rally. What you get is more raw damage, and another weap slot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I truly enjoy it. That is, until RNG kills me. See: mushroom flowers, randomly synced trash adds. RNG based environments that 1 shot are so fucking frustrating. And the auto DC after spiral shadows is obnoxious on xbone. How much longer do we have to deal with that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 17:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I felt my balls drop a little lower and some new sprouts on my chest. 'Twas a good day' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think alcast has some insight into the TD and TBS convo- IIRC he had similar conclusions to yours, but again no formal testing. I could see it being comparable/marginally better than TBS in solo with the right rotations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't had any viscous O drops since my luck is shit but 3 agility, 5 tbs, mael dagger precise and axe sharp, I swap in either Mephala or bloodspawn occasionally. (This is for maelstrom). Bars- DW: venom claw, bloodthirst, bloodcraze, igneous, vigor, flawless DB. Bow: rearming, poison inject, endless hail, flappy wings, noxious breath, standard. My high score on VMA is 480k. Just got thru vSO last week also. Not sure how else I can optimize my rotations- should I be light/heavy weaving thru literally everything? 
  
Stamblade is essentially the same setup, with killers blade, siphoning, and relentless in place of the dk skills. Same gear and weaps.  Seem to have more survivability issues with him though, as I have to eat all the damage rather than reflect/shield it. Any suggestions on staying alive better with him? Blur/shuffle? Or just gitgud and roll dodge more/defense harder? 
  
I'm gonna get on pretty soon if you wanna halp via chat. My GT is fallingbuckets 
  
Appreciate you taking time man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice write up. You on pc?

Edit- just saw camel toe write you're on Xbox. Drivebyforty right? Seen you on the leaderboards a bunch. I wanna get with you to amp up my stam dk and stam NB just that much more. Right now I'm at 47 secs bloodspawn on both. Would you be so kind to talk in game? Teach me your ways sensei </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete girlfriend, hit the lawyer, welp Jim. Got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 01:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a downvote button for...this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fishing is a distraction. Video games, a distraction. Reddit? No bash homie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only staff ability you'd use is ele blockade/wall of elements. Sap tanks are awesome man! Dark elf is a great choice for that as they have both max mag and max stam bonuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong spot sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, dark elf puts out more dps with the amount of fire damage you'd be using on a magblade. The max magicka is not far off either. Nightblades don't care about recovery. I realize you're aiming for pvp, in which case it would be different, however, dark elf magblade is good shit for min/maxing in pve. Weaving and ele blockade, shooting star... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, have the off tank bring the lamia to the blue totem and then kill lamia. Ignore green totems and dps Cora as soon as it's out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Venom or bullseye by Alcast on YouTube  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [discussion] stamsorc vs. stamplar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planning my next stam char. The sorc would be a khajiit and the stamplar probably redguard. What would you all recommend and why? I have all the endgame gear already (just not viscous ophidian jewelry.) already have a stamdk and stamblade. Only have 1 char slot left if I don't delete a toon. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
