<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9619</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is 7.9 cents a round before shipping good on this 22 ammo?  
  
Also oos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found Netflix subtitles to be a bad size. I pick small and they're tiny, I pick medium and they're way too big. Have no idea how they'd fit large ones on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of states have water rights with other states. I don't see resources really being an issue. Lots of new laws will need to be put into place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Euro was supposed to replace the dollar, and it made sense and it was about to, then the whole world lost all of it's money because of rich assholes bankrupting the world and scamming everyone. It kept the dollar afloat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will there be reporting and deleting of literally fake news like the Brazil Purge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's filming the drunk guy before there's an issue and before he crawled under the fence in focus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big proponent of city states. I think most of the largest cities should become their own states. It would reduce gerrymandering and increase reflectivity of preferences in the House and Senate. I'm also for increasing the number of Representatives to an unwieldy number so they have to form coalitions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn man. I didn't know they looked down on soldiers like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ignored the silicon valley people wanting to break away from the union in your comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just stating the facts. You can google it if you want. I have no preference what those states do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People hate reality.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Norcal has wanted to merge with southern Oregon for a while. Make the state of Jefferson I believe. And now silicon valley wants California to leave the union. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I play civ rev </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine just came yesterday, shoved the boxes in the ammo cans I bought with it and I'll never use it cause regular price was like $31 a box and I got it for $17.75 a box.  
  
Maybe if I get my long range gun I'll pull it out. I too am now waiting for .308 ammo to be less than $17.75 a box for decent stuff after that deal. Until then I only have some surplus 7.62 from the 70s and Austria to shoot. Definitely had two misfires so far with that surplus ammo lol. I just want some decent $15 a box .308 and $15 a box FN 5.7 and I'll be happy. Free or cheap shipping and I'd be ecstatic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think most are jerks when it comes to the fees. My LGS is cool and doesn't charge extra. But he was talking about buying it new and I know when I look at a lot of places websites it's more than $10 for the long gun fee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After shipping and FFL fees it would be higher, like what $550? This guy bought the gun locally it seems and now the price has dropped out on him. It sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  background check and transfer fee with paper work
  
Yes. This was a complete thought. There's paper work which includes background check and transfer fee. There's what, 3 papers you fill out for handguns and two for long guns? I get that the fees are different, usually 10-25 buck difference. But most places I see advertised say "long gun transfer fee: $30" or the like. In MD. So maybe the vernacular is wrong, but he's going to be charged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that seems weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What subs auto ban you when you participate in other subs, do the bans make sense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get any when it was like 80cents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They always seem so dang expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much in English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uploaded on Aug 31, 2006 From a norwegian TV show called Uti Vr Hage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it's an 8mm Mauser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man. On r/gunsforsale a guy is selling a savage I believe for like $375. He offered to sell it to me with the scope for $600 shipped. It's a nice set up for the price.   
  
Edit: http://reddit.com/r/Gunsforsale/comments/5spvlx/wts_savage_hog_hunter_338_win_mag_tx/  
  
There's also a lot of 308 bolt actions on sale right now as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a good price for Mauser ammo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I don't see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't find anyone to trade for those swivel bases I could use them for my grandfathers 22. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gold stars at the other end are the remembrance part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current wait time is as long as the background check takes. So normally 10-20 min roughly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sen. James Brochin (DEM) or call them at: (410) 841-3648  
Sen. Robert Cassilly (REP) or call them at: (410) 841-3158  
Sen. Michael J. Hough (REP) or call them at: (410) 841-3704  
Sen. Delores G. Kelley (DEM) or call them at: (301) 858-3606  
Sen. Susan C. Lee (DEM) or call them at: (410) 841-3124  
Sen. C. Anthony Muse (DEM) or call them at: (410) 841-3092  
Sen. H. Wayne Norman (REP) or call them at: (410) 841-3603  
Sen. Victor R. Ramirez (DEM) or call them at: (410) 841-3745  
Sen. Justin D. Ready (REP) or call them at: (410) 841-3683  
Sen. William C. Smith (DEM) or call them at: (410) 841-3634  
Sen. Robert A. Zirkin (DEM) or call them at: (410) 841-3131  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purchasing a long gun from an FFL always resulted in a background check and transfer fee with paper work. No changes to that law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://mgaleg.maryland.gov/2017RS/bills/sb/sb0948F.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude that's awesome. So what do you get out of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I've only seen the federal stuff at 17.99. I got the FN stuff at 15.99 before. I'm waiting for that deal again with some free shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I do each one manually. I should download a plugin or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got a lot of loaded questions. The first one, yes I think that everyone interested in continuing a career in politics beyond 4 years with Trump has very much snubbed him. I mean fuck, the GOP in the house and senate still distance themselves from him. She also wasn't the biggest donor. And ever collectively from her family as far as I saw was not the biggest donor and they've been doing it since the 80s. Sanders asked about it, and I honestly think that her family had made a ton with political influence and I haven't heard from anyone else saying they were considered or turned it down. So until some more qualified people show up in a leaked email I'd bet Betsy contacted Donald and volunteered. And it's Trump so he was probably happy to have one less decision to make about the government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can move. Literally move in mass to areas and take over. https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Free_State_Project they did it. Got some guy elected. Got switch blades legalized. Lol. But you get the idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll skip down to the appointments. Here we have a twofold problem. One, Trump dissed most politicians and alienated tons more. Two, Trump only knows a few people that would even work for the government.  
  
So with problem one he's got no one to pick from. And let's say he did, who do you normally get to run the DoE, someone that's run a large education department like in LA or NY or someone that ran a state one or has some experience doing so. He blew those out of the water. DeVos has private school experience. Mostly raising funds I believe but I think there were other charter things she did on state and city levels. Well if you're a fan of charter schools, scaring public schools to drop unions, or liked the documentary Waiting for Superman, then she might be the right person to be there.  
  
As for Pai he's doing exactly what Republicans want and while probably the most qualified person Trump could pick from was a shitty choice for those that advocate against Comcast and throttling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An honest conversation with some autistic people and a father of a young autistic kid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to check it out. Any limit to the number of accounts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you both be logged on and use it? I thought it was some thing where you had to log on to the other account and you couldn't both play at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you both be logged on and use it? I thought it was some thing where you had to log on to the other account and you couldn't both play at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you both be logged on and use it? I thought it was some thing where you had to log on to the other account and you couldn't both play at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you both be logged on and use it? I thought it was some thing where you had to log on to the other account and you couldn't both play at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you both be logged on and use it? I thought it was some thing where you had to log on to the other account and you couldn't both play at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you both be logged on and use it? I thought it was some thing where you had to log on to the other account and you couldn't both play at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to check it out. Any limit to the number of accounts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the $110 and get cash back. It's sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do that on Xbox? I thought that feature didn't really work right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only equality part I saw was that the supreme court "OK'd" gay marriage, and somehow Obama took credit for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From all these comments it sounds like it would be easy to rule the roads of Sweden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Costco loves you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat. I can't wait to move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, and no instant transfers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MD or Cali? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck selling it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You posted before you bought, rookie mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it break the ToS on sites like Facebook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visitors to the U.S. may have to hand over social media passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visitors to the U.S. may have to hand over social media passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visitors to the U.S. may have to hand over social media passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OOS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what needs to be the top post, very informative. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably better consumer protection laws in those states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 year as well. I don't know any cops that got more than a 2 year degree needed to become a cop if required. And they did it at community colleges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, with how people have been putting other sale items from the same site in posts it I thought it was another item on sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lol, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No proof needed. I know we all bought some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you owned a PC with a DVD drive you might be able to claim $10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give me me a link to the 308.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.guns.com/review/gun-review-canik-tp9sa-faces-off-with-canik-tp9sf/ Looks like some don't have it. They mention is isn't on SF models in this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   insecure frat boys

I don't know any cops that went to a 4 year university with Fraternities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some different ones I got from amazon, came with a 8", 7" and 6" plate. That six inch over 100 yards away is pretty small. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For $8 more you can get ones with hanging holes. Tactical Scorpion Gear TSG-GG44 AR500 Set Of Four 4" x 3/8" Steel Shooting Target Gong Laser Cut https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0112MU69E/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_api_1yBMybZDT1H9B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll have that half hut repaired by dinner time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The map on the wikipedia makes it seem like they're pretty Canadian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.slickguns.com/category/rifles?caliber=3 show_expired=1 Lots of places. They sometimes sell out quick. And of course it depends on what you're getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Devine** is the answer by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe without the Heavy Barrel designation you won't be able to buy it in MD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   if you end an equal number of possessions with an unequal number of points

In OPs post at the top it would seem so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that one boy dumped her after he heard she went on a hike with another boy. I wonder if really he heard rumors they fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does life their compare to a city like new York at the time for middle class and lower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cursory internet search puts it around a 1/3 I'd owned by aristocracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.popularmechanics.com/military/weapons/news/amp19555/why-isis-is-building-mad-max-truck-bombs/ Isis is using captured armored vehicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw no bump in there road as I approached. Two bumps. Nah I won't look in my rearview mirror to see what I hit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just being racist for not wondering if the poster meant in "their country" since people from countries have different cultures but the same race is possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was Obama's purpose and it made it worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't look like the same one in the link below.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone wrap up the reasons these aren't worth it? I think I heard the springs suck so in this short version unsafe. Bad ccw. Etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's federal. This is FNH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replied to so many of my comments because you were so butt hurt I don't even know which we're talking about anymore. I know I'm right and you're wrong. So I'll leave it at that. This message will repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replied to so many of my comments because you were so butt hurt I don't even know which we're talking about anymore. I know I'm right and you're wrong. So I'll leave it at that. This message will repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only for 5 months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think it cost over half a trillion dollars to maintain several ships? A quarter + trillion is more than enough to maintain our current readiness standard. We need to shut down tons of unneeded military builds like tanks and carriers and stop done operations. Instead that same money or only 100 billion could be used to easily fund healthcare in America or update internet or build better schools or infrastructure providing way more jobs and better future all over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billion? Exaggerate much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got some data? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even think about you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not laughing though so your retort makes no sense. It did repeat. Several times in this thread. Just not to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/next/body/hatred/ the DOJ also funds these groups. Hopefully Trump's team isn't reading this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what they're doing. They're changing the organization's name and focus to be more specific. Whether or not that refocusing makes sense is another issue. But they aren't reclassifying white radicals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure did in the majority opinion. That was copied and pasted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't find more current details of political leanings and income online. I found random blood her and there. Also the only other sources I've found have shown independents continue to increase. So it would still hold independents are paying the most taxes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Additional funding they've applied for though might be. I don't know they're budget though. So it could have been an expansion on what they were doing is that they applied for. I'm sure we could look into it and contact them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the fool doesn't laugh at himself. So it makes sense you think I'm hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only want to slash funding on stuff the Democrats want. If they were serious they would cut the defense budget in fucking half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not it isn't. http://www.cnbc.com/2016/06/23/trump-sanders-under-microscope-as-secret-service-costs-skyrocket-this-election.html We spend tons on protection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It said limiting the ability to spend money is unconstitutional because it limits the ability of its members to associate effectively and to speak on political issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's different. Dubbing over it all is fine. If you use it in it's entirety then you are only supposed to use the minimum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proved you wrong again and you just cry making stuff up.  
  
I know I'm right and you're wrong. So I'll leave it at that. This message will repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replied to so many of my comments because you were so butt hurt I don't even know which we're talking about anymore. I know I'm right and you're wrong. So I'll leave it at that. This message will repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replied to so many of my comments because you were so butt hurt I don't even know which we're talking about anymore. I know I'm right and you're wrong. So I'll leave it at that. This message will repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replied to so many of my comments because you were so butt hurt I don't even know which we're talking about anymore. I know I'm right and you're wrong. So I'll leave it at that. This message will repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://9to5mac.com/2011/10/21/jobs-original-vision-for-the-iphone-no-third-party-native-apps/ Steve Jobs pushed for these when the iPhone first came out. I remember people not liking the idea, but man that was almost 10 years ago now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Integrating Progressive Web Apps deeply into Android </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["Huge" issue.](https://m.popkey.co/1c786e/kvKXd.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not enough info there, led me to google more - http://www.adweek.com/digital/fair-use-youtube/ looks like I can add commentary over it and it's ok to use! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5rtohe/former_norway_pm_held_at_washington_airport_over/dda3z65/ That guy makes it seem it's correct to blame Obama though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did he lose for going outside the line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when does it? After it's aired? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I do commentation over it, humorous stuff hopefully, would that fall into some fair use parody thing that would allow me to do this?  Really I want to do it with movies.  
  
Edit: http://www.adweek.com/digital/fair-use-youtube/ looks like it is fair use to do what I am saying. And it would be a parody. Sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Amazing that there are this many people who can't think for themselves

You mean actors hired to read lines to you verbatim? Look at news show hosts, they aren't journalists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't misread, I can't read everything for you or interpret it to your understanding. We've shown over and over that you think what's right is different than what that law says. I can't help it that you think you're so smart yet every time I google Idaho ID laws and cars nothing agrees with you. Terry is the only thing that comes up to counter it, and until someone goes to court over this and a judge says it's unconstitutional it's the law. Sorry mon ami. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.people-press.org/2009/05/21/section-1-party-affiliation-and-composition/  Party by income towards the bottom.
  
Actually it's most likely that Dems don't pay taxes since a big chunk are poor. Independents are high in most tax paying brackets and probably pay the most in income taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it did. About laws being the law until they're overturned. I don't know why you're so combative. You're wrong. It's ok man. It's not the end of your life. You can go out, get arrested for an unconstitutional law and fight it. I don't have the time or money. I agree the law is bogus and sucks, but for now it's the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess you're counting comments that I'm not a part of. I don't care that you commented to something else. Weirdo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You haven't shown me a single thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so I decided to do some actual research since salon is a pretty crap news source.  They're just rewriting [this article from Reuters with a huge lean](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-extremists-program-exclusiv-idUSKBN15G5VO).  
  
Personally I've never heard of the Department of Homeland Security's program Countering Violent Extremism. I am pretty positive most people commenting here haven't either. So let's take a look.  
  
From the Reuters' article:
The program, "Countering Violent Extremism," or CVE, would be changed to "Countering Islamic Extremism" or "Countering Radical Islamic Extremism," the sources said, and would no longer target groups such as white supremacists who have also carried out bombings and shootings in the United States.  
  
Oh shit, is there some other group that does this, sure the FBI and NSA and others do. So what does this program do then?  
  
Reuters:
...the CVE program, which focuses on U.S. residents and is separate from a military effort to fight extremism online, has been criticized even by some supporters as ineffective.  
  
In 2016, Congress appropriated $10 million in grants for CVE efforts and DHS awarded the first round of grants on Jan. 13, a week before Trump was inaugurated.  
  
Oh, so they do grants, I mean 10 million isn't a ton, but ok. Let's go to the [CVE website (yea they have one!)](https://www.dhs.gov/countering-violent-extremism)  
  
DHS/CVE website:
These new grants will provide state, local and tribal partners and community groupsreligious groups, mental health and social service providers, educators and other NGOswith the ability to build prevention programs that address the root causes of violent extremism and deter individuals who may already be radicalizing to violence.  
  
In the Reuters article they mention groups like Life After Hate for ex neo nazis as recipients of these funds.  
  
So here are the CVE's main lines of effort:  
  
**Community Engagement.** OCP works with the Office for Civil Rights and Civil Liberties to facilitate community engagements to build awareness and promote dialogue with community partners, which includes engagements with DHS senior leadership;  
  
**Field Support Expansion and Training.** OCP supports DHS field staff across the country to develop and strengthen local partnerships and to provide training opportunities;  
  
**Grant Support.** OCP is working closely with FEMA to issue a notice of funding opportunity for community-based programs this summer;  
  
**Philanthropic Engagement.** OCP works with the philanthropic community to maximize support for local communities, and encourage long-term partnerships;  
  
**Tech Sector Engagement.*** OCP engages the tech sector to identify and amplify credible voices online and promote counter-narratives against violent extremist messaging.  
  
[Here is a pdf from the CVE about their strategy.](https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/16_1028_S1_CVE_strategy.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration says she will move from New York to Washington at the end of son Barrons current school year, but **rumors swirled** this week that she might stay in New York indefinitely.  
  
So rumors are more than enough to count as news on r/Politics now? We knew she was staying for the kids school, and people seemed to get over it. Now this? Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well SCOTUS did say money was speech and taxes are government infringing on your freedom of speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It said requiring his ID and registration didn't go against Terry or anything else. I don't know what you're trying to prove, but clearly you're wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It continued until it was challenged as unconstitutional. Courts are slow. That's why it took time. It doesn't mean it wasn't unconstitutional from day one.

That's exactly what I said, you've been arguing against this forever. Good God. Thankfully you finally came to understand what I've been saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it does, I guess you didn't read it. It was all about sitting in a car that couldn't even move. NEXT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no more downvoted than you, brought you sources again to another comment but you ignore it. Mwa, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Bad_Cop_No_Donut/comments/5rmati/cops_refuse_to_show_id_question_man_for_using/ddacmwp/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's exactly how I said it works. It was law and it was practiced until it went to court again. Thanks again for proving my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Section III A and B](http://www.leagle.com/decision/2001115334P3d1119_11142/STATE%20v.%20MARTINEZ) I'll wait for BS reason why this doesn't hold up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then explain how stop and frisk worked and was allowed to continue for so long? And how even the first ruling wasn't saying the law was unconstitutional. That's how these things work, just because you don't like it or don't agree with it doesn't make you right. It must be hard to see past your own shit when the mountain of it is so high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get angry that you think what you feel is correct is the same as being correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, yea that's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does as they allow it when approaching someone in a vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that you make up stuff hoping it's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you keep talking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're making a cool out of yourself.

I'm glad you think I'm cool, but I won't stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  diwnvotes.

I thought you were about to say being destroyed by dimwits and I would have agreed.  
  
You keep bringing up the same argument about Terry, I debunked it as that's how new fucking laws work to over-ride higher court rulings they don't like. Fuck it's like you have no idea how this shit works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you aren't legally compelled to provide ID
But he is.
https://www.reddit.com/r/Bad_Cop_No_Donut/comments/5rmati/cops_refuse_to_show_id_question_man_for_using/dd8v7d8/
In State v. Martinez the court referenced State v. Ellenbecker which states: "Section 343.18(1), Stats., implicitly recognizes this public interest by giving a law enforcement officer the authority to require a driver of a motor vehicle to display his or her license on demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was right, you just don't like the answer. I can't help that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moot in which way? Open for debate or closed? Because depending it can mean either. Also why do you like stalking me so much on reddit? Are you in love with me for defying your very nature as a troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you be surprised that I don't feel like wasting my time over and over again just to get responses like, "I don't think so, prove yourself" After I do multiple times. It's morons in this sub that make it just as bad as the pro cop ones on the other side. Have a great weekend, I hope you don't get pulled over and spout your incorrect shit and get your window busted in. I'm sure over on AmIBeingDetained will love to watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've pointed out before I did, you just don't like the answer. I can't make you accept facts, that's not my job. Have a great weekend again stalker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I proved it, you just kept saying, "Nope I don't like that answer here's an older case and I don't understand how law works or how laws written later in narrower scopes or making up new rules to circumvent old rules are done to purposefully get around higher court rulings." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did multiple times to you, I'm sorry you can't accept you're wrong. You can't see past yourself, it's not your fault though. You've just become a part of the internet mentality. Once again, have a great weekend, buddy! Stay safe out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked through this convo of the thread, you're losing. So ;) and have a great weekend, buddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ransomware completely shuts down Ohio town government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn, I forgot how ugly that gun was. I was really hoping it was a hunting knife, I might have bought it then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bass Pro here in MD would not price match on the ammo or even come down at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engineering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I didn't know this had become the new normal price. I tried ordering ten boxes last night. No free shipping. So I might as well go see if they have it Bass Pro/Outdoor and see if they'll honor a price match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UTA materials scientist invents breath monitor to detect flu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UTA materials scientist invents breath monitor to detect flu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nvidia stops promotional game resales by tying codes to hardware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have stopped responding to them when I realized they weren't after proof, that's why I asked them to prove me wrong, because they can't prove themselves right either. Same thing, they just can't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed the one that said they have the authority to require ID, insurance and registration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to Order Dodd-Frank Review, Halt Obama Fiduciary Rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? They have no proof and take their own bullshit without proof to mean more than the evidence I've tossed all over this thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm too lazy to look online right now. So it's the accurate way to say you still can't prove yourself right lol. Come on. It shouldn't be that hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People complaining about the Tea Party or Republican politicians lump them all together with no real "good ones". There's no ok right. You basically have to clarify your position perfectly. If you just say you're a social Democrat or some form they're less likely to think you're a sjw at first. But the media and stuff in this polarized place we are doesn't care about middle of the road or moderate anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I tried it. I grabbed the handle with my right hand. I didn't have to look in my mirror but when the cyclist hit my door I was safely on the outside of the door protected from the cyclist. I guess it works pretty well to avoid being hit by cyclists. But he scratched the inside of my door and his face left an imprint on the inside of the window :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone uses that excuse for everything. Not all cops are bad, not all Muslims are terrorists, not all violent Trump protestors are rioters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seeing 4 years ago. Weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No free shipping with ten boxes this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already did a few times throughout this thread. I can't help it that people don't like the answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood completely. Seems you're still unable to defend your position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just in place some rules about the tournament instead? Like making them take the rays with them or limiting them to one a person or boat? Make them try harder for the biggest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not about this son! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other one does in one of my other posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In one of my other comments and another guys around her that decision cited another one that said the driver must present ID as the cop has the authority to require I think was the language. Since these laws were after Terry and haven't been pushed to a higher court dismissing them they are legal. States do this shady shit all the time.  Slight language changes that make it now not illegal per a ruling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another case cited in that one says a cop has authority to require ID insurance and registration when a person is in a car. So they combine the two to equal their authority. Until it goes to the supreme Court and a non Scalia supercop powers allowed justice is elected that would hold up. Same with them getting people at dui checkpoints despite scotus admiting it was unconstitutional but only slightly annoying for the innocent or whatever bullshit they logic leaped to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes say different! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've said nothing in this convo to lead me to trust you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Idaho would probably new a state it holds up in. You're a sore loser. It's ok though. Most people on the internet are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it seems then that the Idaho law will stand for now then. Thanks for backing me up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the guy you were talking to. You never asked for state results so...you better start googling or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't be for a while. Just got home from work. Guess you can't prove me wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's accurate. Sad you down voted my comments. Good luck in life little man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their facts are about absolute numbers of deaths with guns. Circumstances and such don't matter to them. Basically you have to think you aren't trying to convince them, but you're trying to convince the normal people that make up most of the voting population, give them facts and show the other side is dumb and ignorant and you stand a better chance.  
  
This election cycle the democrats instead tried to play in the crazy court with Republicans (really Tea Party people) and Trump et al out crazied them. The few facts that popped up were what swung the election for a lot of people. TPP, Hillary as a crony, shitting on Bernie by the DNC, Trump being lied about in the media constantly. Normal people say the 5 facts there were and went with them. Even at the top of this article, the Dems in Wichita calling everyone else "extremists". Normal people are like, "Whaa? Owning a gun in Kansas and taking it with you is extreme? But old farmer jones always has the 1911 and he's awesome!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What rights do you have on someone else's private property? Not a lot. In city limits on publically accessible land as well, you don't have much to stand on. Cops can already put GPS devices on a car in a parking lot or driveway without a warrant.  
  
The whole community policing thing and scotus allowing DUI checkpoints and cops very often approaching cars in parking lots puts what you think is the law in a dark corner and pees on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got to stay ahead of them, you can't let them call you dumb for making up words. That'll detract from facts and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you can't read then, no point in trying further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
