<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7749</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 21:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mrsubject7749

Danke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spiele mit Bart. Holy Shit endlich gehts weiter :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

[For reference.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=upcydsLcxNw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 01:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> t4 - gentle
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 23:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy moly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 19:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My game of the year, god I want more of this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 10:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this seems too "easy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 16:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope we see you in more tournaments in the future :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I think you are spot on and SE is pretty reliable with their release schedules. I would also love to see dungeon style end game raids, Coils are nicely designed and hard in the beginning, but longer and bigger raids, like CM at launch, would be awesome. Or old school FFXI-Sky, something to raid with the LS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best news for me, here in Germany its not that normal to have a credit card rdy and I just always used PlaySpan (with my paypal acc) to get my subscription for the month. Was pretty suprised when I couldnt see the payment option yesterday, maybe I should read more official news . . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 18:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 19:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good decisions with caster changes and being live! Looking forward to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a PS3 just to play the HD remake, FFX was so good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 17:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I doubt they designed Turn 5 to be beaten by the *majority* of players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 19:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the clarification, it seems like a huge honor then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 19:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice read, especially for me, as a non-MtG HS fan.

One noob question: What is the hall of fame in MtG and how important is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had a *million* Flame Imps, that helped :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 19:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German here. Im sure it is somewhere in this thread, but you cant wear just POLIZEI on your shirt. I can even remember, that a "funny" shirt POZILEI couldnt be sold anymore because of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 19:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 17:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really good production value and I love that there was a qualifier, makes it very interesting to watch! Just one minor thing, yesterday we couldn't see when the upper player had a secret in play, maybe that can be adjusted :) Keep up the good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 20:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scary how history always repeats itself . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 19:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REYNAD'S BIGGEST ENEMY?

THE BURNING ROPE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 21:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Letter Media is the best thing on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excited! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as I said, if you know when the first golem hits the battlefield you should have your Twin Snake Buff and IR up + your off GCD's. Also try to hit the mob at the right position (flank  back). In terms off PB, I dont use it there . . . But im the kind of MNK who rarely uses PB in my normal rotation, I only use it to save my GL stacks, when the boss is disappearing and for the first ghost add to burst the bosses HP to 47%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 15:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Main MNK here, beaten T9 5+ times now (ilvl 107). Yes the T9 golems should be handled quickly, don't rely on your Dots there. Dont be fooled, even your best rotation cant do the job if one dps is dead at the beginning of this phase (we kill the green always before he changes color).

As a general advice for playing MNK:

You can do the theorycraft all day long and have the best rotation etc but I find two things more important:

Knowing the fight and the timing of phase changes (thinking ahead!)

Reaction to unusual stuff (dps too fast/slow, multiple deads)


IMO MNK is one of the best DPS classes, because of his consistent and steady DPS output + some decent burst DMG.If you stay alive and know what comes ahead your DPS output will be with the top.


If you have any specific questions, just shoot them at me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 14:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odin representing in this thread :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 11:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GJ EoS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 12:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and 43 Mio gil :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 00:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice readings, spent way more time with your blog than I thought before :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 12:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*See my vest*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qsFHEK_o9U8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I wasnt sure :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 18:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mind to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 14:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently read, that a lot of footage came from the guys from Hatfilms (now Yogscast). There more you know :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 19:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a coop mode or multiplayer?
Looks awesome as expected :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 12:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cater too much to the casual crowd, don't know where this will end . . . 

EDIT: Well maybe I choose the wrong thread to voice my opinion. All I can see is that a lot of friends are leaving/have left the game because it got very stale after 2.2. It still boggles my mind how they can create such nice raids (CT,ST) and then make them piss easy AND don't even let my FC join as a premade group. Or Hunts. Or EX Primals etc pp. I think i'm just very sad, that IMO they go the wrong route with this game. I would love some hard 8 man Dungeons, I would love some dangerous Overworld mobs, I would love some option in terms of equipment (I dont mean vanity), I would love to do something as a FC ingame.

EDIT 2: Can someone explain the downvotes, Im just voicing my opinion. Im not attacking anyone here. I still play every week t 6-9, but the group-rope-jump style for most of the content , leaves me with a bitter taste for the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 17:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OR BEING A DOOR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 20:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooosh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your answer. I dont even know if I want an AKIRA live-action movie, the classic anime is just perfect for me. But then again I saw this trailer and its incredibly well made and for a real live environment, it captures the spirit of the original quite good. Lets see what will come :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything further planned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 13:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I can remember reading that years ago, so funny :)

What was the name of that jap player, which blogged a lot of stuff too, yuffie or something? She had to change name at some point I can remember but was always telling story from the JP Community, which was for me a total different world back then (like '07 or something). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 19:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he said multiple times on stream, that when Naxx is out he will build new decks around the new cards / meta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 21:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so rude and so cute . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 15:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.hearthpwn.com/decks?filter-deck-tag=1 filter-class=64

or just use a variation of Amaz' deck like Iam :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 23:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I found that midly interesting, no reason to be that cocky  . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 22:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ding Dong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 22:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange to see so many misplaced letters and stuff from a mastermind like Kubrick, is there any reasonable explanation for this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 23:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hit as in punch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 16:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like you, will use it thanks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 16:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking a break for 1 month . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 15:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a German thing, we are sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 20:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> badumshhhhhh . . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 14:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it will be 1 Weekly - Hunt Tuesdays after T6-9? Will be epic . . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 12:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, Im from Berlin, will visit Meltdown for some HS action, maybe we can meet there people :D

If you guys want to add me - subject7749 #2135 (around Rank 15 ish) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 01:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah totally with you. I appreciate trying out new/different stuff, but this is not working with my eyes for long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 23:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your style, go for it tiger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain the context here, sorry for not knowing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 11:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean the beginning ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I cant hate you . . . keep it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 22:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that feels so good . . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 22:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard soon^TM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 22:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see the "other" side for once here, keep it up mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about being prepared for a tournament like this with an own account, how about dealing with the messages when they appeared the day before and in earlier matches? You are making this way to easy for RDU, he handled the situation quite bad and I personally dont think he understands what the problem here is: No Transparency and No even ground. We can argue all day with our tinfoil hats whether he set up the "hi mom" system etc, but he got a message with the opponents hand in a live final game and nothing happened? This just makes a joke out of the game and I don't like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 16:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wont show support to RDU, he had the chance to pause after the first messages and give the game to Amaz for fairness. Instead he managed the situation like a little child, just hoping no one sees the shit. its his fault for not being prepared, Amaz had an own account for shit like this. At this point its not about cheating, its about the integrity of the game and dreamhack. In every other important sport event he would be DQed/banned/investigated, here we don't even have an official word. Welcome to the real world RDU and Hearthstone. . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 15:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That or maybe its the 10.000$ price money on the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 23:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why cant I believe that, when we have multiple instances now with important cards drawn and something gets called out on RDUs screen. Thats what I find suspicious. And the fact that RDU played really good and imho doesnt need the help with cheating. I just want to have a fair game to watch :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 22:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats is outragious, rematch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NERDCHILLS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 20:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> down nooooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
