<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6292</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 01:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday, we knew what waited for us today. An hour ago, I was given the news... Now, I wonder if she'll still be here tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 07:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christian pastor, at the viewing, goes up to speak in front of grieving Catholic family members. Ends up preaching his faith in lieu of a eulogy, pretty much ignoring the deceased completely, and getting what little he actually said wrong.

He did it again at the cemetery, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Release all post restrictions, and permaban all existing mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cautious, self motivated adult in distress seeks stable future for himself and his family. He doesn't really care what happens to himself along the way, as long as his family is protected. Levelheaded and fun loving, this man will never hesitate to crack a joke. - no matter how bad   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.inventables.com/categories/inspirational/inspirational-materials

Have fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seen this joke before. Well played, though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reason to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if that's a band, an album, or a song.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knock, knock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know who that is, although context clues lead me to believe he's the lead singer. I just listen to music I like the sound of; usually, I couldn't tell you which artist/group produced any particular piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have pretend conversations with myself. It's actually a fun mental exercise; I write down my concern, analyze it, and respond to it. It's a tool that helps me identify the key points of a given issue, as well as what can be ignored about it.

*Are people going to think I'm crazy because of this post?*

Not sure it really matters, given the nature of this community. Still, some people might ask questions.

*That might make things a little awkward*

If it gets too awkward, just don't respond to them. Never feed trolls, and all that.


...for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nickelback.

I get it, most of their songs are recycling their own concepts. I just like how they sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been under a lot of stress lately dealing with a sudden, unexpected career change. Today went significantly better than the past few weeks, but it still wore me out. She decided to celebrate the modicum of good today by distracting the kid with a movie, "forcing" me into bedroom, taking the lead for a surprise 3-rounder, and then locking the door behind her once we'd finished so I wouldn't be disturbed by our kid as I took a recuperative nap.

Damn, I love my wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 06:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of the fabric promotional posters from the initial release of Windwaker on my wall. A few weeks ago, I glanced at it from across the room and noticed something odd... The logo on the sails of the pirate ship - to the right of Link, behind his sister - are covered in just the right way that they sort of look like a green Dickbutt.

From a distance. Slightly blurred from nearsightedness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 00:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food would be #1, I think.

Followed closely by not-food in second. Imaginary food takes up third place because, while it seems tasty, it just doesn't fill you up like real pie or asphalt can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 05:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 04:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speech.

Could be a blessing, or a curse. We'd certainly find out just how much cats hate us, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 04:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone sucks, but everything is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 04:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumbledore's Army </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 08:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my first smart phone last year, in may. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 08:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Know with certainty that virtually nothing you do will ever be done right the first time. Enter every situation fully prepared to make mistakes, and to learn as much as you can from them. You're not perfect, but here's a secret: no one else is, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 08:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you can look back at everything they did and say, yeah it hurt, but it's over. It's over, and I'm a better person for having survived it.

When you can think of how you were wronged, and then forgive the wrongdoer. Right or wrong, prolonged wrath poisons your mind. Forgive, even if you can't forget.

When you can look at your life ahead, and see it more clearly than the life you've left behind, you'll realize that you've already moved on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 12:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a little difference. I fix the equipment that gives them a display, whereas they read said display, interpret it, and relay instructions to the pilots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close, ATC radar mechanic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're gonna miss this.

I forget the artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fix airplane finders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Babies were there sometimes. Sometimes there were new babies. Never thought to ask why until after someone had already explained it to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Durian  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robin Williams as a mouse... Or a cat... Or both.

(Mrs. Doubtfire) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a kitten...no, a variety of baby animals held by plentiful scantily clad and/or nude women (and a couple men thrown in), all just barely obscuring a wall of books.

The meaning: cute critters and porn that distracts you from the wealth of knowledge available behind it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 07:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandpa's funeral was ny first, and I was too young to remember anything about it besides being bored. Then, my grandma moved on, and a few months ago my new step-grandfather died, too, so his was my second funeral.

What's worse, I was besieged by memories of the first funeral all during the second. Same relative-status, same funeral home, same room, same carpet, same route to the same cemetery, and a very similar service at the very same pavilion. The only difference this time was that some asshole pastor decided to give a sermon instead of a eulogy. 

It wasn't even an appropriate sermon. It was targeted to convert the catholic crowd to Christianity, and didn't even remotely suit the circumstance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 05:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I might take a stab at it, the advice here is that an overwhelming majority of people seem to believe that people have to have an actual external reason or justification to become depressed. While that is broadly true, for people who suffer from chronic depression due to a naturally occurring chemical imbalance in their brain, there is rarely if ever an actual tangible reason for depression to strike. When the balance shifts, their depression sets in, and that's all the reason to be had.

To put it in simpler terms, they're depressed because their body is not producing enough of a specific chemical to keep them balanced. To simplify even further, they're depressed because they're depressed. It wasn't triggered, it just happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 23:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same one you won't be told. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 23:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The holocaust. First time folks didn't walk out of the showers, the gig would be up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 23:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one self portrait by Vincent van Gogh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect situational judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 06:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dying is easy. Anyone can do it at literally any time.

Living, though... Pushing oneself beyond your own preconceived limits of sorrow, joy, fear, anticipation, rage, and control, over and over again in a never-ending cycle of ups and downs; constantly reacting and adapting to a world in flux; pulling off what might seem impossible just in the nick of time, or failing spectacularly; seeing a light in someone else's eyes to show you made a difference, hearing a laugh or a sob that you know you caused. Any number of an infinitely varied and unpredictable conglomeration of stimuli, reactions, emotions, and outcomes, absolutely NONE of which would ever occur if you weren't there as a catalyst.

Death is easy.

Life is beautiful in it's complexity. Difficult, yes. But beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine yourself. Everything there is about you that makes you you. Imagine all of that stuff piled up in the middle of a large, empty room.

Imagine that you're standing against one of the walls in that room. You're only a few feet from everything that makes you you. You can step forward anytime, reach out, and make full use of any aspect of your glorious you-ness.

That's sort of like normal, metaphorically speaking.

Now, imagine the same scenario, only your arms and legs have gone numb. You've slid down the wall, and you know full well that you're stuck there. That pile of magnificent you-ness is just out of reach, but you can see all of it. You can't touch it, though, can't get a single bit of yourself back from where you know it has always been. Worse still, you know that you won't be able to until the numbness fades... and there's no knowing when that might happen.

You exist, but you're not you. And you know it. And that just makes it worse, because you desperately want it - not to be you again, but rather, to to be able to muster the strength of will to even care enough to miss it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old references?

Nope. Chuck Testa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sorry, can you hold that thought for a minute?"

They politely wait for you to handle your business, bit you don't do anything. Finally, they say something like, did you need to do something?

"No, I just *really* wanted you to stop talking about that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A razor blade and a bucket. No explanation, let them figure out what it's for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artichokes can't play tennis very well, but the rutabaga is a racquetball pro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My elephant got into the llama pen a few months ago, and I'm not sure exactly how they managed it, but that pachyderm popped out some of the fluffiest mutants I've ever seen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust, but confirm. In all things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephen Lynch: Hallelujah 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=prvvKpuVp_I
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a five square foot bathroom. I'd die.

Granted, I could always grab the shower curtain rod, or something.

Unless they're all gathered outside the window. In that case, I could escape into the main house. Pretty much my only hope, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found my wife on that site. I know several others who have, as well, and a number more in happy relationships started from that one website.

The problem that most people have with free dating sites such as this is the thought that "you get what you pay for," when, in fact, that's just not true. Any dating site is only as good as its user base. Granted, free means more people might use it who you might deem "undesirable," but even if you paid for eHarmony or something, you'd still have to sift through dozens and hundreds of profiles before finding someone worthwhile.

My own thought on the matter was this: *do I really want to* pay *for love?*

I did not. It worked for me, so hopefully it'll work for you, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most things on the internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 19:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephen Lynch: *Hair* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 06:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine yourself. Everything there is about you that makes you you. Imagine all of that stuff piled up in the middle of a large, empty room.

Imagine that you're standing against one of the walls in that room. You're only a few feet from everything that makes you you. You can step forward anytime, reach out, and make full use of any aspect of your glorious you-ness.

That's sort of like normal, metaphorically speaking.

Now, imagine the same scenario, only your arms and legs have gone numb. You've slid down the wall, and you know full well that you're stuck there. That pile of magnificent you-ness is just out of reach, but you can see all of it. You can't touch it, though, can't get a single bit of yourself back from where you know it has always been. Worse still, you know that you won't be able to until the numbness fades... and there's no knowing when that might happen.

You exist, but you're not you. And you know it. And that just makes it worse, because you desperately want it - not to be you again, but rather, to to be able to muster the strength of will to even care enough to miss it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 06:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friday.

Always Friday. Friday. Gotta get down on... Friday...

Everybody's looking forward to the weekend...

Never a weekend... Always Friday...

Friday...

Which seat do I take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 03:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that writer's strike a few years back? Well, that's when TV execs realized that people will watch literally anything. That they didn't need writers to garner ratings. 

Turn off reality TV. Watch quality programming instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 03:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overlord!

Yes, I know there's a sequel. Playing it now. Wanting another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat burgers and sandwiches from the outside in. My rationale is that I should save the most savory part for last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fifth Element.

Did you even realize that the main antagonist (Zorg) never interacts with the protagonists in any meaningful way?

Sure, he sends people after them once, and sets the bomb, but otherwise he has no contact with them. If anything, Zorg is little more than a Deus ex Machina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason i couldn't explain, I knew my life was complete when I first laid eyes on her. 

Before I could react, she jogged past me and around the corner, out of sight. 

Without a thought, I jumped up from the table and ran after her, spilling my coffee everywhere. 

The hot liquid scalded my leg, the pain making me stumble off the curb.

My head snapped up as the taxi blared its horn, and I had just enough time to realize I was right.

-tried, probably too hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opera scene in The Fifth Element. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 01:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hidden in plain sight, under the really really fluffy couch cushions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 06:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still socially awkward. However, I've learned that it can be overcome by acting as though you're not. Doesn't make sense, I know, but it works. I can't really tell you how to do it, either, but I can explain my method.

Essentially, I'm quiet around new people until I can recognize how they respond to some basic interactions. Then, I speak when I have something relevant to say, presenting myself as someone worth listening to. Finally, after a day or two, I have developed a rapport with the person, and can almost act normally around them. I still have to make a conscious effort to involve myself in interactions, but if I get awkward, I still have that basic foundation of credibility to keep me clear of  the "weirdo" classification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 06:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logical reasoning skills.  Specifically, the ability to identify and interpret context clues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 05:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estimate low... 60*7=480/day

480*7=3320/week

3320*52=172640/year

172640*4=690,560 

$690,560 for four years on reddit, averaging six hours a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 05:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in my family, there were set rules, which were enforced by both of my parents. We had set bedtimes, a chore schedule, and an allowance that shifted based on whether we actually did out chores. We also had the freedom to explore the house, visit friends when our homework was done, and generally discover what the world holds without our parents holding our hands.

Then I grew up and got social, and learned that none of the above seems to be the case with anyone else I've ever met, my age or younger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 05:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am uniquely ordinary, and especially typical as such. I am much more than I ever have been, and far less than I have the potential to be. I am one with no one, and share that with everyone. I am my own, and the only such thing in this universe.

I am me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 04:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helps restore focus on those long trips, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To reach the other end of my personal timeline and be able to look back at what I've done with as few regrets as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 04:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like numbers in my username, so I slapped the keyboard randomly, then deleted letters until I found a sound that I liked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 04:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have survived long enough to create an army of my own; one which has produced yet another biological victory in the face of all odds. I have successfully furthered my legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 23:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tv drama: action freeze frame!

American cartoon: epic pose freeze frame!

Anime: freeze frame of all major characters in a cool looking pose! Also, 10-30 seconds of the main 2-4 characters walking/running without really going anywhere. Also also, posed photo of everyone at the end!

...I'm bored with this now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 23:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, prices won't ever go down. They'll stay the same - rise, even, claiming it's because of "instability" or some other crock of shit - and profits will rise.

Greed is the one thing more certain in this country than death and taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 23:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paying for healthcare provided by the government, other than taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oreo truffles.

Super simple, too. Take 1 package Double Stuff Oreos, 8 oz. cream cheese, and blend together  into paste. Form into 1-inch balls and put them in the freezer to set for 20 minutes or so. Next, melt white chocolate (almond bark or similar, won't melt at room temp) and dip the balls in with a fork or something. Let set in the fridge, enjoy at your leisure.

They. Are. Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kathleen Mint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 17:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. No way. Absolutely not.

Mostly because it would piss off my wife. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the grocery store and squeeze all of the fruits and vegetables that bruise easily. Then, fill a cart with all the dairy and raw meat you can find and leave it sitting somewhere random in the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looooot of people not in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day I won custody of my daughter, with the help of my loving then-fiancee, against a pair of crazy people trying to ruin my life and rip my child away from me for at least five years under false pretenses.

That was a good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 05:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead people. 

In movies, they always look exactly like they did when they were alive, only slightly paler. In reality, though, dead people are almost instantly transformed when their heart stops.

Every muscle relaxes. Various bodily fluids, which were kept evenly distributed throughout the body by the living pulse, immediately start flowing to the lowest point of the body. This makes the face and other elevated areas wither, the skin hanging in loose, unnatural folds; meanwhile, the lower extremities swell and stretch from the settling fluids, expanding and distending like a skin balloon. 

You don't understand the term glassy-eyed until you see eyes that are still wet and reflective, but are perfectly stationary. Living eyes are constantly moving, so that glass-like stillness is particularly unsettling.

You don't understand what is meant by "waxy skin" until you see the shine of a person's bodily oils as they grow cold, solidifying like grease on an oven tray.

You can get to their side in as little as 15 minutes, and they've already undergone this transformation. Source: just recently had all of this burned into my mind, and I got there 15 minutes too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 04:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best guess is that Weird Al isn't greedy or desperate enough to license out his work to such things. Having made as many songs decrying the greed of people in general and the music industry specifically, I think it's pretty clear that he either doesn't need to worry about money, or doesn't care to.

Either way, I respect the hell out of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social skills. Very much social skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You a stupid hoe, you-a, you-a stupid hoe. You a stupid hoe, you-a, you-a stupid hoe. You a stupid hoe, you-a, you-a stupid hoe."

Seriously?!!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Who and Sheldon Cooper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't notice well-done makeup without a baseline reference, but if I know what you look like clean-skinned, then it's a very noticeable addition, normally good.

If it's *not* well done, though, then it's usually immediately quite jarring. Ke$ha is a good example of that. Or Mimi Bobeck, from the Drew Carey Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unwarranted character attacks. 

*(troll target has surfaced: target locked)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 05:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I respect your opinion, sir, and do not begrudge you for it."

...well...on Reddit, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone's entitled to their opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like all these comments critiquing my interpretation of the story only serve as justification if the prompt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate if you want, it was no secret. One of my first responses on this, minutes after posting, was a statement of enjoyment of the series.  As for the thanks,do you really think I shouldn't be grateful that a stranger gave me a gift? If anything, I should think you have better things to do than harangue random internet strangers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 02:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That got oddly specific and vaguely insulting fast, but... Fixed, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 02:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, too! You put in into terms I hadn't considered, but that's basically how I look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
