<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1178</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 02:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... 56 North has Scotland's widest range of gins and the trimmings to boot! Andin Heads and Tails you can drink 3 foot from the stills where Edinburgh Gin is made. Get on it!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My name is subject1178 and I am am alcoholic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 23:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight I went to my first AA meeting after being sober for 24 hours. I was pleasantly surprised to find that the first share said he was an atheist as did many others. Thanks a bunch to this sub for inspiring me to finally get of my drunken ass and do something about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 05:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Madrid recently and every. Single.Bar. Was offering a range of G n'T's. In fucking red wine glasses with the measures to suit! Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 17:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no particular order - restock fridges, soak and scrub bar mats, wipe down all back bar surfaces, polish and dry shakers, remove and soak sparklers, wipe down tables and table legs, Hoover seats and floor, clean out all juice and fruit pourers/containers, bring in outside signs, put grates up, strip spul-boy and leave to soak, clean toilets, empty bottle and rubbish bins, sweep away cigarette ends, mop floors, cash up and then get the fuck out of dodge. If the bar was any bigger single man closes would be a nightmare, thankfully they're pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 09:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? If whisky aint your thang i can understand why but its a hell of a lot better than a slippery nipple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Filling an event room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 19:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks
Now I have an interview next week for an Assistant Managers job at an awesome bar/kitchen in Edinburgh  that I'm really hoping I get. They've asked me to come into the interview with ideas or filling their 150 capacity function room above the bar on every Saturday night. They already do live music and ceilidh's at the weekend but it's just not pulling the crowds in. It's a fairly high class venue (or at least wants to be) and I'm a little stumped. Any suggestions for events you can hold on a Saturday night?  I'm going into the interview saying they need to push their marketing as a first thing, cos there isn't any at the moment. Cheers folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 02:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's departments in the council using up their budget - seen any badly filled in potholes recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 14:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> International Vodka and Beer Bar - Edinburgh's smallest and best wee bam bar haha! high volume, fast pace, rowdy, stag do friendly at the weekends, frozen strawberry daiquiri's, lots of blue curacao... Basically the opposite of your bar. Good fun though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 22:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Edinburger here! Where dya tend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 21:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edinburgh has a bitching craft cocktail scene and one of the worlds best bars (Bramble) is here. As for getting work with them? Almost impossible unless your part of that clique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 21:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's illegal for us to do happy hours in Scotland... Bit of a mixed blessing I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 23:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yyyaaaaassss!!!! Took bloody long enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 22:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't say that... Please don't... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 16:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna go to work in a few hours then spend Sunday preparing to go to Madrid early on Monday. Which makes me extremely happy because I haven't been abroad in bloody aaagggeessss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 15:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight up 86 them. Just tell they're barred next time they're in. Gotta make a stand on it. It's the same drill as cutting someone off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 01:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 03:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish :( flights from the UK are crazy expensive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 01:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Solid advice, pulling through to my last hour now. It's gonna be fine in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 00:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, but not helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 23:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Back of house! Don't make me laugh - I am all the staff! Purely a wet bar. Also don't smoke anymore :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked a bit! Hangover is being defeated slowly but surely. Cheers for the advice, my usual go to can of Irn-Bru didn't make a dent... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 20:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont I know it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 19:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleared the cellar earlier and let me tell ya, kegs are not friendly to hangovers :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 19:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool - how much bitters? Healthy dash? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working hungover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 19:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a beer tasting last night put on by one of our suppliers and today I have become hangover, destroyer of souls. I'm talking 7th circle of hell hangover, hot and cold at the same time, smell of booze making me gag type stuff. To top it off I'm in the middle of a 13 hour single manned shift... Urgh. Any tips to help me through this awful awful turn of events? 

Edit: cheers for all the advice folks, I'm pulling through to the end now - Final hour, it's been tough but this hangovers arse is being kicked up and down the street by a combo of red bull, bitters, ginger ale and a shot of vodka in the red bull as well as a bit of old fashioned pulling myself up by my bootstraps. Couldn't have done it without you! Drinks on me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 13:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> International Vodka   Beer Bar on Rose Street in Edinburgh is pretty good as a pre-club bar sort of space before hitting up George Street if you don't fancy spending a load of cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 21:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get breaks?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 20:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tis the trend for stupid shit like at the moment, its just part of the theatre of it. The Belle Epoque Flip is damn tasty and their aged Boulevardier is a cracker. Still, why would you go there when you could go to Bramble eh?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 20:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, their cocktails are superb so I can kinda forgive them... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you turn beer into water your probably not fully Scottish... Ken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 05:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double gin, double lime cordial, shaken served up (or in lack of a shaker over ice). The Gimlet everybody! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whisky or fae doon sooth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 05:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The recent post pointing out the number of folks in the corners drinking pints of McEwans and Tennants, looking like they don't want to talk to anyone got me thinking are there any Scottish pub chat folks in here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 13:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been slightly too embarrassed to post after I let all the yanks in a few months back... That and my new job means I have very little Reddit time :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 15:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know a "stagette" is called a hen party. At least it is in Scotland... Sucks having shitty nights like that man, but it's awesome that your staff responded positively to the stripping down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attracting locals into a mainly tourist bar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 15:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a small bar in Scotland that is situated in the capital on a street full of bars mainly aimed at tourists. Our is a little different in that it is a pre club bar catering to stag and hen do's and anyone else really. Our main issue at the moment is that our PR staff pull in 80% tourists, whilst its great being busy they are not repeat custom.  Any advice on how to pull in more locals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 05:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frequenting Viz are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 15:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish I had that - instead I spent my night getting fucked in the ass by cocktails solidly for 4 hours. No shakers no glasses nothing by the end. Single manning because it's a Monday to boot. Blurgh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 15:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ours was like that but I pestered my manager till he let me change it, now we have folk complimenting the music all the time. Much better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 14:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds pretty similar to what we do - The TruThoughts record label has been a godsend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... music? What do you guys have playing while you work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 05:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be it a dive bar, a club, goth bar, country bar etc etc what do you have playing while you work? Do you get a choice? Take requests? Design the playlist yourself? Fave songs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelvingrove - 100% absolutely the best Art Gallery in Scotland. It's big but not flashy, fantastically laid out with the finest collection of Scottish art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bartender at the moment so probably not every day life but it's here anyway. Usually I'm asleep in the morning and waking up around 12pm. Once I'm awake I usually eat a small meal, most likely salad with a load of vegetables through it. Now it's about 2pm so I do a little bit of work for my job (I run their social media and graphic design stuff) at which point it's time to go to work. I start work at 4pm and work right through till 2am and with no shops open really when I finish work I tend to bring a sort of snack box with me to graze on throughout my shift. Usually some oatcakes, a bit of cheese, some tomatoes etc. when I leave my job I walk home which takes me about half an hour. I walk past the castle here every night which I think looks awesome when it's all lit up by big colourful lights. I usually get home just before 3am, have a meal of stew or pasta, sometimes chilli before crashing out and starting all over again. Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 16:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much - I really appreciate that, just what i needed to hear today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 16:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite right - not sure what thats called then but it is very tasty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 17:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good way to start people on Campari is the Americano. 1 part gin 1 part Campari ice topped with soda. It mellows the shit right out, brings it down to a taste closer to grapefruit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 16:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the weather is nice Malleny Gardens in Balerno is a great way to spend the afternoon. Bring a picnic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 18:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no need to counter - I play the 227 at Euston which, if we really are going by the extended rules, brings down the congestion charge of 77. Check and wang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 03:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blocked by the thirtieth fatality on the line. Rotate the tube! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 04:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries :-) if you ever get the chance check their live show - the recordings don't do it justice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 15:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on my way into work to go and serve alcohol to some of the bammiest bams the world has ever seen. What is it about sunshine that brings out the terrible people? Ah well, I'll have a pint in the dark when I finish so it's not all bad I suppose... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 19:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do love Bombskare, always nice that Andy and the rest of em kick about after gigs for a few drinks and such </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some more Scottish Ska: The Victorian Trout Conspiracy - Watershed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 17:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 17:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and Gordon's! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bacardi White 
Smirnoff
Jack Daniels
Blue Curaao 
Gomme
Lime Cordial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working every day :-S heading into work now with the most righteous of hangovers. I genuinely think I'm going to die. Hulp meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 21:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every club does this, to be honest any nightclub that does should be reported and fined/closed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drink more... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 16:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing - does an Ice Luge not also dilute the shot a little? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 03:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Connery plays his favourite sport about the same time every day. Tennish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 03:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sources? For all your facts and figures please :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
