<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 14:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teaching: "have been teaching full-time in a low-income elementary or secondary school or educational service agency for five consecutive years, you may be able to have as much as $17,500 of your subsidized or unsubsidized loans forgiven."

Public Service: "If you are employed in certain public service jobs (government, 501c3) and have made 120 payments on your Direct Loans (after Oct. 1, 2007), the remaining balance that you owe may be forgiven."

[Source](https://studentaid.ed.gov/sa/repay-loans/forgiveness-cancellation#teacher-loan).

But she quotes a "pays a living wage equivalent to number of hours worked," which I interpret as way more than 501c3 and government agencies can afford at duties she could assume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 21:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A huge amount of people in show business have fine arts degrees. Steven Colbert has a Fine Arts degree. 

I know plenty of people with Fine Arts degrees who have good paying and/or very enjoyable jobs.  It just takes an immense amount of work to get that kind of job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can't really work, but want to be paid a lot, and in a position that has federal loan forgiveness."

Sounds like she's going to get scooped up real quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 13:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In 2009, Chevron and the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia extended and amended their historic operating agreement, originally signed in 1949, in the onshore Partitioned Zone (PZ) between Saudi Arabia and Kuwait. The 30-year pact underscores Chevrons standing as the Kingdoms oldest private partner and reaffirms a long tradition of friendship and shared success. Working in partnership with the Kuwait Gulf Oil Co., Saudi Arabian Chevron (SAC) operates four fields and more than 1,000 wells; in 2005, the PZ produced its three billionth barrel of oil. In recent years, SAC has consistently exceeded production targets while compiling millions of work-hours of safe operations."  

"In Saudi Arabia, Chevron is the only private international oil company with
active production."

[PDF Source](http://www.chevron.com/documents/pdf/historyWithAfuture.pdf)  

Chevron is one of the major operators in the ME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL part 3: US Gas, Global Future: New markets bring new ways to look at receiving LNG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL part 2: US Gas, Global Future: To preview 2nd wave of LNG export projects, think small </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL part 1: US Gas, Global Future: At eve of exports, LNG expansion projects stoke fears of overbuild </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US coal market value falls by nearly a third in roughly 2 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can confirm, we did license this Patriarchy Bingo Board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  what the racist in question is demonstrating is a knowledge of two of the most famous firearms of the present day.

Is a Desert Eagle well known outside of the gamer crowd?  The main reason I know of it is CS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 21:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://www.wired.com/2003/09/diamond/[1]

Thanks for the article, really cool stuff.

"He said that my father's research was a good way to get a bullet in the head," Linares recalls.

Wow.

Edit: 2003 (still really cool) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 16:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *honk honk* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 13:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>      Beetlejuice
 
 
 
 Beetlejuice?

Beetlejuice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 00:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  gt;Nonbinary Femme

 gt;He

 gt;they 

I'm pretty confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would literally be rape you dick-having shitlord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 00:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Namaste has it's roots in Hinduism... So I guess the Buddhist appropriated it from them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 00:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House of Saud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (compared to about $93 per barrel in the free market)

What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am obviously not your average 15 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 22:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When she says "anyone," she assumes that that which is referenced identifies as "one," and that's not ok.  It's multiist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 20:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Comment.  I guarantee she will reply calling you an oppressive shitlord.~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 17:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't throw all your *doots* in one basket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 15:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, actually, [this is the real reason](http://i.imgur.com/zL8ytHA.png).

We gave the pilot of *Chris, Riley, and Charlie's Safe-Space Talking Adventure* a shot, but the ratings just didn't give our Patriarch Overlords the projected revenue necessary to adequately fund the FY 16 Oppression Campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 14:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they had this trigger warning *before trigger warnings were even a thing.*  You could say that Matt and Trey were ahead of their time in progressivenesses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 00:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks promising.  I'll throw my *doot doot* in the ring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 23:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me:

Who is Kesha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some weekends I become 1/32 scotch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 20:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protesters reportedly shouted F you, you filthy white f- f you and your comfort and f you, you racist s.

I sure as hell hope this is fake.

Edit:  Watching that video, I'm going with this is all very, very, horribly real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 22:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should band together and supply food for this occasion! I'll bring bacon wrapped, deep fried sticks of butter.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 23:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  penises

Wow, trigger warning plz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 22:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2010s:  Where people learn how to view society from dank tumblr maymays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 21:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.... what the fuck was that?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those poor souls.  I've heard that some are so brainwashed that they internalize the biggest patriarchy they can find, while some can only internalize so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 18:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The cheering for Rubio after he rants about "rebuilding" the American military is the reason why Rand will never be elected (at 6:10 but had to include Rand's comments).](https://youtu.be/8diyMhu5U2I?t=5m34s)

Truly sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 17:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really pisses me off because some of the most attractive people I know are dirty mixed bloods.

One set of friends - decent looking white dad, ok looking korean mom. SMOKING hot 5'10" daughter, Really good looking son.

Another - Kenyan mom, white dad.  Insanely curvaceous, gorgeous daughter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 16:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try to run some back of the envelope numbers if I get a minute, but the elasticity of demand isn't great enough to counter a 30-40% decrease in prices and tax receipts if it's a direct percentage.  Fluctuations in budgets can further inefficiencies - having to hire and train, then lay off employees for example.

Another comment above you suggested a 5 or 10 year moving average, which could be more consistent.  Keeping up with inflation is definitely the key, *if* the starting value is enough to offer decent upkeep for the infrastructure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 16:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the saddest part is that this type of person's life completely revolves around this obsession to the point that they constantly are typing midodynist/misogynist.

There are political and social topics that I am passionate about, but I let it fucking go enjoy my life from time to time.  Not with these folks. It completely consumes them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 14:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would bring wild fluctuations in times like these - last year receipts would have been close to twice this year. In boom times, money would be wasted, in bust times we would have shortfalls.

A $/gallon with a set annual increase linked to inflation would be more consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 00:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed.  Gotta admit it's pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 21:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Atlantic absolutely nailed it:](http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2015/11/the-new-intolerance-of-student-activism-at-yale/414810/)

"According to The Washington Post, several students in Silliman said they cannot bear to live in the college anymore. These are young people who live in safe, heated buildings with two Steinway grand pianos, an indoor basketball court, a courtyard with hammocks and picnic tables, a computer lab, a dance studio, a gym, a movie theater, a film-editing lab, billiard tables, an art gallery, and four music practice rooms. But they cant bear this setting that millions of people would risk their lives to inhabit because one woman wrote an email that hurt their feelings?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 17:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY LESLIE SHUT YOUR FUCKING MOUTH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Text if you get paywalled:

Peabody Energy, one of the largest global coal producers, will submit revised investor disclosures after the New York attorney-generals office found it misled the public and investors about the financial risks associated with climate change.

The Peabody settlement announced Monday is the first to emerge from the state attorney-generals probe of oil and energy companies, and reflects a rare move forcing companies to make certain disclosures about climate change.

ExxonMobil is also being investigated about whether it misled shareholders and the public about climate change risks and how it could affect the company. The company received a subpoena last week requesting emails, financial records and other documents.

The Peabody case is seen as distinct from Exxon, which is also being investigated for consumer fraud, said people familiar with the probes. In comparison with Peabody, Exxon is suspected of making a broader number of claims and potentially misleading statements to consumers stretching from the 1970s to this year, which could carry large penalties, the people said.

Peabody will not have to pay any fines because it was difficult to prove that shareholders had been harmed as the claims the company made involved the future affect of climate change on Peabodys profits, people familiar with the situation said.
Peabody will have to file revised disclosures with the Securities and Exchange Commission that accurately and objectively represent climate change risks, including concerns about the environmental impacts of coal combustion...[that] could significantly affect demand for our products or our securities, the state attorney-generals office said.

As a publicly traded company whose core business generates massive amounts of carbon emissions, Peabody Energy has a responsibility to be honest with its investors and the public about the risks posed by climate change, now and in the future, attorney-general Eric Schneiderman said. I believe that full and fair disclosures by Peabody and other fossil fuel companies will lead investors to think long and hard about the damage these companies are doing to our planet.

Peabody repeatedly denied in SEC filings that it could predict the affect of potential climate change regulation on its business, although the company and its consultants made projections that such rules would have severe affects on Peabody, Mr Schneidermans office said.

I believe that full and fair disclosures by Peabody and other fossil fuel companies will lead investors to think long and hard about the damage these companies are doing to our planet

For example, Peabodys internal projections showed that if certain regulation for power plants and future electricity generation were enacted, it would reduce its coal sales by at least 33 per cent.

Peabody did not admit or deny wrongdoing as part of the settlement, and will include disclosures reflecting the settlement starting in its third-quarter filing. The company said any future claims about the difficulty of making projections around climate change regulation will be accompanied by statements that show the company has made predictions about the affect of certain laws, which could hurt the markets or the company.

The company has always sought to make appropriate disclosures, Peabody said in a statement. Subsequent disclosures evolve over time. Peabody has been involved in major global initiatives to reduce carbon emissions for nearly two decades.
Mr Schneidermans investigation may widen to include other oil and energy companies, while other states could join in the probe.

The investigation into fossil fuel companies has drawn parallels with the probe into the tobacco industrys knowledge of the risks of smoking. That led to class-action lawsuits that resulted in huge payouts.

However, Howard Erichson, a law professor at Fordham University who is an expert on class-action suits, said it was difficult to see how similar actions could be pursued over climate change.

Its different at both ends, he said. With the effects of climate change, some of them at least are experienced by more than seven billion people in the world. And some of the cost is imposed by billions of individuals as well as an immense number of companies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peabody Energy misled on climate change, says NY regulator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 23:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.  And this is the first I've heard of this.  I'd say it's a fairly accurate complaint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have gone with "TIL my penis is Aethergender" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is pretty unreal.  It's truly hard to imagine what's going through her head.  Is she defending long neck pixelated dog syndrome or something?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky.  All my facebook friends do is post baby pics and share stupid buzzfeed-esque articles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me xe didn't get shadowbanned, that's the sharpest comment I've seen in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 16:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  Not a single non-binary with an androgynous expression. Incredibly closed minded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  wild pigs

mmmmmmm wild pig.  My buddy worked as a ranger in the swamps of Louisiana and had motion cameras set up all over.  He would always try to get a fresh catch when he visited.  Delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was quite a bit of suffering in the dying process in the pre-Temple Grandin cattle slaughterhouses, from what I understand. 

That being said, my chickens are probably some of the happiest living beings on the planet for the months they get to play in fields and eat delicious food, and then get a quick, relatively painless death.  I hope to be getting cows soon so they can live a similar life, then my family gets a massive amount of happiness shortly after. 

I still think the industrial process has suffering, which is why giving up meat is one of the worst things you can do.  The most effective thing you can do is financially support the businesses that do it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 05:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to make a triggered joke or something, but it's not even funny at this point.  Just straight fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 04:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  Just wow.  Thanks for the loop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  , I didn't realize it was a crime for me to date a 21 year old woman that I'm attracted to

You aren't attracted to them that's your patriarchal engrained privalege. You should really check that and learn what a real strong attractive woman looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually zombies are of West African, Haitian and Brazilian origin.  I sure did see a lot of culturally insensitive racists this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the context of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also directly correlated with the opening of immigration from the middle East.

[Boy do I love cultural enrichment](http://i.imgur.com/7OJvoZh.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it a tax/filing service?  Aren't they aiming to reduce your taxes as much as possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woops,  [Updated chart](http://si.wsj.net/public/resources/images/NA-CG479_BUDGET_16U_20150713140009.jpg).  But the results are actually a larger decrease in the deficit.

I'm not sure if you understand "budget deficit" if you said this:

How exactly do you think it's possible that Obama reduced the amount added to the debt each year yet he added 10 trillion total whereas Bush added 5 trillion total? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How exactly do you think it's possible that Obama reduced the amount added to the debt each year yet he added 10 trillion total whereas Bush added 5 trillion total?

[Fairly simple, see this chart.](http://si.wsj.net/public/resources/images/NA-CG479_BUDGET_16U_20150713140009.jpg)

In reality, the effects of the deficit for both presidents had much more to do with the fact that we went into a recession in 2008. Recessions vastly reduces government receipts if spending remains the same, or in this case increased for the stimulus.

Edit:  Put in updated chart, previous one was old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 21:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In fact, Saudi is producing at record levels.

[Sure, but very small on a percentage increase basis (sorry, peak oil chart)](http://peakoilbarrel.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Saudi-Arabia1.jpg).

By not-manipulating the market now (or just ever so slightly) Saudi is working to ensure it can manipulate it later on.

The cat's out of the bag with shale, SA market manipulation powers for prices above $70 is all but eliminated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some decent points, and I agree with consolidation of US producers benefiting SA, but he uses the same old rhetoric of SA being the ones who flooded the market, because they didn't manipulate the market *against their own benefit,* when in reality their prodx was flat, and US shale were the ones who flooded the market.

Edit:  One more note:

Most smaller shale producers will struggle to make it, if the price of oil remains under $60 per barrel, which it will probably do until Saudi Arabia cuts back on production.

Many smaller shale companies are doing fine, as long as they aren't over leveraged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 14:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of context image macros of Bernie from buzzfeed.  Just what this sub needs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 13:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for nuclear specifically, but I lived in China for a long time.

A good friend worked for a Western company that designed facilities which extracted metals from mine waste water to clean the water.  The company worked with mines all over Canada, the US, Chile.  The companies in the West had tailing ponds and worked with his company for regulatory and general health purposes.  The mine in China dumped the waste water directly back into the river, and found his company only because nickel prices were particularly high at the time. 

They had an exact turn key design built for highly corrosive processes.  The local engineers took the design and stripped it to the absolute bare bones.  They took out the durimet screws and replaced with cheap stainless steel.  When he was very adamant that they cannot do that, they told him they couldn't get durimet in China.  They removed the nickel depositing bin, and replaced it with migrant workers shoveling nickel without gloves.  There were leaks and sulfuric acid spraying from about every joint.

Again, I can't speak for nuclear, but for the mining industry (and construction in general) this is the norm, not an exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 14:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](http://i.imgur.com/hJLtZla.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL: As Pilgrim falls, 11% of nuclear generation at risk of early closure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 15:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decompression sickness is from the nitrogen in your blood that goes into your tissues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Surprise Wizard!](http://i.imgur.com/GJtr5wM.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 20:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell if serious, but:

OKcupid told him there's  1844...................... people that like him/her.

Thinks that's strange so googles the number.

A reddit thread comes up explaining that 1844...................... is a messup, and should be displayed as -1.

So he went from 1844...................... people liking him/her to -1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 20:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a dangerous combination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 20:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix and chill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine what they could achieve if they would continue to develop these technologies, would support renewables, and stop the hatred of nuclear?  They could have carbon free electricity in no time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 14:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The news came out after WTI dropped $4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 23:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't many non-ancap libertarians supportive of a sales tax over income tax?  Wouldn't libertarians be supportive of closing corporatist loopholes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 18:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that sudden concern was why WTI dropped $3 yesterday, dampening the domestic rally?

Edit:  Poorly worded, Brent clearly dragged down WTI with OPEC #s yesterday, but $50 was a big level for WTI.  Iran news has been there for months, won't affect price until something actually happens.  I'm not holding my breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rising numbers of Americans believe climate science, poll shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 18:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. shale firms snap up $50 oil hedges, risking rally reversal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 14:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 17:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you try a private window?

[You can do the fake referer using RefControl or another service, but if the google trick doesn't work it might not work either.](http://forums.redflagdeals.com/easy-trick-bypass-wall-street-journal-financial-times-paywall-updated-1713403/)

[Chrome UA spoofer works for almost everything for me, even FT which has a stronger paywall, but it changes your layout](http://cygnush33l.co.uk/bypass-the-financial-times-paywall-ft-com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this keeps on going for a few months, it will be back down in the 30s very shortly after.  There's finally some needed bankruptcies and consolidation happening, and a continued rally will, again, put those on hold and turn back on the spigot.

That May rally to mid-60s was the worst thing that could have happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The process is fair," Stebbins said. "I understand that there are people who don't want to look at these things, it hurts them emotionally and makes them angry. I understand that. But the science is not supporting many of the claims that are stated. And the facts in terms of the PSB process is that projects are denied or are required to do extensive mitigation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 18:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the guy on the left bring two mannequins to hunt with him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 23:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now onto the other big one, record storage. We'll hit 4.0 Tcf by end of October and November will see its second year of L48 injections, we could get 4.2

ICE swaps are at 4.0.  I def don't see 4.2.

Then, get into Feb, you're at record seasonal storage and production won't be dropping significantly, your shoulder season won't see much demand as warmth arrives earlier and you're due for sub $2 gas for the March and April forward contracts by the time you get to Valentine's day.

Most weather vendors are predicting warmer early winter, colder late.

Also, per Genscape: "Normal and extreme weather scenarios leave [end of season] storage within 5-year max/min ranges" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 19:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that we're above historical storage and production levels, 

There's a little choked back, both for shut-ins for hopeful winter pricing and waiting for take-away capacity coming online, but Marcellus and Utica are the only plays increasing.  Everywhere else is losing b's. 

and international economies appear to be slowing

LNG is a very tiny demand at the moment, total .05 bcf/d now.  Liquifaction and shipping are ~$4-6/mmbtu to go international.  International slowdowns will have very little effect on LNG exports. Russia deals would more so.

Exports to Mexico have been been very strong, but estimating lower for the month average.  Still well above last year.  There were very few analysts projecting 3bcf/d late summer.

we may not see much of a price increase this winter.

Agree upside potential is capped, but HUGE short CoT for MM.  Incredibly bearish GFS runs all week, and yet still not falling.  That first whiff of cold air could see a very quick .20 rally, possibly even larger with the short squeeze. Very crowded on the short side.  See May this year.

I also think a scorcher El Nino winter is priced in. 

Disclosure, I'm long NG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 22:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kills man while texting and driving, "Within scope of duty" and not charged.](http://finance.yahoo.com/news/police-officer-not-charged-killing-095951755.html)

[The fucks ups in this story are pretty intense. Nothing happened.](http://www.telegram.com/article/20150821/NEWS/150829750)

[Blowing apart a 2-year old, recommends no charges](http://abcnews.go.com/US/family-toddler-injured-swat-grenade-faces-1m-medical/story?id=27671521)

I'm sure we have different definitions of "caught red handed," but still not sure if you are trolling or just willfully ignorant to believe that police don't get off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 17:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Soon the dollar will not be the world reserve currency anymore and the US will be just another market for corporations.

What do you envision being the world currency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 21:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main difference I see with Austrian economics is it always comes back to 100%, exclusively ethics arguments. If there is *any* negative externality, it is wrong by Austrian economics, no matter the objective economic outcome.  Which I understand and is the basis of the school, but debates here tend to start on shoddy economic foundations, when questioned and picked apart, always come back to redistribution and taxation are literally slavery and theft at gunpoint.

at $10.10/hour min wage it's estimated that 500,000 people will lose their jobs.

Do you believe there will be *any* economic benefit?  

[The Economist](http://www.economist.com/news/leaders/21591593-moderate-minimum-wages-do-more-good-harm-they-should-be-set-technocrats-not) has some pretty decent arguments for moderate minimum wage.

Nor is a moderate minimum wage as undesirable as neoclassical purists suggest. Unlike those in textbooks, real labour markets are not perfectly competitive. Since workers who want to change jobs face costs and risks, employers may be able to set pay below its market-clearing rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 19:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's taking an argument to it's extremes to try to prove a point.

You say that the relationship isn't linear, then defend that argument...

at some point, the minimum wage will have huge negative externalities, agree or disagree?...

Completely agree. At $20000/hour it would have huge negative externalities. That's why no one is advocating for it, and why it's such a terrible argument.  At $10.10, very minor externalities.  Do you not agree there would be positive externalities from a marginal increase?

[prices and wages are not levers that set value, but rather, are metrics that respond to value. Therefore, since government cannot legislate value, attempts to control prices/wages will generate unintended consequences.](http://www.learnliberty.org/videos/unintended-consequences-of-price-controls/)

hmmmmm.  That's the thing, no one is arguing there won't unintended consequences.

For the record, I'm not advocating for a drastic minimum wage increase.  I'm simply saying that the economic arguments here are terribly embarrassing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 19:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other problem is that Austrian economists only talk in absolutes, where as mainstream economists talk in terms of cost benefit analysis. So Austrian economists will frequently reply with a strawman, "If raising the minimum wage to $15 is good, then why not just raise it to $20000?" Which is a really stupid question.

This could not be more right, and this garbage is spouted regularly around here. Do you think this is a good argument? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny that the person constantly bombarded as an *ELS troll* is one of the few in this whole thread with real world economic literacy.

As a disgruntled main party-er, many of the premises behind libertarianism are quite appealing.  Then I come here and the economic arguments are embarrassing The "why don't we make it $100/hour" and "why don't we just give everyone a trillion dollars" - top comments in the last minimum wage thread - make me want to leave and never come back.  Thanks for the input on this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 21:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm asking you if this program had a tangible goal that was achieved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you disagree this happened?

"It literally kick-started the whole utility-scale photovoltaic industry," Moniz says. The program funded the first of five huge solar projects in the West. Moniz says before that, developers couldn't get money from private lenders. But now, with proven business models, they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 18:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not exactly libertarian, but don't know how much I would qualify as continue the drug war, especially compared with other Dems and the whole GOP. I think that legalizing all drugs is still a fairly fringe policy.](http://feelthebern.org/bernie-sanders-on-drug-policy/)

[Wouldn't end the drone program.](http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/252270-sanders-i-wouldnt-end-drone-program) 

[Thinks that the US should have the strongest military in the world. Voted for Afghanistan, against Iraq war.](http://www.pbs.org/newshour/rundown/bernie-sanders-u-s-prepared-use-military-force/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMA REQUEST:  RYAN DUNNE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 17:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Their early work was a little too new wave for my taste.](http://i.imgur.com/1W2Q7B6.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 16:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  then there will be less reason than before to choose the inconvenient one.

Sure, but to assume it's a neat, linear relationship is wrong.  And that's an assumption that everyone here uses, while smarter proponents of a minimum wage increase understand it's not a linear relationship, just like every other factor involved.  That's why the "Why don't we make it $100" and "why don't we give everyone a trillion dollars" are ridiculous arguments, and show little understanding (not saying you said that, but it's all over this thread). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 05:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merely commenting on your:

I have no idea how the real world works but look

and reflecting that on this sub. I don't know why I still try here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 05:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife offshores a few hundred PM positions go India. 50% bottom of the line on the surface, but she's lost large customers because of incompetence. Plus 35 holidays. Plus her having to travel to shit hole Mumbai 4 times a year because without direct management they are the most worthless workers on the planet. They are moving all project management back to the US, for P L purposes. So, different companies have different experiences. 

Not sure what this has to do with my commeny on automation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 05:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that these oversimplified textbook-esque examples are just as bad as the shitty economics. Why do you think that markets  and labor opperate purely on the dollar value?

What if that second one is 9 to 5 rather than shitty service hours? What if that second one is much more presentable in social situations? What if that second one has much higher chance for upward mobility? What if that second one isn't fucking McDonalds or a similar service job where your life is miserable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 22:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except folks here regularly lambaste their imaginary liberal friend and Bernie for not knowing any economics, while this thread alone is full of:

*why don't we raise it to $100/hour

*why don't we give everyone a trillion dollars

*the cost of living will go up by a 1 to 1 ratio

*nobody will ever do anything besides minimum wage jobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 22:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ZOMG the used Doritos are only $18.14! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
