<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6524</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6% upvoted. Impressive as hell! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> putting characters on auto-pilot, it'd be a great balance.

But you CAN do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna motorboat that cake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THanks so much =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this would be literally the only way I could manage to get a sour feeling in my stomach this offseason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Patriots already offered him a strong contract a few months ago, which he declined, with the story being his agent asking for him to be the #1 paid CB in the NFL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Washington is sitting back....twiddling their thumbs and watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 34 and hate the direction xv and the vii remake are going combat-wise, and I also disagree with you whole heartedly with how you feel about ffxii. And thats ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omfg bro.....I am fairly certain I had a light heart attack when I saw this title.......Jesus I am still shaking. 

Dont ever do this to me again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even have to be told. I guess I'm lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [2014 version](http://www.military.com/daily-news/2014/12/18/congress-again-buys-abrams-tanks-the-army-doesnt-want.html) of essentially the same article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about that one, yeah you are right, I will ammend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's simple math. Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this is obviously an *opinion* thread, so in mine, here is my list (skipped a couple systems):

NES: Final Fantasy

SNES: Chrono Trigger

SEGA GENESIS: Shining Force

PSX: Xenogears

N64: Ogre Battle 64

SEGA CD: Lunar: The Silver Star Story

GAMECUBE: Tales of Symphonia

DREAMCAST: Skies of Arcadia

SEGA SATURN: Shining Force III

PS2: Dragon Quest VIII

WII: Xenoblade Chronicles

XBOX: Star Wars Knights of the Old Republic (shit system for RPGs, so had to pick this game even though its on a multitude of platforms)

XBOX360: Tales of Vesperia

PS3: Legend of Heroes: Trails of Cold Steel II

Wii U: Xenoblade Chronicles X

XBOXONE: Scalebound (lol)

PS4: Tales of Berseria 



edit: dont know what I was thinking adding KOTOR, its not even a JRPG, lol. Fuck Xbox.

edit: changed N64 from "hahaha" to Ogre Battle because I forgot about it until reminded in reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well McDaniels said just a couple months ago that he chose to stay in New England because its the best fit for him and he loves it here. Bob Kraft responded to it with "We will definitely remember that".

I think it is highly more likely McDaniels is our HC after BB leaves than it is he leaves and trades for JG next season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure we were ever brigaded harder than we were at halftime of that game. It made it that much more satisfying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must not be a Patriots fan for very long if you think BB would sacrifice any part of his team whatsoever so one of his coaches could be more successful elsewhere.

I refuse to believe you actually think this is a possibility, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gambit system is one of my absolute favorite systems to be able to customize my experience. I absolutely love it. The closest thing I found to it was Tales of Hearts R on Vita. If you liked gambits, you should play that game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We aren't going to be remember for jack shit except destroying the Earth. *That* will be America's only real legacy in a few hundred years...if there is any civilization left at that point to remember it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if there is a config file you could go in and manually change the resolution. I have it on ps4 so I cant look to see if I could help you any further unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is literally perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it's me, a guy that specializes in game of throne house sigils carved into trees. Give me a call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There is no way in hell next year is my last year"

-Tom Brady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its fun to pretend though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure people know that werthers actually makes soft and chewy caramels in addition to their fossilized hard candies. They are fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is still a dick, I imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was like 37.....lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in New Hampshire, so I'm *very* close to New Orleans and Denver both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds amazing!! We just need to find a guy to pay for the other half now!! =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I ask is that you pay my entire way, and I'm there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god you sarcasm tagged that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yo man the party already happened you missed it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't wrong, though really, legitimately technically, neither was I :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food industry workers who would never eat the food produced for sale by your employer: Where do you work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ask the handler. "Sir, is that a bomb sniffing pup, or a drug sniffing pup? Im asking for a friend". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part about Marvin Lewis is that he is probably going to be the next Jeff Fisher. Once he is *finally* let go by Cincinatti after a few more playoff losses, he is going to do the exact same thing to another franchise or two afterwards. I wouldnt be able to contain my rage towards this guy if I were a Bengals fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure I will be the only person to say this, but, The Mothman Prophecies. 

Something about that movie gave me the chills more than any other. I think it was the combination of it being loosely based off true stories, and it's horror and suspense being created in your mind, rather than on the screen in front of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm disappointed in the way some people think the relationship is something that has been well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they attempted to alter Hades to their advantage but something fucked it up, like Sylens maybe. Fuck it, maybe Sylens actually IS one of these people and used Aloy to fix the problem he and his buddies created. Wouldnt be surprised if half the things he told her were lies, or he left out the most important information, like where he came from before joining the eclipse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 3-4 seasons of Lost is some of the best TV ever made. Get upset at how it ended, or some questions not being answered afterwards all you want, but to say watching those seasons was a waste of time says it all about your "tastes" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be wrong, but I dont think so. I remember listening to one of the datapads where someone was talking about how they wish they were one of the people on the ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am  very curious about the masters who woke up hades that sylens mentions. I think it would be really cool if the ship that we were told exploded while trying to leave the solar system actually survived.

Then, for hundreds of years, generations of humans live and die on the ship, until they get word earth's atmosphere is back.

Maybe after a few hundred years on a ship, these humans went a little crazy and want to take back their planet from the "fake" cloned humans currently.on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this was a life changing post for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very good show. One of the only good ones on syfy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first game that I read every piece of lore I found in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cost for PSNOW really isnt that bad, IMO. 50 bucks for 3 months. When you spend more than 50 for a single brand new game, it makes sense to me. 

I have been very happy with the service, and there are a ton of JRPGs on there.

edit: man....the absolutely retarded downvotes on this sub lately have been such a turn off. I have been here for years now and I have really noticed a change lately...like an influx of children or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell is the point of this post? Honestly, please tell me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Titsack  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time I managed to get off with my left hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ONLY* a porno! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just stopping by for the thumbnail

edit: She is Diana Russini and [here is a gif of her getting doused by water doing a split](http://giphy.com/gifs/lead-van-dammes-13tcr2LNcoiU3S) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an insane comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 hours Into Firis and only just realized you can fast travel to landmarks as well as camp fires. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if true, I imagine it's much more frustrating dealing with the pats, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't one of those cute shitposts. This is the real deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op doesn't f5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love this kid so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [https://media.giphy.com/media/RpV3QJUNDLPAA/giphy.gif](https://media.giphy.com/media/RpV3QJUNDLPAA/giphy.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I just responded to someone else, I made it 6 seasons without ever cringing at anything. 

I have cringed about 10 times this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. TWD for a number of years was something that was a major part of my life. It was one of the few times a week I would be social and gather with people to do something together, in this case watch a show. 

I considered it one of the best shows on TV for many many years. 

What I have seen it become over the last couple years really does bother me, yes. Am I taking this more seriously than other people? Of that I have no doubt. 

What frustrates me as much as the show, are how some fans, such as yourself, seem like you have a duty to defend it and its decisions at all cost. 

Of all the events that have taken place in TWD's story, Rick and Michonene together seems like the one that is the most *obviously* poorly done. 

I had never cringed at this show once until some of their scenes, mostly the ones this season. 

It is awkward, forced, and poorly written....and if fans would just own up to it and  admit it, instead of defending it, maybe we could get some change and get our show back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only reason I still watch. Andrew Lincoln might be my favorite actor in the world, and he keeps me tuned in, despite the fact that I often fall into fits of rage at how his character is written. He does such a good job for having such horrendous dialogue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because its garbage now. A shadow of what it once was. Gimple has completely destroyed the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what it meant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ. This sub is a lost cause along with this show now. After 7 years of defending it tooth and nail, I am done. I cant believe people on this sub think it works. Its fucking mindblowingly bad and you cant understand how people could think it? fucking lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just enjoy it. The story remains just as epic in 2 and 3, if not more so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got counseling! What a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone will look like that against the greatest rebounding team of all time, the 2016-2017 Boston Celtics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Draymond Green  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOK AT THESE BEAUTIFUL REBOUNDING MOTHERFUCKERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Draymond Green is the biggest piece of shit in professional sports </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT THE FUCK NO FUCKIUNG WAY FUCKING SUSPEND THIS PIECE OF SHIT WSROPFJSDGLKNSLKJGSDGHSGHSGSGSGGS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LLLLLLAAAALALALALALALA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IM ROCK HARD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey its me your ghost's, ghost's former college roommate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly pity you that your small brain cannot comprehend that there just may be a lot more things that women have to deal with health-wise than men do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what the ff series should have done years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know why its so hard for you to understand. When we were down by 19 points, we needed 2 TDs, 2 conversions, and a FG to tie. Straight up. 

You dont get to pick and choose exactly WHICH conversion counts as the one that was needed because of the missed extra point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only people who havent finished the game yet think this is DLC not a sequel =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your grandma is a special lady!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendo has seen the light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant wait till the day he actually uses the defense: "Look, I lie quite a bit. How can you blame me for not keeping track of so many of them? Ok? I'm only human. I'm only human. You people just want to destroy me." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hold him personally responsible,  but I certainly hold him professionally responsible. If it was sporadic and not more frequent in important games, I'd have no issue, but it has become a pattern that has lasted through two playoffs and an entire regular season. Even then, I'm willing to give him another try, but if nothing changes, I'd want him gone by midseason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kudos! This had the investigative quality of a Ted Wells case!! Take my upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty easy to not hold that extra point against him when we won, lol. Imagine if we missed the Second 2 point conversion? It would have been 2 years in a row we miss out on overtime in the playoffs because of missed extra points by our kicker. He's getting off light because we won, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the only game other than the last of us to feel more like an experience than a game to me. One of the best games I've ever played. I beat it yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are losing Bennett and possibly Amendola. We will need a couple guys who can catch the ball. He is a good deal if its very cheap. If its not very cheap, then yeah, I wouldnt want him either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was with you until you mentioned Horizon. Nothing about that was a hack and slash approach I dont know what you are talking about. I know you werent being negative about the game, but I dont see what you were trying to say there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know how *exciting* it would be for people, but I def can see him getting cut at the end of camp. Hopefully he'd pick up the playbook and excel though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lets get Jim Brown back to play some RB too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. And the gameplay that made the franchise successful. How have the games been recieved since ffx when they switched systems? All of them were recieved much more negatively than their predecessors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing it first has no impact on being upset at it being an action game. I like action games, I'm sure I will have fun playing the remake, but it's not what I wanted for this game and that is not going to change after playing it, whether I love it or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't akin to fcebook changing their feed appearance, but changing the platform entirely.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't ever remember a president talking so much shit about a previous president in my entire life. If anyone had reason to, it was Obama after the mess he inherited, but he never spoke of gwb with anything but respect, and that is just ONE of the differences between him and trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this have to be about me rejecting change and not about SE just making a new IP if they want to make action rpgs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit you are right!!!! I am embarrassed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully it's pliable as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. There is zero element of strategy any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a few hours until Firis is unlocked on Steam!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time posting/visiting this sub, as it has only been recently that I have gotten majorly into this series. 

I have a tendency to avoid pictures and gameplay of games when possible, but today in my excitement I checked out some info on what to expect in Firis, and I am blown away before even playing it. 

Its bigger, has a giant connecting zone instead of the old overworld map,  has many varied locations with bigger focuses on exploration...

There are weapons and SUB WEAPONS for each party member (sounds awesome!!)

Really though, it just LOOKS amazing. It really looks like the levels are from a real, high production value JPRG. 

Cant fuckin wait to load this up later!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explain to me why many other games are still made today that arent action based then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does everything have to be fucking action!!!!!!!! Aaaagggggghhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can juggle while performing heart surgery!!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eddie Royal is probably the more likely WR to end up on the Patriots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of talk about Cooks and Marshall, and while I'm not saying neither is def gonna happen, it's not likely. 

Royal was released and I think he is the prototypical type of vet wr who could come in and be more productive for us than he would be for any other team. And he won't cost much. 

I know it's not the sexiest idea, but it makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking A...its so weird seeing the Celtics listed with that group. I'd love to get used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the Atlanta Falcons blew a 28 point lead?

edit: 25 point lead. /shame  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know how we have the deepest team in the NBA while simultaneously having the NBAs worst player in Tyler Zeller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how the fuck did crowder miss that junior high layup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not that we needed the game companies, its that we needed (need) nintendo to be willing to work with outside developers better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
