<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1922</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veteran police officer, gunman dead after confrontation in Holladay, Utah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 01:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 21:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of ISIS's victims are Muslims. It's ignorant to think that they only hate America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 21:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  All us non-Muslims are why ISIS wants to destroy America

That's not true. They are willing to kill anyone who doesn't support them, Muslim or non-Muslim. Most of ISIS's victims are Muslims btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 18:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, the U.S. department of Justice should not be blamed

Correct, because they don't support sexual assault.   It doesn't matter how many Americans commit sexual assault,  because they still won't support their actions and shouldn't be blamed because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to ignore my question, then i don't see a reason to respond to your copypasta from an Islamophobic website.

So, should we blame the U.S. Department of Justice for supporting sexual assault? Yes or no?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 18:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If there's thousands committed by a group of people of which there are 10,000, and thousands committed by a group of people of which there are 10,000,000, then there is an issue with the first group

Then there is an issue with the criminals of BOTH groups. And i'm still waiting for your answer to my question.

 There are thousands of sexual assault cases each year in America. Should we blame the U.S. Department of Justice for supporting these actions? Why or why not. Hint: It has nothing to do with population size or number of criminals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still didn't get my point which was very simple. Either that or you are purposefully ignoring it.

Example: There are thousands of sexual assault cases each year in America. Should we blame the U.S. Department of Justice for supporting these actions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 17:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We do blame christianity when the leaders of the church molest children too

Then you would be wrong about that too.  Why would you blame Christianity? Does Christianity advocate for sexual molestation?  Sexual crimes are found throughout the world, regardless of race or religion. It's not just Christians or Muslims who have committed of these crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 16:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's okay to have bb and airsoft guns that look like just like real guns, but it's not okay to paint nerf guns like op's picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 15:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding? That got a ton of media attention which is again how you know about the story in the first place.  And why should a religion be blamed for something religion condemns? Should we blame Christianity for all the pedophiles out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 14:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying its impossible for people to want to limit free speech? Because that's certainly not true.  Like I said, people can choose not to allow insults and penalize those who insult the government.  It's like how people have limited free speech in their jobs in the West, you'll get fired if you say something racist for example.  You may also get fired if you publicly say something bad about the company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 07:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what if another country chooses to limit free speech to prevent insulting the government?  Maybe the Chinese are more bothered by these insults than we are here in the West and so they choose not to allow them.  Why is it bad if they want to run their government differently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taiwan must abandon 'hallucination' of independence, warns Chinese media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 06:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 05:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see this with color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 05:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been to China so i don't pretend to know what's good for the people there. It's pretty ethnocentric to think that the type of government system in your homeland must be the best for everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 05:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every city has some problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is Alan Rickman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why else would you be repeating the experiment? What are you trying to prove? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We're all just people trying to get by. We have plenty of common ground. We all want our families to be safe, we all have friends and things we enjoy and don't enjoy.

That response may be good but do you really think it would be effective on r/worldnews?

 Yeah, we're the backwards ones, when [inset comment about the American government/western culture here]

I wouldn't say that because it doesn't address the problem,   Instead I might say something like how "we shouldn't blame all of America because some Americans commit crimes, so it's not right to generalize for Muslims either". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so you're trying to find what races are inherently evil by this experiment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  More than a thousand were involved in the NYE incident in Kln alone. Is that what you call "a few"?

According to some reports, many of those guilty were NOT migrants and not all of those people were committing sexual assault. But whatever, let's generalize only for migrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 01:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We repeated the experiment about 5 times in 3 different countries, all the same result.

Why would you keep repeating this social experiment if it bothered you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they don't get covered up, which is why we constantly hear about it. Also, if an immigrant commits rape, why should Islam be blamed when Islam prohibits these actions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, we would blame the mafia because they approve of his action. Similarly if an ISIS attack happens, we should blame ISIS. Don't blame Muslims for ISIS, blame ISIS for ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 23:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refugees who commit crimes should be penalized or deported, but we shouldn't blame all refugees for the actions of a few. I am with Alan Rickman on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 23:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a general post, i'm not specifically talking about terrorist attacks. 

 When John commits a crime yelling "Praise God, Die all of you non-believers," then surely his faith is also blamed. 

It would depend. Does John's religion actually encourage him to do this crime?  Or is John too emotional because his family was killed and decides to attack in vengeance, hoping God approves of his action? If the latter, then religion shouldn't be blamed if religion condemns John's action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why not address an issue that is killing innocent women and children world wide?

That's not what i meant.  Obviously the issue of killing innocent civilians should be addressed and we should definitely do something to prevent further harm, but we shouldn't blame something or some group that is not responsible for such harms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama declares emergency in Flint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 21:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 20:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are referring to concubines, which is also basically a marriage and is discussed in the FAQ. This also has nothing to do with the recent crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The difference is that isnt happening weekly and all around the world.

Frequency makes no difference. If a belief system condemns an action, then the belief system shouldn't be blamed when the action is done. 

 but 99.9% of terrorist attacks globally are committed by Muslims. 

That's not true at all. Sure, in our times, Most terrorist attacks can be considered to be by Muslims but if you learn just a little bit of history then you'll know that this isn't a Muslim dominated crime.

http://www.start.umd.edu/gtd/globe/index.html

If you go back in time 20 years ago, would you still be making this argument? I highly doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you can agree with me. So where are all these /r/islam regulars who make this mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mistake, ok here is a typical comment that got 100 points, how would you respond to it.

*"Islam and islamic culture is totally backwards compared to the first world. I don't want an influx of muslims in my country if they won't integrate"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Abdullah commits a crime, and incorrectly thinks that Islam supports the crime, then Abdullah should still be blamed.   Just like how we can't blame Christianity for the Christians that attack abortion clinics, thinking God approves of their actions. 

lol, funny how you're trying to make it seem as if modern violent Muslims groups are bigger than they are. But the fact is still that 99.9% of Muslims don't commit violent acts. And we have spoken about how these terrorist groups form and why they attack in dozens of other topics, go check them out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say you had an unfair comment. I asked how i could improve my post and make it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that you shouldn't blame an entire group for the actions of a few when the group is against those actions.  Can you accept this now?

Yeah, if you can find examples of /r/islam regulars who make this mistake, i'd like to see it and have a word with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 18:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yet it seems to be only muslims?

No. We hear about it mostly from Muslims in the last few years, but study a bit of history and you'll see that this can occur in other groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 18:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish more people would take the time to read long thorough, well articulated responses from Muslims, but the fact is many people won't take the time to do that.

 That just antagonises people. 

I could have had a better title, but practically any criticism could be regarded as antagonizing.  I didn't think this post was unfriendly or sarcastic when posted and it was posted in /r/islam to a generally Muslim audience and not /r/worldnews after all. Perhaps you could show me how you would respond when Islam gets criticized unfairly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 18:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sooo. who do we blame exactly

If Abdullah commits a crime, blame Abdullah. 

It's that simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 18:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you misunderstood the caption, and you happen to be one of them.... 

Here is a comment of yours from 6 days ago:

 the rape culture of islam codified in the quoran has been known for centuries a. Nevertheless the latest imigration/white guilt/ race baiting trends of the left has allowed this phenomenon to develop. And its only getting worse. Weirdly enough i can guarantee that a lot of these women woud have probably been the first ones to tell yuo how islamophobic and racist you are for being against islam. Oh well enjoyed getting raped. Because it will happen in increasing numbers and the race baiting culture the left has created will shelter the rapists. Keep in mind that the leaders of the child rape gangs in the UK were yelling to the judge that he is islamophobic for convicting them for rape of children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 17:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people who visit those subs also visit r/islam, and some Muslims visit those subs, and then you have the occasional topic on here like "why do Muslims do these things" or "what does Islam say about this incident"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 17:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And when Catholic priest Luigi rapes a boy, Christianity is to blame.

No, Christianity is NOT to be blamed, unless Christianity advocates  those kind of actions (which it doesn't).

 When an Atheist murders Muslims, Atheism is to blame.

Atheism doesn't get blamed.

 When a Muslima in hijab gets mistreated in France, the French are to blame.

No, they aren't to blame either. 

 Somehow, nobody here contests that. I wonder why.

Maybe because we don't say those things.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 17:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just r/worldnews, it's a lot of other subreddits as well. Maybe it's not the best post to make, but i think a simple rebuttal to all the attacks on reddit recently can be a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Doesn't Islam(you can correct me here) teach that whenever a woman doesn't cover up, it is considered slutish? I remember arguing with someone here that women in the west are all begging for attention so much that they are considered slaves for that.

Except Islam doesn't teach that.  Men cannot have any sexual contact with women outside marriage and are told to lower their gaze.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 16:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The picture above is general, you are talking about something specific.

 assuming you mean a Muslim, does claim Islam as being responsible for his attack. 

What attack are you talking about? Where does the Muslim say "Islam is responsible for the attack" and where is the proof that Islam would support such an action? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is /r/worldnews/. Don't expect people to care about informed opinions about an issue when the usual suspects are blamed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/worldnews logic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 16:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The box that cereal comes in is useless.  Its just more to recycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 17:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monopoly is a lot like real life.  The banker usually ends up winning somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 10:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the teacher a Muslim?  Wearing a hijab doesn't make someone a Muslim.  Many Christian women in the past wore veils like Muslims today, including Mary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, atheism is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 22:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article barely says anything. Let's not jump to conclusions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 05:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how all these exMuslims keep surviving apostasy and are here to tell us about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 04:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all salafis are like that but I have noticed a fair amount of younger salafis in the West to be that way. I feel like these Muslims would be a lot better off living in Saudi Arabia. It's important to know what time and place you are in, and its also important to get a decent halal job.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 18:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The content of /r/exmuslim is basically this](http://i.imgur.com/hmXR0Zr.png)

I expected it to be like a supportive sub for ex-Muslims and how to deal with leaving Islam and the struggles involved. Topics like,  how to deal with Muslim family members, what to do during Ramadan, or discussions about meetups or moving on to living a secular life.  There were a few topics like that on there, but it's mostly just complaining about Islam or what some Muslims do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 14:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or ditches sex for masturbation to porn. 

A lot of married men will at times masterbate to porn instead of sex, and this bothers the spouse.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 14:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the classic definition of rape was about penetration (by penis).  The modern definition is far more broad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 21:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted in /r/worldnews 

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/3x4h8u/muslim_in_a_hijab_victim_of_violent_islamophobic/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim in a hijab victim of violent Islamophobic attack on a London bus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 21:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, i hear a lot of talk about reviving the caliphate or global Muslim unity, but even before we do any of that, we need to work locally on building bridges and means for open and respectable dialogue between different masajid and Muslim groups. We're already divided enough here in America and it's time to find common ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're still surprised that isis exists and that it has supporters living in Western lands today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? There is nothing wrong with questioning 9/11 or any other attack, especially when the evidence doesn't add up. The problem is when you assert things without proof.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is just questioning things. Nothing wrong with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do so many people get surprised when attacks like this happen? Britain's Parliament just approved of airstikes a couple of days ago and ISIS has been at war for a while now. People die at wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As Muslims living in the West, we shouldn't think that we aren't going to be tested. We have to struggle and be patient with our neighbors, some of whom now consider us all to be terrorists. We have to be forbearing with any backlash from our community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do people think that they will be left alone because they say: "We believe," and will not be tested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common words pronounced that badly? Soo-nAAA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She makes a ton of mistakes in this video including mispronunciation of some basic words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Found this video posted in r/videos](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/3vfhoi/the_holy_quran_experiment/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Holy Quran Experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 00:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 51 votes, only 3 points right now. 

Not sure if this is normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posted in /r/worldnews and /r/news.  People need to know how common these attacks are.

https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/3v23gx/muslim_cab_driver_shot_in_back_by_passenger/

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/3v237p/muslim_cab_driver_shot_on_thanksgiving_by/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim cab driver shot in back by passenger 'ranting about Isis' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim cab driver shot on Thanksgiving by rifle-wielding Islamophobe ranting about ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of question often leads to a debate, so you may want to ask your local Imam. The situation in France is different than the situation in other countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 23:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned about their religion. They don't tell you a lot at first, but when you dig deep, you can see how unorthodox their beliefs are. [Here's a sample](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/1vltgo/some_questions_for_the_ahmadiyya_community/).

I recommend watching this Muslim's videos on Ahmadiyya:

https://www.reddit.com/r/Qadiani/comments/37ymyc/shahid_kamal_leaves_ahmadiyya_group_and_becomes_a/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Passerby attacks headphones-wearing Muslim student he suspected of taking orders from ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 23:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like i said, a 2-state solution isn't enough.  It almost seems like a joke because of what Israel is doing.

Gaza is under a chronic power shortage due to the siege; Israel has severely limited the fuel supply needed to operate the only power plant in the territory. Only 46 per cent of Gaza's electricity needs are being met currently; this has triggered rolling power outages of 12 hours everyday. Amongst other things, this lack of power means that hundreds of crucial medical devices at hospital are non-functional, including Gaza's only MRI machine.


Israel's siege has meant that it is virtually impossible for Gazans to leave the occupied territory. They can't even leave to visit their relatives in the West Bank, let alone in Israel. Gazans with spouses in Israel or the West Bank are forced to live in separation; simple matters such as raising a family are rendered impracticable. Permission to leave even for severe emergencies is rarely given.

By dividing Palestinians, Israel successfully employs the 'divide and conquer' strategy like colonial powers of the past. The people of Gaza can't even seek asylum in other countries due to this restriction on movement. Even students are prohibited from going abroad, or even the West Bank, for higher education; visas of several winners of U.S. Fulbright Scholarships have been revoked in the past.

The Israeli army conducts weekly incursions into the Gaza Strip to destroy the land it has declared as 'no-go zone.' Its tanks, bulldozers and military jeeps, accompanied by helicopters and drones, systematically destroy fruit bearing trees and agricultural land in the Gaza strip. Civilian infrastructure in this area is also demolished; this includes hundreds of houses, wells and chicken farms  mosques and schools are demolished as well.

The Israeli army created a 'no-go zone' along the Israel-Gaza border that Palestinians cannot enter. This 'buffer region' extends up to 1,500 meters at times into the Strip and includes some of its most fertile land. As a result, 35 per cent of the agricultural space in Gaza is off-limits to farmers. This has seriously damaged the food economy and harshly penalized innocent farmers. Palestinians are fired at arbitrarily if they try to enter this region; farmers suffer serious injuries, and at times death, as a result of this indiscriminate firing.

Israel has announced that access to the sea six nautical miles beyond Gaza's shore is prohibited for fisherman. This means that 85 per cent of fishing waters granted to Palestinians under the Oslo Accords is now inaccessible; this has severely impacted Gaza's coastal economy. Similar to the restricted areas on land, Palestinian fishermen are regularly exposed to warning fire by Israeli naval forces, their fishing boats are intercepted and they are detained  all for the harmless act of fishing.

This is a short list of the some of the unspeakable crimes Israel commits on a defenseless population; they are at the root of this conflict. Rocket attacks from Gaza are a desperate response to these injustices  how does our government manage to omit this when brazenly expressing support for Israel ?  In light of the above, let's try to counter some of the nonsense coming out of the foreign affairs office: No people would ever tolerate an oppressive occupation and an unjust siege, so why should the Palestinians?

Of 1.5 million people living in Gaza, 1.2 million are registered refugees spread across eight camps. These refugees are made up of Palestinians, and now their decedents, who were expelled from present-day Israel in during the mass expulsion or Nakba in 1948. Since the newly created state of Israel denied the right of return to these refugees, they have been trapped in the refugee camps for the past 66 years. These refugee camps are overcrowded, cramped and under utter disrepair  unlivable by any standards.  Attempts to rebuild or renovate the camps have been restricted due to the siege. The humanitarian crisis in the camps is only magnified compared to the rest of Palestine; unemployment is high, food is scarce and fuel is scant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 22:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading something like this in the Bible too. I guess these kind of narrations would be controversial today because of how typical roles in a modern relationship would be different than the normative case in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 17:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, that's actually the excuse some Zionists use to claim that Israel belongs to the Jews.

I would be open to a 2-state solution, but Israel keeps doing stuff that makes this option very difficult for Palestinians. 

http://muslimmatters.org/2014/07/19/8-reasons-why-israel-is-under-rocket-attack/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Who looks like the terrorist here?](https://i.imgur.com/1Jscbaz.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 03:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be careful when you post a topic like this because it could lead to more harm. Harms like backbiting or pointless arguments or being crossposted to another sub, leading to more arguments.

 I wanted to comment on how frustrated I am that a movement that got a ton of traction turned out to be a PR stunt (if that's what it is).

Why are you assuming it was a PR stunt? A month ago, i've heard various theories on the internet like how he really intended to bomb the school, or how his dad with the help of Obama orchestrated the whole thing to get sympathy from the media or how his sister also used a hoax bomb and they were just waiting for the media to give them attention. Now some people are saying that his plan was to make money the whole time. But all of these theories are based on speculation, not facts.  

- It wasn't a briefcase, it was a pencil case.

- We have no idea how much he actually tinkered with his project, people were just speculating based on a single picture. 

- His sister never brought a hoax bomb to school, she was just in trouble for a different reason years ago. 

- No proof that father is still running for president.

- Ahmed's engineering teacher really did have an assignment for him. 

- Ahmed really did show his clock to his engineering teacher before getting in trouble with another teacher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 03:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why post it here then? It has nothing to do with Islam.

 Apparently the clock he made was really just a store bought clock that was disassembled and had the components placed in a briefcase.

No. A lot of people on reddit came up with various conspiracy theories about how this 14 year old orchestrated this whole thing for his own gain. Most of the accusations are just speculation without proof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 06:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 23:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're also quoting from a Shia book that is biased against Sunni scholars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to historian Michael B. Oren, in his book Power, Faith, and Fantasy, Bartholdi would carve the likeness of an Egyptian peasant woman holding aloft a torch of freedom. The monument, twice as high as the Sphinx, would guard the waterways entrance and perhaps double as a lighthouse. Its name would be Egypt (or Progress) Bringing Light to Asia.

Thus, as the Daily Beasts Michael Daly pointed out on Wednesday, the nations symbol of all-American freedom and charity was in fact originally conceived as an Egyptian  and by default in those times, a Muslim.

For the next two years, Bartholdi worked on sketches and tried to persuade Ismail Pasha, the then-khedive (viceroy) of Egypt, to finance his project. But the viceroy was bankrupt by 1871 and in no condition to support a monument as large as two sphinxes.

This compelled a distraught Bartholdi to take solace in a cruise to America. As he sailed into New York harbor, he saw the egg-shaped Bedloes Island and started considering a new location for his majestic vision, imbued with new meaning.

Not long before, Bartholdi had a conversation with the French abolitionist and fervent supporter of the the North in the Civil War, douard Ren de Laboulaye, who proposed that France offer the United States a gift in recognition of the end of that conflict. After years of negotiation, it was decided that America would pay for the Statue of Libertys pedestal and France for the statue itself.

The dedication of the completed monument took place in October 1886. Oren describes the occasion in the following way:

 *The thousands of spectators who listened as President Grover Cleveland pledged not [to] forget that liberty here made her home gazed up at a creation that bore little resemblance to the one Bartholdi had visualized for Egypt. The Muslim peasant had been replaced by an idealized Western woman and the name of the piece changed from Bringing Light to Asia to Liberty Enlightening the World. Only the torch remained, unextinguished.*

 *Over the next forty years, Lady Liberty would provide millions of immigrants with their first glimpse of America, kindling their hopes for better lives and beckoning them with the possibility of freedom. For Egyptians, though, as for the many Middle Eastern peoples destined to come under foreign rule during that period, there would be no such illustrious symbols.*

So when politicians such as Ted Cruz suggest that only Christian Syrian refugees should be allowed to enter America, and critics respond with the ideals that the Statue of Liberty stands for, their statements have a particular historical resonance.

https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/morning-mix/wp/2015/11/19/americas-most-famous-statue-was-muslim-before-she-became-lady-liberty/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Statue Of Liberty Was Born A Muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 18:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And by saying this only applies to heathens of that lived then and there, then prayer only applies to Muslims who were talking to the prophet at the time he revealed the verse that demanded prayer

I'm not claiming that it only applies to one specific time. I'm saying that you have to know the context: People who broke the treaty and are at war with you.  This is the context which does not exist today for the Muslim world. A lot of verses from chapter 9 wouldn't apply today for the Muslims because the context is entirely different. 

If the Muslim world supposedly did establish a caliphate properly and if they did made a treaty with a non-Muslim nation, and if that non-Muslim nation did break that treaty, then you could argue that some of those verses from chapter 9 apply today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Context is important](https://i.imgur.com/R0xuMfQ.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who here is blaming French Jews for anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 05:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid it's going to be worse in France. Right after the Charlie Hebdo incident a year ago, there were over 50 anti-Muslim incidents reported in France in just 1 week (although most incidents were just vandalism). [Graph](http://tellmamauk.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/antimuslim-attacks-charlie-hebdo-II-final-resize.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 21:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a JSA in school is anything serious as you are making it out to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Peterborough, Ontario] Mosque deliberately set on fire, say police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 21:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Muslim Scholars Are Saying About The Paris Attacks. You might be surprised. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 02:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 22:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the attackers appears to have come in France along with refugees, but nothing is for certain right now. It is true that with the refugees coming in, there is going to be a slight increase in risk but that doesn't mean all refugees should be abandoned completely because of the actions of a few. Where else are they supposed to go? What European countries can do is have them go through rigorous security screenings and other additional security measures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Response to the Xenophobic Comments... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 20:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do terrorists attack? Muslim responds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 05:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 03:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shouldn't have recorded that. Now our secret space plans are out in the open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing panel discusses the struggles Muslim Converts go through </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 22:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 17:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good that you are restricting yourself from what might cause harm, as one narration says *"The world is a prison for a believer and Paradise for a non-believer"*.  But i think it's also critical for Muslims to still have a halal way to chill and enjoy life.  Maybe find a hobby, play sports, games, read books, etc.  Meet other Muslims to hangout with, try to find the right balance.  Take the [Fiqh of Chillin class](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=we1YiA6xutU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 02:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know countries like Saudi Arabia don't help the poor? Recently, Saudi Arabia was criticized by a lot of people in the West for not helping any Syrian refugees, when [the reality was that they had helped probably more than any European country](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/anhvinh-doanvo/europes-crisis-refugees_b_8175924.html).  Part of the problem is that people base their view on those countries based on some negative stories in the media. Saudi Arabia along with other Arab countries have a very bad image in American media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I only said that science agrees that paradox can exist because science can't explain paradox even though it exists.

What existing paradox are you talking about that science agrees that can exist? Science doesn't deal with paradoxes. 

 Logically possible in case of God, but not logically possible for us. 

Which is exactly why it's NOT a paradox.

 Paradox is logically possible for God

It was never a paradox for God to bring things into existence from nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No. Paradox is out of logic. That's what makes it "paradox".

Exactly. Paradox is against logic. Science has nothing to do with it.

 But the fact remains that Allah is capable of accomplishing stuff which are logically impossible. 

How is God bringing things into existence from nothing logically impossible?  I think you are confusing the scientific method with logic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 16:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But science testifies that paradox CAN exist. 

You mean logic, not science.

 In the end the Quran is the only living proof of Allah's existence and His wisdom.

That's not true. There is proof all around us about Allah.  And you haven't proven Allah is paradoxical. Someone can be merciful to those who ask forgiveness and seek vengeance to those who do not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you intentionally look for drama on this sub. We already told you that some did believe in Hell. The discussion should have been over. Please go be a troll somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 01:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some did say that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 23:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected it to be like a supportive sub for ex-Muslims and how to deal with leaving Islam and the struggles involved. Topics like,  how to deal with Muslim family members, what to do during Ramadan, or discussions about meetups or moving on to living a secular life.  There were a few topics like that on there, but it's mostly just complaining about Islam or what some Muslims do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sub cares way too much about what happens here.

[The content of /r/exmuslim is basically this](http://i.imgur.com/hmXR0Zr.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 03:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link is safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 22:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the atheist claimed certainty while having a methodology that says that you can't be certain about anything. It was a contradiction on his part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 21:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly the problem with the philosophy of the atheist in the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
