<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7666</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of it is that his death was so public. We knew it was coming. In a way, we were even hoping it would come, just on his terms. I really didn't expect it - with absolutely no medical justification, of course -- to come by surprise like that, so it was more shocking than it probably should have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry Pratchett. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon :)  There are a couple different ones there. This one is fairly basic, with an unfinished back, but it works perfectly for what I wanted (i.e., to freak out visitors). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked up an Eye of Agamotto replica prop and had enough odd things around the house to make a display for it. Had to buy the little easel it sits on, though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made an Eye of Agamotto display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Library books have been paid for, as has already been noted. But mostly it's a question of scale. Millions of people will not be reading that book at the same time; there's not much chance of a library copy of a book hurting the publisher's bottom line because even with a copy in every library in the world, there's only so many people who can borrow it at the same time. 

But when something is pirated and offered for download, millions of people can and do download it immediately and that can affect publishers. Spotify and Pandora and other streaming services at least pay the artists, even if not very much. 

Copyright issues aside, if it becomes easy to just take everything an artist creates, the only incentive for people to ever pay is because they want that artist to continue making more. Is that enough to sustain the art?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was what the [paramedics told the police, according to the police report](http://www.news-journalonline.com/news/20170215/police-disabled-daytona-veteran-beaten-by-suspects-accused-in-turtle-killing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Disabled Daytona veteran beaten by suspects accused in turtle killing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the original story this story is referencing.](http://www.news-journalonline.com/news/20170215/police-disabled-daytona-veteran-beaten-by-suspects-accused-in-turtle-killing) 

For those asking, the turtle was killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Tea, obviously. And a little honey.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is now my favorite closed-caption, ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he's said. He endorsed Clinton in 2016, but spoke with Trump after he won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly jokes that are expressly racist or sexist, such as Eric Bolling's "boobs on the ground" comment about UAEs first female fighter pilot, Mariam Al Mansouri or a [teacher giving a black colleague a KKK robe](http://www.koco.com/article/elk-city-ag-teacher-apologizes-for-racist-incident/4311046). Jokes about rape that make fun of the victim rather than the rapist. Jokes about poor or homeless people, or the victims of police brutality. 

Granted, there are plenty of left-leaning people also making such jokes -- Justin Bieber and Steve Harvey both had to publicly apologize recently for jokes about racist stereotypes -- but generally when I see what I'd consider right-wing jokes or memes I see a lack of empathy for anyone outside the joker's immediate groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great deal of humor I wouldn't characterize as either. We are all humans, and there's a lot of shared experience that applies to everyone.

When it's clearly partisan humor, I'd say look at the target of the joke. Are they punching up or punching down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite was when we went out for breakfast at a fast food place one Valentine's. I "forgot" my phone and ran back to the car while she ordered for us, and while she was waiting for our food I set up a table around the corner with a tablecloth, wine glasses, music playing, flowers and a candle. 

She laughed and we had a fun breakfast. The staff at the place loved it and took pictures. And the guys in the room were staring at me, like "Dude, you had to set the bar first thing in the morning?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best part of doing something incredibly romantic for my SO in public on Valentine's Day is the looks on the faces of all the guys around whose SOs are seeing me do it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, those poor people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually, because the people behind the desktop site didn't care enough about making a good mobile site and then suddenly everyone was spending more time on their phones and the companies were caught offguard.

Same reason so many desktop sites look so bad. The companies behind them don't care or don't think anyone else cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just coming to post this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's closer to what I'd consider fanfic. Most of the examples I hear in these kinds of questions aren't, to my eyes, fanfic, they're unsold stories from the original author. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, the pompous "if it's popular it can't be good" attitude is still prevalent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found autographed copies that way, most recently about four Jennifer Crusie paperbacks, with inscriptions.

I did pick up a used psychology textbook once which had a bonus 70s-era Polaoid picture of a very male, very naked man in it. I didn't think to check to see if it was marking any specific chapters... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of people across the world suffer from a lack of clean water and I'll get annoyed and walk away if the vending machine only offers Dasani </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing in one of the biggest losses in American electoral history. Unless, of course, the GOP gets all the voter suprression laws they're salivating for pushed through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want him gone, but I don't wish harm on him. First and foremost because I dont want to wish harm on anyone, but also because he would then become a martyr for his followers and I have no idea what the most extreme of them might do in response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [www.scarleteen.com](http://www.scarleteen.com/)

Comprehensive, common-sense sex education for teens (or anyone else) that doesn't talk down to them, doesn't condemn, doesn't preach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask me then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a counter to Schimmelhorn, check out Esther Friesner's "Chicks in Chainmail" series of short story collections, each one crammed with stories from writers a little tired of the female-warrior-in-the-chainmail-bikini trope.

One of the writers, Margaret Ball, had so much fun writing a story for one of the books that she wrote a whole novel on the subject, called "Mathemagics," where a fantasy warrior-woman came to this dimension so her kids could get a good education and had to learn how to deal with people here. Still has the sword, though... It's a light read but a fun one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I won't lose any sleep over it, but I don't feel any pleasure or satisfaction in his death, and I worry that people who feel the same way he did will point to people gleefully cheering it and use that as evidence that they are victimized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't celebrate anyone's death. 

Which may be one of the differences between me and him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently I just finished reading through the works of [T. Kingfisher](http://tkingfisher.com/), the pen-name Ursula Vernon uses for her non-children books. They tend to be fantasy retellings of fairy tale stories, with slightly more-on-the-ball people involved. Not humor books per se, but I smiled and laughed as I read them. Good "I need to relax my brain and enjoy the afternoon" books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asprin's "Myth" books are very pun-filled, but his Phule series isn't.

Robert Sheckley was the funny science fiction writer from the late 50s to the mid-70s. Some of it may read dated now, but he was definitely an inspiration to later funny writers.

Esther Friesner wrote mostly fantasy, usually (but not always) with a funny touch.

You could also try Reginald Bretnor's Schimmelhorn stories. There's a collection, "Schimmelhorn File," and a novel, "Schimmelhorn's Gold," about a Swiss inventor and scientific genius who makes the most bewildering, bizarre inventions and chases girls until his wife catches him. Sexist as hell, but funny.

Other books I've liked: "How to Live Safely in a Science Fictional Universe" by Charles Yu, Harry Harrison's Stainless Steel Rat series (great at the time, perhaps a little dated now, and don't read them in a row or they get repetitive, same for Keith Laumer's "Retief" books), John Scalzi's "Redshirts" (friends also like his Old Man's War series, I haven't tried it yet), "John Dies at the End" and "This Book Is Full of Spiders: Seriously, Dude, Don't Touch It" by David Wong, and. just to toss this in here. "The Princess Bride" by William Goldman. If you haven't read the book, even if you've seen the movie, read the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might try looking back a few decades. Robert Asprin's "Phule" series, anything by Robert Sheckley, any of Spider Robinson's short stories or Callahan books, half of Esther Friesner's work, "To Say Nothing of the Dog" by Connie Willis, the Red Dwarf books, even Poul Anderson's "The High Crusade" is based on a funny idea. 

You might also try comics. I'd put Warren Ellis' stuff up against any other funny sci-fi, especially "Transmetropolitan," "Planetary" and "Nextwave." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abandoning core concepts of what made the characters popular for decades only worked for a short time, too. I applaud them for taking chances and trying new things, and some of it worked, but too much of the New 52 was bleak and flat for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot do. This one doesn't. It was the annual "huge story that changes EVERYTHING oh and someone shocking dies" thing year after year after year that finally broke me of decades of following favorite characters. Now I tend to follow favorite writers and artists instead, and I favor self-contained stories that don't get yanked into whatever stupidity the editors thought of at the last retreat. 

I'm glad for the industry as a whole that people buy them and they bring in new readers, but after the tenth NOTHING WILL EVER BE THE SAME AGAIN event I'm just tired of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the first few minutes it wasn't working for me. I hadn't read about how they'd be doing it and the introduction of a fake Sir Terry was a little jarring. But very quickly I settled into it and enjoyed it. It is Terry's own words, after all, and Kaye did a very good impression of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, even using a VPN you're asked for a TV license. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any word on when or if it will make it to BBC America?

I may or may not have watched it anyway, but I'd like to be able to direct friends to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local comic shops are likely to have it, and local bookstores that carry graphic novels. Or you can order it at [Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/Superman-Secret-Identity-KURT-BUSIEK-ebook/dp/B00C54SVZ0/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1486878402 sr=8-1 keywords=superman+secret+identity) or [Comixology](https://www.comixology.com/Superman-Secret-Identity/digital-comic/48438?ref=c2VhcmNoL2luZGV4L2Rlc2t0b3Avc2xpZGVyTGlzdC90b3BSZXN1bHRzU2xpZGVy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember the Stop Online Piracy Act (SOPA) bill that, among other things, made ISPs liable for illegal content moved through their service? I'd expect to see something like that again. Also more copyright laws tied to trade agreements, requiring countries we do business with to adopt our copyright laws and penalties, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. With the business-friendly people currently in power, you will see all the draconian anti-pirating laws come rushing back, likely completely unchanged, with a much better chance of passage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a version of this could be really interesting if told well, like an AU Harry Potter in a more realistic setting, but I'd make it clear it was an AU and simply wouldn't bring the abandoned bits up at all, rather than disparaging them. Or, say, a kid who grew up reading Harry Potter suddenly discovering the *real* wizarding world, which has some big differences...

There was a DC miniseries called "Superman: Secret Identity" where a kid named Clark Kent, presumably in our world, was getting really tired of all the Superman jokes and gag gifts he got every year. And then he developed super powers... It was very well done, with a slightly more "realistic" direction to it, but because it wasn't trying to rationalize the actual original characters it didn't come off as condescending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I write every day, but not always on a large work.

I'd gotten out of the habit of writing when I let my interest in photography take over, but after a few years I realized I'd been missing it and wanted to begin again. So to get back into the habit, late last year I started posting pictures I'd taken accompanied by short stories the pictures inspired. I've managed to write something -- even if it's very short -- almost every day since then, posting them to my site and my social media sites. It's fun, and it's getting me antsy to try something longer again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree it's a bigger fact right now, after the commercial. But it's not the only reason. The book has been referenced for quite some time now, generally in response to Mike Pence as VP and what a Trumped Supreme Court is likely to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, because everything has exactly one answer. Oh, wait, are we talking in logical fallacies or not? I've lost track.

Yes, the upcoming show certainly has a large part in the increased sales of "Handmaid's Tale," but it's not the only reason. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like was a total unknown when he announced his candidacy. We knew what we were getting. 

Personally, I'd say he had been making us less safe long before that, by lending credence and staying power to the claim that Obama was not American. He helped undermine Obama's legitimacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Handmaid's Tale" was mentioned a lot by people who were more afraid of Mike Pence, or what a Supreme Court stocked by Trump might do. I heard it referenced quite a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember seeing a Super Bowl commercial for other recent unexpected bestsellers such as "1984" and "It Can't Happen Here." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  One of the great achievements of free society in a stable democracy is that many people, for much of the time, need not think about politics at all. The president of a free country may dominate the news cycle many days  but he is not omnipresent  and because we live under the rule of law, we can afford to turn the news off at times. A free society means being free of those who rule over you  to do the things you care about, your passions, your pastimes, your loves  to exult in that blessed space where politics doesnt intervene. In that sense, it seems to me, we already live in a country with markedly less freedom than we did a month ago. Its less like living in a democracy than being a child trapped in a house where there is an abusive and unpredictable father, who will brook no reason, respect no counter-argument, admit no error, and always, always up the ante until catastrophe inevitably strikes. This is what I mean by the idea that we are living through an emergency.
-- Andrew Sullivan, "[The Madness of King Donald](http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2017/02/andrew-sullivan-the-madness-of-king-donald.html)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know  So, where are the upcoming shows for the other recent new bestsellers, "1984" and "It Can't Happen Here"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear is the mindkiller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An unconstitutional law that only lasts three months is still a unconstitutional law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly humor and ridicule seem to be the only way to get his attention. Millions of people marching are no big deal or he says they were paid to do it. He blows off any criticism and says "everyone" supports him. He does what he wants to do, even when it's not thought out or explained and even unconstitutional. 

But he cannot STAND to have his image questioned. He hates implications that he is not as rich as he says, he hates anything that threatens his alpha image (small hands), he hates anything that he thinks makes his staff look weak. It's been months since the election, he is the president of the United States, and he can't stop talking about how much he won and how many people were at the inauguration, even whipping up 3-5 million of illegal votes out of thin air without the slightest bit of evidence because he can't accept that he lost the popular vote.

The GOP is largely lockstep behind him. The Dems do not have the strength or, too often, the nerve to stop him. He seems to be systematically diminishing the worth of the media in investigating him (at least to his followers) and he clearly has no respect for the judicial system and I fully expect changes to come so that he can't be blocked again. 

Marches and protests and humiliation are pretty much our only weapons until the mid-terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Previous bans were on specific groups of people coming from known high-risk areas, for a limited time, based on a recent occurrence, and even then people were let in if they passed evaluation. 

This ban is against seven countries that have not been implicated in terrorist crimes in the U.S. and ignores several countries whose countrymen have. And there no exceptions for people with green cards or people who have passed the extensive vetting already in place. 

Basically because it was a sloppily-written, too-vague law that seems less designed to protect the country and more to keep out members of a specific religion whether they're legally allowed to come here or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. Whenever cases make it to court Trump just settles anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'm pointing out racism? How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [@subject7666](http://www.instagram.com/subject7666)

I photograph pretty people, fire, local musicians, and other cool things.

I also post pics and some tiny stories they inspire, but Instagram isn't always kind to paragraphs and hates quotation marks, so sometimes that works better than other times :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not like it's a tough thing to call.

The White House doesn't seem to care about violent attacks from pale people. None of them appear on their list of 78 terror attacks they say the press has underreported -- interesting news to the many news sites that covered many of them exhaustively, including a local TV news station that won an Emmy and one paper that won a Pulitzer for their coverage of some of the listed attacks -- and the task force charged with investigating all terror and hate groups has been repurposed to only look at Muslims. Hateful white terrorists are, apparently, no big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prediction: if they are associated with the protesters they will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law.

If they turn out to be white Trump supporters the investigation will be quietly dropped, possibly after a word from higher up, and the story will disappear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My usual problem with Gaiman books: I want to listen to him reading them, but don't want to wait that long to finish them.

I got the Kindle and Audible copies, and alternate between listening in the car and reading when I can. I may have a problem... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same. The one saving grace in that episode was "Up yours, children!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the look you want. 

Me, I shave along the top, on my cheeks, because growth is sparse there and I like it neater. I also shave the two spots under my bottom lip, same reason.

The rest of it I had been keeping trimmed but since Thanksgiving I've let it go to see what I get, only trimming loose flyaway hairs every now and then when they won't behave. I add some beard oil and don't shampoo it too often and so far it at least looks intentional :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/beards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A tie between the shows that revealed the pasts of the principal and Ned Flanders. Messed up both charatcers for me.

Stopped watching soon after, for these and many other reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has no experience in any level of public education. 

She has worked for decades to promote the diversion of taxpayer dollars to go to private, religious and for-profit schools without requirements for accountability. 

She does not support the Individuals With Disabilities Education Act, Title IX, or other public education iniatives. 

She has singled out education reform as a way to advance Gods kingdom." 

She has contributed to many groups with the goals of bringing religion and creationism back to public schools. 

She has financial dealings with several educational programs of dubious worth that she can now strike deals with.

So much more.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, parents. Or just people worried about public education in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I expect is what we got.

What I'd like is for President Trump to reveal his taxes and show that he has no current financial ties or obligations to Russia. I'd settle for him to treat other countries -- Mexico, Australia, the European countries -- with the same deference he gives Putin instead of worshipping him and insulting everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, Haley did say that. That doesn't mean Trump believes it -- several people in his cabinet have said things contrary to things Trump has said. 

Trump has been belligerent to *everybody*, enemies and allies alike. That doesn't get him any points with me.

It is true that Trump has repeatedly praised Putin, talked about how strong and effective a leader he is. He has talked about weakening or abandoning NATO, which would greatly benefit Putin. A disturbing number of his cabinet and close advisors past and present have financial ties to Russia. He had flatly refused to condemn any of Putin's actions, dancing around the question whenever it has been raised. He has fought hard to minimize accusations of Russia influence on our most recent election.

Trump may not have anything to do with Putin, and Putin may have nothing on him. But Trump has not done even the easiest, most obvious ways to dissociate himself from Putin and I think it bears further examination. Also, ridicule.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Dance Article] 10-year-old dancer breaks out some moves at a hoops game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more I think about it, I think "Lexicon" is more appropriate for Trump, but the rest of the GOP is reading "Jennifer Government." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love the Super Bowl commercials every year but I don't think I've ever made a purchase based on one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, but I'm just happy they put anything there.

Also, it's a book about the power of language, and in the new world of alternate facts and doublespeak I think's it's appropriate. Maybe not as much as "Jennifer Government" would have been, but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone comes up with a one-syllable word everyone likes better than "phone."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would cheer me to know that the real Australian prime minister reads Max Barry, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL took pains to put an Australian SF book on their Prime Minister's book shelf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do read over 200 books a year and have for many years now. It may take me a week or more to get through a dense or complicated work, especially non-fiction, and I may burn through lighter fiction at the rate of one a day, but I average out more than 200. (I tend to read sentences at a time, and I read at breaks, at lunch, in waiting rooms, way too late in the evenings, etc. As obsessions go it's a fairly harmless one.)

And yet I also spend some time on social media chatting with friends, catching up on the news and seeing what's going on. Perhaps the author of the piece needs help managing their time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have been happier if it was in the right order but it did get me to stop and laugh as I was walking by the parking lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, nice. I couldn't think of one :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wise advice from Aaron Burr's dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally, something good on TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a few days, I can say that it's mostly fixed the problem. About 8 times out of 10, deleting an email now drops me down to the next email. But occasionally it doesn't, and I haven't identified what triggers it yet. Still, better than it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought up the term "apatheist" to describe my attitude toward religion -- don't know, don't care -- and was set to tell people about it when I checked online and saw it had been around awhile and there was already a website selling merch. And this was back in the Yahoo/Excite/Ask Jeeves days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This afternoon, when I read that people on Facebook were marking themselves "safe" during the Bowling Green Massacre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO. My first born is 32, he can pull his own ass up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's written and spoken extensively about screenwriting, both the process and the business of it, on his website and in his podcast Scriptnotes with his buddy Craig Mazin. 

Even if you don't like his writing, the podcast is extremely useful and answers a lot of questions new screenwriters never think to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't recall seeing any quotes from him that I'd consider either Nazi or fascist. 

However, he has written and said many things that are *also* believed by white supremacists and would-be fascists, and because he's gay, Jewish and dates a black man they embrace him whole-heartedly because he makes their side look marginally less white-male. 

Milo is very [anti-feminist](http://www.breitbart.com/milo/2016/10/07/full-text-milo-feminism-auburn/), [very anti-BLM](http://www.breitbart.com/milo/2016/12/13/milo-black-lives-matter-last-socially-acceptable-hate-group/), and [very anti-Islam](http://www.breitbart.com/milo/2016/09/27/10-things-milo-hates-islam/), and he delights in poking at people he feels are too sensitive until they react. He's a self-described troll. Personally, I think he'd have been hugely disappointed if last night had gone smoothly and he'd given his talk with no drama or news coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this very morning I finished reading ["Summer in Orcus"](http://www.redwombatstudio.com/portfolio/summer-in-orcus/) by T. Kingfisher, which is not only a portal story but it includes a young antagonist who has read other portal stories and occasionally uses that information to guide her actions. Great book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that did it! I'll want to try it for a few days but so far it seems to have fixed my problem. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agent Coulson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Web interface, Chrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I delete emails, how do I control what happens next? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use GMail for home and for work, and often I'll have tons of email to go through. And it drives me crazy. This may be tough to explain, but...

I read email A and need to keep it so I click on Email B. Email B I delete, and suddenly I'm back at email A again. I move down to email C, delete, and I'm back at A.  Every time I delete one, the focus goes back up one. But then I skip down to Email E and delete that, and now the focus moves down to Email F. Instead of the focus moving up, it moved down. Sometimes it goes one way, sometimes the other, and if I go too fast I end up deleting emails I wanted to keep. 

Assuming that makes any sense, is there any way to control this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. I'm fine with any pairing, combination, or what-have-you provided you don't have to change the character's personality to make it work. Once you do that I've lost any interest in reading it because you're not writing about the characters I fell in love with anymore.

(Again, nothing against those who enjoy it. Just not for me.)

Now if you can write a wild, AU story and still keep the characterizations, motivations, etc. consistent with the original, I'd be a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what you mean by making sense. If a pairing could come about by a slightly different turn in history -- this character met that one first, instead of this other one, and everything else progressed as you'd expect -- no worries and some of the ones I've read are amazing. I'm gender-neutral as far as pairings, I can see anyone with anyone *provided you don't have to change the character's personality to make it work*. Once you do that, as far as I'm concerned you've lost me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't word it very well, but I was responding to the "whiny, overly emotional teen" reference. 99% of the time I'd agree with you, and then I read one like the one I referenced, [Gotham High] (http://archiveofourown.org/works/8524186). So I can't condemn the concept outright, but it only works for me if the characters still remain believable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note I'm not saying it isn't possible to write a good fic that way. One writer has created a [Bruce-Wayne-in-High-School fic](http://archiveofourown.org/works/8524186) I like a lot, for example. But I'd also note that she doesn't have him meeting any other heroes or villains years before canon (he knows Zatanna, but there's no meeting Clark Kent 10 years before he's supposed to, that sort of thing) and she keeps him in character with some interesting insights into how someone damaged enough to eventually become a vigilante might socialize. 

But the farther away you get from the world the characters inhabit, the less I'm likely to be interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sherlock, but because it's not providing me with what I want: more stories in the same world. I've seen a few I liked, but there aren't a lot of witty, challenging mysteries being posted. 

No problem with various shippings, but I'd rather that the relationship not be the focus of the story. Not interested in reading about the characters working as barristas or in high school. I just want more Sherlock stories than Moffat/Gattis can provide and I absolutely do not understand why there aren't any official tie-in novels. Considering the source, collections of new short stories would be awesome. I suspect Doctor Who makes a pile off their books and some of them are excellent. Where are the Sherlock stories?

ETA: This reflects my own taste in fanfic, obviously. YMMV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it is a place for discussion of books. And the OP did specifically ask which novel *most closely predicted*, not completely predicted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the White House doesn't care. 

["Saturday's ruling does not undercut the President's executive order. All stopped visas will remain stopped. All halted admissions will remain halted. All restricted travel will remain prohibited. The executive order is a vital action toward strengthening America's borders, and therefore sovereignty. The order remains in place."](http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/28/politics/2-iraqis-file-lawsuit-after-being-detained-in-ny-due-to-travel-ban/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Muslims, whether they're in the now-banned countries or the "nice" ones we still let in or living here, are watching this. The last two presidents were careful to condemn only the violent extremists. Trump has condemned the entire religion, and made ISIS recruitment that much easier by turning the country into the anti-Muslim place they always said it was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close enough to a book I'm already writing, so nope :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gaiman has said that "Ocean" was a short story that kept growing. 

While I don't disagree that some of his characters and their histories/motivations remain mysterious, it doesn't bring me out of the story. I don't necessarily want everything wrapped up in a nice complete package. I want that slightly unsettling feeling that there's still stuff in this magical world he builds that I don't know and won't know. (Obviously YMMV and if it doesn't work for you, my opinion won't change that.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still "M Is For Magic," short story collection that's listed as mostly for children. Several but not all of the stories in it are in books on your shelf.

Plus his other children's books. "The Wolves in the Walls" and "Fortunately, The Milk," and "The Day I Swapped My Dad for Two Goldfish" and "Odd and the Frost Giants" and "Crazy Hair" and "Hansel and Gretel" and the Chu books and various illustrated poems and alphabets and...  You're probably going to need a bigger shelf. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the models are grungy or dirty, absolutely.

If the models are elegant and poised, but clearly either delighted or disgusted by their surroundings, certainly.

(Also? I'd love to shoot there.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the author clearly doesn't understand the universe, or wants to take characters into a direction that makes no sense for them whatsoever. Dude, just write your own story, don't twist these characters into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton is irrelevant here. She is not president. 

Trump did hold an event for veterans, and he gave them the money [four months later](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-politics/wp/2016/05/30/tomorrow-trump-will-give-more-details-about-his-donations-to-vets-heres-what-we-still-dont-know/?utm_term=.01f59189f3ed), which was a week after the Post ran a big article debunking his donation claims. This is on top of the Post exhaustively debunking his claim of the millions he personally had donated, [which they couldn't find](https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/a-portrait-of-trump-the-donor-free-rounds-of-golf-but-no-personal-cash/2016/04/10/373b9b92-fb40-11e5-9140-e61d062438bb_story.html?utm_term=.bda1f832115e).

The tax returns are vital since we have no way of checking what conflicts of interest exist, or what Trump may owe to Russian companies or Chinese banks. "Trust me" is not a valid policy.

["And in terms of high-end product influx into the US, Russians make up a pretty disproportionate cross-section of a lot of our assets; say in Dubai, and certainly with our project in SoHo and anywhere in New York. We see a lot of money pouring in from Russia. There's indeed a lot of money coming for new-builds and resale reflecting a trend in the Russian economy and, of course, the weak dollar versus the ruble," Donald Trump Jr said.](http://www.eturbonews.com/5008/executive-talk-donald-trump-jr-bullish-russia-and-few-emerging-ma)

Trump has been [sued more than 3,500 times in the last three decades](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2016/06/09/donald-trump-unpaid-bills-republican-president-laswuits/85297274/) for not paying contractors. He told the Wall Street Journal,  "I love to hold back and negotiate when people dont do good work. If they do a good job, I wont cut them at all. . . . Its probably 1,000 to one where I pay."
[Here's why he gets away with it.](http://fortune.com/2016/09/30/donald-trump-stiff-contractors/)

 If you were voted in to be president based on a campaign of staying as a political outsider would you fill your most important cabinet seats with insiders?

He ran on the slogan of "draining the swamp." Apparently he drained it and hired everyone he found. He slammed Clinton repeatedly for her Goldman-Sachs interests but he hired two of them himself.

As for the better relationship with Russia, better diplomatic relations is fine. But he's right on the edge of toadying to Putin, and many of his staff (including, possibly, himself) have significant financial ties to Russia. The more he refuses to reveal those ties, the more I have to assume they're shady.

He's welcome to stack his room with people with constructive questions. Instead he's stacking it with people with fringe, pro-Trump, anti-fact websites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work! You have a great eye for catching iconic moments in a show.

Concert pics have led to other work for me, including promo work for a band, but it mostly paid for equipment upgrades (no small thing). No way I could make a living off it, and I have great respect for anyone who can make it work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of your counterarguments seem to assume that this money is being denied to clinics and such and people can just go elsewhere. In many places where these services operate, there *are no other medical options*, or there are very few. That's why they're there in the first place.

And they've all been told now that they may not even say the name of this legal, occasionally medically necessary procedure or they will lose the funding that enables them to perform many other needed services besides the one banned. For many of them that's no choice at all, they have to comply or shut down and not help anybody.

This is not based on science or medicine. This is an imposed choice by someone holding the pursestrings over millions of people's lives in an effort to ban a legal medical procedure because God or something.

Imagine the same gag rule, but about insulin. The Bible has a verse about medicine from sheep being bad or something, and the US has just said that any aid organization that even whispers the word "insulin" to a diabetic will lose its funding.

The organizations would probably go along, having little to no choice. Did the US force them to? No. But the reality of their situation forced them to, and the US put them in the position where that had to make that utterly unnecessary choice knowing full well what their answer would have to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The effect is the same, though.

Organizations providing aid to desperately needy people now have the option to provide them with all the information they need about the full range of medical options, but have their budgets severely slashed to the point where many would probably have to pack up and quit, OR they can keep the funding as long as they never ever ever ever even mention the option of a *completely legal procedure*.

Trump and the GOP are imposing their own moral beliefs on the world about a legal medical procedure and they are blackmailing/strongarming world aid organizations to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Have to take my dog back to the Human Society we just got him from for his heartworm shot. How do we prepare him for an overnight stay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just adopted a lab mix dog from our local Humane Society. Wonderful, friendly, affectionate dog, but he's still clearly very anxious about being left alone. Has to know where we are and what we're doing at all time. We've been working with him and reassuring him and getting him used to where he lives now, but next week we have to take him back to the Society and leave him overnight for heartworm shots.

Is there anything we can do to help calm and reassure him before we leave him back where we just got him four days ago? We'll get him back the next day but I'm afraid we're going to break all the trust we've been building up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To you, perhaps. To others, perhaps. To me and several million marching and countless more watching and cheering, it was a legitimate protest, no matter how it may come off to you.

And there were protests when Obama was elected. There just weren't as many people at them, by a large factor. I fully support anyone's right to peacefully protest. It's an American thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a mandate to promote and try to pass legislation that advances their goals, of course. They do not have a mandate to ignore the stated needs of over half their constituents. Trump does not have a blank check and should not be allowed to believe that he does. 

Which, I grant you, is silly. His whole life and career have been based on the notion that he can in fact do whatever he wants and it becomes OK or legal or ethical simply because he wants it, and it's worked for him. But a lot of what he wants requires the legislature, and they cannot be allowed to believe that all Americans agree with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get it. He does not. He needed it big and undeniable and in his face.

His supporters do not. Many of them are quick to dismiss dissent as coming from a minority, probably paid for by liberal billionaires. This was a massive, grass-roots movement.

And other politicians, on both sides, need to see how their constituents feel, in no uncertain terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with the other comments here, there were other reasons to march in protest.

- To remind this administration that they do not have a mandate. This president did not win the popular vote. There are many millions of people who do not agree with the stated policies of Mr. Trump and the people under him despite his claims to the contrary, and this was just demonstrated in a way that cannot be denied although he's certainly going to try to.

- To remind themselves that they are not alone. For many people the months since the election, culminating in the inauguration day, were rough, emotionally black times. We have seen our countrymen enthusiastically cheer for and then elect someone to be president who is not only unqualified for the task but who demonstrates why he should not be in the White House every time he speaks or tweets, and we have seen him load the Cabinet with people who seem specifically chosen to destroy the department for which they were chosen. We have seen the various bits of wishlist legislation floating around that now have good odds of passing, bills that limit and restrict the tools of democracy while opening the gates to business. We read the proposed budget plans which seek to strip funding for many woman-friendly programs. It has been very easy, these days, to think that everything is lost. We *needed* this bright day of solidarity, of defiance, of triumph, of humor, of sister- and brotherhood. We needed to know that many millions of people agree. We needed to know that enough other people felt the same way that it would create the biggest single-day protest in the history of the world. This was catharsis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see it. Suicide Squad was supposed to be silly and weird and off (just, hopefully, in a way pleasing to millions of people). But BvS should have been a home run and it so completely wasn't. I think it was far more of a disappointment than SS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's important that there was sharing going on, not taking

YES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
