<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol didn't wighton f himself up on a trampoline or something and miss a couple months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shopping for zippers on amazon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donnie Darko: Genisys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mega line is gimmicky however there are some modding gems in it... the bigshock, hotshock, cycloneshock and rotofury can be rebarreled to shoot elites and a spring upgrade makes them beasts while being extremely easy to mod. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharks

Eels

Dragons

Rabbitohs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea its really underrated, everything about it was unsettling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am i the only one that thinks the warriors under kearny will make top 4?


He had a terrible team at parra, this warriors side is ridiculous good.

His test record is awesome and he leaves and at near full strength they were challenged by scotland and england!, that anzac test last year they lost 16-0 (aus scored a try right at the end) was crazy... they should have lost that 50-0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hostel

The Canal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a teenage girl at the center of the story that tries to take down the morally corrupt government on her own all while juggling a love triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sweet, thanks for the details with your experience... too glossy would have not been right for my look so i'll go for about 3-4 and remember for the future when I want glossy go full on 7. 

Was gonna do the topcoat in the morning, good thing I saw this before knocking off.

Thanks again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the heads up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome, thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About to apply clear coat, need help before I go ahead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished painting a nerf element, 3 coats of flat black vinyl dye then dry brushed gold, silver and gunmetal.

I've reached topcoating time and have a duplicolor clear topcoat i'm going to use. My question is:

How heavy do I go with the top coat?

The can says: Apply several light coats , allow paint to become touch dry between coats. 

Since this is automotive spray for a plastic toy, seven is overkill right?

Also I lightly applied about 3 coats of black vinyl dye inside the shell to the dart holder, is it a bad idea to topcoat inside there? it's not sanded but was washed with warm soapy water beforehand.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep plastic containers, also keeps dust and bugs off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hayne still would have been a beast in the halves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea not fair to take a dump on movies with a small budget compared to the $300mil blockbusters with every resource at their whim and the "best" but usually miscast actors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 09:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also with slamfire your begging for dryfires </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitchell Pearce, Joel Monaghan and Scooby Doo.

Roh Oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can visit all the frats in the USA and sign up some bros to make the move to australia to take up league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow the only reason a team should make a play like that is when they are missing a piece in the puzzle to become contenders, hunt is a very structured player and isn't a big issue with the dragons attack that they play too structured?

Just one example of when I think a 6yr contract is acceptable could be a hypothetical scenario with the cowboys. On thurstons final season throw the checkbook at cleary/taylor just as they have gotten that couple extra seasons experience under the belt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, i'm a noob. Still haven't modded my first stryfe/rapidstrike and am doing my homework on batteries and motors etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11.1v or 7.4v? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> any 2s lipo you'd particularly recommend?

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that they actually want the director to do the remake which could end up something like how ju-on - the grudge ended up...which was good. 

He pretty much made the same movie even set in japan again, but with the bigger budget looked more polished.

I'd imagine that if the original wailing director got the nod again, he'll set it in South Korea but just make the protagonist a white guy from america or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zombeavers was actually really good satire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we'll sign ash taylor for like 250k no worries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was this one guy on ebay about 4 years ago I had a big go at, he sold modified mavericks for $70aud and actually had sold about x10. He advertised them as hitting 100ft flat with streamlines and none of the buyers left negetive feedback on him.

I guess some kids got them without doing a range test and were satisfied it hit a little harder. Now what mods do you get for $70 you say?

-Spring stretched

-Penny Mod

-AR removed

It wasn't even painted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol $100 for all the ammo

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with crossbow arms! 

lol plz no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, also no need to sand the internals right?

I don't wanna sand the inside all up if I don't need to haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read heaps on painting and opinion is like split down the middle in regards to vinyl dye without primer vs primer and acrylic lacquer.

If like you said to just use vinyl dye for internals, is there a reason not to clear coat the inside? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping to start painting soon and one thing that bothers me ive seen from other paintjobs are magazine blasters with jam doors... without a mag inside or if you remove the jam door like I do my OCD kicks in and that black blaster with yellow/blue internals sticks out alot.

I'm looking to paint the insides of mine, are there any painting pros that think its a bad idea? if done properly etc. sanded, primed, 1-2 basecoats and topcoated will the moving internal parts like a metal boltsled/trigger wreck that all up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> broncos, storm, dogs, roosters and raiders likely to join them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> des, bellyache and bennett coaching 101 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's lost his mind, the nines gives an excuse to start drinking at 9am through to the afternoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 09:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RAWR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how organized and aesthetically nice wall mounten nerf guns look, but does anyone have an answer for dust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know who made it but does anyone remember the old EA rugby union games on PS2? a new one was made on PS4 and looks like the PS2 version! they also didn't have the licensing rights so a bunch of stadiums and players are just made up.... 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-eFI6EP2sJw

it could be soo much worse lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mash sprint button.

The only way to make meters is spam the pass buttons to the right then back to the left willy nilly.

The incredible logic in building a team where you can literally have x17 wingers with 99 speed/acc/stamina and pwn properly built teams.

The god awful AI who will run right next to you in support and just as you've drawn in the last cover guy and press the pass button, the dickhead in support stops and your pass goes over the sideline.

Still no fantasy draft options when starting a frachise mode career!

It seems like big ant has been using the same engine since the PS2 days... won't be buying whatever turd of a league game they make next.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 12:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shotgun cycloneshock comes to mind but I want it to look good aesthetically too, sure I can buy the barrel but when you hack parts of the blaster to mod it ends up looking like the hammershots inbred baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol my nephew was shooting his brother in the face while he was covering and is like hahahaha, then he got shot in the leg with a firestrike with just AR removed and got all shitty at his brother for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
