<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1856</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, we don't have *that* many issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco Bell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How frazzled and confused I get when someone hits on me, can't seem to shake it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats and kittens, I can't even look at pictures of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drama-filled kind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using the restroom in the morning, trust me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cat pictures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thumb on top while handshaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 19:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started to choose steak over a burger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate, 70% dark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FREE 72 oz steak meal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are awesome for doing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [chipmunk](http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/0/3948/969765-chipmunk4.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when that happens. Some really hot ones just don't know how to carry on a conversation, it's sad :(.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely get your timing down, just apply the usual standardized test taking tips. 

The analogies are are kind of weird, I remember getting one about baklava and phyllo dough... there's really no good way to prepare for them, I guess just look at examples if you can find some? Goodluck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Kaplan tests were harder than the PCAT. Just take at least one more practice test before the real deal and you should be fine in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think option 1 might be easier to move around in and more aesthetically pleasing, but option 2 looks like it would be better to keep the rain off of you so I would go with option 2. 

Also, from my experience, Lands End has better quality than Uniqlo (by quite a bit too). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, glad I could help! They look comfortable (a must if you have kids) and if she doesn't like them, you can always exchange them in the store! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no weakness...
Just kidding. If this is for an interview, I'd probably say I have trouble delegating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would highly suggest physically writing down the goals too, there's something about the satisfaction you get when you grab a pen and check off something you've achieved versus just mentally checking it off in your head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally! I think most people equate JCP with clothes for your mom or grandma but I don't think that's true at all. I think the quality isn't on par with Nordstrom or anything like that, but for the price, you can find some pretty nice things in my opinion. I get asked where I get my clothes and people are so surprised when I say JCP.
I like the Liz Claiborne and Worthington lines for business casual/conservative attire. I do like Joe Fresh and MNG too!

They also have *really* good clearance deals all the time. I've gotten some silk Joe Fresh blouses for $2 each, a few dresses for 97 cents (yeah, I know), and so many nice pencil skirts for $5 or so. And lastly, they always have the $10 off of $25 dollars (this weekend included) coupons, that's basically getting an extra 30-40% off your purchase if you try to buy $25-30.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sir, deserve a husband of the year award! Please tell her a stranger thinks she looks awesome and she needs to flaunt what she's got!
I know you noted some of the stores she likes, but when I think conservative yet classy, I usually go to JCPenney's to be honest (I usually buy my pencil skirts and dresses here for school/work). Here are a few of my suggestions:

[shirt](http://www.jcpenney.com/joe-fresh-34-sleeve-roll-tab-mixed-print-shirt/prod.jump?ppId=pp5005180298 catId=cat100210006 deptId=dept20000013 extDim=true topDim=Item+Type topDimvalue=button-front dimCombo=Item+Type%7CSleeve+Length%7C dimComboVal=button-front%7C3%2F4+sleeve%7C currentDim=Sleeve+Length currentDimVal=3%2F4+sleeve _dyncharset=UTF-8 colorizedImg=DP0226201517020169M.tif)
[skirt](http://www.jcpenney.com/worthington-full-pleat-skirt/prod.jump?ppId=pp5005160177 catId=cat100250097 deptId=dept20000013  _dyncharset=UTF-8 colorizedImg=DP0316201517032477M.tif)
[shoes](http://www.jcpenney.com/liz-claiborne-paula-peep-toe-wedge-pumps/prod.jump?ppId=pp5004950775 catId=cat100250187 deptId=dept20000018 N=1005020045 extDim=true topDim=Categories topDimvalue=wedges dimCombo=Categories%7C dimComboVal=wedges%7C currentDim=Categories currentDimVal=wedges N=1005020045 _dyncharset=UTF-8 colorizedImg=DP1223201417020317M.tif)

I hope that somewhat helps and best of luck! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Texas: CVS is hiring in a number of cities, Target is hiring in El Paso  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was a great woman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good, but a little tart.
It's the best hot sauce to go on a breakfast burrito or potato chips~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,
As the title indicates, I am planning to spend a few days in Denver and Rocky Mountains National Park during my roadtrip from Texas to Oregon.[route](https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Amarillo,+TX/Rocky+Mountain+National+Park,+Colorado/Yellowstone+National+Park/Grand+Teton+National+Park,+Teton+County,+WY/Eugene,+OR/@39.4423258,-121.9369639,5z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m32!4m31!1m5!1m1!1s0x870148d4b245cf03:0xd0f3d11c6836d2af!2m2!1d-101.8312969!2d35.2219971!1m5!1m1!1s0x876979e4455903e9:0xfa27ee43a78e8217!2m2!1d-105.683639!2d40.342793!1m5!1m1!1s0x5351e55555555555:0xaca8f930348fe1bb!2m2!1d-110.588455!2d44.427963!1m5!1m1!1s0x5352519ec95d1ba9:0xa5a0b88ecc91a337!2m2!1d-110.681763!2d43.790428!1m5!1m1!1s0x54c119b0ac501919:0x57ec61894a43894d!2m2!1d-123.0867536!2d44.0520691!3e0)
I've done some reading on the world wide web but wanted to post here for additional insight on the following: weather and driving conditions in Denver and RMNP during this time, absolutely must dos in Denver (I'm a young professional in my mid 20s), camping tips in RMNP, trails to definitely hit up in the park, food recommendations, and anything else you want to mention to a visitor of the city and park.
Any information you can provide will be greatly appreciated, thanks in advance kind stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think taking practice PCAT tests and reading the prep book helped more than most of my classes did. That said, I would just take classes that are suggested in your degree audit as a sophomore (Microbiology, Genetics, Gen Chem, and basic Bio were all helpful for the test in my opionion).

In terms of GPA, it's really hard to say since admission is based on a number of factors: GPA, interview, extra curricular activities, etc.
Personally, I think anything under 3.0 or so is when you should start really worrying. As someone mentioned earlier, the PCAT does test your knowledge of the material somewhat, but it assesses your ability to take standardized tests more. So I would just try to do well in school of course, but also find a good prep book to review with and take as many practice tests as time allows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend waiting until the spring semester of your P4 year to buy a book. New drugs (and sometimes guidelines) come out all the time so if you buy one now, you probably won't have the latest information for the NAPLEX after you graduate and will have to buy a new one at that time or resort to your class notes. 

If you're asking about a book to help you focus on the important stuff in school, I still think it's overkill. I would just focus on what you're taught in your classes and that should be sufficient. I think most schools teach you stuff that they know will be on the NAPLEX exam with a fluff class every now and then. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving through Denver and Rocky Mountains National Park (RMNP) late May/early June </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2-3 nights in Yellowstone at the beginning of June--seeking advice/pointers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,


As the title indicates, I am planning to spend a few days in Yellowstone during my solo roadtrip from Texas to Oregon [route](https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Amarillo,+TX/Rocky+Mountain+National+Park,+Colorado/Yellowstone+National+Park/Grand+Teton+National+Park,+Teton+County,+WY/Eugene,+OR/@39.4423258,-121.9369639,5z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m32!4m31!1m5!1m1!1s0x870148d4b245cf03:0xd0f3d11c6836d2af!2m2!1d-101.8312969!2d35.2219971!1m5!1m1!1s0x876979e4455903e9:0xfa27ee43a78e8217!2m2!1d-105.683639!2d40.342793!1m5!1m1!1s0x5351e55555555555:0xaca8f930348fe1bb!2m2!1d-110.588455!2d44.427963!1m5!1m1!1s0x5352519ec95d1ba9:0xa5a0b88ecc91a337!2m2!1d-110.681763!2d43.790428!1m5!1m1!1s0x54c119b0ac501919:0x57ec61894a43894d!2m2!1d-123.0867536!2d44.0520691!3e0). 

I am writing to see if anyone can give me tips on where to camp, road conditions during this time, what to watch out for, things to definitely see, safety issues one might encounter while camping alone, and anything else you can think of. I'm also planning to do 2-3 nights in Grand Tetons as well, so anything you can tell me about that will be fabulous!

I've been camping before, but not alone and it was at campsites. I know the basics of camping but I'm in no means a true backpacker of any sort. I'm in shape, but probably can't run a half marathon at this given moment.

Any information you can provide will be greatly appreciated! :)
I'm super stoked for this trip!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 16:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That duck hunting game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 23:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister always says to me, "you know, you should be grateful for what you have". 


I AM, that's why I take all these trips and don't spend all day studying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lilly Pullitzer has stuff that's not super bold. I got a white mini skirt on sale for $4.99 once, the quality is excellent too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! 9 called and says he wants 10 back. 

*winks creepily* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The AOL dial tone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fly...


that has been dead for a few months (ate it on purpose because I was like 5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
