<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8653</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! Done editing! I hope that I have provided enough information. Thank you so much!!!

Paul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 06:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, my apologies... Is it too late to include this and have it reactivated? It seems to be getting some positive feedback. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 05:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Will do. I do have a longer video but it's just me and my wife kicking the heavy bag. No punching and footwork.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 05:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 4 kids (15y/o girl, 6y/o boy, and 2y/o male twins) and all of us are physically active. When they pull off something like this, I remind them of my role as a parent and as someone who is more experienced in life compared to them. I express to them that I love them, and I care for them; and for that reason they have to respect my words when I say no more. It works all the time. There will be hard feelings sometimes but love and compassion can take away that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it too late to get in shape? I thought so but thank goodness I was wrong! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 05:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 35 year old father of four. I design for a living and lived a sedentary lifestyle up until about 6 months ago. I smoked, never played sports, overweight for the most part of my life, had severe sleep apnea, and was a former meth addict (college years. The habit forced me to drop out of an engineering degree on my 3rd year.) 

A couple of years ago I was diagnosed with severe anxiety, depression, and PTSD. I was taking a progressive dose of anti-depressants. The meds were supposed to make me feel somehow confident and uplifted- and was supposed to help me cope with my OCD as well. It made me feel OK at first but later on it made me feel empty and suicidal. After a while of taking it, I found myself no longer enjoying that things that I used to enjoy- like making art, designing merchandise, and cooking. I suspect these activities are somehow tied to my OCD.

I spoke to my family doctor about it and she suggested that perhaps I should try natural means of defeating my mental illness such as exposure therapy and exercise. Due to my plantar fasciitis and joints, back, and knees problem- the only exercise that she would allow me to do was swimming. Thanks to my social anxiety- I abhor swimming. 

July 2015. My 15 yr old girl and 6 yr old boy joined a Muay Thai gym in our area. Driving them and picking them up from the gym became my exposure therapy of sorts. I like the vibe but was very hesitant because I always had the mindset that I was not made for sports. At the urging of my wife and kids (we live in a tiny apartment and, thanks to my severe apnea, they can't stand my snoring anymore) I decided to join them. My doctor was against it but I was born a rebel so I persevered and I found that I thoroughly enjoyed the sport.

I have since lost more than 20 lbs and I continue to burn anywhere between 1-3 lbs per week. My relationship with my wife and family is now waaaay better and I no longer need my prescription. Being physically fit changed my life.

[Here's my Before and After photo. 5 months difference.](http://i.imgur.com/Zlupy3p.jpg) Sorry I have to watermark it, I don't want to fall prey to those with mercenary motives who steal photos like this and use it for their own profit. 

[This is me hitting the heavy bag with my wife.](https://www.instagram.com/p/BDHr0IaQu5C)

[Me shadowboxing.](https://www.instagram.com/p/BDMZoJzQuw4)

TL;DR An overweight, depressed, traumatized, and sick 35 year old father of four who never played sports his whole life tried Muay Thai and almost 6 months later became awesome. :-D

Edit: I violated Rule 4: Progress/Achievement posts require relevant information. Sorry mods! :-)

*********Some information about myself:*********

Beginning (September 24, 2015) Sex, Weight, Height, and Age: [M, 200 lbs, 5"7, 34](http://i.imgur.com/kqUFPwH.jpg)
Ending Sex, Weight, Height, and Age: [M, 178.6 lbs, 5"7, 35](https://www.instagram.com/p/BDH5QhVwu7d)

*********Detailed diet and exercise routine:*********
I jumpstarted my diet change by [eating nothing but sardines with rice and olives](https://www.instagram.com/p/998s1EQu2Q) (and a lot of greens) for breakfast, lunch, and dinner for the entire month of November 2015. From December onwards- I pretty much eat anything that I cook and serve my kids but in moderation (I have a Filipino background and we consume a lot of rice. I used to eat more than 2 cups per meal but now I'm down to 1). I have my cheat days on Fridays and have pizza and soda. On Saturdays I workout even if I don't really have to so I can eat my Tim Horton's chocolate dip donut. I drink a medium sized 1 cream 1 sugar coffee in the morning and sometimes at night as well. I smoke marijuana 10 minutes before workout and throughout the day actually. I still smoke the occasional cigarette but I can now go for days without it. I have four kids and a business to run so I sleep anywhere between 3-6 hours only every night.

*********Exercise routine:*********
Monday, Wednesday, Friday: Muay Thai conditioning and some bag/pad work
Saturday: Light warm up and some bag work

What is Muay Thai conditioning? It varies but basically it's about 45minutes - 1hour of nonstop workout followed by about half an hour of hitting the pads or the heavy bag. Here's a sample workout: 

Warm up routine:
*3-10 minutes skipping rope or 10-20 minutes run
*3 sets of 40 jumping jacks, 40 front back front, 40 alternating knees, 40 right kick ups, 40 left kick ups, 15 jump squats

Heavy bag routine:
*4 sets of 25 right swing kicks, 25 left swing kicks, 25 right push kicks, 25 left push kicks, 50 speed jabs and cross punches. [Here's a video of me and my wife doing 50 swing kicks each each leg](https://youtu.be/R30EIHJZjTo). 

*********Here are some tips that help me get from point A to point B.*********

* BE TRUE TO YOURSELF. I admitted to myself that I was sick and I needed help. And so I did admit and I did it publicly. I joined Movember on 2014 and [I blogged about my struggle on my own business website](http://www.fraternalties.com/blogs/news/15850180-demons-depression-and-mustache). Some people thought that it would be the end of my business career for coming out like that but instead my business received more interest. Nobody joined me on my Movember campaign though.

* USE SOCIAL MEDIA. Let your intent be known. I always wanted to be fit but the attachment to my bad habits was strong. When I was trying to quit smoking, I read somewhere that it would be helpful if you let your family and friends know that you're quitting. There's a psychology behind this but that's beyond my area of expertise. So on November 2015 I participated in Movember once more and told my followers in Facebook about it. I also made a cringe-worthy [Movember day 1 video](https://youtu.be/LTpj8xtMTLs). I only managed to get 1 MoBro supporter- my personal trainer but that was enough to motivate me.

* ADD SOME GIMMICK. The more dramatic the better. It's fun for you (and your audience and those around you will react positively!). Example: [I ate nothing but sardines with rice and olives](https://www.instagram.com/p/998s1EQu2Q) for breakfast, lunch, and dinner everyday for the entire month of November. [I skipped rope with PVC rope wearing my suit and tie](https://youtu.be/KqGzMqaOPtM). There are other crazy stuff that I did but the idea is to push yourself and enjoy doing it.

* INVOLVE YOUR LOVED ONES. Be an inspiration to each other. Actually, in my case, my wife and kids involved me. My kids are so into Muay Thai that my 6y/o asked me to make him a [Youtube channel dedicated to Muay Thai](https://youtu.be/B-P-2wQY8gE). My 15 y/o girl can't wait to fight in the ring, and even our [2 y/o twins are active in the gym](https://youtu.be/Y9_h6zBAeZ0). 


Edit 2: 50 kicks each leg for a total of 100 kicks per person. 
Edit 3: Trying to fix formatting to make it more readable. I'm fail at this. Also added a couple of words for clarity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 04:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he is Simon marcus' trainer.

Was. But definitely agree- one of the best. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beginner looking for critique. Please help me improve my shadowboxing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 04:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing your thoughts! 1) Yes, thank goodness! 2) [I hope so](https://www.instagram.com/p/BDMZoJzQuw4)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apologies if the purpose of my post seemed to you that way. Like you, I don't concern myself with politics of anything. I'm merely curious. I totally agree with you that [results are all that matter](http://i.imgur.com/Zlupy3p.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 13:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 13:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The certification itself doesn't mean anything.

Of course. Real certification comes from experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 12:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One who is certified to teach I suppose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 07:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a beginner student, and haven't been to other gyms but most practitioners that I have met so far refer to the actual certified teachers as "Kru" and masters as "Ajahn". As for the trainers/coaches, we call them by name. Also, Ajahn Suchart whom I have personally met is big on culture, spirituality, and such so he appreciates students call their teachers with the proper salutation to show respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know your Muay Thai ancestry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 06:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I start:

Home gym: Krudar Muay Thai Don Mills

Lineage: [Kru Benson Virtucio](http://www.krudar.com/personal/trainer/benson-virtuccio/)  [Kru Darwin Miranda](http://www.krudar.com/personal/trainer/darwin-miranda-2/)  [Kru / Ajahn Suchart](http://ajahnsuchart.com/true-stories-shared-by-traditional-martial-artist-to-pass-onto-the-next-generation/)  [Kru / Ajahn Yodtong Senanan](http://www.sityodtongmuaythai.com/en/history.html)  Kru Suwan Senanan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 04:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is an International event. I Googled and can't find any other reference but we're celebrating this [cultural event today here in Ontario, Canada](http://www.siamno1.com/schedule-2/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Kru of Muay Thai Day to all! Here's my son learning Wai Kru for the first time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 04:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 02:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not making me financially richer but Freemasons somehow help me stay alive by buying my merchandise. I don't have a regular day job and not receiving benefits from the government save for daycare subsidy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IHOP will be giving away a free Short stack of pancakes to guest who donate to Shriners Hospitals for Children! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hey.](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/ff/1b/b7/ff1bb71cc72d201f0efc2b97fa2ae823.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A toast to exceptions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll message you bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gasp! A female Mason! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 16:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm originally from the Philippines where cockfighting is also a big industry. Prized roosters fight to death with 2 inch blades attached to their shins. As you may already know, we have a blade culture over there. I wonder if this is how they do it in Thailand as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Muaythai but if we're talking strictly "martial" arts, I'd go with Filipino Combat Systems where you get taught how to disable or kill an opponent with emphasis on economy of movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Foreigner. Non-Thai](http://imgur.com/a/CAAFd) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 17:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The greatest enemy of knowledge is not ignorance, it is the illusion of knowledge." -S. Hawking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What others think of me as a Nak Muay Farang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 14:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 14:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's one](https://www.facebook.com/fidelity192/photos/a.192808274066887.57364.192806994067015/982050485142658/) that I designed for Fidelity Lodge No. 192 AF AM in Colorado. 

Also made [custom neckties for them with the same logo that I designed](http://i.imgur.com/IMWMXu3.jpg). 

edit: word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 13:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm struggling to quit smoking completely. I'm a bit shocked to know he smokes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 13:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have photos of the event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 17:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL don't feel bad my friend. I completely understand. Last night I found myself wondering why this post was getting downvoted. I couldn't help but compare its performance to my previous [video post in this sub last week that received a respectable 42 likes](https://www.reddit.com/r/MuayThai/comments/45x1fk/we_are_a_family_of_muay_thai_nerds_we_have_a/?ref=share ref_source=link). This morning I realized that if I watch the video on a mobile device, the annotations won't show. Without the annotations, the video title will seem boastful and pretentious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 16:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your valuable feedback. The video is actually meant to be humorous. He saw Saenchai doing his signature kick and since my boy can do cartwheels he thought he can pull it off. Well, obviously he was wrong. This video is proof to him that a lot of training is needed if you want to be good at one thing (on one of the annotations we mentioned that Saenchai said in an interview that it took him 3 years to perfect the kick). Question: Did you see the YouTube annotations by any chance? I noticed that if you watch the video on mobile, the annotations do not show up. I just realized that the viewer might miss the humour without the annotations turned on.

edit: Saenchai trivia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brutal KO. Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me, my wife, and our kids as one of your supporters, Sylvie! You're life story is inspiring! Perhaps one day our feet will bring us to Thailand and we will have the privilege of shaking your hand. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 yr old Nak Muay dissects Saenchai Cartwheel kick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 05:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 14:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of my Facebook posts and my way of thinking are good indicators that I am a big fan of Manly P. Hall's work. I too don't understand all the regurgitated hate in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 08:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why people are downvoting this so here's an upvote for your sound advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! If you're interested, [here's a video](https://youtu.be/Zhx1QqRYL0Y) of him doing pad work for the first time with our Kru. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words! You should check out his video when he was just starting like this one- [this is him teaching his school buddies some basic Muay Thai moves at the school park](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GheaodULQkE).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 17:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this comment! My boy said [use this](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-UCTVWTwExJs/Tej6qbnYHII/AAAAAAAAABQ/SOMekLmkesQ/s1600/muay+liniment+1.JPG) to make it even warmer. Silly kid. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 17:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh.. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 04:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucks but you must be allergic to one of its ingredients. I use Namman oil on my wife and kids (my youngest just 6) and they don't complain. Consider using more natural alternatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 03:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 03:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 01:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed with anxiety, depression, and PTSD. I am a Freemason and baptized as a Christian but my point of view is different from most of my Christian brothers. 

You can find in ancient holy scriptures many references to mental health problems, albeit veiled. 

This is my favourite from the Bible:
This is why I speak to them in parables: "Though seeing, they do not see; though hearing, they do not hear or understand."

Another of my favourite is this one from Hinduism (also credited to Buddha, etc.)

Be careful with your thoughts because your thoughts become your words. Be careful with your words because your words become your actions. Be careful with your actions because you actions become your behaviors. Be careful with your behaviors because your behaviors become your habits. Be careful with your habits because your habits become your character. And be careful with your character because your character becomes your destiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this floating in FB. Sad to say that I don't get it. :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done!

By tiger oil do you mean [this](http://www.thenaturalhealthmarket.co.uk/image/cache/data/personalcare/balms/muaythai/muay-thai-boxing-liniment-oil-family-700x700.jpg)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are a family of Muay Thai nerds. We have a punching bag in the living room. Here's our 6yr old practicing his strikes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 13:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one is for you](https://youtu.be/sC0yu5ArKIE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 22:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knows but it never came up in a conversation. He's more of an observer and very careful with his opinions. I have relatives though who think we worship the devil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 21:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [can't lie](http://imgur.com/hRfhkF8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 01:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a very Christian family. My [uncle is a well known psychologist and missionary priest](http://www.healingeucharistinc.com/fr-glenn-paul-m-gomez-svd/) from where I was originally from. I consider myself very Christian until I separated from my family and moved to a city far away from my hometown to go to university. I met people from all walks of life, got into drugs, got disillusioned, dabbled with atheism, and eventually emerged as an agnostic. Then I moved to Canada, was Initiated, Passed, and Raised, and now I find myself going back to my Christian roots but with a very different point of view. I consider myself a follower of Jesus but I don't see him as God like most of my fellow Christians. To me he is much like Hiram whose work must be emulated instead of himself adored as a deity. I hope this helps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 06:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a sweet stack waiting for you [here](http://i.imgur.com/JORc07d.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 03:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by TBH what I mean of course is TBT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So for TBH I decided to auction my old Masonic necktie for 0.99 cents. 4 hrs later... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 03:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 13:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doric 316 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 15:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toronto Don Valley District Mason here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 19:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious now. Do they place some sort of book of knowledge/wisdom on their altar? Do they even have an altar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 06:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I think that the small font and see-through pages are marvelous technical achievements in printing. We have to appreciate the fact that the Bible is actually made up of 66 books with around 800,000 words in total. Print that on regular paper (as opposed to the fine and thin pages of the Bible) with size 12 font and you end up with a gargantuan book so heavy that it will never leave home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 06:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will love this replica of the George Washington Inauguration Bible that I received as a gift from the Brethren of St. John's Lodge No. 1 in NY. Did I mention it's a miniature replica? [Here's a photo of a Canadian penny next to a familiar passage](http://i.imgur.com/MRbdWlZ.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 06:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bible, Torah, Quran, Vedas, Tao Te Ching, Bhagavad Gita, Sutras... Sacred texts that depicts the fragile nature of man and man's relationship with the Unknowable. I have never been to a jurisdiction that don't consider these Works and more as Great Light of Freemasonry but if there is such a jurisdiction, I would approach them with caution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 00:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean to say not all jurisdictions consider the bible the great light of freemasonry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 22:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final charge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 05:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids love it there! We get treated like family! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 21:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Kru Benom. Great with kids. He helped me with my [transformation](http://i.imgur.com/V54MXoN.jpg) as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Score! [Thanks!](http://www.evipic.eviland.com/Comments/Images/Rock/You-rock_20.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 01:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top King. Really nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! But just to clarify, that's not me holding the pads. I took the video though. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 01:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words! My son was 5 when he started, my daughter 14. [My twins tried at 2 but failed miserably LOL](https://youtu.be/Y9_h6zBAeZ0).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the confusion. I'm not Benson but he's our personal trainer. He's about to become a dad too! Due in 7 months if I'm not mistaken. We learned today that he's having a boy! Knowing how he is with his students, he's gonna be a great dad for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I train with my wife and 2 of our 4 kids. Here's my 6 y/o doing pad work for the first time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sean Fagan, the Muay Thai Guy](https://www.youtube.com/user/muaythaiguy13) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 15:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I train with my kids as well](https://youtu.be/Y9_h6zBAeZ0)! Our gym is very family friendly! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 15:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL! Thanks for catching that. That's for a different sub. Here's the right link- [holiday, 4 kids, muay thai, punching bag in the living room, nothing can go wrong](https://youtu.be/_t8aY8qE2TI).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 06:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have [four kids](https://youtu.be/_t8aY8qE2TI) but I'm not sure if I can be of much help to you. I'm very new to Muay Thai- I joined when my twins turned 2 around October last year. From my experience, consider yourself lucky if you get a 2 hour continous sleep during the first 3 months at least. If your body can handle the rigour of Muay Thai conditioning with just that much rest time, I'd say by all means do it. Otherwise just enjoy the time with your wife and your little bundle of joy. Congratulations!

Edit: link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why someone would downvote this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 19:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And here's the shot with the crossbow](https://youtu.be/VAOdnmowo0I?t=2m2s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 19:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found it - https://youtu.be/VAOdnmowo0I?t=22s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 19:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep looks like it's him! https://youtu.be/y6etOKeDrmc?t=34s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're talking about that guy with the crossbow right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, King Solomon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Website: [FraternalTies, the tie that binds.](http://www.fraternalties.com/)
Stats from the last seven days. 
I'm surprised to see that people still visit even though I don't have a new offering. 

United States	67%	371
United Kingdom	17%	92
Canada		6%	33
Germany		3%	16
Australia		3%	14
South Africa	2%	12
Unknown		2%	9
Brazil		1%	8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about simply taking from someone (mason, non-mason, sinner, saint) a slice of wisdom or a new perspective that resonates well with you,will that work for you, Brother?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember your creator in the days of your youth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense but have you been Initiated? Your comment seem to demonstrate a lack of knowledge of a fundamental lesson in the 1st Degree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 23:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  greatest benefit of the masonic work?

Ecclesiastes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Grrrr!!!!!](https://imgflip.com/i/xvac3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 21:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. We should find a way to introduce them to Bro. Manly P. Hall.

"What nobler relationship than that of friend? What nobler compliment can man bestow than friendship? The bonds and ties of the life we know break easily, but through eternity one bond remains - the bond of fellowship - the fellowship of atoms, of star dust in its endless flight, of suns and worlds, of gods and men. The clasped hands of comradeship unite in a bond eternal - the fellowship of spirit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to report that I personally know some who posses this contempt and hate for Christians and the Christian faith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 20:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if I may dare say that the Holy Bible is always a good place to begin our comparative studies because, whether we like it or not, many of our society's values and beliefs are anchored therein.

//Edit: weather -- whether </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 20:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 34 year old father of 4. I have a sedentary job working from home as a designer for [my own company](https://www.facebook.com/FraternalTies) I used to smoke a lot, struggled with meth addiction, diagnosed with severe social anxiety, depression, and PTSD. Last year I lost my day job due to my mental condition and almost lost my marriage. I was overweight, suffered from sleep apnea, almost always in a bad mood, and was in a terrible shape overall. Muay Thai helped me find ways to channel my anxiety (i.e. intense conditioning and hitting the heavy bag after) and in effect made me healthier, stronger, more calm, collected, and focused. I get more respect from my kids (the best feeling on earth!) and those around me because people appreciate it when they see [hardwork and actual results](http://i.imgur.com/V54MXoN.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 18:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bruh!](http://treasure.diylol.com/uploads/post/image/183920/resized_jesus-says-meme-generator-buddy-christ-says-you-rock-dude-bedf3a.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
