<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1402</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Flint Water Crisis To Ebola, Readiness Is Unequal For U.S. Health Emergencies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 11:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spain: Great quality tap water but tastes poorly along most of the med coast since it's hard and full of minerals. 

More than 50% of households therefore consume bottled water generating 6-8 billions of bottles of plastic per year. As this generally doesn't get recycled it most of the plastic ends up in landfills and then leaches into the ground water and recovers and finally the sea. Soon we cannot eat any fish anymore due to the amount of plastic.

Refuse plastic!

For more on tap water in Spain see
Http://todosobreelagua.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Miss Flint Wants You To Remember The Flint Water Crisis Isn't Over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lead-Contaminated Drinking Water Goes Far Beyond Flint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually. The issue with cheap restructuring loans is probably that it would have kept property prices artificially inflated. 

They partially managed to do this anyway though for a long time as people didn't understand that property valuations could go down.

The political and socio economic issue though as I see it is that the wealthy generally tended to profit from the crisis while the middle class lost out. There is no solution in sight to this as the wealth gap keeps increasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True with smaller retail banks. US indirectly bailed out bear strain, Merrill Lynch, etc by supporting them.

Anyway, my point was it's very unlikely that letting the banks fail would have been a better route for Spain. In the end I think the government will profit from the banks in Spain as well thanks to the value of the property assets as the market recovers. UK government is at the point of break even now.

 But you already commented on this above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Great Arctic garbage patch' revealed in remote northern oceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
