<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6768</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No time to kick off the lace up cap toes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great legs, but does anyone else want to smack their feet of the furniture?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure where you're from, but you might want to find a local career advisor. Take a look at the following link: https://careervision.org/career-plan-students/

It's in the Chicago area, but you get the gist. I know many students that have benefited from a visit to a place like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrible advice. Finish your undergrad degree. You're almost done. Definitely don't take time off. I'm a college recruiter for an adult, bachelor-completer program, and I work with countless people who changed majors or "took a break"... They come to me 10 years later and lament the fact that they didn't finish. Plus, you want law school... THAT is changing majors! You don't need to switch your major. You need to seek counseling for your depression.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's Karen Lamb? I call bullshit that she coined the phrase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1995, Don Rickles tipped me $20 when I picked up his luggage from O'Hare Airport. He said, "thanks kid". I was hoping to get insulted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lily from AT T commercials?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look cute and dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germans are notorious for wearing leather pants? I had no idea. Women and men?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot a word in my original post... What' the most popular American spirit among Brits? These gentlemen obviously like JD... is that the overwhelming favorite?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude has some big paws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
