<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8135</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> giants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me this was in r/pedofriends and not in the wild somewhere. 

That place is a goldmine for the cringiest of cringe. How it's not banned, I have no idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol you should probably calm down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it is a big problem to worry about things that are outside our realm of control. Thank you for your well thought out response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. What a great way to put it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company is not one to control its employees, please understand this. I never plan to rent anything I own. Why would I pay someone monthly for a living space when I could pay less and eventually own the property? How does that make me stupid? 

Also of note, I do not plan to leave the Texas city I am currently living in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ay yo yo it's ya boy skinny penis comin to you live from Brooklyn looking to make yo commute just a little less fat and lot more skinny aight aight let's get "baby got back" to those beats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ay yo yo it's ya boy skinny penis comin to you live from Brooklyn looking to make yo commute just a little less fat and lot more skinny aight aight let's get "baby got back" to those beats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ay yo yo it's ya boy skinny penis comin to you live from Brooklyn looking to make yo commute just a little less fat and lot more skinny aight aight let's get "baby got back" to those beats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/reditec/gta-online-import-export-soundtrack-gullywax

https://soundcloud.com/reditec/gta-online-import-export-soundtrack-eifel-power

https://soundcloud.com/reditec/gta-online-import-export-soundtrack-take-a-day-trip

https://soundcloud.com/reditec/gta-online-import-export-soundtrack-east-of-all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rockstar Games? - Tundra (sick instrumentals from latest GTA V update) [MIC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small Yoda, Big Yoda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had almost identical problems.

1. Finished the "race" time trail thing and at the finish line, there was no car to collect. (It timed out eventually and just counted as an unsuccessful pickup)

2. Two associates and I tried to sell 3 cars that had been modified individually per client's request. When we exited the garage, they spawned in their respective vehicles and I spawned on foot, rather than the T20 I was supposed to be in. No car to be found. 

After that, I quit the entire game and switched to Forza. Logging in later, I found that I apparently had 180k more (as my two associates had delivered their cars successfully) but the T20 was gone from my warehouse completely. 

Oh well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under anesthesia for wisdom tooth removal around 16-17, I subconsciously became a racecar and proceeded to SCREAM my way through the gears.

Like, maximum volume yelling and escalating pitch, then off the gas, clutch with the left foot, and back on the gas for the next gear with an imaginary gear shift in my right hand. 

Waking up to people filming and laughing at you after you've been unaware of yourself for an hour is quite startling, they had to tell me what had happened.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Import Export Issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tried to sell my first batch of vehicles, got screwed by rockstar like usual. I paid extra for upgrades to be able to get a bigger profit and all I get is a notification telling me to collect my T20. My other two associates spawned in their respective vehicles and mine is nowhere to be found. Did I just lose it? Anyone having similar problems?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
