<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand, could you clarify? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah dude, holy crap that sucks. Screw the PS4, I dunno what I'd even do in your situation. Sending positive vibes your way, for what it's worth.

Edit: screw the PS4 as in the fire damage to the extent to do that to 1 ps4, and like completely destroy another... I'm worried about the house :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty damn solid game lineup!

Tip, if you haven't yet The Last Of Us is a must!

Edit: reading the comments looks like others beat me to the suggestion, it is an amazing game though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm personally not a big VR person (I just know it's going to make me sick) but there's not much point here.

VR is new, it takes a lot of processing power, it makes up for it in immersion... And well VR.

And being sick, probably the best feature. (I kid, I kid) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to add that yeah it should have been this way all along, but way better late than never. At night I keep it dark so I could just look down and see it's color, but this is just how it always shoulda been haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, odd I think all mine feel better. But I just equated that to new VS couple+ years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And 360s, and XBone. I don't understand why Sony gimped on the battery this gen, I hoped the new revised ds4 would have a better battery. Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the DS4 v2 (just 'upgraded' to a slim, old one was it's last leg LPT buying used isn't worth the 50$ saving, also to be fair the thing did last me a couple years) since I can actually see it while playing. Thankfully it's still quite viewable at the dimmest setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of buying a better battery on Amazon, I've read you can 2x+ your battery life.

To be fair I've been thinking of this forever, the question is will I ever actually do it? Meh, probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, did you disprove my edit already? /Sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's battery. I like it as a gimmicky little feature but DS4 battery life is so bad I have light bar dimmed and speaker off to maximize it.

Edit: for, I'm not a fir tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ps4 Slim failure rate survey, Google docs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfLoB5AtioY6xXptKwbmCd_kAy95d70s6GIwhBSZwu6D_nsAg/viewform

Repost cuz I used a URL shortener:

Just bought me a slim, did Googling beforehand and not much info on failure rates (it's just over 4 months old so no real surprise). But thought out of the sake of curiosity I'd try to collect some data. I'm sure the rate is super low, but for science (or my curiosity)!

Will post results (edit:if any real results to post /edit), also made results viewable by anyone.

Edit: collect email address/username are off. Signin required incase someone wants to cheat my dinky little survey, unless they have many gmails but who'd go through that for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, it's a gimmick to me. Albeit a nice one. Unfortunately due to bad DS4 battery life I have mine off to save battery, it is a nice little feature in games that use it though.


Edit:

Doh, I feel like an idiot. This is what I get for being up at 4 am and only speed reading the title; I thought OP meant the speaker. Yes headphones through controller is amazing.

Edit 2: I don't understand the downvotes, I edited in that I made a mistake within like 15 seconds of posting this. Meh, welcome to Reddit I guess? (Kidding, I love you all, even the for no reason downvoters) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ps4 slim failure rate survey, Google docs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, as a smoker, I think some smokers do some research (I have, this is also cuz we actively smoke so it seriously affects us) into it and then get mad when old studies are cited and etc. Not to say any newer "pro" (it not being as bad as thought) studies are accurate, but hey that's science I guess (or not, dunno no PhD here).

Also to be fair it is still worse than just good old air (unless you're in China, and maybe LA haha) AND the smell legitly bothers many, and asthma etc, which are very very very fair con stances. When I smoke in public (edit: outside I would never try and smoke i doors /edit) I try to stand down wind and 15+ feet from people. I also ask people nearby if it'll bother them. There are always bystander passerbys but I try to step away from them if I see them coming. I'm sure I bother many, but I do my best to limit the damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhh Dan, don't worry. We just want what's best for you. Sleep tight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A Democrat is nothing but a Republican in disguise"

"A Republican is nothing but a Democrat in disguise"

Both these statements are true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have anxiety problems so I can understand that. Sometimes when things make you anxious there's no explaining it beyond "it bothers me/gives me anxiety". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Renew your gold now - ending 01.01.2025"

Gotta make sure you don't lapse, I don't think 9 years is enough notice though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, but being honest I wouldn't hold my breath. I know on here and Xbox's own official forums/discussions it's been requested/talked to death and it still hasn't been fixed. But whether or not it ever gets fixed I agree it should.

I hate the intrusiveness of social media/social platforms period including XBL and PSN, like with FB I don't like how people can see when you read messages/are replying. Sure have it as a feature but allow us to turn it off, appear offline, etc. I don't post my life to FB (though not knocking those who do) and if I don't want to reply to someone when they send the message I don't need them asking 3 hours later if I'm mad because I didn't reply but read it.

And people who say if you can't live without these fairly basic privacy features says you should just delete/unfriend/block/cut out of your life anyone it happens with are just full of shit. It wouldn't get to that point if these features just existed and worked, and just because that is your (people who say just deal with it basically) problem we don't need these features need to realize they aren't some grand guru of wisdom and when they sayeth block/delete them it isn't some mystic all knowing answer that is an implied truth of life.

Anyway, sorry /rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I talk a lot of shit for what we (the US) does on the world stage. Then on the 9th of November when Trump won I kind of realized I was a hypocrite. Despite all the shit I talked I realized that I don't want the US to step down from it's roll. I may be being selfish as fuck, but I started thinking of how things could go under a Chinese or Russian world leadership. And don't get me wrong, maybe the world would do better but I don't think it's a risk I really want to see now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only kind of wrestling match worth having.

(It's a joke before a billion downvotes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
