<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject414</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always, I mean never... 

Seriously, my one golden rule is if I come into a gig and the rig is already built or partially built, I will go over every connector and remake any I deem not worthy. In effect, I don't ever want to have to say to an artist that whatever failed was somebody else's fault ("Hey, I DIDN'T build that cable")

That said, I don't just go into a gig and rip everything out and start over just to spend the band's money (a very common occurrence).

Also, I have used soldered and solderless cables and have had equal failure with both. I've also used just about every manufacturers connectors, some I like, some I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to that, I always tell an artist, and I don't care who it is or how big their rig is, I will plug the guitar straight into the amp if that's the only way to make sound in front of the crowd. I'll then work on fixing the problem or subbing in a backup rig, but not take the whole show down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily they have been few and far between. Live TV is the worst though for little gremlins and such. When I did Live 8 in Berlin with Green Day, they couldn't get the acoustic DI line to work on Jason White's guitar for 'Blvd of Broken Dreams' (a pretty big deal). I took a Boss Acoustic Simulator pedal and put it in-line to fake the Acoustic signal, my guitar player (Jason) couldn't hear it in his monitors, but at least it was there for the TV broadcast... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there have been a lot of guitars over the years (too many to count). But playing and working on Malcolm Young's early 60's Gretsch guitars (last year when I worked for Stevie Young) was probably the coolest most iconic guitars I've held on to. And Brad Whitford has some nice vintage stuff too, 'bursts, Strats, Teles, SG's, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been lucky that almost everyone I've worked for has been cool and most have been great players. I must say working with the Black Crowes backing Jimmy Page in 2000 was definitely one of the coolest. Jimmy was such a great person to be around and he loves playing music.

Working on the Experience Hendrix tour, I must say I was surrounded by great players, Eric Gales, Eric Johnson, Dweezil Zappa, Vernon Reid, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it happens. Wonder how often it happens to him? ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every model we have produced is it's own design, not a copy of this circuit or that circuit. We mostly try to shoot for a certain 'sound' we have in our heads. Our first amp The Orangutan was aimed at nailing the guitar sounds we heard on 70's records like Humble Pie, Aerosmith, ZZ Top, etc. 

All of our standard amp models are available on our website, and we do a lot of Custom stuff too. We build to order, so we don't have a shelf full of completed amps, every one is built from the ground up after the order is placed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brad is a great friend and boss. Yes, his role in 3 Monkeys is more of a promotional one, but he has great ideas and input on stuff just like Ossie and I do. 

I was actually gonna start an amp business on my own when Ossie, who founded Blockhead Amps, said he's like to start a new company with me, which was great, he's already been doing it 10+ years. Anyway, we were having dinner with Brad, mentioned the amp company to him and he said "I want in on that". So we made him a partner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA] Greg Howard from 3 Monkeys Amps here to answer your questions! Ask Me Manything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hello redditors!! Im Greg Howard a 20+ year veteran touring guitar tech who has worked for a few cool bands over the years. Worked with Brad Whitford of Aerosmith off and on since 2002, worked for AC/DC in 2016, also Green Day, Daryl Hall and John Oates, Linking Park, Steely Dan, Jimmy Page   The Black Crowes, The Verve Pipe, Cry of Love, along with many others.

In 2007 I started 3 Monkeys Amps with my partners Ossie Ahsen and Brad Whitford https://www.3monkeysamps.com recently we invented a solderless cable system for DC power cables called DC Solderless.

Glad to answer any and all questions about touring, guitar teching, rig building, amps, guitar setups, pedals, pedalboards, our DC Solderless cables, etc. 

So AMA!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe? Looks delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
