<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7184</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar situation (though mine was not international, I have a suspicion that what I ordered actually is coming from overseas) so I just sent a note via RedditGifts to my giftee to let her know the other 2 packages are going to be a bit.  She was totally cool with it - maybe you can do the same! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so very sorry for your losses, OP.  I know that I am a random internet stranger, but if you ever want or need someone to just sit there and listen I will be that person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the current salary already has? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I've never seen anyone with a total negative karma before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it said "duck-nipples" and then I was more confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to also recommend a keto diet.  Best part about it is that you don't actually have to work out to lose weight.  Nothing will be toned, but you'll be skinnier :)  And that's a start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But would you die to know your wife and kids are safe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> harder in that there will be many points when one or both are crying because their needs are not being met RIGHT NOW

How do you deal with this :(  This is one of my biggest worries about having a second baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doggo Treats! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link?  I would love to see :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glory to the Alliance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can have access to a mount, a pet, tabards, shirts, and some leveling gear depending on what achievements your guild has completed, too.

I'm not entirely sure about the comments of your post, though.  I guess an unofficial perk of being in a guild is that you can be carried through dungeons and funneled gear you didn't necessarily earn.

Imo, this person doesn't sound like someone you should worry too much about.  Block and move on to working on your guild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a ton of ~~friends~~ gold.

FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You pay to play.  You should be having fun.  If you're not, then you're essentially paying to suffer.  For those guildmates that you're both friendly with, add them to your B-Net   explain why you are leaving if you'd like.  Then, leave.  You owe the rest of the guild nothing.  If the game is not fun for you but they are enjoying themselves, having your dps shouldn't make or break them.

Join that other guild that offered you a spot.  Or try out a couple different guilds until you find one that fits.  You still have plenty of time before ToS so you should find someplace that works for the both of you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also true.

(Can confirm.  Currently undergoing a war w/ my family about getting my own kiddo baptized.  e_e) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catholics claim unbaptized babies go to purgatory/limbo, not Hell.

I read a sci-fi book that claimed babies could go to Hell if they were born of incest or rape.

I guess both are equally good and believable sources.  Now for the ultimate mind-fuck.  Did the baby born there in Hell have a Soul? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast I made 2 scrambled eggs (can be any style though) with some combination of onions, mushrooms, tomatoes, asparagus, or spinach.  Cooked with a small amt of vegetable oil.  I use various different Mrs. Dash spices.

Lunch is always a salad b/c it's the easiest to make and take to work.  Lettuce, onions, carrots, mushrooms, celery, usually chicken (but sometimes steak or hamburger, depending on what was for dinner the night before.)  Apple Cider Vinegar and Vegetable Oil for dressing.

Dinner is a meat (chicken, steak, salmon, lean hamburger no buns!), and a veggie.  (NO CORN!  String beans, peas, broccoli, onions, mushrooms, etc.)

There *are* vegan versions of this, if that's your thing, but I don't know what they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep mine brief but if you're wanting more details please feel free to inbox me.  I started a keto diet at the end of last April.  I've been on-and-off strictly faithful to it (usually in about 3-month chunks, then I will take a couple of weeks or so and eat all the things b/c hey, I like to holiday and birthday lol.)  In that time (what will actually be a year at the end of this April) I have lost 35 lbs and kept it off, even with the cheat-times.  I am skinnier in a way that I never was before, even when I had time to go to the gym and run 2 miles a day.  I feel better mentally and physically.  When I'm on it 100% I do not have lingering pain in my hip that I sometimes have.  I have more energy.  I feel like I'm in high school again.  My skin looks amazing.

Starting it sucks.  Hard.  The first 2-3 weeks are sheer hell as you first get through your sugar/carb cravings and adjust to portion control.  You might stab someone.  But you get through it and you feel so much better; you do not crave; you actually feel FULL after eating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for posting this, b/c I often think about it but I haven't really asked about it as I'm still quite a bit aways from this.  This is what I've been thinking myself.  I did not have a lot of freedoms when I was growing up (though I was a very good kid, never got into trouble) so I was pretty sheltered, whereas my husband had virtually no restrictions (and yet somehow he was a basically good kid, would only occasionally get into trouble.)  We want to have a happy medium of the 2 styles of parenting.

1.)  I was thinking I'd let BabySpawn play in our backyard alone around 5, maybe next door with the neighbor kids, though there is a couple of years' age difference, so I'm not sure they'd even be interested in him.  Also he'd be out there with our dog.  We live in a quite, nice neighbourhood.

2.)  10 years old for a quick 15-20 min, 12+ for longer.  (There are no laws in my state for a minimum age to be alone.)

3.)  6+, but I would have to meet the parents first, and I'd be dropping BabySpawn off.

4.)  Our walk to what will be BabySpawn's K-4th grade isn't very far but I intend to walk with him at least until 4th grade.  This one I probably won't even stop doing unless he asks to walk alone.

Overall though I think it will depend on BabySpawn's mentality and behavior when he's old enough for this even to matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, just LOOK at my son.  He's a sexy lover.  /s

Omg I felt dirty just typing that out _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sending you some rum right now!  Ffs I was worked up just reading that.  I admire that you can (mostly lol) handle that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so happy for you :)

PS - If you have questions about a keto diet please fee free to inbox me.  I currently do it for a family of 3 (though 1 is a BabySpawn!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be lying if I said no here lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so satisfying to look at :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't lie.  They are actual magic shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your class, I would think.

But basically Deadly Boss Mods, Skada, GTFO, WeakAuras, TomTom, GarrisonMissionManager </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also happening to me, and yes, my region is correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is kind of a general tanking question.

I am wanting to try out tanking.  I have never tanked before.  Do you have any advice?  Not necessarily "press these buttons when X happens" but more mental advice, or things you wished someone taught you when you were learning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Left Freshly Cut Asparagus in a Cup of Water   It Kept Growing Out the Tops! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried to contact your Santa?

2 of the 3 packages I ordered for 1 of my giftees didn't have tracking numbers so I messaged her and let her know the range of dates they'd be arriving.  Maybe you could ask your Santa if there is a similar situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried to give him his own tasks?  For example, I expect you to empty and load the dishwasher daily as needed, vacuum the entire house on Tues and Thurs, and bring the laundry basket downstairs on Fridays?

Maybe he really does want to help, but b/c he's so spaced out, he doesn't think about doing these things?  I can space out a lot myself, so I've found making myself a list helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It cost me just over $15.00 to ship my snacks b/c I bought them locally rather than using Amazon like I usually do for all of my other exchanges.  It was prob the most expensive shipment I've had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having this issue, too.  I hasn't fixed itself.  I wonder if it's some kind of error.  I've tried from 2 different computers, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try not to react to the screaming part and narrate for him "You are mad because you don't want to get your diaper changed, you want to keep playing." stuff

That's a really good idea.  I need to steal this.  When BabySpawn would cry in his seat and nothing I could do would help, I would just turn up the radio to try to drown him out.  Most of the time he would stop and listen.  Which is prob why when the Backstreet Boys came on the other day, he was singing with them, "Bye-bye." bye-bye-bye lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mind me, just cutting onions right here at my desk...T___T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave the house for a few hours, and leave him with the baby.  Even if you're just going to your parents' house to relax and nap, it's "freedom" and some time for you.  It might be that your toddler knows you're around at home, so that's why he's throwing a fit, but if you're not actually home he might calm down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np, I'm going to go see if I can find the exact date I made that graphic when I go home.  B/c I'm really curious now lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can def say that I have heard that song before 2009.  I remember b/c I made a MySpace layout with the lyric "Will you miss me while you're looking for yourself out there" in reference to the guy I was dating at the time considering moving very far away from home (  me) to go to college.  We broke up in 2007.  Sooo.....there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is real, why would your family suddenly be erased?  Do you think you are somehow the subject of an experiment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the second version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also this was an episode of Star Trek:  TNG.  Actually it's my fav episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessss!  I hope you get me sometime :D

Now, having said that, I always specifically mention I like homemade gifts, even if that is one of the premade questions of the exchange.  Keep in mind not everyone is this way, and if they don't specifically say they want a homemade gift, ask.  Don't take it personally if they say no, either.  I don't.  After all, less work for me ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to agree with the ladies who posted here.

1- Take care of yourself.  Please go see a doctor and get meds if you need them.  When you are in a better frame of mind, you can face so much more than you ever thought.  Speaking from experience...just taking daily vitamins (and yes, one of them is Vitamin D!) helped me do a mental 180^o

2 - Set a routine for Baby.  Doesn't matter when you do it, or what exactly you do, but the main thing is that you are consistent.  (We do snack, bathtime, jammies, story, Twinkle Star, bed.)  We start at the same time every night and BabySpawn is generally in the crib at the same time every night.  If your sleeping is happening during the day, invest in a room-darkening shade.  The difference of sleep between having this vs not is freaking shocking.  I have personally witnessed it myself.

3 - Good luck.  You are brave and strong and incredible for taking care of a baby alone.  Please remember this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, mama!  I cannot imagine.  Weaning our nighttime bottle was rough for a week, but you...all the hugs and good sleep vibes to you   your kiddo :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never know; my weirdo dog actually *liked* the sour apple stuff, soooo that might backfire xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind if I PM'ed you about the ab-split?  I have a couple of questions and I don't want to hijack OP's thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought "ftw" was something bad for the longest time when it first came out e_e

Also I think that's bs.  "Wander the Forrest" isn't bad at all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's basically pretty simple, but it IS a serious commitment, so please remember that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if someone doesn't send their rematch gift, or if a user doesn't post their rematch gift, are they also punished?  B/c last I heard, there was no punishment for that, but I could have read it wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep asking for homemade stuff, and so far no dice T__T  I would rather have a thoughtful handmade present over something that cost $100. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ffs I swear there's a secret club they all belong to that they go to when we're sleeping so they can discuss these behaviours xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's just fine, and who knows where I will be when BabySpawn is old enough to care.  Growing up myself I didn't have a TV in my room, and I only had a computer in my room when I was in college.  During my waking time, my younger brother and I watched A LOT of tv.  Sure, we'd be colouring or something in front of it, but it was always on.  Didn't bother us at all.  We turned out fine.

Heck, even now I will put BabySpawn in front of the computer or TV with cartoons on so he can watch and I can get some chores done.  It's not that big a deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing wrong with being selfish once in a while :D  Good luck with your classes!  Looking forward to the ! Update about you passing the classes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there.  I think we all have been at least once or twice.  We're only human.  I'm sure she (and BabySpawn, and all kiddos) have forgiven their parents, and still love us :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear our SOs are just as bad, if not worse than our kids e_e </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what I was thinking.  Nothing inside the eggs, not going to dye them at this point.  But when he's older and knows what things are more, it will hopefully evolve slightly lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coughing and Peeing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on mobile in my bathroom.  I've had a cough for a few days, nothing else, no other symptoms but the past 2 days it's gotten worse.  I really, really wish I could cough without peeing myself a little bit.  I have changed my pants 3x today. I feel like I need adult diapers.  Please ye gods, why  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did twice.  One was a dream I had slightly reworked, and the other was only true in the "I put my hand on a pipe and I could feel it sucking but I obv didn't get sucked down irl" kind of draw.  Both of those stories were not well received. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I *wish* that my 10 was that high LOL - If that's the scale I'm much lower xD  I just meant that I wanted 1 b/c I've seen the commercial and I was curious.  A free dinner would help me in that yay I don't have to plan it, not that I need this to make it through a week.  I guess I worded my scale poorly.  I'll see myself out now -_-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to try this; but on a scale of "need" 1-10, I'm a 10 so please give it to someone else who may need it more.  If you have any left over, then send 1 my way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know your whole story.  Has Dax been "officially" diagnosed yet?  Maybe he's just writing it off b/c you're guessing, rather than having a medical diagnosis?

You might want to also ask yourself  - What do you hope to gain from his acknowledging Dax's autism?  In what ways do you want him to treat Dax differently than he may already?  How do you want your father to "step up as a grandfather?"  Maybe your father doesn't know what you want from him.

Idk, this is just my supposing, like I said I don't know the whole story or what your email lined out.  Hope it helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO MUCH THIS OMG.

Some video games have subscription fees, too, so if he "afford that" he can afford to pay what you deserve.  Don't let him use your guilt against you.

EDIT:  guilT not guilD - maybe I play too many video games ~_~;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually doing the same for my son!!  But, I don't plan on giving it to him until he's 18, so I've been pretty frank about a lot of things.  My hope is that he will be able to process everything when he is that age.  If not, I might hold it until he's 21.  Not sure when you plan to turn it over to your daughter, so that might be a factor for you, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Old Navy Chinos def qualify.  I wear them to job interviews.

As far as the dress code, I would follow it exactly for the first week or so until you see what everyone else is wearing.  My place is supposed to be business casual (like a teller would wear, for example..no jeans, etc) - everyone here wears jeans, not even nice ones...heck, people wear PJs.

Congrats on the new job, and good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear there was something in the air last night.  BabySpawn woke up at 6am flipping the fuck out for literally no reason.  (Well I guess there was *some* reason but we couldn't figure it out either :()  It always seems to happen when we think about having #2.  I guess the universe is trying to warn us ;)

Good luck, and have a cup of coffee ~~with Kahlua~~ for me :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celebrating Easter (The Basket, the Eggs, the Stuff!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kiddo is 15 months old, and this year I want to start an Easter tradition (even though my husband and I are not Catholic) with the basket, hiding eggs, stuff like that.

But, I don't want to go too crazy b/c he's only 15 months and I'm not really sure how much he'll be interested.  (He was 12 mo at Christmas and could care less about presents.  I honestly hoped he'd rip paper or something, but no lol.  So I don't want to set my expectation bar too high.)

I was thinking of getting a basket with a new swimsuit (which would be a thing until he was older; then maybe a highly desired sweatshirt or something), a box of snacks (again, this could evolve to preference with age), and a new toy for outside (yet another thing that could 'grow' with the kiddo.)  I want to do a super-mini Easter Egg Hunt - literally hide like 2 eggs and walk him over to them to show him.

My question is, is that enough?  Will he "get" it?  Will he be even remotely interested, or should I just shelf this until next year and he's over 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could possibly be that he's waking up b/c he's understanding object permanence; therefore he's realizing you're not there and waking up missing you.  It could possibly be his teeth, or it could be anything.  Hope everything gets better for you though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bankstud the Studly Banker Toon agrees with this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind seeing really awesome art on the front page, and seeing a silly MSPaint picture was funny the first couple of times, but those are annoying af.  I guess as long as the art is amazing, I don't mind seeing it sometimes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a girl? B/c I'm a gril and I think he should be pick for his heart, too 3

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/aphoenix best Mod 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, guys.  I'd like to say that people will go easy on you, but I don't want to lie _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, but didn't receive any responses there :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the notice ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly for fun.  I post here looking to improve but sometimes it's hard to interpret what will do well and what won't.  Plus I'd be lying if I didn't say that I like the feeling I get when something I created is received positively :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying we actually get cuddles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Hayong and /u/iia write a story together where all the babies and kids live happily ever after b/c technology saved them in the end, but the Souls of the people who created the technology were sacrificed for this to happen.  Plot twist, the creators were the kids' parents...though still alive and functioning like normal, they are devoid of Souls :*( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happens to me, too.  I've always wondered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?  I wish I could ask people, or they had to provide some kind of reason, even if it's "I didn't like it" or "This is boring."  At least it's *something*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost never vote at all.  I will only down-vote if the story doesn't make sense and has a ton of grammatical flaws.  (Please note when I say "doesn't make sense" I don't mean that I don't get it.  I read the comments if I missed something and if I still don't understand, I'll just leave it alone.)  I only up-vote if the story really, really gets to me.  Though, I've gotten better with using my "power" lately, throwing more positive up-votes out there b/c now I realize that there's not some kind of limit on how much you can up-vote.

It is really, really crushing when I post a story and it's getting nothing but down votes right away, so they got almost no attention.  Actually I've noticed for the past month or so this has been the case.

I don't believe that everything I write should have thousands of upvotes, but I really wish I knew why that was happening.  Are my stories not dark enough?  Not believable?  Did you just not like it?  Where am I missing the mark?  I feel like the stories I try on get nothing but the bullshit ones I write get upvotes.  It's weird and makes it hard to improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited for the comedic horror.  That's always good to read, especially when it's done well.  Not sure about the gore/torture bit, but I guess as long as there are updated tags to warn about it, it might not be such a big deal.  Then again, I sometimes see things that should be flagged but aren't, so idk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it permissible to eat the eel in sushi, or does it have to be plain?  Asking for a friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the minimum we're to spend again?  Is it $20.00? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ye gods yes.  I literally make shit-all at my full time (!) job, but without my meager income we couldn't even afford my house.  And trying to find something else?  Impossible.  Since I appear to be overqualified for anything similar in my field.  (Like literally, put me in entry level for the same as I make now and promote me, plz I promise, b/c my current company doesn't promote anyone ever.)  I really put in 70+ apps through Indeed and got 1 phone call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's stupid af.  I thought the whole point of being a "feminist" is to be able to have a choice for what a woman wants to do.  If she wants to have a career, not have kids, get married, have 10 kids, whatever - it's being able to have the choice to do what she wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very relatable to you; my situation is similar though I'm not a SAHM.

Have you considered trying to work at a fast food place - as a manager?  Or maybe even their corporate offices?  Just throwing it out there.  It's so frustrating to find a decent job.  I really think it's 10% luck and 90% who you know anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's such an awesome gift, and a great way to learn how!  After you get through that, you'll be getting to scarves and blankets easily!  Enjoy :D

(PS - No, I am not your Santa.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Beat skorpyon without leaving circle",  "Beat tichondrius without getting hit by that crap 

Those are achievements, but I think only Tich's is personal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I didn't get it either xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats, ~~nerds~~ friends!  Tbh yours was my fav as well!  Looking forward to next round :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, you don't even know me.  I'm really nice, I swear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks - looks like you're the only one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg that would have been hilarious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

Also, I saw this and I thought it was Friday :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Clog in My Pipes is Pretty Serious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No joke.  Its April 1st and my second wife of only 4 months is doing laundry.  Shes trying to finish cleaning the house because shes having people over for my birthday later tonight.  When suddenly, the pipe backs up, expelling soapy water all over the floor of our basement.  When the previous owners of our house remodeled, they thought that it would be a good idea to leave the grey accordion pipe of the washing machine unattached and just placed into a larger black pipe that attaches to the sewer pipe.  This is where all that water came spilling from.


To my wifes credit, she cleans it up herself while Im at the hardware store buying a new doorbell, but she doesnt know how to fix the clog.  I really love her.  She's stunning, but not that bright.  We met by chance at a local bar.  She was new in town, and I was her first new friend.  Then, something more.


I dont know what happened, she tells me as I come through the front door.  I didnt realize the water was spilling out, and now I keep hearing a strange snuffling noise coming from the pipes.  Like I said, gorgeous but not too bright.


I tell her not to worry.  Ive had this happen in the past, so I know I can handle this.  I place an old paint tray under the pipe access cap and use my pipe wrench to loosen the cap.  Foul, swamp-smelling water starts pouring out over the edges in little rivulets.  For smelling like it does, the water is surprisingly clear.  As the paint tray fills, I replace the cap and dump the water into a bucket.  I repeat this process a few times, until Im able to dump a little Drano into the opening.  I hear some moaning.  Just the air in the pipes, I reassure my wife.


After about 20 minutes, I fill the bucket with hot water and head to the kitchen sink.  I tell my wife to place her hand over the opening of the black pipe where the water originally spilled from, and she complies.  I start dumping the hot water down the drain.  At first nothing happens, but I know things will start moving along soon enough.  I hear my wife gasp in surprise from downstairs.  I-its starting to suck my hand a little, she calls.  I assure her that this is natural.  The water still floats in the kitchen sink, but I can see the clog is going to be loosening soon.  She cries out again.  The hot water starts to move, swirling in the sink.  The suction is now strong, very strong.  She sobs.


I run down the steps to check our progress.  I see that her left hand, the hand that she had placed over the pipe opening, has now been sucked down the pipe.  Her arm is now down that pipe up to her elbow.  Red blood has sprayed against the white paint on the wall.  She is pulling, pulling.  But so is the suction.  She turns to me, eyes wide with shock.  Every time she tugs back, more of her arm gets pulled down the pipe.  She pulls up a bit; I can see bone.  All her flesh has been melted away.  P-pleasehelp mee she begs.  I lick my lips.  I hear crackles and snaps.  That would be her bone, I think.


Her arm is yanked even further down, now to mid-bicep.  The flesh is purpling, bruising, practically bursting with blood with no place to go.  Another tug and her arm is gone up to her shoulder.  At this point shes screaming, so its a good thing were in the basement.  Somehow, it pulls, and pulls, and suddenly shes missing her arm completely.  Blood is spraying everywhere, incredibly red.  She struggles feebly as I hold her open wound over the pipe, and her blood is sucked down the drain.  After an eternity, it seems like she stops struggling.


I drag her to the manhole cover in my basement.  That was another lovely edition from the previous homeowners.  I unlock the cap, and roll my wifes body into the opening.  The growling from the pipes is louder without the lid, but it stops seconds after I hear the wet plop of my wifes body landing on something.  I love you, honey.  Until next time, I call down as I carefully replace the cover and lock.  My first wife can be so serious sometimes, especially about eating.  She never has time for small talk during that time.


I leave the grey accordion pipe out of its larger black pipe hookup.  Good thing the tentacles will come out and clean up the blood, before my family  no, my fellow cultists  come over.  After all, its my birthday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just keep waiting for Baby Steaks... :*( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or that nasty padding they put under it.

Fyi it's called a diaper.  The more you know, lol.  Anyway, I'm sorry for your loss, OP.  I hope you find out whatever it is...wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my only hope T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, off-topic but I have to tell you - I started saying your tagline this weekend.  I knew it was someone, but I didn't know it was you.  xD  So thanks for that, so applicable right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As some other users have mentioned, maybe something happened to him.  My best friend's bf at the time ghosted her for a couple of days b/c he lost his cell phone, and he doesn't have any kind of social media.  Silly things like that happen.  Hoping for the best for you.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very possible.  They say ever baby is different.  Maybe he's just more easy-going this way.  All I would say is don't change anything, if it's working.  Whatever you do, be consistent :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if they feel like you should have pro-level gear, you can always ask them to gift it to you on your birthday or something since you deserve the best ;) /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it makes you feel better, take solace in the fact that all of your babies can hopefully hit the toilet ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh mama I understand you.  I thought I wanted to be a SAHM, and I realized that I simply could not do it.  So firstly, let me just say huge props to you for being one!  I really admire you for it.  Is there any way you can leave the house 1x a night to join a hobby you might enjoy?  Or if you wanted, get a job for a couple of hours a week?  Or volunteer somewhere?  Or join a gym and go to a couple of spin classes (or something like that?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omfg, Husband used to be this way, too.  I was like, I enjoy le sexy time but I cannot relax when BabySpawn is shrieking in the next room.  I know he's mostly fine but still.

What we ended up doing is scheduling in Sexy Time.  Which I know kind of sucks, b/c there's little room for being spontaneous, but at least all of our bits are satisfied.  Maybe that could work for you guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time I wouldn't take BabySpawn out is if he had a fever.  (Or if he was barfing.)  Otherwise, I still take him to the babysitter's house, or I take him out and about.  Seems like it makes him feel better, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that was me this weekend.  With you in sympathy.  Hope everyone feels better soon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU By Wanting to Clean My House... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well actually it was yesterday, but now I can laugh about it b/c it was yesterday.  (Mostly.  I am still crying inside.)

Friday night BabySpawn was throwing up at my parents' house.  It only lasted a few hours, but it sucked.  Saturday I didn't feel quite right, but I didn't throw up or pee out of my butt.  Mostly lazed around the house.  Sunday I decided that I was going to give our house a much-needed spring cleaning before my family comes over for birthday cake.  (Tuesday is my birthday.)  Therein lies my fuckup.

I scrub my bathroom and powder room.  I'm talking wipe down all the little spots you never do on a weekly basis.  I lovingly clean like I used to when I was single and bored.  I'm so proud of myself.  I've cleaned both bathrooms and changed the sets (matching shower curtain, soap dispensers, etc.)  I breathe a sigh of relief.  I vacuum, and steam clean our floors.  (Meanwhile Husband is upstairs taking a nap and BabySpawn is in his highchair eating lunch and watching Bubble Guppies, laughing and happy.  DogSpawn is underfoot, waiting for the inevitable food to drop.)

Husband wanders into the bathroom pale af.  Moans a few times, saying he's going to be sick.  I tell him to relax, and I leave b/c guys, I cannot handle puke.  WELL...A GROWN ASS MAN manages to miss the toilet and pukes all over my freshly cleaned WALL and toilet.  NOPE.COM - I tell him as nice as possible to plz clean up the chunks b/c I cannot.  (Which he does.)  He goes back to laying down.  RIP my clean bathroom.  I wipe down everything he just destroyed.  BUT WAIT THERE'S MORE.

I go to check the dog and baby, wanting to put DogSpawn outside so he can potty.  I notice DogSpawn is covered in some kind of weird brown splatters.  Which I don't understand b/c BabySpawn was eating buttered pasta; nothing brown like that.  I go over to BabySpawn, who is still laughing to Shimmer   Shine...I notice the same brown goo all over his sock.  AND THAT'S WHEN I KNEW - IT WAS POOP!

I drag the dog outside and hose him off, then let him loose in the backyard.  I pick up BabySpawn from the chair and take him directly to my freshly cleaned tub ;_; wherein brown water starts to immediately seep from BabySpawn's pants...(*Dies*)  I strip BabySpawn and start rinsing his clothes and give him a bath.  DURING THIS...Husband rushes in, mumbles, "I'm sorry...BAAAAAAAAAAAARRRRRFFFFFFFFF!"  (At least he got it all in the toilet.)  I start gagging but I hold it all in by some miracle.  Husband runs away again.  I finish up with BabySpawn, get him all dressed as a I text my family to not come over b/c Husband is not feeling well.  I take all the padding off the highchair and throw it in the washing machine.  I take my bathroom rug that now has poopy footprints from BabySpawn all over it and wipe it off as best as I can, and throw that in the washing machine.  I bleach my tub (again.)  BUT WAIT THERE IS MORE!

I go into our bedroom to tell Husband that we're just going to go to my parents' house instead, I need to hop in the shower b/c I feel like I'm covered in puke and poop.  "Okay,' he mumbles.  "But just so you know, while you were washing BabySpawn, I had really bad diarrhea in the power room downstairs."

And that, folks, is why I am never spring cleaning my house again.  T___T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooo TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't even make sense b/c didn't the Lost Desert plot have the 2 main characters fall in love? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Bri Codestone to User 'koolkidz12345'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, but I can't find your requests! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
