<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9822</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I didn't have the taste for them either, now my body is just used to them and quit fighting haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. I'm still overweight and very, very inflexible but I love it so I'm just going to keep working at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100lbs is nothing in the long run, you'll kill it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've managed to find that happy medium in my diet where I can lose fat/gaining muscle. I've had the opposite problem of you though, I couldn't get myself to eat enough calories. It's all about listening to your body which I think you got, keep it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally Reached the 100lbs Lost Mark! - M23, 6'0, 230lbs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before and after photo: http://imgur.com/T4U4C1W

A year and a half into my lifestyle change, I finally stepped on the scale and was at 101lbs lost. Such an amazing feeling, words cannot even describe it. As I sit here writing I'm in the verge of tears looking back on this journey. I was a fat slob, depressed/suicidal and absolutely zero confidence. Now I'm working out five days a week, doing Capoeria two days a week, completely switched to a plant based diet and just so satiated in life. The confidence hasn't fully came around yet, I still see myself as the fat version when I look in the mirror. I'm sure that will change with time though. Never thought I would be this happy but la dee da, here I am. Only 30lbs to go...a year ago that would have sounded like a ton but now, that's weak sauce baby.

My biggest tip to those just starting out: think of this journey in three parts, tackled in sequence. Mental, Diet, Exercise. Tackle your inner demons so they don't hold you back, get that diet on point and exercise to tone your body. The rest works itself out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 23:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda visceral here: I had a complete emotional meltdown, tore my entire room apart. Looked at myself in my mirror and ending up punching it in a fat rage. Contemplated digging out the fat with one of the broken pieces of glass. That's when I decided to live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started with a personal trainer here in the states and he is the best thing that's happened to me. I even pay a ton more than you, about 200 more, and still think it's the best thing I've ever done with my money. In one month he's managed to help me lose 27 pounds of fat, put on 14 pounds of muscle and lose 11% body fat. Definitely a great investment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome, I love the system you have going. Wish I would have thought of that earlier!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, my body is changing so quickly, trying to stay away from clothes as much as I can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I try to avoid clothes because my body is changing sooooo rapidly. My jeans I bought a month ago don't even fit any more. I will think of something I'm sure though hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and past fat self love to couple it with a nice cup of chili, complete with said cheese sauce and a nice Sam Adams. Just looked it up - a casual 1,453 calories in a single sitting. Good lawd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gifting Yourself for Weight Loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, 

Getting ready to hit the 100lbs mark sometime within the two-three weeks and although I won't be at my overall goal after the 100lbs loss, I wanted to get myself a little something for hitting the big 100. Have any of you guys bought yourself gifts/rewards during your weight loss journey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I weight myself every Sunday morning, butt naked, right after I use the restroom but before I eat. I used to weight myself every day but the weight fluctuations can make your head spin/make you too obsessive. Once a week will show you a fairly consistent reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god I have a real great one for you. I live in Central Illinois where the food of choice is a horseshoe. Essentially a bed of diabetes which includes a slab of toast, piled with your choice of protein (I usually went fried chicken), then topped with french fries, then topped with cheese sauce from the gods themselves. Needless to say that's about as many calories in one meal as I eat in a day now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
