<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3445</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toledo Police officer indicted on charges he solicited sex from a minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Members of Local 338 RWDSU/UFCW recently donated and delivered 250 turkeys to Our Lady of Graces food pantry in Howard Beach, and other food pantries across the five boroughs and Long Island as part of the unions annual Turkey Drive just in time for Thanksgiving. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Devotes Life to Adopting Animals Who Can't Find Homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Lucas County grand jury has indicted a Toledo police officer on two counts of unlawful sexual conduct with a minor and two counts of compelling prostitution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toledo Police Officer Arrested On Sex And Prostitution Charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study Finds Cannabis Is Not A Gateway Drug. It's A Exit Drug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two teens build replica of USS Arizona to raise money for Indiana veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Ignore the pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carbon-14 measurements on 231 elephant ivory specimens from 14 large ivory seizures (0.5 ton) made between 2002 and 2014 show that most ivory (ca. 90%) was derived from animals that had died less than 3 y before ivory was confiscated. This indicates that the assumption of recent elephant death for mortality estimates of African elephants is correct: Very little old ivory is included in large ivory shipments from Africa. We found only one specimen of the 231 analyzed to have a lag time longer than 6 y. Patterns of trade differ by regions: East African ivory, based on genetic assignments of geographic origin, has a much higher fraction of rapid transit than ivory originating in the Tridom region of CameroonGabonCongo. Carbon-14 is an important tool in understanding patterns of movement of illegal wildlife products.

http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/11/02/1614938113.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seized ivory comes almost exclusively from recent poaching: study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clean vehicle rebates benefit wealthy, white Californians, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These marijuana investors are ready to spend millions if California passes Prop 64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These marijuana investors are ready to spend millions if California passes Prop 64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These marijuana investors are ready to spend millions if California passes Prop 64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> APD officer charged with assaulting family member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elementary school kids suspended over Kool-Aid mixed with sugar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sugar suspensions: 'Happy Crack' gets South Carolina elementary students kicked out of school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin police officer arrested, accused of assaulting family member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political betting markets show late momentum shift towards Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political betting markets show late momentum shift towards Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political betting markets show late momentum shift towards Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had a couple of fans rooting for him for a minute too. He took to it pretty quickly. Now, I just have to focus on his form. Thanks for taking a look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Not A Job Creator He Is A Sexual Perpetrator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Not A Job Creator He Is A Sexual Perpetrator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] After about 12 tries my 6 yr old son (who spends his free time gaming) made his first unassisted basket with a full-size basketball. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SC elementary students suspended for having Kool-Aid, sugar mixture called happy crack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee student suspended for taking extra chicken nugget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student suspended for taking extra chicken nugget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mom gives birth in hospital parking lot, charged full delivery room fee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannabis Arrests Plummet in Washington State After Legalization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington State Patrol Sergeant: "Prior to legalization in Washington state, odor alone was enough to arrest (90% of his felony arrests)... Now (after legalization) when I stop a vehicle... and I smell marijuana," if its operated by a unimpaired, law-abiding driver, it's simply, "Have a nice day." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emotionally disturbed man Tasered by police dies in the Bronx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago cop arrested on charges he sex trafficked underage girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa Police Arrest Suspect in Ambush Killings of 2 Officers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denver cop caught on his own body camera stealing from suspect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lebanon PD receives anonymous $18,000 donation for body cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Trump's sexual attacks on women were exposed, his campaign wanted to focus on how he would create jobs. But how is Donald Trump qualified to create jobs for Americans with all the animosity he has cast towards women, who make up the majority of the U.S. population? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Can Donald Trump Be Trusted To Create Jobs For Women? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MPD Officer arrested, charged with DUI while on duty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: DC police officer arrested for DUI while on duty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body cameras are on the way for police in state's largest city </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Spring Hill officer accused of rape, sexual battery while on duty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona: Prison Meal Service Donates $80,000 to Anti-Marijuana Campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a gateway drug alright. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man charged with selling employer's 'As Seen on TV' secrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man charged with selling employer's 'As Seen on TV' secrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Children's Services Officials Suspended for Death of 6-Year-Old Harlem Boy Zymere Perkins, 6, was abused for months before his death. Children's Services investigated the family, but failed to identify the abuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 60 percent of Americans Want Cannabis Legalized, New Poll Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 60 percent of Americans Want Cannabis Legalized, New Poll Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So a Hospital Charged a Mom $39.35 to Hold Her Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So a Hospital Charged a Mom $39.35 to Hold Her Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new app has been released that aims to help the people we see living on the street. The new app is from GiveSafe, and allows you to donate directly to the person you see on the street. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louisville Metro Police officer arrested for the second time in weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nevada Democrats: Voter registration deadline violates law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Storm at Uttakleiv Beach, Lofoten Islands by Lorenzo Riva [966x1500] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Hamill trying to sneak a tongue into Carrie Fisher in The Empire Strikes Back costumes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ignorant Trump remarks a setback for fight against PTSD stigma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's tempting. Do you mean pineapple juice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scroll down to the map below and type in your address to find out what hurricane evacuation zone you're in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 15:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually buy enough for two days, so the first one only gets a few minutes of marination. The second half, nonetheless, gets a couple of days at least, and it tastes a lot better; it does go in the freezer though; so it may not be a couple of days really; just the time it takes to defrost in the fridge. I use regular white vinegar; but squeezing two lemons on about 2 1/2 lbs. of salmon is what gives it the taste I like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing spectacular: it's broiled salmon (seasoned with celery, cilantro, garlic, paprika, salt, pepper, cumin, lemon, vinegar) with mashed cauliflower and steamed broccoli Tuesdays. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Though federal regulation tried to dial back automated phone marketing, during the 2016 campaign American voters have been battered by literally billions of unsolicited calls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing spectacular: simple plate of broiled salmon (seasoned with celery, cilantro, garlic, paprika, salt, pepper, cumin, lemon, vinegar) with mashed cauliflower and steamed broccoli. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked this video because if you think of it broadly, with the right education and training your chances of succeeding at anything are definitely greatly increased. Like a lot of people get into business without learning how to perform even the most basic marketing and sales tactics that have proven to work. It is like trying to become a pilot without taking the courses and training on jets before you try to get into it commercially.  Nothing is ever guaranteed, of course, but with proper training a lot is possible.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] If you think it can't happen, here's proof your chances of succeeding are a lot higher than you think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The growing use and legalization of cannabis are leading to increased exposures across all age groups, including in adolescence. The touting of its medicinal values stems from anecdotal reports related to treatment of a broad range of illnesses including epilepsy, multiple sclerosis, muscle spasms, arthritis, obesity, cancer, Alzheimers disease, Parkinsons disease, post-traumatic stress, inflammatory bowel disease, and anxiety. However, it is critical that societal passions not obscure objective assessments of any potential and realized short- and long-term adverse effects of cannabis, particularly with respect to age of onset and chronicity of exposure. This critical review focuses on evidence-based research designed to assess both therapeutic benefits and harmful effects of cannabis exposure, and is combined with an illustration of the neuropathological findings in a fatal case of cannabis-induced psychosis. The literature and reported case provide strong evidence that chronic cannabis abuse causes cognitive impairment and damages the brain, particularly white matter, where cannabinoid 1 receptors abound. Contrary to popular perception, there is little objective data supporting preferential use of cannabis over conventional therapy for restoration of central nervous system structure and function in disease states such as multiple sclerosis, epilepsy, or schizophrenia. Additional research is needed to determine if sub-sets of individuals with various neurological and psychiatric diseases derive therapeutic benefits from cannabis.

http://www.pedneur.com/article/S0887-8994(16)30478-7/fulltext </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy Marijuana Use May Damage the Brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China on Sunday began using the world's largest radio telescope to survey the heavens and listen for signals of possible extraterrestrial life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An apple store in Green Bay that doesn't sell Apple computer products, has customers confused </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon UK found guilty of trying to airmail dangerous goods | Online retailer fined 65,000 and ordered to pay 60,000 costs for despatching batteries and aerosols for airmail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon has been fined 65,000 for trying to fly dangerous goods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon fined $84,000 for shipping li-ion batteries by air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mesa charter school sued, accused of teaching religious doctrine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study Finds Fitness Trackers Might Impede Weight Loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter sentiment analysis finds two candidates have never been more controversial-or unpopular </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter sentiment analysis finds two candidates have never been more controversial-or unpopular </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl Suspended After Being Sexually Assaulted In School Stairwell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michigan high school suspended student who reported sexual assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York City skyline from Queens on September 11, 2016 [OC] [5184x3456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sandy High School student suspended over homemade charger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sandy High School student suspended over homemade charger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOPD officer arrested, accused of raping teenage male relative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 13:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOPD officer arrested, accused of raping teenage male relative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 13:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waterway lined with brightened buildings on each side in Osaka, Japan by u/Iamthetophergopher (x-post r/travel) [2048x1365] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 15:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Cuomo aide, eight others charged in New York corruption case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Cuomo's former 'gatekeeper' charged in New York corruption case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Cuomo Aides Charged in Federal Corruption Inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Bad Off Is Oil-Rich Venezuela? It's Buying U.S. Oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Bad Off Is Oil-Rich Venezuela? Its Buying U.S. Oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with a hacker: Gh0s7, leader of Shad0wS3c - One of the world's top hackers reveals how attackers own corporate and government networks, how stolen data is sold, which exploit markets are exploding, and why hackers are excited about Android and IoT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with a hacker: Gh0s7, leader of Shad0wS3c - One of the world's top hackers reveals how attackers own corporate and government networks, how stolen data is sold, which exploit markets are exploding, and why hackers are excited about Android and IoT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A police officer in Gloucester County was charged with soliciting a prostitute while on duty and witness tampering, prosecutors said Friday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A South Jersey police officer has been charged with having sex with a prostitute while on duty and then trying to cover up his crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Paralympians ran 1,500m faster than the gold medalist at Rio Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman arrested for allegedly stealing french fries from police officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supervisor Of "Massive Fraud" At Wells Fargo Leaves Bank With $125 Million Bonus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 00:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen accused of being a fake doctor arrested again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 00:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One company is looking to turn your smartphone into a laptop, delivering badly-needed computer access to hundreds of millions of people living in the developing world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Bur Federal de Investigaciones (FBI) arrest hoy a cuatro agentes antinarcticos de la polica puertorriquea por violacin a los derechos civiles al arrestar a un individuo hace casi dos aos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeKalb officer admits to buying drugs while on duty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia policeman charged with raping woman on way to jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia police officer arrested, charged with raping woman on way to jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Tesla Autopilot drove a man with a blood clot to the hospital, and expanded the autonomous car debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Tesla Autopilot drove a man with a blood clot to the hospital, and expanded the autonomous car debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian Netflix customers are going to have a tougher time watching geoblocked movies and TV shows after local VPN provider uFlix announced it has pulled support for unblocked Netflix content. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 17:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the DVD "My Stunts" Jackie Chan takes you behind the scenes to show how he perfected his dangerous craft of falling and crashing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man pushes girlfriend from plane, saves her life before dying in crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explosion shakes SpaceX launch site during test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sugar Land police officer arrested in cattle theft ring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess both; for if you're more educated you have less to worry about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police body cameras go departmentwide in Waukegan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Marijuana Use Grows As Fewer People Worry About the Risks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More U.S. Adults Using Marijuana Than Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  596 500 adults participated in the 200214 surveys. Marijuana use increased from 104% (95% CI 9971082) to 133% (12841370) in adults in the USA from 2002 to 2014 (=00252, p00001), and the prevalence of perceiving great risk of harm from smoking marijuana once or twice a week decreased from 504% (49605125) to 333% (32643396; =00625, p00001). 

http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366(16)30208-5/fulltext </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An increasing number of U.S. adults are using marijuana, and attitudes about the drug are shifting  fewer people perceive pot as harmful, according to a new study published in The Lancet Psychiatry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court upholds ban on gun sales to marijuana card holders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 14:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Jordan (Age 41) Vs. Damon Wayans Sr. (Age 44) One On One (September 21, 2004) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new collaboration between Google DeepMind AI and the UK's National Health Service hopes to cut radiotherapy planning times (to treat head and neck cancers) from four hours to just one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Expansion, New Yorks Medical Marijuana Program Will Offer Home Delivery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Expansion, New Yorks Medical Marijuana Program Will Offer Home Delivery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former church staff member was sentenced Tuesday to 50 years in prison for sexually abusing a seven-year-old child and possessing child pornography in 2013, federal authorities announced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Democrats ask FBI to probe Trump campaign for link to hacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House aims to help immigrant entrepreneurs bring startups to the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard can save the business of World of Warcraft by killing the monthly subscription fee, selling high-quality in-game purchases, and remastering and marketing classic content in modules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google won't fix login page flaw that can lead to malware download </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Hamill trims his beard, teases fans about 'Episode IX' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Documentary short shows how 80-year-old lady became a champion bodybuilder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Idiocy of Mumble Rappers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Service dog is ready fight raptor at Islands of Adventure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Connecticut Supreme Court Reinstates State Employee Caught Smoking Pot On The Job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over Half A Million People Arrested In California For Marijuana In The Last Decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over Half A Million People Arrested In California For Marijuana In The Last Decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over Half A Million People Arrested In California For Marijuana In The Last Decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biggie smalls son rapping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're Popping Your Pimples Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenager brags about getting a train ran on her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The secret behind Finland's successful education system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lady teaches how to make a girl want you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Squat with Knee Pain - SQUAT FIX!! (Knee Pain No More!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Make A Girl OBSESSED With You (INSTANTLY) - Proven By Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston police to randomly assign 100 body cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge has thrown out a proposed $100 million settlement negotiated by a Boston lawyer on behalf of more than 200,000 Uber drivers in California and Massachusetts, saying it places too low a value on potentially costly claims drivers could bring under California labor laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge has thrown out a proposed $100 million settlement negotiated by a Boston lawyer on behalf of more than 200,000 Uber drivers in California and Massachusetts, saying it places too low a value on potentially costly claims drivers could bring under California labor laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
