<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7051</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cock-a-doodle BOO! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 18:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 14:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty, you have to make your own karma. Shit happens to everyone, it's all in how you deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 12:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hubby was the same way. He hit forty and BOOM, everything changed. Put on a few pounds, but not a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fifteen minute call, well you know... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 02:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My pet lamb, Merle, was hit and killed tonight, thought I'd share one of my favorite photos of my boy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 07:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 14:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not heard fantastic things. I am very glad I have employer coverage. Shitty Employer coverage, but coverage nonetheless. AB Blue Cross saved our butt a few times (Hubby is diabetic, gets expensive), but given ANY other choice I wouldn't choose it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 05:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well OBVIOUSLY they aren't going to turn you away with a life-threatening infection. But if you walk in with a bad tooth they are going to tell you to go to your dentist. TMJ issues are also referred to dentists. The my nearest hospital is a gong show and I'd pull my own tooth before I'd wait 7 hours to be told to go to the dentist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Here they would say "go to your Dentist". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 04:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you looked into Alberta Blue Cross coverage? If you really need dental it can take the "ouch" out a little bit. (Fellow Albertan here!!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 03:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No regrets. Been 15 years, still don't regret it. Not once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 03:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left out of mine. And the whole twelve people I had there wouldn't have objected anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 23:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small weddings are the best! They save money AND drama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burgers and pizza for me at that cost. For a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 21:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You bastards just made me realize Junior High was 25 years ago. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 20:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junior High girls are the worst. I went through hell. My now 18 year old son had a few problems, but being a girl in Junior High is a fickle beast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 16:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plantar warts, more specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are swift and precise with the ban hammer today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 02:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 02:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed!! My hubby really is my best friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 02:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she's married to mine, too! I love that man with every fiber of my being. I miss him after a day of work and just love being with him. He's handsome, funny, handy, loving and an amazing father. We've been together 20 years, married 15 and I swear I fall more in love with him every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 01:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no. We were buds, too. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 20:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looked like my Dad, too. My Dad passed suddenly six years ago, This is like losing him all over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 21:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friends don't let friends not know what Reddit is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 19:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTH, man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 18:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 19:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh, Chemistry Nerds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HELLS NO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 06:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, if I can do it ANYBODY can. Stay focused and never give up. Have a bad day, get right back on the horse the next day. Treat yourself in moderation. Start rewarding yourself with anything OTHER than food (one of my bad habits). It'll take a while, it'll be tough, but it'll be worth it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 06:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I lost 120 lbs a few years back and kept if off, I just wanted to give you the heads up that it often takes a long time for the skin to firm up (if it ever does). After two kids and a 120 lb weight loss a tummy tuck was basically a non-option! Keep up the good work and remember that you WILL have good days and bad days and then you will have awful days and MONTHS, but you always have to stay true to yourself and your goals. If you keep that in mind ANYONE can make their goals a reality. The 30 lb weight loss looks great on you, just remember, though, you were beautiful before and you're beautiful now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 22:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize, only people in monogamous relationships have sex. I forgot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 23:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was a "leetle" uncomfortable. But it's been magic for 7 years (changed once). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 23:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IUD's are sent from the heavens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 23:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that whole pesky STD thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 19:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK-YOU. Yes. I hate the man-hating "feminists". I have a husband and two sons whom I love very much. I love men. Men are great, and so are women! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 05:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two that survived are getting huge now, but our girl has scours again. Not sure if it's because she insists on eating the chicken feed, or if she's gotten into something in the yard. Sigh, naughty lambs. It was quite painful for us to lose our little Pearl. Bottle lambs are very rewarding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 04:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need someone for the weekend of August 16th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 04:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to say watch him close for signs of scours and dehydration, we had a little girl that looked just like him that we lost to dehydration. And he's adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 17:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think depends on the fiber/dye type on what will or won't be bleached by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 23:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bleaches them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A boy and his kitten... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 15:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 23:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Yes I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 17:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys OBVIOUSLY have not met the right girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 23:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're fantastic. Thanks for making me smile! And thank-you for what you do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [FRANK AND BEANS!](http://youtu.be/vzRuKnb2uuY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 years with my hubby. I still do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 23:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels great!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 17:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just says "I knew you could do it". He loves me any size, but knows I'm happier when I feel healthy (I lost weight for my health, not for aesthetics, that was an added bonus). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 17:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 17:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked them up and they appear on the Freemasons of Alberta site (I'm Canadian). There's a very good chance they are no longer in good standing, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 17:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me happy. I know the Freemasons set out to be an honorable group of men, unfortunately like many things, somebody has to twist it and adulterate it into sometime unseemly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 17:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They drank almost every night of the week, husbands not getting home until 3AM on a work night. Drinking at the "Lodge" drinking at the bar, drinking at alternating houses of members. The only events that happened were booze filled parties, motorcycle rides (not charity, just cruising) and large screen viewings of "Sons of Anarchy" (they fancied themselves a biker gang). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 17:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there was AT LEAST three affairs (that's all that were discovered, who knows if there were more). So yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 17:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For people with knee issues a stationary bike (or regular bike) and the pool are great exercise as neither is full weight-bearing. The most important thing to remember is that just because you have one bad day doesn't mean you should give up. Have a bad day. Eat the chocolate cake, eat the ice cream. Try to limit portions of bad foods. The next day you go back to eating good. Eating good 5 out of seven days is still better than eating bad 7 out of 7 days. It's important to keep healthy foods around you at all times, so when the temptation strikes, you can eat that instead of the bad stuff (I carried a bag of carrots in my purse). To relieve stress yoga is great. It's gentle and you work at your own pace. Even walking is a great stress relieving exercise. It doesn't have to be a fancy exercise. It just has to be an exercise you will do! Hope she continues her journey (It never really ends). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 16:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is basically a biker gang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 16:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband dead up refused to let me get a lapband. Too much money. Best thing he ever did for me. I lost 120lbs through diet and exercise. I've never felt better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 16:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a gong show. Drinking, partying, everybody sleeping with everyone's spouses. It was definitely not keeping with the "bettering" yourself mandate, which is sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 03:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we have a Freemasons Chapter in my city. A friend of mine's husband joined the group. This group of Freemason do not want to better themselves. They use the gatherings and meetings as an excuse to get hammered and stay out all night. It's destroyed three marriages because of philandering, my friends being in of them. It's a disgusting Chapter and I can't help but think of all Freemasons as losers and alcoholics now. It's nice to see that there are other chapters out there like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 03:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no, you missed his point! It was defiantly (or rebelliously) overrated. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 04:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both times mine broke I delivered in under an hour. It varies but my sister in law's water broke and she delivered within ten minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so proud of myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a little cat nap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 04:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 00:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I'll gladly sacrifice a few orgasms to feel good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 00:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have added Wellbutrin as well. I will settle for tons of energy and a libido again! (though my husband is begging for a break!). I'm very content, and while I orgasm less now than before, I didn't really orgasm that easily before the meds. Meh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 22:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be weird but I have NEVER had an orgasm from penetration. Just clitoral stimulation. It's become steadily harder since I started the antidepressants, but not wanting to kill myself anymore is MORE than worth a few side effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antidepressants, all of them, have "sexual side effects" usually reduction of libido, Lexapro, in particular makes it difficult to orgasm. Takes FOREVER. Like 20-30 mins at least. It's not worth it. Besides, I like to focus on his enjoyment. That makes me happy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 22:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the one I'm on. FML. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 19:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Antidepressants have pretty much ruled them out in my case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 07:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ba-dum-tisssss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RAWR! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 03:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 19:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it has lots of calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 19:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually a thing. Good job, Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely believe you! The crap this dude espoused is a black mark on southerners, but doubt that the majority still think this way. His version of the south diverges from reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 17:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coward couldn't even stick to his guns. Dumbass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 15:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the south is a shining beacon of human rights. Just because your "insular community" of southern bigots likes her, doesn't mean "the majority" of women like to be "subservient". Antiquated oaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 14:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have friends with children in the school. A grade four student was caught with a weapon and a hit list. Very sad story all around. I'm sure the letter was to deal with a rumor mill that was probably rampant by that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 16:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I remind you that self posts don't get karma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key is IDENTICAL triplets. Fraternal triplets are more common. Identical means the zygote had to split three ways, that's like winning the genetic lottery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 05:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more like 1 in 500,000.

http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiple_birth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 18:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son has fallen asleep at an NHL hockey game and fell asleep at an indoor auction yesterday. He's 11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 00:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! We'll just use hydrogen. Nothing could possibly go wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 17:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> + </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 16:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 90lbs I lost were pretty easy, the last 30? A lot tougher. The final 10? Near impossible. It's consistency, persistence and sheer will power that gets you there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 06:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takes dedication, but if I can do it ANYONE can :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 06:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have "atypical depression" makes you wanna eat everything in sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 06:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other "deformities" that accompany Prader-Willis Syndrome. These people are eating their bad feelings, guaranteed.

Source: Used to be morbidly obese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 19:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're retards. And when you offend retards they HAVE to tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 17:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a right to take and post a million pictures as much as we have a right to think they're an attention-seeking moron for slathering their children all over social media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 17:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [_](http://imgur.com/drlG8kk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 05:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need an updated photo of your cutie! Bet he's big now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, wait, they have a big dick category? BRB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 23:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree as well, perfect choice of grout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 07:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're married, I can tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 00:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more than a shitload, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 20:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to google that. I was very confused for a moment:

http://youtu.be/Hn7B5FdwBK8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 05:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GAWDDAMMIT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 05:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go away, troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 04:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last one killed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 03:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up depression symptoms. Anger, irrationality and emotional outbursts are all part and parcel. Do your research, PAL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 19:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UUUUGH! You're killing me!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate cookie cutter house!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 18:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Alberta, but I'm from Halifax. I miss all the colors that houses have. Everything is white, grey or brown here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 18:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody needs a little alone time. When my depression flares I get rage-y. If you don't leave me alone when I ask, you will feel my wrath, I guarantee it. You can help someone by leaving them alone, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 16:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the actors are older than their book characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 04:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As was any reference to Edward Snowden, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 04:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BEAUTIFUL!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 00:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get a jury duty notification here (Canada) you STILL have to ask for an exemption on the grounds that you are a student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 00:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PRETTY sure men measure their chests, too. Just sayin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 22:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
