<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Python is winning the War on Matlab.

Not really. I assume you are a "casual user" in the sense that you code your own stuff with bits from numpy/scipy. I also mostly do this, by the way. Most of my code nowadays is scipy/numpy/opencv.

Matlab has a lot of very specific toolboxes which simply don't have anything similar in Python. See: https://uk.mathworks.com/products.html

Python plus its scientific libraries implement a tiny bit of that. Civil engineers, electronic engineers, even chemists or economists still use matlab (or LabView) in the "real world". Plenty of people in the lab where I work use Matlab / LabView because there's no other way around.

Don't get it wrong, Scipy/Numpy is not killing Matlab. Scipy/Numpy is just a fraction of what matlab does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I don't have the time anymore to sit down and enjoy long sessions of gaming. On the other hand the 3DS is perfect because it lets me enjoy gaps where I can play in short bursts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I did. My phone is detected there and I can locate it. I still cannot unlock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a question. I have a lazy eye, thus I cannot watch 3D movies or enjoy the 3D thing in the 3DS. Will I able to enjoy VR or am I screwed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok. Crap. What about dirty update ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why it should be locked now ? So you can only install once ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried that. Maybe I need the Chinese one. I'll try that tomorrow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My phone had a vendor ROM and I installed global using the method in the wiki. Isn't that enough ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannot unlink Redmi 4 Prime (stuck at 50% and 86023:hardwareID when trying to add account and device in Mi Unlock Status) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says, I always get stuck at 50%. I have tried every guide I have seen out there. I have received the text, mi.com detects my device. I login using my phone number. I have 8.1.2.0 (MBEMIDI) which I installed following the guide here. I also tried installing all the drivers as the wiki suggests

Something I have realized in "Mi Unlock status" is that when I click "Add account and device" it returns me a "86023:hardwareID" followed by some chinese characters.

I don't really know what to do or how to move forward. I am a bit lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aldo would eat Cody. Aldo would just wait outside and murder him with leg kicks. Basically, it'd be the same as against Frankie, but Cody is not Frankie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is also cheaper if we compare it to any other country with private healthcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source about Dana saying that ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as many people have said, they can take the jpeg and modify it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  for the real reason people don't want to give up raws:

People here thinks that someone is going to get married, then ask for raws and ruin the photographer career just for fun.

As you said, people that will ask for raws probably know what to do with them. In which case, very rarely  they will sign whatever they do with the photographer name. Remember, it is their wedding. They don't want to make a catalogue. They probably just want to share pics with family members and friends. if they want to edit the pictures, they can also use the jpeg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a photographer myself. But just as a "normal person". Missing family members in a wedding is what I would consider a flagarant mistake.

If I am getting married and I don't see pictures about X or Y, I would be very very annoyed. To every wedding I have been, the photographer always goes around and takes pictures of everyone. 

Moreover, in a wedding it is very easy to see who is "important" just based on their position.

So yeah, independently of the quality of the picture, if my wedding photographer forgot some family members, I would be very annoyed. By the same reason, if an important family member is getting married and I don't see any picture of me around, I'd be confused and ask this person what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they got it in Nature Chemistry, which is one of the best journals around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/31/1621318114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team of Stanford researchers created what might be the cheapest, simplest disease-diagnosing solution yet: An inject-printed microchip that can perform multiple tests and costs only twenty minutes and less than a penny to make. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.nature.com/nchem/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nchem.2716.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemist have done what was considered impossible: they created the first stable compound with helium, using sodium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice pictures, and something different. I am tired of the daily iteration of the Clyde picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your point? That reinforces the idea that going against freedom of movement is bad. At least now people are "legal", pay taxes, registered to the NHS,...

If now it is 500k, wait for post-brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The occupants of the house were in when the burglary took place.

WTF, was there violence? How did it happened?

This is very scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any story to share about each guitar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have downloaded it. But I am kind of lazy about learning it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know the exact laws, but if you work over X days in a country, it doesn't matter where you are from, you pay taxes there. In which case, these romanians workers will have a big problem, because they would only have a tourist visa in England. Also their boss would have even a bigger problem. 

People will always do illegal things. People are bringing workers from India or Pakistan. You cannot make your laws in a way to avoid "cheating". You need to have the proper safety measures within your country to detect when that happens.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  because in practice it would just be a case of people go to Scotland and use it as a bridge to go wherever they want in the UK

no, it isn't. Unless they stay 10 years in Scotland and get the british residence.

The moment a EU national goes to England from Scotland and tries to get a job, rent a flat, get a phone,... the system would just tell this person that they have a tourist visa and that such thing cannot be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  not technically feasible.

It actually is. They want to make you believe it is not, but it is.

You don't really care about people physically coming in or out, and regardless of brexit or Trump's wall, that's impossible to control, because people can get in as tourist, which in the UK means to buy a 30 ryan air ticket from any EU country.

What you care about is what they can legally do. And that you can very easily control. Scotland can keep their current EU agreement, while England can ban EU national direct access to the job market or NHS, like they already do to anyone from any other country.

Politicians think you are stupid, and want you to think that it is not technically feasible because if a EU national lands in Glasgow, what stops him or her to just travel to England and get a job? Well, the travel is difficult to control, but the job (or renting a flat, or getting internet, phone, gas,...) is very easy to control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ufraw, darktable

I have used ufraw, but, aren't darktable and ufraw the same?

I also have big problems with ufraw lately, I have a sony camera and it seems to fail to properly detect it. It is kind of strange because in a macbook the lens correction is perfect, but the chromatic aberration fails. On the otherhand, on linux the lens correction fails, but the chromatic aberration is perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's your budget? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think this was an inside job. Either a friend, or a friend of a friend, or someone who went to your house recently, or someone you bought something from gumtre,... basically someone who already knew what was there.

Pros, if by pros we mean one of this gangs who have the tools to do this, they won't steal this kind of equipment because it is very specific. the macbooks and ipads, yeah, the guitars more strange because most people have shitty guitars and they wont take the risk for 50, all the other stuff, very strange. Plus it'd take time to disconnect everything. This is someone who knew fine well you were out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very steange. What are the odds of your random ned/white trash hitting gold in a flat like that? Moreover taking all that stuff instead of running away with the first expensive thing they find. In particular all those specific things. That probably take ages to steal.

Basically, I think it was someone you known  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 11:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did they get in? Which part of the West end ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 min per fight because it's not ppv.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killing the chickens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first guy Francis fought. I remember that fight, that when Joe went to ask the stuff, Francis said like "1 second" and went to check the guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering all the nurses the UK was receiving from other EU countries, this with Brexit is a perfect combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant Luis Henrique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Henrique Silva I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Henrique Silva. First UFC fight I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order to keep the price down while providing the 3D effect, you need to cut down the hardware. In the case of the 3DS it was a 240p screen. It was a huge trade off between a good price, a good hardware or 3D. They went for the 3D, and they had a high price and bad hardware. That's why the 3DS almost bombed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 3D thing is dead. The switch is not 3D. I am 100% sure Nintendo makes another console in the DS line, it won't be 3D.

Why? It makes the system too expensive and you need to cut down the hardware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Looks like a damn mobile game. :(

?

A lot of 3DS games look like "mobile games" in terms of graphics. But once you play them, and you feel the controls, the depth of the game, the art details through the game, dialogues, how well the game been tested,... you feel a huge difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 10:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tried in different days. Always same error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problem unblocking, "network error" on Mi Unlock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I put my username and password, it waits for 2-3 seconds and it returns a "network error". If I put a wrong password it says "incorrect password", so the network error message is not relate to the login.

I have tried with the mi unlock from the wiki here, also the one from XDA and also the one from xiaomi website. All of them give me the same error.

I have tried this in 2 different computers in 2 different networks (home and work), so I don't think it is a problem with my computer.

In any case, is there solution? Am I doing anything error? I have already received the unlock text from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature21039.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the largest search to date involving 700,000 people, researchers have uncovered 83 new DNA changes that affect human height. These changes are uncommon or rare, but they have potent effects, with some of them adjusting height by more than 2 cm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 202 to 205 I mean. 202 he left the octagon limping hardcore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conor is kind of doing that when he fought against Nate when RDA went out. Nate didnt give him anything and it was a high risk fight. Also, 205 after the 202 war was also kind of early.

That said, I fully agree about the 6 weeks. He should have never had medical clearance. Now after the TKO he will be 6 months off, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Motivation isn't in limitless supply.

It is not only about "motivation". Being fat (when it is related to a unhealthy diet and lack of exercise) fucked up your metabolism and makes you addicted to things like sugar and fat. So there is a very real addiction that you need to keep under control.

There is also the big problem of life style. A lot of people have an unhealthy diet just because there's no other way around. Not everyone is lucky enough to have 3 hours every day to buy fresh food and cook it. Not everyone has the money to buy already prepared fresh food.

There is also a big psicological problem. A lot of people eats under stress, sadness,...

I don't know. There are a lot of causes, there are books about it. But it is not just "motivation". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  then she should be doing something to stop being fat

She is probably trying, but it is not that easy. People seems to think you can just stop being fat, eat healthy and go to the gym. People is fat for a reason, it is not just "bad luck", it is not just like buying the wrong t-shirt, that you can go and swap. Until you discover that "reason" it is completely impossible to change.

Plus there's all the fucked up metabolism and sugar and fat addiction. It is a real addiction, like smoking.

I was fat most of my life, and I tried to many times, and I always failed. Sometimes it was just lack of control, sometimes it was just bad luck (for example once when I was doing really well 6 month into it and losing weight I had a sinus pilonidal which was quite huge, and I had to have surgery and basically stop doing exercive for like 8 months).

So yeah, it is not that easy to "just stop being fat". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you comment is meant to say "it is OK for a guy to be fat, but it is not OK for a woman".

I suggest you do a very simple experiment. Create 2 profiles in a on-line dating site. One with a picture of a fat guy, one with a picture of a fat girl. They don't need to be ugly or anything like that, just fat.

One week later check how many messages have they received. I am quite sure the fat guy would have received an average of 0.

Fat guys in the dating world are completely alienated, out of the game, classed as "losers". If they try to dress smart or something like that, then they are made fun of, called neckbeards or fedora-tips.

The main difference is that it is not OK for a guy to express his real feelings, while it is OK for a woman. A woman can say "I am fat, and it sucks", while a guy can never say "I am fat, and it sucks", unless it is meant as a joke.

Let me tell you something, I was fat, and it sucked a lot, and I don't mean it as a joke.

In the dating world, as a fat person, I felt a didn't exist at all, I was transparent, ignored. it sucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   While I'm sure fat girls have a harder time dating

Imagine fat guys. I was a fat guy. I tried to date. My success was 0. Not even dates, to be honest, never went to that stage. It is also a cycle that eats itself. As you are less successful, you become more toxic as a person, which doesn't help at all, and probably more fat.

Moreover, nobody gives a fuck about fat guys. While fat women have all the other women "jumping down your through about it", as you said, and saying the things like "you are also pretty." Nobody gives a fuck about fat guys.

At least that was my experience. I am sure there are super succesful in dating funny fat guys, but I have never met one. On the other hand, I met a lot of fat guys, like me, just classed as "losers".

I am not fat anymore, by the way. I changed it around 7-8 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 10:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bundled  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are from the UK, try Gumtree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is 0 chance Gibraltar will get free flow of workers and tourists but not EU from Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature21071.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restoring native plants 'boosts pollination'. Removing invasive exotic plants from natural areas can act as a boost for wildlife, a study suggests. Bees, butterflies and birds returned to remote mountaintops in the Seychelles only six months after exotic plants were removed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me a single reason why a EU national would favour staying in the UK and outside of the EU.

This basically means they would need to pay for VISAs (with all the risk and stress it generates), or the 1500 pounds to get the permit of residence.

Best case scenario it would cost them money (few thousand pounds), worst case scenario they would need to leave the country.

I am EU national. I know plenty of EU nationals. I do not know a single one who would vote to stay in the UK and leave the EU. It is just stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would ignore the east coast, I mean the part where you go Aberdeen - Fraserburgh, and go instead through the Cairngorms which is actually very nice, and then use those extra miles in the west coast, like for example a bit of Skye, Mallaig, Oban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the main thing is going to be EU nationals basically. During indyref1 they voted no, during the second one they would be yes. They are around 200k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There was already a referendum in 2014, which reached an end point that has remained in place. 

The situation with respect to 2014 is completely different.

There are at least 200k people (EU nationals) who we know would vote differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they should merge the ceremonial weigh in with the real one at like 12 noon, and that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that the polls stay the same, when we know 200k people would vote different (EU nationals), says a lot.

Remember that the first referendum was 1.6m vs 2m. 200k swap means a lot there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they won a LAN just before TI4 against Cloud9, but then they underperformed with sketchy drafts. I will never understand why they never picked Lycan, they only team that had it available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 46/54 as a starting point is not bad. indyref1 started way worse than that for the yes, and then it recovered until the 45.

In a poll people is always going to go for the status quo. Another example is Brexit: https://ig.ft.com/sites/brexit-polling/ Remain had a big advantatge, until the very end.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  + low taxes

not really when you consider private health plus "university fund for your kids" plus "pension plan". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you go to Gumtree. Private landlords are much much better IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a big problem with narration in the UFC, and I feel with the new owners it will only get worse (more hype and shit).

Thankfully I am spanish, so I can listen to the spanish feed (god bless Werdum), which is much better to watch it live. I love Joe and Mike, but for the repetition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange. When I was viewing flats that never happened to me, and I viewed flats which had other views previously.

In my experience letting agents never gave the flat to the first "ok", but said the classic "if you want it, gives us your details, and the landlord will choose among the ones who want it". It is very stupid to give the flat to the first person who wants it if there are several views arranged. It is better to wait for the candidates, and then guess who will give you less problems.

It also happened to me in few flats, that I said yes, and then they called me to say that the landlord didnt choose me. 2 or 3 days later the flat was again up for grabs, but this time 50 pounds of expensive. I phoned them and they say "the person who the landlord chose didnt want it, so we had to put it up again".

If you market a flat for 500 pounds, and you have 5 people who want it, it is obvious that you can ask more for the flat. I don't know how legal that can be though, but it happened to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The Squier Classic Vibe series is already basically MIM quality.

They can do cheap guitars in USA. They choose not to just to keep the "made in usa" as a premium line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's not cheaper than straight up making them in America.

I always felt that the fact why the MIM were cheaper was not just cost labour, but quality of materials, quality checks, expertise of the workers,...

Whoever claims that the difference between MIUSA and MIM is just 150 miles is lying. It is very true that in a blind test you might not feel the difference, but use both guitars for 10 years and then compare them. And I am saying this as someone who has MIM fenders. As an example, in every USA guitar I have opened the electronics looked way neater than in MIM guitars.

Fender can make guitars in USA almost as cheaply as they do in Mexico (I mean, the cost of labour might be 5$ an hour in mexico against $12 an hour in USA, considering they use noob luthiers). That doesnt explain the 600 dollars of difference.

They choose not to, just to keep the USA ones as higher quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it gets better, yes, but it never gets amazing. The demand varies with the students coming and leaving.

From now on it will get better, until august or so, when students come again.

The fact that they cancel a viewing is very strange, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you cannot read the paper, this is from where I got the news: http://www.theverge.com/2017/1/26/14397178/memories-mice-optogenetics-ptsd-trauma-triggers-neuroscience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study suggests that its possible to break the link between two memories.Scientists taught mice to be afraid of two different things, then to associate the two fears with each other. Finally, they destroyed the link between the two memories and found that the original memories remained intact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's open jaw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They couldn't get full UFC.tv which now will be blackout  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck do they write "2 title fights". This is a complete joke. The previous LW title fight was just 5 months ago.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: https://www.osapublishing.org/optica/abstract.cfm?uri=optica-4-1-114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mini light gyroscope made. The smallest optical gyroscope yet made fits onto a computer chip with a volume of just 15 cubic centimetres. Instead of producing interference in a large fibre-optic loop, the light resonates inside a minuscule crystalline cavity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20150897 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Across the United States, electric vehicles are more detrimental to the environment than petrol-powered vehicles thanks to the pollution created in generating electricity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature21056.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artificial intelligence can identify skin cancer in photographs with the same accuracy as trained doctors. The Stanford team said the findings were incredibly exciting and would now be tested in clinics. Using AI could revolutionise healthcare by turning anyone's smartphone into a cancer scanner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/3/1/e1600327 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists are using the process of knitting to make artificial muscle that moves more like we do. They created a textile actuator, or textuatora new kind of smart fabric that can control movement. They coated cellulose yarn with a polymer that shifts and stretches in response to electricity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bellator is the other big one. Probably way cheaper than UFC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Xiaomi/wiki/advanced/flashfastboot

you will need to use fastboot probably.

try to see if you can go to edl:

https://www.reddit.com/r/Xiaomi/wiki/advanced/edl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you go to the xiaomi subreddit and ask for help. if I had a similar problem I would reinstall a rom and see if that fixes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The phone is Redmi 4 Prime. 

MIUI version is MIUI Global 8.1 | Stable 8.1.2.0 (MBDEMIDI).

It came with a vendor rom, and following the wiki I installed this one.

I have tried the association through data and wi-fi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help unlocking phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When in "Mi Unlock status" (in advanced settings"), when I click "add account and device", it thinks for a bit, and then it says it cannot connect to the network (the phone is connected to the network, so that should be fine).

I have already received the text from xiaomi granting my unlock.

I don't know if related, but in "mi account" I don't know how to enable "find my device", although my device appears there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, a TKO, KO or sub should get a bonus IMO. Apart from Fight of the night, which I think is a cool bonus.

The problem: UFC are cheap as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bobby Robson coached Barcelona for 1 season. His main problem here is that his style was not "FCB DNA". But then he had an amazing team, with Ronaldo on his super peak when he had knees, Guardiola, De la Pea, ...

I remember during the Brazil Carnival Ronaldo dissapeared and went there, and then there were some pictures of him there in Brazil having fun. So in the next press conference they ask Robson what would he say to Ronaldo, and he said "I will tell him, next time he goes to the carnival he must tell me first, so I will go with him".

The story of Robson and Barcelona is longer than what most people know. Robson was the all time favourite coach of our president back then, Nuez. Nuez always wanted Bobby, but it was not possible until the very end. Terry Venables, for example, who was here for 3 years, was suggested by Bobby, and the legend says that Alex Ferguson was almost signed by Barcelona as suggested by Robson, but the thing is that Venables ended up winning the league 84 85, so Barcelona couldnt fire him and get SAF instead, which was almost signed.

In hindsight it was a mistake, because the next 2 season by Venables were pretty bad, to the point that the players locked themselves in a hotel and didnt wanted to play. But then we got Cruyff, and everything became better.

EDIT just in case, Ferguson to Barcelona has been confirmed by him ""I was once invited for talks with Barcelona in London when they believed Terry Venables was set to pack his bags," he wrote. "It was Terry who approached me with the job offer in the first place, but eventually he had a change of mind and decided to stay in Spain for a little longer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with low alcohol tolerance also have excellent self-control  as a study published Tuesday in PNAS on alcohol-intolerant undergrads points out. Not only are they good at saying no to alcohol, theyre good at saying no to other vices as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/17/1605599114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Americans tend to lose a parent, other close relatives and spouses at earlier ages than whites, creating a devastating grief gap, new research suggests. Studying more than 42,000 racially diverse Americans, it was found that death strikes black families significantly earlier than whites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using 20 years of data sciencists analyzed how jet lag impairs MLB performance. Their results were surprising, and in particular they showed big jet lag effects after eastward travelling, with very limited effects after westward travel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can exactly be done with 9m? it seems a lot of money, but it is near nothing for this kind of public work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Ultimate_Fighter:_Team_Joanna_vs._Team_Cl%C3%A1udia

This is the last one during spring. TUF24 was the autumn one.

In any case: April 20  July 6, 2016. Finale the 8th July. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Honestly, the reason why I've never spent much time on Reddit is because despite the thoughtful, hilarious, and intelligent users, there is an overwhelming amount of negativity to be found. 

I am sorry to say that's how life is. The negativity comes from the anonymity. People doesn't need to lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Didn't know what to do and the clock always clicking down just made me 

I am glad I am not the only one who felt this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished the game like a month ago in the 3DS. Back in the day I played OoT, which is my favourite game ever, but I never played MM.

I didn't enjoy MM as much as I thought I would do. IMO the time limit simply kills the game. One of the best things of Zelda is about exploration. Especially in the dungeons, you need to backtrack a lot and think about the next step. You don't have time for that in MM. I had to use a guide to many times because I was running out of time and I didn't know what to do. This is something that annoyed me a few times in the game. Literally not knowing what to do. You can feel the game was rushed in 1 year.

So I have a bittersweet feeling about MM. The game looks amazing. The time mechanic is horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you are from, but in my experience, anywhere in Europe, at least west Europe, any shop has Fender guitars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I have heard great things about Fender too, though unfortunately we haven't been lucky enough to stock them. 

wait you have a guitar shop and you don't sell Fender? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it compare to Darktable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe not faster, but Ronaldinho's acceleration was amazing.

watch this goal:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ZNvjyTDrBI

Neymar has never done anything like that in Europe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get a 2DS second hand, you can get one for like $50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Iirc, Barca was offered Ronaldo back in 2008 or 2009 by Man U and Barca accepted but Ronaldo refused to move to Barca and wanted to go to Madrid instead. 

I don't buy this. The reason why RMadrid bought Ronaldo was because the previous president (Calderon) had a contact with Manchester United saying they'd buy it for a set price. When Florentino joined the team again, he had to honour this contract.

Legend says, though, that while he was in Sporting, Ronaldo was offered to FCBarcelona. But Barcelona prefer to buy Quaresma instead. I think at some point that summer United had a friendly with Sportning, and they bought him in the spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Messi the beginning (Messi I)

Messi I is my favourite Messi. He didn't score as much his impact was brutal. I still remember that game against Chelsea and the red card to Del Horno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post is very strange. You should read it twice because it doesn't make much sense.

a 2DS can play 3DS games. It will lack the 3D feature, but it will play all the games except Xenoblade Chronicles.

and old 3DS will play all the games except Xenoblade Chronicles.

So basically an old 3DS and a 2DS have the same library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The amount of hate on neymar is unbelievable. Even Bara fans for some reason can't seem to like him, even though he brings so much to the table for us.

He is very good, but, considering we paid for him 110+ millions, was it worth? I am not sure what to answer.

Also, from the first day he didn't really seemed to care about the club itself. He never really connected. No one will be surprised if he leaves the club in 2-3 years.

I feel like Luis Suarez connected much better, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same opinion. Ronaldinho was magic. Hard to explain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Neymar is arguably in the shadow of two players.

Neymar was only behind Messi during the first year, and for a while Messi was injured so Neymar was the best in the team. He was very good, but far away from super star like Messi or Ronaldinho.

That was his first season, but Ronaldinho made a huge impact during his first season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Perhaps it would be fair to say Neymar is more quicker and athletic but Ronaldinho surpasses him in technical ability.

Ronaldinho was way more athletic than Neymar. Ronaldinho was built like a robot, he was supper strong, with thick legs. Neymar is more lanky. Ronaldinho used to throw guys around just going shoulder to shoulder with the ball. Neymar cannot really take any contact.

IMO Ronaldinho was better in basically every aspect of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a common sentence but "goals doesn't tell the full story".

Ronaldinho during his peak was miles better than Neymar. Ronaldinho during his peak was on Messi's level. Sadly his peak lasted something like 3 years because he prefered money and party.

On the other hand, because Messi plays in Barcelona we have rarely seen Neymar playing as a 10 (only when Messi was injured, but it wouldn't be fair to rate his 10 game for a few games). 

Ronaldinho is one of my favourite players ever (with Romario).

My favourite Ronaldinho goal: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ZNvjyTDrBI

I don't know, I feel Ronaldinho was magic. I also felt Messi was magic during his first years when he was a wild winger. Maybe I am just getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ari guy looks like someone who spends a lot of time sun bathing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to tourism in the 21st centuries. Hordes of Chinese, Indians, Russians and Americans come to Europe for a one off trip in their life, so they don't care about price. Local people are just phase out (same as in football).

Any popular place has crazy prices. I think I paid 23 euros to enter the FCBarcelona museum. It was a total scam. You basically see some trophies behind a glass and some videos that you can easily YouTube. But this is just everywhere.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opposite. You're the one who said it has remained steadily at 45/55 while I said that it is impossible because at least the 200k EU citizens would have swapped sides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 11:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 45/55 is technically impossible. 

EU people who voted all of them for the no would now vote for the yes. That'd put the thing more like 48 to 52  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have fought Cole Miller or Siver. What the hell was he doing fighting Yair or even being matched against Llamas?

Not only that but if you watch his last fights, what the hell was he doing fighting people like Rory or Nick Diaz?

Put BJ against old guys out the top 15, it can be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this as a very easy fight for Duffy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S155041311630643X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tumours slowed by diet tweak. A high-fat diet speeds tumour growth in mice, but this can be counteracted by drugs that lower levels of a metabolite in the blood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people who listens / watches Joe's podcast, they know what they are getting into. 

You are not going there like "let's see what James has to say about Metallica". You know it will be about Joe's stuff. And that's what you watch. It is different because it is him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And thats why this casters have partner with high mmr to call them out if they talking bullshit. 

I don't think you understood what 345atom said: "Theoretical knowledge can often outweigh practically being able to apply something." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study finds parents who talk with their high schoolers about science and math can increase competency and career interest in the fields. The findings show a 12% increase on the science ACT for students whose parents were provided with information on how to convey the importance of science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/10/1607386114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/10/1612113114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The genes that predispose people to attain higher levels of education have been in decline over the past 80 years, and researchers are suggesting that theyre now under negative selection, which could have a big impact on our species in the coming centuries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/10/1615867114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complex life might have come and gone on Earth long before the multicellular organisms we're familiar with today arose, a new study suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is being a dick. I know a lot of people will say he is a funny and so much bantz (mostly because he is the champ, and champs seem to get a pass here), but he is being a dick.

This post by TJ was quite cool, and he had a douchebag answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I never really understood the hate for the 3D. I always really enjoy it.

It is a gimmick that was never really implemented in a game, apart from the wow effect, and it made the console way more expensive, with subpar hardware and shitty screens, and it almost caused the console to flopped to the point that Nintendo had to lower the price a lot and bleed money.

The problem is not the effect itself, which is neat, but what it meant for the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think it is a gimmick. The fact that Nintendo released the 2DS is them saying it is a gimmick. Can you imagine a DS without touch screens? Impossible.

The 3D effect almost killed the console when it was released because at the beginning it had a very high price with subpar hardware because they compromised the hardware in order to use the 3D screen. One of the big things about the NDS is how fast it was cheap. I remember buying the Nintendogs pack for 150 euros. 

Remember that the NDS was initially 150$ and then very fast dropped to $120. The 3ds was initially $250. That's just mental.

IMO if they had just released the 3DS without the 3D effect with a lower price the console would have done much better. Anyway it is doing very well. But it almost flopped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point still remains. If you cannot manage your own country because you need to manage Brexit, then you shouldn't be a PM.

In any case, she has teams, cabinets, experts,... she is not really doing much, she is an administrator, a kind of a CEO. The same can be applied to any other president / PM btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She's got her hands full with Brexit. She might pivot to that stuff after. 

If she cannot tackle two or more problems at the same time she shouldn't be a PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a politician. You will always like what they say. The question is how much of it will be real, and how will it be implemented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redmi 4 Prime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I see RAM usage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am using 8.1.2.0. I can see the free RAM using the left button in the phone when it shows all the opened apps. But I would like to see this in more detail. Like how that RAM is being used, what other apps are using it, and so. I have been through the settings (and also tried in Google) but I cannot see the option to check it.

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using the Wiki I think I installed a good one (global I guess, official, because my phone is locked) 6.0.1 MMB29M ... 8.1.2.0 (MBEMIDI)

I hope this is the good one. Let's see if I can unlock it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should I follow the instructions in that link as he did?

http://en.miui.com/a-232.html

what's wrong doing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> strange. seems very easy. you didnt need a special cable or recovery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about my new phone (Redmi 4 prime) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am new to Xiaomi, and I only wanted to know which phone do I exactly have, and which OS.

When I go to settings, model number says "Redmi 4" (nothing about prime). Although it says it has 3.00 GB RAM and 32GB total memory.

The android version is 6.0.1 MMB29M

The MIUI version is MIUI Global 8.0 Stable. 8.0.5.00(MBECNDG)

Is this one of the scam versions I should remove asap?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New user, very slow speeds (arch linux) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 11:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably this has been asked a lot, so I am sorry for repeating myself.

I got PIA yesterday and I am very disappointed with the speeds offered. I mostly want it to stream video, and the moment I enable the VPN the video goes to very low quality. I have tried in several servers (US east, UK london, UK south, Netherlands, Romania, Sweden).

I did a torrent test, and without any vpn I get around 1 to 1.2m, which is my usual speed. Once I enable the vpn, any of the servers, it goes between 50 to 250k.

In order to install it, I basically followed the info in Archlinux wiki. I installed openvpn and private-internet-access client. Then in terminal "pia -a". Then in login.conf my username and password. And finally "opencv --config" to my config file.

They offer a 1 week refund, so I think I will do it, unless I am doing something wrong that is killing it. I expected it to be slower, but it is going down to around a 10% of my real speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 09:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone expects Trump to trump the dollar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weakest cards IMO, even weaker than fight pass only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing. I love it. It has all the ingredients for being awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3ds had initially a very similar price  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendo is going full force with the switch though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 500 makes no sense. I go every 2-3 months to Barcelona and I rarely pay more than 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very simple. If the Switch is a success, the 3DS line is dead.

If the Switch fails, they will keep the 3DS line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not. The last thing we need is more expensive planes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really believe that? 

Do you really think that running a train is not expensive that flying a plane? 

The main difference is monopoly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Mario Run cannot really be considered a game. 

Mobile games are miles away from any 3ds game. As much as mobile gaming improves, Nintendo improves even more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flying is also not subsidized </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two friends living in Newcastle and Birmingham met up in Malaga because it was cheaper to fly to Spain than getting the train to see each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Spanish from Barcelona. So yeah I've been watching futbol all my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 10:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there twice so I recommend it 100%. Also from their museum itself there's a very short walk to the Clyde falls which are very nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is short, he has kind of short limbs. I see him being like Mendes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it he a ufc card with mma fights and then at the end box in a ring ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd be a wrestler I think based on his body type.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot remember a single game where I used the stylus to be honest. Most games are top screen for the game itself, bot screen for menus / maps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Youth is certainly on Conor's side, but as far as athleticism and conditioning idk about that.

Athleticism and conditioning is directly related to youth. I am 31 now, and I like to exercise. When I was like 25, my body recovered within hours. Now I even feel it the next day. Conor should only sign if USADA random tests are available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If we're saying 'close fight'.. he'll need a lot more than a year to catch up with somebody who has been boxing every day for his whole childhood and adult life. Conor did box but not even 1/10 the amount Floyd has.

The only thing in Conor's favour is that if they fight in a year, he will be on his physical peak. He will be like 28-29, while Floyd will be 40 or even 41.

If it was Conor being 29 against Floyd when he was 29, then there's no chance for Conor. But the older we are, the worse our body behaves. It is just life. When MJ was 40 with Washington he was not doing the numbers he was doing with the Bulls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they speak about this, like a fighter having clear flaws and no one taking advantatge of it, I always think about Leo Messi.

Leo Messi, arguably the best footballer playing today and maybe in the while history only has a left leg. He is not tall, or strong, or super fast. He has good acceleration, low center of gravity and the best left leg ever. The thing about Messi is that he almost always dribble to the left. I remember 10 years when he started people were saying "he is just a one trick pony, one people prepares for him, he is done". Well, 10 years later he is still the best.

I don't know if Conor fighting is as good as Leo playing football, but being uni dimensional is not a bad thing per se, if you are miles ahead in what you do than anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing. I wonder if we will ever get Conor in JRE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering that Pokemon SuMo and N3DS were sold out everywhere, at the moment they are very far away from failing. They'd need like 2 handheld failures, and that's unlikely to happen when they are the only ones in that segment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Transworld Sport. 

omg memories I remember this program when I was a kid in the 90s, I used to love it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is a 3DS succesor I really hope it doesn't have a 3D screen. It was (and is) a gimmick that just made the console 50$ more expensive. Not a single game uses it except for the "wow" effect, and the hype of 3D movies and all that is phasing away. Also, the use of the double screen, while it was amazing in the NDS it is rarely used in the 3DS apart from extending the menu options and the like. I would prefer a single bigger screen.

That said, I think if there's a 3DS (or DS line) successor will greatly depend on the success of the Switch. If the switch fails, then we will see a new DS console. if it rocks, then they will merge it with the DS line as the new portable console. That's why IMO nintendo is not being 100% open with it. Same as they did with the DS, saying it won't eat the game boy. The moment they saw the DS was a success, they killed the game boy.

That said, I really hope the Switch is a success because I really like the concept of home / portable. I will wait though to see if when they remodel it or whatever they ship it with a better battery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  skinny

? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't miss my first guitar. It was a spanish guitar I bought more than 15 years ago for something like 50 euros. It was utter crap. Horrible neck, horrible sound, horrible everything.

I also don't miss my first electric guitar. it was a brand named "kohler" which as far as I know was only sold in Spain. It has a HSS configuration. My parents paid for it like 80 euros. I didn't like it back then but it was the cheaper one, and I don't like it nowadays. The neck feels good, and the electronics are stable even though the guitar is around 15 years old. It probably needs a refret. To make things worse I had the horrible idea of covering it with stickers, but then I didn't like the stickers to I removed them. Nowadays the guitar has a few very ugly stickers marks that I don't know how to remove.

I haven't played any of these guitars in like 7-8 years, I haven't even taken them out of the bag. They are in my parents house and I want to bin them, but my parents are not doing it because they have space. if these guitars had some value I would sell them.

I have never felt too attached to any of my guitars, to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can yeah that's why I have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about the finish. The guitar is exactly like this one:

http://www.guitarjames.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/2015-03-01-17.47.33.jpg

Same color. As far as I know they only did this color in 1999.

What would annoy me the most if that the thieve would get like 300 pounds at most, while I would need to speed 1000 for a new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although Nintendo is not making it clear, everything seems to indicate that Switch is going to replace 3DS. The 3DS is like 5 years old, it is at the end of its cycle, and with the new Pokemon there's almost nothing new announced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://science.sciencemag.org/content/355/6321/194 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First animal cells may have been created by viruses. Scientists at the University of California have for the first time discovered just how extensive that virus reprogramming can be, effectively turning bacterial cells into animal or plant-like cells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I don't know what I expected, but 280 with only one game (that you need to buy, so that's an extra 50-60) is too much for me.

I have never bought a console on release, so I will wait until they make a good bundle (like next christmas?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independently of the "deal" we are paying 30 more pounds for a similar product on release.

I am not blaming Nintendo or anything like that by the way. As you said, dropping to the previous 250 when the price in dollars would be 295 would be impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I think it is interesting how fast it can have an impact on our daily life. Most people doesn't seem to care because "they don't trade". Wii U was released like 4 years ago. 30 pounds is big difference. It is half of the cost of a game (or like a full 3DS game). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Nintendo console "Switch" will cost 280 (vs $300 in USA). Previous Nintendo console "Wii U" was 250 on release (vs also $300 in USA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What really surprises me is all the business people who take him as an "ally" and then basically they are scammed to hell. An example of this is Peter Lim and Valencia. Another example is Deportivo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Always fancied a Stratocaster, aye?

It is actually not worth that much because it is from 99 and it is bashed with a few dings here and there, plus some of the frets needing to be new some of these days, but it is my guitar and I don't want to lose it.

I can imagine a random thieve going to one of this "cash now" shops would get at most 300, but for me to get a new one would be 1000 or whatever is their cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gate leading to the shared backgarden/parking always open lately. I did close it, but they keep it open. Anything I can do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a tenement building. There is a square formed with different of these tenement blocks, and there is a parking / backgarden inside the square. This parking is only accessible through a gate, which for the last 4 years I have been living here has always been closed. Well, it opens when a car gets it, and then it closes.

For the last week or so it did surprise me that every time I walked in front of it it was wide open. At first I thought it was just a car coming in or out, but yesterday I waited like 10 minutes and nothing came in or out, so I went to check the gate, and it seems someone is using a belt to keep it open. So I remove the belt and let it close. This morning I went again and I saw that someone placed the belt again, so the gate is wide open again.

Why do I care so much? Because I live in a ground floor with a big window giving to the backgarden. Anyone with a brick or with some sort of basic lever can easily open my flat and steal stuff (I have, for example, a Fender Stratocaster made in USA which I don't want to lose [it is actually not worth that much because it is from 99, it has a few very visible dings and it probably needs a refret, but I dont want to lose it because it is my guitar, and because a new one would cost 1000 pounds, when this one is worth at most 400], and my laptop and shit like that.). And I know that in the last 6 months people have seen some idiots trying to break in into houses through the backgardens.

I have always felt safe knowing that the gate was there closed. Yeah someone can climb in, or squeeze in while a car is going through, but that is unlikely to happen. At the moment it is open 24/7. It is also a quiet backgarden. It is not like someone breaking in a flat through the street window with people moving around. There's no one really in the backgarden apart from the odd car coming in or out once every few hours.

I don't know what to do. It is a big square so there are maybe 10 blocks, potentially a lot of users who can use that parking. I contacted my landlord but it is unrelated to him. That gate is actually there to protect the cars, not the houses. I don't know if I have anything to say about that gate being closed (as it is supposed to be), or if now I must live on knowing that it will be open 24/7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try http://sci-hub.cc/

There's no legal way to circumvent it. Sometimes if you go to the websites of the authors they have the PDFs there for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v541/n7636/full/nature20799.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have demonstrated the first laser based on an unconventional wave physics phenomenon called bound states in the continuum. The technology could revolutionize the development of surface lasers, making them more compact and energy-efficient for communications and computing applications </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/3/1/e1601558 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists recreate stellar combustion conditions using compact lasers instead of the huge ones previously used. They achieved it by hitting nanowire arrays with ultra-short laser pulses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is just the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any of you read the article? It is total crap, and the person who is writting it doesn't seem to know much about football. For example, right from the start:

"What a surprise to find that sporticidal maniac Gianni Infantino has added yet another awards ceremony to footballs calendar. "

He is not adding anything, you idiot. FIFA player trophies and French Football one just divided as a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not really into bagpipes, but Hevia is famous in Spain yeah, Also Carlos Nunez: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tG_hDYqdpqs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Spain both instruments are called "gaita", which means bagpipe. I wonder how different is the sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's make-up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 12:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I turned it off and then turned it on if I needed to grind at all.

I like this.

In my second run of Pokemon Y and had it off all the time, and the grind was real. I spent around 45h just to finish the main game, without trying to catch all the pokemon. At some point, I think it as gym 7, I had to switch it on, because otherwise it was just impossible to move forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am waiting for my copy of Pokemon Moon, and I have a quick question. is the share experience as broken as with XY? I mostly buy the game for the main story, and I want it to be a challengue. Not impossible, but I don't like it being an easy walk as Pokemon XY, where I basically 1 shot everyone without grinding. (then I try the game without share exp, and it was almost impossible).

Just wondering what I should I do, keep it on or off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought Pokemonn Moon, waiting for it to arrive. Is the share experience as broken as with Pokemon XY? I want the game to be a challengue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galicians (NW Spain) playing the bagpipes. It is also their national instrument, no kilts though </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 10:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a strong opinion in favour or against PEDs. It just shocked me watching their bodies after mostly watching UFC fights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
