<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah THAT was a master troll.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Means you scored above average! I got a 141 so you beat me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and I both! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The BLE will do an oral review of the test with you. Take advantage of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is beyoootiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MAZAL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think went wrong? Don't despair, two classmates just passed after failing the Feb '16 exam. Why they felt compelled to take it during Spring 3L I'll never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What'd you do different the third time? Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit show of advice here. Do you have test anxiety? Did you run out of time? Did you complete every section? Did you miss something major on an essay? Was your MBE bad? Several of my classmates failed the Feb '16 bar and passed this time. In one case it was purely the taker psyching themselves out. Another, it was not understanding (after three years, mind you) how to write a proper Bar essay. 

Start studying now, but take it slow. If MD publishes past bar essays and answers, read EVERY ONE of them. Outline them. Utilize the retake guarantee the prep course likely has. If it's Kaplan, submit as many essays as you can. Also, do not overlook the MPT and do several practice ones under test conditions. SOURCE: I just passed the TX bar and thought I didn't have a shot in hell. 

Why would you begin to think a fail is the end and you should toss the JD out the window???  So go sign on as a paralegal somewhere and go for it again in February.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prep course is at fault? "Blame" is the wrong concept in any case. It's an exam, if one does not pass one did not meet the standard and blame is useless. Fail is still fail regardless of fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...The opel omega that zigs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lime is still the flavor in Ukraine and Russia. Unfortunately you can only purchase them in Ukraine and Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and double the price tag. Fuck the ELR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genius advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. Fuck TeleFlora. Always go local. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's called dispute with the credit card... eff every bit of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....if this weren't /r/aww I could leave the NSFW snarky response that is so richly deserved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remote? Meet face. Face? Meet remote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....every time I think Reddit can't suprise me more, it does. Love that this is a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question I'd be asking myself is what good a degree from a UK law school do if you intend to return to/remain in Canada. Also, Sussex from an initial glance isn't one of their top universities. Looks like there's about ~50 law schools in the UK and Sussex is mid-pack. Do they have a Criminology program that is notable? 

My thought is; you're better served going to a Canadian law school if you can get into one, especially if you intend to live and practice in an area that utilizes civil law vs common law. This is especially true given costs of attending school in the UK. If you can't get into a Canadian university? Consider whether lawschool is really the right path.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Network network network network. Seriously. But not just professionally. Socially as well. I would not have made it through law school if it weren't for a rich and enjoyable life outside school. The Meetup app is great for this; events tailored around things of interest to you. Also; make sure to make time and take time AWAY from school. You can be too focused. If there's other law schools in your area, meet some of those students and compare notes. Great way to make friends and get/give fill-in material that might not covered in your/their classes.

Source: Graduated in May with honors, just passed the TX bar first time out, and was phoning it in quite a bit of the time whilst enjoying life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved my 1L year. Then again I may be odd but I loved all of law school. Having a tight section really helped. We were absolutely a family. Graduated this past May and know I'll remain tight with them all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yuuuuup... skip the bullcrap and go for the nuggets that matter and are relevant to the overarching area of focus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Law was savage back then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you want to go to law school? This is the most important question. 

Some schools your experience will help but these are going to be lower/4th tier schools that are only useful if you already have a career path and/or connections and just need the JD. 

You're a sophomore so you have plenty of time. Focus on getting your GPA as high as possible and start studying for the LSAT now. Take practice tests on a regular basis. Plan to take the LSAT the June before your senior year in college. You will then have your score and a good idea of your graduating GPA to consider when applying. If your LSAT is subpar you can retake it but schools see ALL scores and will average between them. If your first LSAT is low, consider that an indication you may wish to give law school a miss. 

Truly, if you have a solid realty business going? Focus on that and stick with it. You'll avoid the expense of law school and make as much or more money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a sheltered soul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool!! Now they can f*ck up an entirely new set of poor machines! Source: had to go ninja on several laptops for people in my class just to return the ability to turn the thing off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're a rock star student and/or the states both use the UBE and the exams will be largely identical I can't imagine this is advisable. Trying to keep one state's laws straight and endure the exam is difficult enough. I'd take one and then take the other at the next opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fifteen minutes!" "PSYCH!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iiiii'm goooone GIT ME A SHOTGUN AND [KILL ALL THE WHITEYS I SEE!](https://youtu.be/vKXZCbpYgSo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotchu fam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't work; it's a [dual band](https://www.cnet.com/products/samsung-gt-e1080-black-gsm-cellular-phone/specs/) phone and only works on 900/1800Mhz GSM which isn't in use in the United States. T-Mobile still uses 2G GSM on 1900Mhz but it's likely going away within a few years. 3G feature phones are a bit thin on the ground; the Alcatel 768 would seem to fit your needs if you can find a used one that was T-Mobile or MetroPCS branded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...yes,dear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/losttheplot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but at least he wasn't gonna put up a fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL some athletes pee on their hands in an effort to toughen them. If anything, this likely softens them. Urea, a major component of urine, is an ingredient in many moisturizers, but to have an effect it must be absorbed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like you're jerking someone off into your mouth. Source, did this whilst in view of a mirror.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um... don't feel so bad. Moved with parents when I was fourteen into a fixer upper. House had a pool that hadn't been filled in probably ten years. Deep end was home to a 'pond' with a thriving colony of frogs. First night my best friend stayed over we naturally beelined for the pool. After screwing around on bikes for a while (it was a very large pool) we made for the frogs. Probably 30-40 frogs from smaller ones to full grown big ass toads. 

So what do we do? See how high we can toss them and watch them go splat on the plaster. I felt no regret over this as a child, but did later in life. We'd toss them up vertically, their legs and arms would shoot out full length as they spiraled upward, then hang for a brief instant and come plummeting down. Amazingly, none were killed by this but the splats were very loud and very 'splat-ty'. Exactly what you want as a fourteen year old. 

The frogs? They'd lay, still and no doubt shocked, for a few seconds to over a minute. Then they'd gather themselves up and progressively crawl/walk/hop off back to the 'pond' at the deep end.  In our defense, we never tossed a frog twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's funny is more people have opportunities for him even now than Moises Alou. Bartman's turned down Superbowl commercials, home plate seats etc etc etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you Jobu, I do it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...most of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Caray and Bill Murray at the first Wrigley Field night game on 8-8-88 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...or I could have experience there and elsewhere in Asia, and have tried several unlocked phones from the US that had service in some areas of a city but not others because they didn't support all the bands the carrier did. Every SK carrier uses at least two LTE bands. 

Definitely agree Korea's phone market pricing is very very strange and it's easy to stupid overpay for devices and service. Might just be easiest to find someone PCSing elsewhere and buy their Korean phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're around wifi frequently it's great. If you use many gigs of data a month fi isn't for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not good advice unless OP has an iphone 6/6s/7 or a galaxy s7/edge.. Radio bands differ widely and a US phone may get limited or no coverage at all there. Frequencycheck.org is the bible for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 21:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still going to be based on T-mobile, Verizon, AT T or Sprint except in certain circumstances in limited areas of the country (C-Spire, US Cellular, Viaero, and other regional providers). 

Burning Man's Papa Legba camp and Burning Man in general are not valid to use as an example of not providing reliable services. There's nothing and nobody out on the Playa except for BRC when it's there. There's zero reason to build out permanent coverage there. Commnet has provided roaming coverage there but quite frankly many Burners prefer the disconnect from default world. Not sure why Range Networks decided not to continue their camp/network but absent that, you're not going to find a commercial cellular service that'll cover Burning Man except a satellite service like Iridium which are horribly expensive and offer data speeds equivalent to 1988 dialup at it's best (9600bps). 

If you want the ability to use multiple carriers and have frequent access to WiFi, go with Project Fi. 

TL;DR: Verizon is, on balance, the most reliable network in the country, business practices aside. You may be mistaking phone issues for network problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely an internally routed IP. T-mobile does the same thing and uses a DoD IP block for internal purposes. Were the government monitoring this way, VZW and AT T would likely have similar DoD IPs and they do not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came from where? If purchased from a secondary source, that's the distributor/vendor trying to pass off a stolen/refurb phone off. Betting it 'fell off a truck'. Samsung is not sending out refurb S7's as new but scumbag secondary resellers do this all day every day. Source: Been to Shenzhen, seen guys stuffing 'remade' devices into boxes and shrinkwrapping as new. Have seen guys in Houston taking delivery of 'diverted' goods and reselling them on Ebay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attorney, are you? Specifics would depend on the jurisdiction of the country/state/municipal laws in question, but that burden of proof would be to CONVICT, not arrest. That's the DAs job. Dine and dash is no different than a beer run or a pump and fly. You're taking goods and/or services without paying. Whether intentional or not, you're still very likely to get arrested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ever go to Scotland. It's the land of the well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...funny, I've stopped seeing someone over treating a server like shit as well. All sweetness and light to me but go full on bitch to the person handling your food? No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 12:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible that the pre-trial agreements were to limit sentencing and penalties to a level that was higher than actually imposed thus the agreement would have no effect. If you agree to no more than eighteen months confinement and get six months the agreement is immaterial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wipe your phone or start uninstalling software one by one. Could be spyware? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What nobody's said?? His plan will NOT NOT NOT work over there. If his international feature is on he'll be roaming and it'll cost a fortune. As has been said call and suspend service while he's deployed and then get a cheap prepaid phone and SIM card while there. iPad or iPhone on wifi will do hangouts and IMessage. Google voice will do phone calls back to the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case it seems warranted and the perfect response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 13:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mature.

Manure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 13:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...or just THINK you get shit done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 13:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't call me dude, pal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 13:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul of Frytreides? Is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples Macbook Pro Touch of Genius Forgets the iPhone 7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earthquake Rattles Rome, Shaking Historic Palazzi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the northeast and west coast absolutely. Airtime was not nearly as expensive in the South and carrier/dealer subsidies were a thing plus at the time activations paid residuals until the customer cancelled. My first phone was a used trade in. At the time the cheap phones were Uniden bag phones and sold for ~$99 on a three year contract. Car phone installs added about another hundred to the cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is /r/thathappened leaking? Those were the days where knowing a little bit about networking and computers in high school would get you paid and get you a 'demo' line from one of the cellular dealers (good old Southwestern Bell Mobile Systems gave out demo lines like candy if the dealer sold enough). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carter Orders Pentagon to Stop Collecting Recruitment Bonuses From Calif. Guard Vets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 04:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, so unlike elsewhere analogue was not banned, just no longer required. So almost all carriers went to more spectrum efficient technologies almost immediately. But especially out in the boondocks there's always some independent carrier that keeps old tech alive for the customers that just won't move. IMTS (precursor to AMPS/0G) was 40+ years old and still in use into the middle of the last decade in Canada. Believe the last carrier was Bell Aliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta be kidding me. That. Was. The. Original. Flip. Phone. The one that defined the term. The mass market version everyone had was the DPC-550. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the story of my life, with matzo ball soup on the side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nokia's first phones did indeed [look like bricks](http://orig03.deviantart.net/1aaf/f/2014/319/e/8/nokia_cityman_1320__nokia_s_first_handheld__by_redfield_1982-d86ikct.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used both! And it was 1989 that flip-phones rolled out. We didn't have caller ID, so you'd let incoming calls roll to voicemail and only respond to pages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not [exactly](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Motorola_MicroTAC#MicroTAC_9800X). 1989 to be precise. The MicroTAC, MicroTAC Alpha, Lite, Digital Alpha, Digital Lite, UltraLite and Elite all preceded the StarTAC. I had one of each as they were released. 

The Elite and StarTAC were VIP versions from Motorola direct. Motorola had an awesome cellular service that required a contract with them, but could be switched from city to city at will. They had number blocks with carriers throughout the country. So I could call them up and get a New York number if going to NYC, then get a Vegas number if going there, etc. Saved a ton on roaming charges and just returned any voicemails I got on my primary number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the officer asked permission to search means he didn't have probable cause. If he did, he wouldn't have needed to ask. A refusal to permit a search may generate reasonable suspicion but that refusal alone is insufficient to reach probable cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cellphone 1980 link above that /u/P14159265 posted is the prototype for the first handheld phone held by Martin Cooper, the inventor. It wouldn't work today even if it were compatible with the AMPS analog cellular standard because AMPS networks have been shut down. (It is possible there's still one running somewhere.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up until the body change from W123 to W140 they were pretty much rock solid. A 420 or 560 SEL will still be mostly bulletproof today absent fuel distributor problems and even that just results in a rough idle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confIrm, unless you were a maniac and went for the 450SEL 6.9 you were getting a turbo D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had my first handheld in 1991 and flip phones became a thing in 1987 or so. My first phone was a "transportable"which was a carphone with transceiver and 1lb lead acid battery. Three hours standby, twenty minutes talk time. High high high tech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get signalcheck and it'll tell you the underlying roaming carrier. Was flawless across about ten countries thus far with the base Fi SIM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clouds reflecting off the wing of a plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fritos burn and will serve as birthday candles in a pinch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, the 2707 never happened although the Russian Concordeski was a thing for a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great electrostatics but those holes in the panel mean they're ruined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the United States Air Force has a Pipe Band that was formed in 1950 from bagpipe players of Irish and Scottish ancestry exclusively. The Band played at President Kennedy's funeral. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1981 Lincoln Town Car. 5.0L 302 V8. 130HP, 230lb/ft torque, 14 seconds 0-60. You used every damn one of those ponies to just get the huge beast moving and down the highway. Air-cleaner moan FTL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 19:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. One character that can cause entire departments mass heart attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 18:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An admin person will see it and hopefully route it properly which, coming from the executive suite, will get attention  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....unless you do the exchange personally with your own money. Which might also get you fired. Or might not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have Band 12 support which will mean no service in certain areas when here in the US and the Z has limited global LTE support (only band 3 and 7). That said, those two bands will get you LTE on at least one carrier almost everywhere in the world services are offered. Whether you can roam on that carrier is another matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any Verizon smartphone offered today is both GSM and CDMA but not all have Band 12 support (as is the case with the Droid Z).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In NYC, Houston, Austin, Dallas, SFO, LA, and Denver I've only roamed on Verizon 3G.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 09:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The state where you were married is crucial here; that law controls how long it takes to get divorced and what you need to do to get the divorce. Some states have no waiting period to divorce, some have as long as an 18 month waiting period before you can divorce. 

If she has an attorney do NOT just sign off on the decree you're handed. Even if she doesn't; if you aren't drafting the paperwork have someone look over it because in most states what you sign is what will take effect even if the family law code provides differently, because that divorce decree is also an enforceable contract. 

If things are truly amicable let her have all the furniture and household items and use that to negotiate her taking on more of whatever debt you have (if any). Go find several much younger and better looking rebounds and enjoy freedom and the joy of doing your own laundry and ironing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Wheels on the bus go round and round..." "SHUT THE FUCK UP, CARL!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running slightly faster due to jet exhaust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cargurus is an amazing site for shipping used cars. Shows you how long the car's been for sale and the price history. When something has been sitting around for 5 months they can bluster all they want but will almost always bend over to get it gone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lighten up, Francis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ruining things in what way? Trying to force her to talk is likely to make her withdraw further. Might try just saying "I hope you'll talk to me about what's going on. I respect your choice if you don't want to. I'm here either way and am not going anywhere." Leave it at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 10:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I came to post. That's the smell of cheap Chinese factories and plastics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/bestofreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given outsourcing, you quite probably do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the deduction called for damage? GPLD?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and a good attorney. That's textbook neglience and the hotel is quite likely liable for the entire loss because the area wasn't secured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP COMES THROUGH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well...Fuck.....OK...breathe....recover...we good....OHNO...FFFUUCCKKK! Fine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judges can pretty much write whatever they want in an opinion. I've seen "Scarface" quotes, Star Trek references, song lyrics, even an entire opinion in [prose](http://lawiscool.com/2007/08/12/law-is-poetry-literally/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only in name. Same with the store in So. Africa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Foot Locker is the last of the F.W. Woolworth company, one of the world's largest retail chains during the 20th century. Initially a sub-brand of a subsidiary, Foot Locker became the corporation's top performer as traditional stores declined. The corporation adopted the Foot Locker name in 2001. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MVP RIGHT HERE! Also, happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...kinda akin to the Lambo scene where he made it home without a scratch... or didn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely were concerned about human trafficking. The "that's my child/parent" gambit is used often which is why they ask. It's not about you, it's about catching the assholes that kidnap, enslave, and torture kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be my hell. I love indian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DDDOOOOIIINNNGG!? GET AWAY FROM HIM!"  
"C'mere ya little asshole. ISAIDCOME H E R E!"  
"Now...(gritted teeth voice) What. The. Ever. Loving. Hell. Were. You. THINKING!"  
"...b.b.b.b.b.bbutttMOOMmmm!!"  
"SHADDUP! I don't want to hear it. You could've gotten yourself KILLED! We are LEAVING."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL liking Tejano is a problem. Actually, I prefer Norteos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but I like Tejano? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta start young if you want to enjoy your kids and your life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 05:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't but does now. I regularly use Band 12 on my Nexus 6 with Fi when on T-mo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....annnnnd it's blocked. Hence, the GIF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sushi Chef Level : Beginner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaching Tradition From From Brother To Brother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sushi Chef Level: Beginner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL an academic analysis of the Darwin Awards was performed and concluded that males are significantly more likely to take idiotic risks and thus remove themselves from the gene pool than females. This resulted in formation of MIT or "Male Idiot Theory". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 06:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 06:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darwin award candidate, sounds like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 06:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A certain 'towering' hotel in Hong Kong that's part of the Stariot family charges TWO THOUSAND DOLLARS as a deposit. Doesn't matter length of stay, could be one night. They whack your card for HKD$15,000 at check-in. I'm curious what the hell happened to cause THAT policy to be enacted. I had a one night extension two months ago and had to check out and in again. No luck keeping the deposit they already had. Nope, charged me another one. Did not complain and didn't contact corporate. I feel for anyone using a debit card there though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 01:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering if you are at the property /u/SCSWitch left... sounds like very similar situations. Keep your chin up, it DOES get better! Look at it this way, it wasn't and isn't about you. Unfortunate that he can't be a decent enough person to know he's talking to another human but at least you won't do that to someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [video](https://www.buzzfeed.com/andrewgauthier/the-president-uses-a-selfie-stick).  

Here's the relevant [SubReddit post](https://www.reddit.com/r/ThanksObama/comments/2vpleh/game_over_folks/). While /r/ThanksObama is still restricted to new posts, it appears a mod recently made a new post  where Obama "thanked himself" for lower gas prices and other achievements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 05:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 7 days "FFFFFUUUUUU JJJOOOEEEEYYYY!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When options packages go from personalized to extremely personal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not a dumb question. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/2e04kr/what_is_doxxing_and_why_is_it_used/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When doxxing and SWATting became a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...any fap/cringe-worthy NSFW sub, and there's so many out there that are quite beyond most imaginations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we visited our newborn daughters' grave by ourselves for the first time. FWB that became even closer friends. LPT: When the condom breaks, stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Sports Team's Fans (Professional or Collegiate) are the most butt-hurt after a loss? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note 3 from which carrier? If Verizon, it's missing Band 4 LTE which is the primary band T-Mobile uses for LTE and UMTS. Without that you're reliant on Band 2/1900 which they use for fill in and EDGE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VoLTE is band independent. Though required on Band 12 because the data-only LTE signal has better reach than their Band 4 AWS and Band 2 PCS services which offer UMTS fallback/circuit switched voice, it will still operate on B2/B4 and eventually be the standard for voice as UMTS eventually goes away. USCC and T-Mobile both utilize Band 12 for LTE and VoLTE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USCC is implementing VoLTE, and will roam with T-mobile (and vice versa) at the beginning of 2017.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Haiti and Liechtenstein independently designed identical national flags and only learned of this when they competed at the 1936 Olympics. As a result, Liechtestein added a crown to their flag. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 23:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: He knew he was talking about meeting you and wanted her to have picked you the entire time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Boston Law Enforcement agencIes asked Dunkin Donuts to stay open while the city was on lockdown during the search for the second Boston Marathon Bomber. They did, and provided food and coffee to officers for free. Starbucks, and the rest of the city, were shut down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you had some non-package mods or are talking about 157km/h, ain't no way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadowbusted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women going hard with balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...still getting blown, just not as hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....But then you're possibly replacing the made in US quality stuff with made in China breaks every time-a. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
