<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5756</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 20:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Group therapy starts next week and I am waiting for the antidepressant prescription to go through.  But today, I am sitting at home guilty about the fact that I am not at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 20:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so.  I've actually considered going back to school to become a School Psychologist, and the experience would definitely prove useful if I went that route. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 05:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have a lionhead English Spot mix - like me!  My bun [Fluffy](https://scontent-sea1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xaf1/v/t1.0-9/11143292_10103390360512211_1858750454105421186_n.jpg?oh=4e87e3b0182e87a030c4c5c5561b6b07 oe=573FC5C0) looks a lot like yours, except her spots are more grey/brown.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 04:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my girl Fluffy does the same thing.  When she pees outside of the box, it's usually in the same spot and a few days before we change the litter.  It's her way of expressing her displeasure with the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher with Depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 04:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I was diagnosed with an episode of major depression and anxiety.  It has been a rough school year for me with a lot of changes that brought me to the point of uncontrollable crying for two days in a row, migraines, muscle tension, and an inability to really get any work done with my students.  My principal suggested I take the day to go to the doctor, and now I'll be out for over two weeks attending group counselling sessions and starting antidepressants.

Everyone is telling me that I need to take care of myself now, but I can't help feeling guilty.  I feel I am letting everyone down and worry that I still won't be of any use when I return in a few weeks.  This is supposed to make me feel better, but all I can think about is how awkward it will be when I return.  What will my coworkers and students think?

Has anyone else on this subreddit been through a similar situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 22:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in Gardena and there are a lot of different micro-cultures within the city.  

One of my favorite facts about Gardena is that many Japanese immigrated to the city, so there are a lot of fantastic Japanese restaurants.  It's what I miss most about living there!  Definitely look up the Shinsengumi chain of restaurants.

I never came across any active gang members in my 10+ years living there, just some graffiti every once in awhile.  Then again, I lived in what some may call the nicer part of Gardena.  My elementary school (Chapman Elementary) received the California Distinguished school award and was ethnically diverse.  In fact, I've never found another city as ethnically diverse as Gardena.

My suggestion is to do some research.  There are websites that can help you determine things like crime rate in any city that can help you pinpoint where in Gardena you would like to live.  I would highly recommend moving there as long as you do your research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 20:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I adopted both of my buns from http://www.rabbitrescue.com/.  They are a wonderful rescue, taking in expectant mothers and even rabbits with medical issues.  They are located in Southern California and also accept online donations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just need to rant... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 02:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today was an awful day.  

It was supposed to be a great day because my kids put on a play showing off their awesome reading skills to their parents and other students at the school (my kids are in Kindergarten, for the record).  Then we received a memo that there would be assemblies and field trips during the day.  Also, my full time aide would be pulled out for pretty much all day.  He's been pulled from my room every day for the past week, so I shouldn't have been surprised.  

Why is this a big deal?  Well, because I have a class of 30 kids and he's in charge of our stage crew who are designing costumes, scenery, and props so everyone is involved in the play.  Since he keeps getting pulled out, we haven't gotten practice or to finish those things.  There was an aide who offered to help, but she didn't finish until 30 minutes after all of the parents and students had arrived to watch the performance.  I had to improve while waiting.  I ended up leading everyone in nursery rhymes and Simon Says.  Not to mention a student cut herself with fabric scissors she found laying around so deeply that she wouldn't stop bleeding for like 10 minutes.

I'm sure it wasn't as bad as I thought it was, but it's frustrating planning all of these fun things and then not being ready because admin decides to pull my aide and change the day.  I feel like a failure for not being able to figure it out and be ready for what was supposed to be a great day.  In the end, it was probably my stress that made the day not as great as it should have been for the kids.  I feel like I have failed my kids by not being prepared.  THAT is the worst feeling of all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize she would still smell my rainbow bunny.  He had a hard time getting along with the other bunnies at the shelter, the girls kept attacking him.  =(  Wonder if it has anything to do with that.

Thanks for the perspective about the chin rubbing, I will definitely keep that in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have spent about $100, but i think less than half of that went toward the matchmaking services.  Most of it went to the shelter to help them continue taking care of and feeding the other rabbits - well, and to make sure that I wanted to adopt for the right reasons.  http://rabbitrescue.com/matchmaking.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input, I will definitely use vinegar as a precaution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell by your flair that you have quite a bit of experience.  =)   Thumper died from a sudden onset of bloat.  I will make sure to disinfect.  Do you use vinegar or soap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 05:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's real!  http://rabbitrescue.com/matchmaking.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
