<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1847</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only am telling a story and telling what went through my head.  It wasn't intended to be political per se.  Just that's what is going through my head right now with some of the radical changes I'm seeing in our country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> point taken
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  Would be funny though if someone else did something as stupid as this.

By the time I realized what was going on I spent the rest of the ride home thinking of every "clue" that was right front of me that my mind wasn't quite connecting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since some people are questioning this let me clarify.  I don't know  what you [5] is but to me that is happy, healthy, highly aware.

I tend to have an edible on the weekend as it helps me keep working into the afternoon through some of the "ol' man pains".

I was in no way "impaired".  And I *never* leave home with anything in a vehicle.  Just found the events of the day funny and thought i would share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am positive they are now putting up roadblocks and searching every car in GA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Saturday morning I needed to make my Home Depot run at a [5].  I live in rural GA so it's one stop down the interstate about 10 miles.

I bought some 16' lumber, loaded it in my truck and started back home.  I was feeling pretty happy and I always get a bit nervous when I am carrying lumber so I decided I would go on the back roads home rather than take the interstate.

As I came up to the main street stoplight in our little town I thought "man, it's busy today".  Cars were backed up at the light which is very unusual.  I finally got to the front and did a right-on-red when there was a break in the cars going through.

Wow.  I can't get over how busy it is today.  Well, hopefully this will thin out in a minute when we get out of downtown.

But as we get out of town nothing changes.  The road is very winding so I can only see 5 or 6 cars in front of me but the traffic is only moving at about 30 miles per hour.  What the hell?  Must be an accident or something up ahead.

This goes on for several miles until I finally get to a straightaway where I can see up ahead for a mile.  I see just a stead stream of slow moving cars and... what's this... a cop car is about six cars in front of me and he has his lights on.  Oh he must be pulling someone over or going to whatever accident is ahead.

The car line keeps moving.  Slowly.  Now the paranoia sets in.  That cop isn't jumping the line to get to an accident.  What is he doing?  It's almost like he's keeping us in line.  Oh my god!  There must be a roadblock ahead.  Oh shit!  Trump must have issued an executive order to stop all cars and search them!

Now I'm passing a farmer that was working on his fence.  He has stopped working and is watching the parade of cars heading into the greatest roadblock/drug search of all time!  You smug bastard!

Here it comes.  Around the next corner there are two more cop cars blocking the road with their lights on.  They are corralling all of the cars into... into... what?... the Baptist Church parking lot?  Why would they search us there?

Guys, I am so stupid.  It literally took me until I saw the cars directly in front of me get motioned around the cop cars that I realized I was in a frickin' funeral procession.

Holy shit that was an intense trip to Home Depot.

TL;DR - I joined a funeral procession without knowing it and spent 15 minutes thinking I was be herded into a police drug/alcohol search point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tears on the potty. Thanks a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man his traps are huge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A baby pelt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 40's no question.  So much going on with the family plus time just seems to continue to run faster the older you get.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  I'm a recovering Catholic too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this one!  

My parents are now in the late 80's and get very offended when I mention the racist things they said when I was younger and deny *ever* being racist.

"Look at all the porch monkeys" was one of my Dad's sayings that stuck with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, well, that is one family tradition that your children are probably happy they never were a part of.

Sorry to hear it happened to you but good for you putting it in your past! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What family tradition from your childhood did you not carry over to children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinner with the whole family around the kitchen table every evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a ginger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming the guy owns a chain of car washes? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When mirrored the left side of Tommy Lee Jones face looks like him but the right side... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm... Yeah I did.  I split the picture, cloned each side, mirrored it and merged it back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I mirrored both sides of Harrison Ford's face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanted to see the two emotions Harrison Ford was showing us. The result was a bit disturbing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you!  I want a baby trash panda but just haven't had the situation come up yet to adopt one.  We rescued and raised a baby skunk a couple years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, I see what he did there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times in one frickin' day can this be reposted??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one of the worst titles I've ever seen associated with this weekly repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that. But I did give you a great deal on the house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all seriousness it really didn't look hard.  Just messy.  Think of a giant can of Great Stuff spraying and expanding.  It looked like it took a little practice to know how much the expansion would go to not over apply it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I could help you friend.  I have done foam in my last two DIY builds but I had it done both times by a professional firm. 

After watching it twice now though I am not feeling as afraid of it from a DIY perspective so I intend to do it myself on the lake cabin I'm building.

If it's cool with you I'm going to tag you and follow up to see how your experience goes with it.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Turn off the breaker before working on it.

LOL.  Not that the rest of your comment is spot on but funny to see you add this at the bottom.  We've all been there. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always is quite random.  The comment or post that you think the least about tends to be the ones that surprise you.

That said it is a total joke.  There really is nothing interesting in the lounge other than other people trying to figure out what it means because they just got gilded.  A true reddit circlejerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a similar project this weekend.  Just use a masonry bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is funny but only for a brief moment in time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other thing that is hard, especially when posting on reddit with your DIY projects is that it doesn't take much ignorance or lack of detail for "experts" to jump in and tell you what you did wrong.

For instance, I have done extensive research on pouring concrete slabs as I have needed to do several now for an office/garage and horse barn.  

Everyone will tell you that you need to use rebar no matter what.  However I have found (and learned from the farmers around me that have been doing this for a looonnnngggg time) that if you get 5,000 DOT mix with fiber mixed in you don't need rebar.  I have now poured some very large pours like this and have not had one crack.  

It's a case were what was probably "standard practice" years ago or in one area of the country (northern with frost heave) dictates how certain people approach what they HAVE to do with a project.

So again, listen, learn, try.  Go with what you believe is the best approach.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just need to repeat that important warning - you are not going to find a consensus on just about anything so look for the important points and separate those from the "opinion" points and even then know there will always be people that disagree and deride you work (assuming you post your projects here).

Just use your head and have a thick skin.

EDIT:  ALSO don't be afraid to make mistakes.  They happen.  Learn from them and apply the learnings to your next project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice little guitar there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are welcome!

And here's the most IMPORTANT DIY tip I can give you.  If you don't know how to do something look on Youtube.  I can't tell you how many times a YT video has saved my skin.

Sure you might watch 5 videos and all will tell you something different but across the group you will get the jist of the main things you HAVE TO GET RIGHT and the "optional" things that everyone has a personal opinion on.

I rented an excavator a while back and succeeded at throwing a track.  Without Youtube I would have been done for the weekend.  But 5 minutes later I knew what I had to do - it just took me another hour to fix it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like mine Sunnyside up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  I hope to finish the office up in the next week or two and then I will post a photo album showing all of the mistakes and learnings of doing this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently finished the floor of my office which had originally been planned to be a garage and so the concrete pour was very rough finish.

I used self-leveling underlayment/concrete and after a few hit-or-miss learning tries I ended up with what looks a bit like marble.  Then I finished it with an epoxy sealer.

Very happy with the results.  I'll be posting a DIY project album on it soon but here's a quick pic: http://imgur.com/a/6zrZb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember.  Only stupid people pay taxes.  Some smart orange man told me that once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This!  Just like some of the biggest Hollywood blockbusters that have never turned a profit.  Accounting is an amazingly malleable thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may sound weird but Tarantulas are huge chick magnets.

I had a red-legged tarantula named Lilly when I was in college.  I would take her out on the quad and let her walk around and it was amazing how many girls would come up and ask to let her walk across their hands and stuff.

Ultimately, Lilly got freaked by a gust of wind on graduation day while I was carrying her in my hand and jumped.  She did not land "cat like"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open it up!  Maybe there's a golden ticket in it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You needed to specify "outie" not "innie" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't read the other comments so I am sure people will be saying "REBAR!!!" but my experience is that if you use fiber reinforced you should be fine IMO.

Two years ago I poured a workshop/office/garage (36x48) using DOT 5,000lb mix with fiber.  I have had no cracks or issues but to each his own.

EDIT: I'm in GA so no real freeze issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a lack of respect for both the office of The President as well as the current occupant.

But if it's someone they like, well then, of course it will be Mr. President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lothario Lizard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the high-maintenance to those fingernails you have your work cut out for you but Congrats and Best of Luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bird's eye view of a forest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This idea is best.  

Always go with the easiest solution first and if you don't like it then you can move on to more complicated or expensive solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely an old well that was backfilled that has collapsed in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that shit happens in transit but damn at least tell me who sent them to me instead of just a card that says "Merry Christmas" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outdoor cats that live in our horse barn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank Reddit.  It spun and didn't return.  When I it reload on the page it must have resubmitted.

Sorry you think it is stupid as fuck.  I guess my user submitted content isn't up to your standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No - just falling apart and beat to hell.  I removed the one in the bottom corner that was just a strawberry with no chocolate left on it before I thought to take a picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have five barn cats so I build them a 3-story "cat hotel" in my workshop so they could get up and away to feel safe at night (coyotes and whatnot) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of our cats fell off the top of the cat hotel and hit head first into the cat food bin. The piece that broke out is kinda shaped like her head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of our cats fell off the top of the cat hotel and hit head first into the cat food bin. The piece that broke out is kinda shaped like her head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone sent me these for Christmas. No name just a card that said "Merry Christmas". I wish I knew who to thank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cedar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over a $2,000 of Wagyu beef filets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a bunch of people start dancing in public for no apparent reason why can't someone join in?  

Douche would be trying to slam dance with the group or disrupt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you used Prime that'd be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donkey dreaming she's on the Olympic Equestrian Team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donkey dreaming she's on the equestrian team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My broke ass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a quality comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My broke ass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the first picture here I have to go with /u/austinsplumber - wax seal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is no one going to mention that damn pictures on the wall aren't straight?  It's driving me nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweetgum pretty sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice explanation.  I'll add to it from the tax perspective.

Sole proprietor files the taxes for the business via a Schedule C on their personal taxes.  The business can take deduct legitimate expenses and pay normal salary to the owner (taxed normally - i.e. W2 income).  Any profit of the business is subject to a roughly 15% self-employment tax and then taxed at normal rates on the owner's 1040.

LLC profits are dispersed to all members prorata via a K-1 statement at tax time.

Corps come in two flavors - C and S. S  also pays out profits on K-1 to shareholders.  C corp pays corporate taxes on any profits before dispersing via dividends to shareholders which are then taxed on the dividends.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hummer Bummer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, wish I had business in Maine next week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the music but nothing about that was "impromptu"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Squatted down.  Took deep breaths.  Then stood up and held my breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this position a new position or am I replacing someone who has left?

What is your voluntary turn-over rate?

What has been the company's financial performance over the past 3 years? (assuming it is a private company)

Is the company profitable?  If not, where does the company's funding come from?

Oh, and about 20 more.  

Remember - you should be interviewing them as much as they are interviewing you.  It shows you don't just want A JOB you want THE RIGHT JOB.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me find a GIF of the scene from Stripes when Hulka asks the guilty person to step forward and Murray starts to step forward but doesn't and Ramis does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention they were fantastic when there were just 4 of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept thinking - weird fish.  I've never seen one swim upside down like that.  Stupid me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney announces new live action remake of Pixar Cars! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may help: https://www.gentlemansgazette.com/scotch-whisky101-a-beginners/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One second away from a Darwin Award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be interesting sits back in recliner with popcorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Smart don't come out of books, kid. Smart is making the right decision at the right time. Like now. What's it gonna be, Matty? You gonna spend your life crying and rocking yourself to sleep at night? Or are you gonna dig deep and find out what it takes to reshuffle those cards life dealt you? Your call." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me way to long to realize that was a fishing lure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The short answer is "no" but the longer-answer is I'm still trying to figure it out.

I mean, I was a "forgainst" vote.  I don't really care for Hillary but I voted for her because Trump scares me.

I detest his ego.  His racism.  His misogyny.   His overall flippant and dangerous personality.

But then I've watched what he has done since becoming President-elect.  Almost every announcement I am initially in shock.  But then I think, you know what - maybe he is literally mentally unstable but he plays it with such hubris that people think he is a genius.  Not crazy but maybe crazy like a fox.

Now I'm starting to wonder just how bad could this be?  Maybe a total shitstorm is what American politics needs.  

Republicans for 8 years have predicted Obama's policies would be THE END OF THE WORLD.  Know what?  It hasn't happened.

Maybe the screaming about Trump will turn out to be the same.  Will he cause some damage?  Surely (Obama made some bone-headed mistakes in my opinion - all presidents do).  But will the world end?  Will America become a third world country?  No it will not.  

But maybe the shitshow will be sufficient to wake people up and scare some sense into the politicians. 

The first time the Republican congress goes against Trump and he starts tweeting shit about them the curtain will be dropped and the public will see all of the lies and machinations that are Washington.

Maybe this presidency is exactly what America needs to get up off its fat, crybaby ass and start acting like adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was walking in the forest trying out different photo filters. Really happy with this one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the transformative nature of it - Wolfenstein 3D.  There was nothing like it when it came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if they are buried they are by definition "winterized".

In this case I put in some above ground sprinklers in our vegetable garden this summer and when I was checking all the hose bibs and what not around the house before a hard freeze I totally forgot to turn off the water cutoff to those sprinklers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes you need to winterize PVC pipes even if you live in the South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes you need to winterize PVC pipes even if you live in the south. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now, I did not word that very eloquently so your point is well taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What I've always found amazing is that my P stinks almost immediately after eating it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vertical like that is most likely a result of settling.  

Since you aren't having any water issues I wouldn't worry too much about it at this point but you should always check with an expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I see the N*S*F*W* notice now.  Didn't realize NSFL tag would automatically mark that as NSFW.  I'll give it another try.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brought down by K-9 unit (NSFL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 14:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in GA.  Roughly same weather as SC.

I just finished my 500 sq ft stand-alone office using spray foam.  I also used spray foam two years ago in the master BR addition I built onto our main house.

While it was more expensive I am VERY pleased with the results.  When they are done there is not a pinhole where air gets in.

I installed a 14,000 BTU AC/Heat combo unit.  It hardly runs.  The room holds the heat or the cold pretty nicely.

My two cents would be it is worth it if you can afford the additional.

BTW - you can do this yourself.  I do most DIY myself but this one just seemed like something not worth the rental, mess, and learning curve for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help finding a set of panels of Cap throwing his shield hitting bad guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any Cap fans out there?  I could use your help.

I am building my home office and have one wall that will be a moving partition made up of four 4'x8' panels.

I am looking for a set of panels from an older (70's or before) Cap comic that contains 4 comic panels with the first being Cap throwing throwing his shield and the next three being the shield hitting bad guys - bouncing from one to the next.

I know I've seen panels like this many times over the years but short of going through every old Cap comic I have I was hoping someone here might be able to point to some issues where this was shown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be once a day but once we added the bidet now it's every other day or sometimes even every third day.

With the bidet and brushing your teeth the stinky parts are taken care of.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not sure that's what he wished for (wait for it) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Busy as a three-legged cat taking a shit on a linoleum floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that as "Where" and thought - damn reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like ALF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely on 1 and 3.  Pretty sure on 2.  No idea on 4 - I was thinking a little Quicksilver look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take me to the Everything's a Dollar store? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look you little shit.  Don't pin this on me. 

You are the one that just went down to the bank without our parents permission and got a cashiers check for all the money in our account and sent it off for that stupid "build your own computer" ad in the back of Popular Science!

So get ready.  When those boxes arrive Dad is going to be pissed!  Mom will just cry.  And you'll get grounded to our room but at least they will leave the boxes in there too.

So it's all your fault we grew up developing software, starting companies, growing them and selling them, and never truly growing up.  Fuck you for that!  Now I'm stuck a 52yo kid at heart with time and money on my hands.  Thanks you little, unathletic, nerdy, loser!

My one word of advice.  Give up on the D D character rolling program.  By the time the damn thing loads off the cassette tape and you run it you could have rolled up half a dozen good characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 14:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming you know which line is running from the GFCI to the garage, right?  If so, just bypass the GFCI for that line while you are rewiring it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 14:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said that in Scoobie Doo's voice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your little dude is cool.  

What is the biggest fish he has caught so far? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you destroy your dog's award OP?  That's just mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy those multiple accounts are hard to manage huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screen grab from the new Spiderman homecoming trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay.  Just trying to narrow down where you are on this.

So if someone is actively accepting money from the government they shouldn't be able to vote, correct?

You said "welfare".  I assume you mean just poverty related social programs like SNAP or WIC?  What about Medicaid?  How about Medicare?  That is used by retirees who are not contributing to the economy.  Should retirees be able to vote?  

Back to my suggestion.  If you really want to only reward certain citizens with right to vote (setting aside the Constitutional issues that raises) shouldn't you reward those that are contributing the most by letting them have the most votes?  Why should the hamburger flipping "socialist" get as many votes as I do.  I'm a "job creator".  I make a lot of money.  I should get a bigger say in things.

If you think I am being sarcastic, you are right.  If you simply follow this logic to its conclusion the dreaded 1% (of which I am part) will control all aspects of society and will determine how you lowly peasants of the 99% live.

Be careful when you start alienating groups that you look down on because there will always be a different group looking down on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is in your opinion every citizen should not have a full vote, correct?  

So what do you think would be fair? Maybe one vote for each dollar in taxes that a person pays?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  I hate feeling out almost as much as I hate making a typo in a comment.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was building a scale model of the hobbit house I am building and got a surprise visit from Jack Skellington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even when I am just drawing out where the bed is going to go when I finish building the house he thinks he knows where he belongs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blows my mind when a big duelie truck passes me on the interstate with their dog just hanging out in the bed of the truck.

Every time I see a dead dog on the highway I assume it feel out of one of these trucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five bucks?!?  Are you shitting me?

My hat off to you servers.  I wouldn't survive one shift without throttling some asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't.  

I agree with you that both candidates knew the rules of the game as it is currently played and someone won fair and square.  I have no issues with that.

I just think that everything else in America has evolved over 240 years.  Our laws are always changing to reflect the reality of our changing world.  Why should this be sacrosanct?

I appreciate that Clinton has refrained from being a sore loser.  I appreciate that she quickly conceded and has fought the prodding of others to open up a can of worms this country doesn't need.

That said, we have had popular vote winners lose two of the last four elections.  It just seems like the right time to have a reasoned intelligent discussion of what options could exist to make our voting system the best it can be.

The problem is we are past the point of rational, friendly discussion - which in my opinion is the first step to seeing America fall from its perch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  But how about proportionally allocating electoral votes at the state level?

I live in GA.  Clinton got 46% of the vote but because the electoral votes are "winner-take-all" my vote, along with the votes of 46% of the citizens of GA mean nothing.

States shouldn't be "Blue" or "Red".  They should all be different shades of Purple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently in your eyes it is "ignorant" to question an antiquated system that seems to ignore the will of the people and simply asking about the legality of bringing a lawsuit to allow the judiciary to review the situation going forward somehow makes me ignorant?  Okay, whatever.  

Trump has his victory and unlike the people that are/were Obama-haters that couldn't "come together" to support the legitimate winner of two terms I will support our president because that's what we are supposed to do as Americans.

Look - I'm 52, white and wealthy.  It makes no difference in my small life whether the country is run by righties or lefties (I'm an independent).  But it does matter to me that all citizens have their votes count.

If we want to keep the electoral college great.  But at least allocate the electors proportionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they would.  And at this point with state "winner-take-all" electoral votes there is no point in voting if you live in a state that is heavily red or heavily blue.  

The current system is unfair to *all* voters it just depends on the outcome of a specific election as to who is disenfranchised at that time.

If every vote counts maybe people would feel more engaged.  I know several people that didn't vote because "it won't matter - I live in GA".

I've always fought this mindset but when 2.6 million more people vote for a candidate and they still lose something is horribly wrong with the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  I was totally unaware that over 3 million illegal aliens voted.  Just wow.

Of course I'm sure you can provide a link to a *reputable* mainstream news source to confirm this right?  Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "winner" of the Presidential Election lost by over 2,600,000 votes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if it would be possible but could Clinton, DNC, or even named voters - file litigation to challenge the validity of the electoral college but do so in a way that does not challenge the *current* election results?

My thinking is this - removing first the specter of voter fraud via the recounts - the issue could be narrowed to a real and present issue that will continue to affect our country's elections.  However, if the attempt was to overturn/challenge the current election that would be too divisive to the country.  (I can't believe I am saying this - I hate Trump!)

But could a lawsuit be brought simply to deal with the longer-term issue while accepting the injustice of the current situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having separate interests in addition to things you enjoy doing together.

"Me" time is important to both people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got that reference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.  Cooter Brown. 

I've really learned that he is, like, 1000% better engineer than I am but he's little so whenever I can help out a little - clear out an area and put in an earthen dam to get him started - he'll take it from there and create a masterpiece.   :)

For clarity - Cooter is a wild beaver.  He just lives on my property and we have developed a respectful relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I totally love my comfy chair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lack of coffee is...disturbing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the way I have the superstructure laid out now it looks like this: http://imgur.com/a/4Os0Y

I am looking for an "A frame front that is providing the major support to the main centerline beam.  Then the two "rib" beams coming in from each side will fit into the 90 degree pocket created where the centerline beam meets the A frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh after seeing this reply I realize the comment was asking about "roof water".

As I clarified in another comment this isn't really a traditional "hobbit house" - i.e. it will not be earthen on the top.  It will actually be solar panels on the south facing side and off grid.

My wife started calling it "the hobbit house" and it stuck.  I prefer "the beaver lodge" because I am building it on a hill overlooking a small pond I have been building with my beaver.  He does most of the work but I help him out sometimes with some clearing and a few strategically placed berms.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water service?  I have already run water from one of my wells about 600 feet away (as well as 100 amp service - although this well be all solar with a Powerwall once I am done with construction and the grid will just be backup).

If you meant water as in moisture I am using a french drain around the foundation and it is on the top of hill so I don't foresee any ground water issues.

In this picture you can see the electric and water on the left side.  Right side you see the septic outflow (I still need to dig and put in the leaching field)  http://imgur.com/a/ZbMz3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  You. have. no. idea.

If it wasn't raining Sunday when I did this I was honestly planning on finding 2" saplings to do it in wood. 

I hate that I used PVC but it is serving the purpose to get length and angles for the beams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome.  I hesitate to call what I'm building "a hobbit house" but that was what my wife started calling and it stuck.

It is really more of a "lodge with a hobbit door".  

It overlooks a pond I have been building with my beaver so I have taken to calling it "The Beaver Lodge".  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure... if you don't laugh.  http://imgur.com/a/ZbMz3

I did the rough excavation using my bobcat until I hit granite then rented an excavator to get through that.  Flying the drone to get pics I can see where I am several feet out of round on the left side but next step is to find the exact center and mark out the 32' circle.  I am generally already over that size so other than a little clean up once I pour the foundation it will mostly be backfill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am excavated down 8' at the top of the hill (back of the hobbit house).  At the front the slope of the hill brings that down to 4'.

The walls will all be poured concrete.  I am toying with lining the forms with tree bark to give the walls some texture.  If I don't like that I'll have to come up with a better interior finish.

Current plan is:

-Pour the floor in the round with all plumbing embedded in the floor (I have already dug for the septic outflow)
- embed vertical rebar around the perimeter during the pour
- Form the walls in 4' sections and pour them one at a time using rebar to connect/reinforce each section to the next.  I intend to include 2' conduit in the walls to allow for running of the electric in wall.
- Using pine from my property I will harvest 2' diameter logs varying from 25' to 45'.  Stripped of bark.
- Pour "block" post anchors 1 cubic yard
- Custom welded "anchor brackets" embedded in each block
- Calculate angles.  Recalculate angles.  Once again for good measure.

I am still not sure on how I want to connect the beams.  I was thinking mortis and tenon but I just don't see that working given there are 7 large beams coming together at one spot.  I think I am going to have to come up with a custom bracket to fit them in.  We'll see as we get closer. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure.  Works on mine.

Her issue was that I took it a little too far.

After I did the excavation I used a drone to take aerial photos.  Then I took physical measurements including topography so I would have the slope of the hill to include in my ciphering.

I put together the superstructure with PVC to get a feel for the skeleton and get lengths for the logs and angles for the joints.  But of course I was having fun so had to go ahead and the interior touches to get a visual.

Although the model is rough I am very pleased because it has finally taken a design that was stuck in my head and made it concrete so now I can think through were maybe I should adjust the design a bit more.

BTW - this is 1/12 scale.  32' diameter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm building a "hobbit house". I've completed the excavation but I needed a scale model to start to visualize the superstructure. My wife says I'm weird. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm building a "hobbit house" and needed a scale model to start to visualize it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Paul McCartney album drops just in time for the holidays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Industrial pond dye.  Shit was in every crack and crevasse for way too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 20:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to spellcheck the TOC: Investements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That man does not understand physics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Veer *out of the path*.  Don't try to outrun it for godsakes.

Man I hope I can remember to dodge if the time ever comes I need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The morning was still but the children awoke restless. "Can we please go outside today? Please daddy!" Three little faces, young and excited to see the world and all of its wonders.

"Kids, I wish you could go out and play like you used to but for the time being that's not really something we can do" I replied, with my most knowing fatherly grin. "Soon" I confidently added knowing in my heart how much I hate lying to them.

It's been a long four years since "The Revolution" that swept President Trump into power. Amazing in hindsight that none of us saw it coming. Of course until it was too late. We're a republic. The greatest of the great. The world's only true super power. Surely the checks and balances of our great constitution will ensure that no one man can destroy what our fore fathers built.

But Trump tapped into something inside of us that most didn't even know was there. A primal hatred. A pent-up anger against anything and everything "different". We watched the world shift, evolve, and grow for 50 plus years. Never once did we see that our old prejudices weren't fading away. They were just moving deeper into our core - away from view. Away from any ability to understand and address the root of those frustrations. Until it was too late.
Trump swept into power on what initially felt like a minority point of view. But once in office the depth of our country's hatred rapidly boiled to the surface.

At first the changes seemed ugly but manageable - a banning of Muslims from entering our country, a growing Police State to "secure and protect" us all from the ongoing random acts of terror that were plaguing the country.

Oh, and the wall. Don't get me started on the wall. What was the final bill, $4 trillion? And by god, he sure did get Mexico to pay for it. Amazing what fear does to people. Trump was right in the end. With unhinged threats and a finger on the nuclear "option" people tend to fall in line.

My daughter's nuzzling under my chin brings me back to the present. Her eyes pleading with me once more - "Please Daddy?? We just want to go outside and play!"

But this day would be just like so many before. All of us stuck here in this small hidden room. Quiet. Waiting. Worrying if - when - we may be found out. Hiding in our own country for fear that our "differences" were just too much for a citizenry bent on ensuring conformity to "their norm". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My son and I were there too](http://imgur.com/a/Ty4lk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MRW my wife says its Nookie Night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 03:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good eyes!  Yes that's the classic version. We've also played annual family tournaments with the modern (soldier, cannon, horse), and my favorite, Lord of The Rings Risk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a sports fan but I really enjoyed wearing this sweatshirt around my rural GA town last year. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go Panthers! (EIU).  

My wife went to Clemson.  I just stole her sweatshirt. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess that's better than last pic I was in where everyone called me Blackfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
