<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5987</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sickening? That would be cool as fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calories in just the stuffing and vegetables in frozen TV dinner with turkey   mashed potatoes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat [these Marie Calendar's TV dinners](http://www.mariecallendersmeals.com/frozen-dinners/roasted-turkey-breast-stuffing) somewhat frequently (don't judge) but I never eat the stuffing or the vegetables. There's 290 calories in the whole meal but I have no idea how many calories are in just the stuffing   veggies alone that I can subtract from my total lol. The turkey (with gravy), mashed potatoes, and stuffing are proportioned pretty equally. I usually subtract about 50 calories to be on the safe side but if I can subtract more that would be great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the intent of the rather misleading title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Important to note for stupid people: despite the name "national socialism" had nothing to do with socialism and was ideologically pretty much the opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *cough* nationalism in general *cough* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one dude who's smiling... Ugh that is so fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure to do [this one!](https://i.redd.it/led4eeq1s0py.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao who pissed in your clam chowder? Also you go from being from NH to being from NYC? Bad trolling is bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I grew up outside 128, that's definitely not true. The outer suburbs are generally the nicer richer ones with a few exceptions like Brockton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost all of them are in Latin America, and a couple are in South Africa and the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And gun laws... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicagoans drive wicked slow and way too fucking carefully. My uncle is from Chicago and drives at about 10 MPH and literally stopped at every crossroads in the middle of nowhere with no one around for miles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: some birds have developed wiggly windy cloacas due to bird rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you can make it in different ways, but all of the bleu cheese dressing I've seen in stores and at restaurants has had egg in it. Sometimes the ingredients in homemade vs store bought/restaurant food are different too. For example I'm always allergic to homemade cookies but there are certain store bought kinds I'm not allergic to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's oddly specific. Do you know OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't flaunt them and carry them around in public in inappropriate places like certain southern and western states though. They're just very rural states and use them for hunting. Vermont actually has by far the most people living in rural areas of any state and NH is pretty up there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Hampshire. Vermont is the hippie state with cows and ice cream and Bernie Sanders. New Hampshire is full of back-woods hicks and Massachusetts' rejects.

I once entered a Walmart in Manchester NH and saw what looked like a 12 year old with a full beard pushing around his drunk father in a shopping cart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That always seems to be the case. My friend's dad was very religious and homophobic, he turned out to be cheating on his wife with a transwoman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots are Russian trolls, this is well documented. Of course a good amount are just brainwashed too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's egg in bleu cheese dressing. It has mayonnaise in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf that was also true in Massachusetts up until recently. Everyone used to go to New Hampshire to buy alcohol on Sundays. Now it's just for *cheap* booze, fireworks, and tax-free shopping. They're going to have to go to Massachusetts if they want to buy weed pretty soon though so it all balances out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when a bunch of states and cities banned official travel to North Carolina over their bathroom bill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Thanksgiving was largely unknown outside of New England until after 1846. When it first spread to the rest of the US, all the other states celebrated it in different months, ranging from October to January. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably am. I'm also a recovering anorexic and have an anxiety disorder so it's hard to know exactly what is causing what at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ha ha, of course The Gay does not exist in Glorious Motherland, is symptom of western degeneracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the line of thinking unfortunately. People who've managed to change something are always the harshest towards people who haven't, since they think "if I can do it anyone can" and because they want to distance themselves from it since they're afraid of becoming that way again. It's the same with rich people who look down on poor people. When I was anorexic I used to frequent fatpeoplehate since I wanted to distance myself from that as much as possible so that I wouldn't gain weight. In my opinion, it's nothing but a symptom of people's own insecurities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have social anxiety disorder. It got worse when I developed anorexia and isolated myself for a long time as a result. I've had issues with drug addiction to cope with my social anxiety that probably made it even worse in the long run. It's going to be a long and tough road for me to get anywhere close to normal, if I ever do. 

It's a huge downer to explain all my issues to people nor do they probably want to hear about it, plus they'll just think I'm weird (I am but I'd rather people didn't know that) so I just say I'm introverted and call it a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always used sour cream since I'm allergic to egg and thus pretty much every other option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on the proper dipping condiment for buffalo wings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always used sour cream since I'm allergic to eggs and thus both blue cheese and ranch. Would recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do wild turkeys always seem to be roaming around outside just before Thanksgiving? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think they knew they were in danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I was a normal person. But if you're not very talkative you get people asking what's wrong with you and calling you shy all the time even if you aren't. People just assume you're oversensitive and weak, so saying you're introverted is a way of saying "I'm not weak and I don't give a shit what you think about me" while explaining your lack of talkativeness. At least it is to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Poppy - My Kind of Woman (Mac Demarco cover) [psychedelic/ indie rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asktrumpsupporters is about as useful as asking North Koreans about their undying love for Kim Jong Un. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree, as would most people on both sides of the gun debate. The goal is to prevent people who would use guns to harm others from getting a hold of them, not to keep guns away from everyone. Unfortunately we aren't doing that successfully right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it can but I'd imagine it depends on the person. I was having random muscle spasms a lot for about a year and weed just made it worse and made me focus on it more. But I also have an anxiety disorder and I'm a very internally focused person, so weed just amplifies that for me I guess. The muscle spasms were likely caused by the anxiety disorder in the first place though so not from anything like cerebral palsy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. And I spent about 10 whole minutes trying to post this video under a title like "Hillary Clinton eats babies while praising Satan" but it got removed for being political :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Literally just a video of a man staring at a tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here it is.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit really loves this kind of stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Borneo rainforest is 140 million years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly I'm kind of like whatever you do you, they were obviously both using each other. But trying to screw his family out of the money is pretty shitty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She mostly looks so different because her makeup style in 1930 vs in the 50s was vastly different, and she wore a lot of makeup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoking a hookah, 1921 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old are you and how old do people generally think you are? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guns aren't, but some people are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but it's the South, let's not act like its a beacon of tolerance nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are my favorite Redditor ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The April Fools blizzard happened just before I was born. My mom had a bunch of stories about trekking through snow while 7 months pregnant with twins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couple, 1920s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Weasels Ripped My Flesh", 1956 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/rdbyJJX8NbSBW/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let not caring distract you from the fact that Atlanta blew a 28-3 lead against New England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what the point of having Rickon in the series at all was. I basically forgot about him until he died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET HYPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more like "at least he wasn't an actual joke". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He used to be the White House Easter Bunny. No joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something really funny is that the term "concern troll" was popularized in online HAES communities (health at every size, basically obese people who are convinced they're healthy and don't need to change). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he knew it would pass no matter how he voted and he's trying to get Libertarian cred. Rand Paul is just a typical conservative republican, but he rides off of the popularity his father had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet they all do. Or at the very least don't care enough to do anything about it (since he's a Republican and Republicans can do no wrong). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Shouty Spice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lillian Gish, Cecil Beaton, photography, 1929 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lillian Gish, 1929 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glass Tears, Man Ray, photography, 1932 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to AIDS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that kind of pisser, that would be New York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wicked pissah kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What city outside the US is most like Boston? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I totally agree that New England is the best but I'm also a cynical fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birds have something called a cloaca which they shit, piss, and have sex through. It's really windy and weirdly shaped because of bird rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are garbage confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in like Toronto would probably be New York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They already have a ton of salt and seasonings in them so it doesn't make any sense to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Canadian cities were US cities which city would each be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spooky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you high on bro? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am never leaving New England again, it is the best place in America by far.

I'm sure this will prove highly controversial on r/Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your "type"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Godfather and Jaws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine not very highly since they'll lose their jobs to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how that works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It was 3-28 yesterday.](http://i.imgur.com/TpsT933.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do to not let yourself be distracted from the fact that the Atlanta Falcons blew a 3-28 lead against the New England Patriots in the Superbowl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just have trouble distinguishing people you don't know well. Also humans all are 99.9% related, because of a population bottleneck where only a few thousand survived, who we're all descended from. So you're not totally wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's Texas, they're obsessed with high school/ college football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They definitely seem to follow each other in crazy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it should be Canada and New Zealand. NZ is the Canada of Australia (overshadowed by their larger sibling), so they can relate to each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boston, I just have manners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One where you fly, they're called flyover states for a reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like [these types of collars](https://dtpmhvbsmffsz.cloudfront.net/posts/2015/05/10/554ffac0fbf6f94990009ff0/m_554ffac0fbf6f94990009ff1.jpg) tend to make people look old even if they aren't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of clothing tends to make people look older or younger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started out as Soviet propaganda tactics, Putin is somewhat trying to recreate the soviet days and uses the same tactics. Trump started doing it later. Others follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By searching ridiculous shit to fuck with them. Also I own a phone and a Samsung Smart TV, I'm screwed either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite rapey ogre? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When people say this I just give them my best serial-killer smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can all the time cause I don't need glasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to AIDS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The South probably would have had slavery a lot longer. Gay marriage would definitely not be legal there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the server. Sometimes they'll shout at the person, sometimes they'll just be silently pissed off, sometimes they'll assume they forgot. Generally they'll give you shit service if you ever come back though, and I'd be afraid of them spitting in my food or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a euphemism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tipping at restaurants is necessary like it or not (unless the service was extraordinarily shitty), and leaving a really meager tip is often seen as more insulting than not leaving one at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in school very recently that was just the adults making a big deal out of it, the kids didn't give a shit and thought it was stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often they say "I hate this generation" because they think they're different/ special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a normal day in San Francisco? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just a boring person who knows some interesting people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your aesthetic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your aesthetic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda get the appeal, it makes each party feel more masculine/ feminine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I just don't care really and didn't grow up in a religious household. It isn't relevant to my life in any way. It's nice to imagine that there's something more out there, but I don't waste time thinking about specifics nor do I really believe in anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agnostic, it's the only one that *is* right for absolute sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homework. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not so well probably, I'm 5'2 and 100 lbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immigrating doesn't mean you hate your native country or are "abandoning" it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's a kind of shitty but catchy song and it was used in Shrek. Shrek memes started being a thing and then people just associated it with rapey ogres which is prime internet comedy fuel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it's the wrong decade though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats 2007-2008. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think those rubber band things were popular in 2009. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skinny jeans, thick eyebrows, contouring, ombre hair if they're a girl or an undercut or man-bun and possibly facial hair if they're a guy, chokers, maybe that Kim Kardashian-knock-off look that so many people do, etc etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, they're the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm wrong and my mind could be changed in the future if things change, but I've never heard of a transracial person in my life nor have I heard one argue as to why they should be recognized as a group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gen Z until we come up with a better name. Same as how Millennials were called Gen Y until that was thought of.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
