<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 07:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** **NSFL** 

I was not prepared for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan Tudyk is todays Kevin Bacon.

He's a fantastic actor that doesn't get anywhere near as much praise for his work.

I can also recommend his own initially crowd funded show (I think it got picked up after its first season) 'Con Man' which is kinda like a self reference sitcom where he basically plays himself as an actor in a SciFi show who goes around different conventions. Nathan Fillion is also in it (and is equally amazing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 08:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I really want it to be like mechwarrior 2 and MW2:Mercenaries where it was very sim focused. 

I didn't like the sound of prebuilt mech variants though with no customisation though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any character voiced by Alan Tudyk deserves extra screen time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shiny is an amazing song, I just wish that Lin had sung it instead of Jermaine:

https://youtu.be/DnOUgFjs9sg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True Romance. 

He didn't direct it, but he wrote it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't need to be a big ass to be a nice ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curse your sudden but inevitable betrayal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does make her looks less feminine though and that doesn't mean she can't still be a strong female lead.

While this next bit isn't necessarily directed at you, I hate that people skate around this pseudo feminist bullshit, and the divide between your upvotes and /u/enjoytheloss2 's downvotes portray this well.

People can use words to be descriptive without being derogatory. It's very easy to guess that it is a male playing the guitar in the trailer prior to seeing Ellies face, and then you can see the feminine features of her face.

In a literal sense, she had a ponytail in the first game which is a hairstyle predominantly worn by females, the long flowing effect of a ponytail is feminine in that of itself anyway. Having far shorter hair is most definitely *less* feminine, it just doesn't make it masculine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 09:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In light of you comment, with all the international war and peace keeping initiatives etc, the only thing that governments should be pooling their resources into should be healthcare and medical research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so, *Fetal* *Gear* huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as it's funded by Sony it's in all likelihood going to be PlayStation exclusive. 

Probably PlayStation 5 mind you, but exclusive nevertheless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think OP just used the term loosely as some Fry look different to their adult forms just like insect larva. It may or may not be the correct word, but most people reading it will know exactly what OP meant. Maybe 'juvenile' would have been more appropriate?

Also, it's pretty cool how you can plainly see the head of this matches the head of your typical moray (although i'm not sure if that is indeed the species in the image).

Edit: I'm wrong guys, I get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I want from housing is for it to be worth while visiting friends houses, and your own of course, without removing the need to visit existing towns.

Putting things like crafting tables in player houses will severely reduce player footfall through towns etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 10:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I understood it was that the main series of films were going to be your stereotypical Star Wars films, and the stands alone ones were the films that they would experiment with. 

I'm down with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 10:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok, so I wasted a skill point then haha :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 08:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also like to know if abilities you morph into stamina  consuming abilities still get their damage based from their original magicka stat? Or does that change once you morph that ability? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 08:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I have the exact opposite opinion, save for the one scene where K2S0 throws the grenade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just reminded me of this song, and now I have to go see my mother and i'll be humming and singing it the whole way :P

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1fumeHDUk34 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anything at all I can do for terrible baby acne?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey /r/daddit

I've already been to a Doctor who has said for me to just wait it out, but my three week old son has terrible baby acne. Even googling images I can't find another image of a kid who has it as bad as he does.

Does anyone here have any experience with dealing with it? The pustules are now popping when he rubs his face and i'm scared he's going to get a nasty infection from it.

Heres an image:

http://imgur.com/GVPhcco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are on the same shard, so yeah I'm not going to be competitive :P

Just how much money are these guys spending? :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comparing it to No Mans Sky? Hell even Ataris ET game is better than that and that one was so bad they literally buried all the thousands unsold copies

As long as FFXV is good enough and more open than FFXIII, I'll be happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 08:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok, last time I played was like 2 months after release so a little while ago :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 04:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any reason why my skill list under Restoring Light is different to his? Aside from Healing Ritual the other skills are completely different in the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berics resurrection shows that there is hope for those who died. Imagine how Deus ex machina another resurrection of a main character would be without that being established first. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're floof is amazing!!!

Quick question, but do you find having a pet fox that they still have that smell? Wild foxes smell pretty strong but I'm interested if domesticated ones still have that odour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 10:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First death to gain immortality?

Sounds like a decent payoff to me :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA just photographed an object moving past our Sun, and it looks remarkably like a certain Sphere... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 09:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 08:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a similar issue, is like to not have to start over from scratch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a word derived from the mmo Ultima Online. In that game the in canon reason for servers was that the world was shattered into lots of mirror images of itself, each one self contained and individual.

It's kinda a slang term for servers now, so basically in SW:GoH it means the batch of players you are assigned to, so when you look at the leaderboards, number 1 isn't first place in the world, just on your server. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's pretty appropriate here haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the tickets and go see him. 

I know how horrible this is going to sound but at his age he probably isn't going to do something like this again. 

David Attenborough I honestly think is one of the most loved people when it comes to the natural world alive today, akin to say Elvis to music. 

Don't miss this opportunity to see him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 09:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read in another thread that Halle confirmed it, but whole knows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 09:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anybody actually gone the entire way and watched a whole porn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 09:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, I didn't ask a question :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understand this, comparing overwatch to battleborn is like comparing Super Mario Bros to Metroid. 

Yeah both games are first person, and both games have a decent cast of playable characters with individual skills, but that's about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 12:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to get all P.C. about it, but isn't that kinda sexist?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I'd love this, I wouldn't want to see it without John Candy :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you say, having synchronised progress across platforms would be pretty nice. After playing Gears and Titanfall 2, I really want to play on PC but not be penalised when the player base drops. 

For instance, I've literally never been able to play any core mode in GoW4 aside from Team Deathmatch, there just isn't he playerbase on PC. I could then PvE on PC, and then dig out my controller and play competitively on Xbox. 

I would LOVE to be able to do that with Destiny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping its intentional that she sounds a little like a naive little girl, and that the main reason shes there is to contact her dad, only becoming a badass (or dead ass -vader) at the end of the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humble bundle has an incredible deal including thebAnSong of Ice and Fire role playing book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know that saying that is like blasphemy on reddit don't you..:P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 13:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Chanel or Dior is a high end brand peasant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 11:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who I played vanilla WoW with. 

In our first year, I racked up 56 days played. He did 216. Practically two thirds of physical time that year was spent by him at his computer playing wow. 

Edit: I miss those days :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then people who preloaded saw the install size and freaked out, and it went waaaaaay downhill after that. 

What annoys me is that NMS isn't a terrible game, if the lies hadn't been told to make it out to be something it isn't, I can guarantee more people would have enjoyed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In November and a week or so either side:

- Gears of War 4
- Battlefield 1
- Call of Duty: Infinite Warfare
- PSVR
- PS4 Pro
- Pokmon Sun and Moon
- Final Fantasy XV
- World of Final Fantasy
- Dishonoured 2
- Skyrim Special Edition
- Watch Dogs 2
- The Last Guardian

To be honest I would have hoped they push TF2 back to January or even February just due to product saturation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 13:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I always saw Batou as more of a Dolph Lundgren kinda person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as we have so much customisation with pilots, I'm a little gutted that we are stuck with various presets for the titans. 

It'd be a really nice touch to be able to completely modify our titans (mix chassis with limbs from different sets etc, OS looks and voices) and then take that titan also into the single player campaign. 

I can see why that wouldn't work in Tf2 but that'd be a really nice touch for TF3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember going into Sainsbury's on launch day for MW2.

There were 9 people in the queue holding copies of the game , including me. The other 8 were women between 40 and 55 years old with three women debating if they're sons would benefit more by spending the fifty pounds on something other that a 'stupid computer game'.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 15:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, in the crowded crop of October/November games, this is the one that has been most worth my 50. 

Also, there is no season pass with it, and all maps etc will be free updates for everyone. I just hope enough people buy it to show EA they can make a few quid without shilling all their customers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like comparing a newborns bottom and a sheet of industrial sandpaper now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tribes: Ascend wasn't bad.

I've not played it for a couple of years or so, so i'm not sure if its still any good, but yeah skiing and firing your spinfusor at folks miles away was lots of fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the best birthday card message is:

Congratulations it's your birthday,
It's time for lots of fun. 

So roll this card up nice and tight,
And stick it up your bum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's why you should not be able to change what weapons a class of titan has. You can see what weapons it's carrying, irrespective of the shape of the actual robot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Locked preset builds I agree with, but I do feel that we should be able to fully customise aesthetically those titans. 

I.E: So, you have 3 titan classes, with each class having 3 models, and  each model with 3-4 preset loadouts. So you had *some* customisation where you had a choice of weaponry for that class of titan (you can't put a heavy rail gun on a light titan for instance), but you could then aesthetically unlock lots of heads arms legs and bodies for each class of titan, and colours and decals effectively giving you a set bunch of loadouts but lots of customisation for the player to identify themselves. 

They took a step in the right direction here, I just don't think they *quite* went far enough. It does give me high hopes for TF3 though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 12:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump sat alone in a boggy marsh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the UK, at 10:30pm this eve there are 276 player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game will have more legs in terms of long term numbers due to the lack of paid dlc alone. 

I really REALLY hope this model comes back into the fore. Fuck paying 90 for a game to get all the extras, or the usual retail price for a game stripped of its core features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I started watching his stuff a few years back after buying Destiny.

I watched his review, disagreed with it in parts (I really enjoy Destiny and still play it pretty regularly now) but laughed a lot regarding it although I could see the sense in his arguments about the game.

As you say, he may fuck about a lot but he is usually pretty on the money with his reviews. It's just a shame he is so busy now he can't put out the content that folks want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His recommendation is heavily weighted on encouraging the no season's pass policy Titanfall 2 took, which I'd agree with. 

This needs to be advertised more. I've been on the fence regarding this, Battlefield 1, GoW4 and COD.

That single thing made my mind up after seeing Joe's review. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While these guys are bro's *technically* they aren't spiders. They are arachnids for sure, but IIRC they are called Olipoids or something like that which are classed as a separate family due to their lack of body segments.

EDIT: Opiliones is the family tree that they belong to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's quite ok legally to *allude* to a problem with a company. It the moment an actual accusation goes public he could be sued for defamation / libel and lost business. 

By being vague and not stating what is exactly wrong, he doesn't give them anything concrete to sue *him* for.

 I played the first level of Phoenix Wright Ace Attorney once. I know what I'm talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha you made me laugh out loud!

Not enough to give you gold, but pretty close  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be frank, until MMO's comeback to focusing on the social experience I can't see any of them, Star Wars or not doing very well. 

For so long there has been a massive focus on solo content (lots of people keep calling this casual, there is a difference), that what's made mmos of yore great has been stripped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.imgur.com/gallery/qCsLjxj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 09:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn that Midgar Zolom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they fix the destruction tree?? It still seems prett poor imho. 

Started this play through as a destro Mage and I'm really struggling to kill anything more than one mob before I'm oom and then have to resort to a one handed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 09:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly,

I think the wait is because he is worried about what the internet will do. It doesn't matter how perfect the book is, there will be haters and if past form is to be used as a yard stick, they effect GRRM greatly. 

I think he is pulling a Valve software and is on damage limitation. The rage will be far less when not giving people the product in the first place, than it would be putting out a book that a small but very vocal minority hates. I can understand that too. The guy jus let wants to Netflix and chill, play with his action figures and retire, and after the lengthy career he's led, I can understand that. 

People rag on the show, but come on. It's *amazing* and will give people the ending that they have been waiting two decades for in under the next two years. He knows TV better than literature, he trusts D D with his apparent magnum opus, he has an escape route with Game of Thrones. It's the biggest TV show since Dallas, or well, ever. I think he's content knowing that his work gave birth to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 09:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preordering physical editions with limited edition gear is pretty much the only time I can say preordering is ok, if you really want those physical bonuses. A pipboy? Cool. A life size lancer? Sweet. 

Preordering an unlimited production digital edition that you can download exactly the same was on release day without fear of it sellling out? Yeah that's what is completely stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyui works? I didn't think it would, I'll have to download it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played through the original 3x with that as my primary build.

Now with Special Edition, i'm trying a mage which is fun, but annoying in equal measure (god damn menus), but every now and then I really miss my bow :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do not try and sugar coat it

I see what she did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great actor, but I'm not feeling him as Drake. My first thought was how he just feels too young. 

Still, after heath ledger as the joker, and batfleck I'll reserve judgement till I see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading or hearing in an interview somewhere that EA specifically asked that Battlefront be a game that 8 year olds can play.

That statement literally sums up all the issues that I have with the game, which is a shame because with some balancing and some tuning to the movement and customisation, we could have had an amazing game instead of a pretty good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think he might be gunning (literally) for revenge at how sudden his movie death was.

Wash didn't die, they just faked his death so Zoe didn't cut his balls off. He wanted a divorce see, but he was so scared of his warrior woman wife that they had to collude and fake his and book's death so he could run off and marry one of those nice women from Jaynestown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Source 17 the way things are going </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I was going to be bitchy about how no life you must be, but honestly...

I'm jealous :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   they completely ignore some parts of gameplay, doing tweaks there only few times a year.

Yeah, you'd think they'd have a small but dedicated team handling that kind of content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uber is ruined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 12:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I feel that having griefers in an open world game like this is part of the fun. You're going to find some dicks out there in the wild who just want to watch your cobra burn.  While it's *incredibly* frustrating when it keeps happening (and to be fair your example was one of the most dick moves I've seen by any griefer), I do feel in moderation it enhances the sim experience. 

The problem is that there isn't any real way to properly balance those encounters. If you make it so people get punished for attacking unarmed ships, traders and shippers wouldn't have anything to worry about. There is no perfect system for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 12:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just use Sean Murray as an adjective?

I'm glad he will know that he has caused the 'Munsening' of himself by spouting so many lies (and my god I need to go back and watch Kingpin again now!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this too as a Nord on my first playthrough. I recommend taking Alchemy, you're going to need those health potions :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 08:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, he doesn't look fat. 

He looks like a power lifter. +1 to Disney for portraying the character as a more realistic depiction of a strong man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss ET. There really hasn't been anything like it since. The Clanbase EU ladder scene was great as well, IIRC my clan was ranked 2nd in Europe at one point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Serious Replies Only Please] 

We didn't find out what it was, but we found it was there, and that was that she suffered from vaginismus, vulvodynia, and vulvar vestibulitis.

I'll let you google those, but if you ever experience pain, or clamping down there preventing sex, get it looked into asap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the number 1 reason for this is because 20 wave and 50 wave bounties both pay out the same amount of xp.

You could complete wave 20 three times easily before you complete wave 50 with randoms. That is the real problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lockers are actually pretty useful once you have your first turret or two.

By this time the fab should be about level 2 at which point you can store two weapons in them and two fully loaded heavy weapons (love those TriShots) are good burst DPS on the boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] How to carve a pumpkin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 13:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 10:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imho he best country town bonfire night is Brockham bonfire. Its a little further (near Dorking) but if you want that little England vibe it's great. 

If you have kids (or are late teenage yourself) then Ripley bonfire is much closer, has a good display and a fun fair and a couple of alright pubs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret NAZI ice-base ordered by Adolf Hitler discovered in Arctic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 14:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't upvote this enough. There are some quite emotionally damaging things that can happen during sex, particularly with wedding night virgins. 

Being able to have a giggle about it would make something like vulvadynia or vaginismus far easier to deal with instead of compounding the problem, and take literally *years* off of sorting that kind of problem out. 

Edit: Thinking about it, not a lot of people know what Vaginismus is.  if sex is painful and super tight, it probably is that and it can be treated. Go to your doctor, or a specialist sexual therapist. It CAN be cured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 14:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's with all the build up to that moment. 

Here's a (sorry, mobile) YouTube link to the piece I mean: https://youtu.be/MFK0yG8xG5I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 10:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PCMR:

Personal Computer Much Respect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh?? I mustve missed that? What do you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has written A LOT more music than just for Game of Thrones. Check out his back catalogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Light of the Seven, where Cersie does the unthinkable in season six. 

Literally, that whole scene hinges on it's music. I like Ramins music anyway, but that score really put him up there with people like John Williams, Danny Elfman and Mr Zimmer in my opinion. 

Watch it again with the sound off. It makes all the difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 08:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, I unlocked an achievement that was for completing  the game on Hardcore or Insane. You should have that too if you completed every act on the right difficulty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WebMD thinks pink eye is the black death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is better imho than Social TDM, but I want to play Warzone and Dodgeball ranked. 

At the minute though the matchmaking problems leave as much choice in modes as an Amish barbershop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which right now is an issue as the install base for gaming pcs is going to be pretty small in comparison to even 7. 

If they go all out and really support their store with great titles, they might encourage people over to it. There is no reason why the Halo games couldn't be on it for instance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The skill ceiling is pretty high there, I feel flashers are far more easy to get decent at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this is the best part:

https://gfycat.com/ScentedAcceptableCivet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 09:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good god... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also missing:

- Warlords
- 2 PvP modes
- 2 PVE modes
- 1000's of customisation and mods
- Veteren/Hero/Elite system

there is lots of stuff missing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A better one would be a building company selling timeshares (or something) in a property they were building that would be beside a stream in the country. Five months into building, the government decides to dam upstream, meaning that it dries up and there's no longer a stream beside your building. You move into it for your timeshare and see there's no stream, and blame the building company. You ignored or didn't see the letters sent to you by the company about the stream being dammed that's outside of their control and their lobbying efforts weren't successful, they offered a refund but you didn't avail of it (either through negligence or ignorance).

I have not got any emails detailing this, and it absolutely is false advertising to sell a product with a list of features on delivery. It's not unreasonable for people to be annoyed, although I'm not salty enough personally to ask for a refund. Sure the game is ok as it is, but it is NOT what was sold to me as. Using your analogy, it'd be like delivering the house with no windows, instead of them saying we couldn't pit the windows there can we move them to the other side of the house. They are just missing altogether. 

 If you pay for something two years in advance, the reasonable person would expect that there may be unforseen challenges or circumstances causing problems to that product in the timespan.

That's pretty insulting to be honest. The time factor is irrelevant and to be frank the business should be *more* inclined to deliver what was agreed instead of less when making a sale on extended delivery  terms (legally though that shouldn't make any difference). It didn't say: "These are features we hope to have in the game, but we reserve the right to change our minds" either.

Anyway it's clear your quite happy to make some pretty strong assumptions about me, maybe next time you reply I won't be bothered to read it through negligence or ignorance. 

tl;dr: I didn't buy Planetside, I bought Eternal Crusade when it said it was going to be open world, had 1000's of weapons and other features that are missing. Planetside has nothing to do with this discussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even know there was that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only ever been able to get a game on Team Deathmatch, which is a shame because I love the slower more deliberate Warzone mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was an engineer and I was teamed up with four snipers last night on insane. I told everyone I had the discounted turret perk and that we'd probably need them so try and avoid spending until we had at least one, no one answered and everyone dashed off after placement the fab. 

It was a great game... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that reference smeghead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clever bastard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For anybody that bought something a year or two ago and then came back to find out that "it's different!?"...well, it doesn't take a genius to tell you that's a predictable outcome.

When someone is selling something and tell me what features it has, if I know I'm not going to receive it until two years time, why shouldn't I expect to get what I was sold??

If you went and bought a sofa from a catalogue and was told you have to wait for an extended period of time and then the wrong sofa turned up you'd complain wouldn't you? If not, you can buy stuff from me anytime you want if you don't mind beijg given something different that what was sold to you. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate, they had an inforgraphic up right before launch detailing loads of things that still aren't in the game. Literally LOADS. I'll find a copy of it when I get home  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Emails were even sent out to every single one of those folks in January stating "If you want a refund because it won't be Open-World on release, you're welcome to at this time". 

Well, they sure as shit never sent that email to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I've had two elite packs, and two legendary skins drop (weapons), so I just scrapped those and instantly had enough for two character skins. One I bought with money, the other with credits. 

Sure the system *heavily* wants you to get your credit card out, but with a little patience you can get a couple you want over the next week or two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't played them, start with 1 and work your way through.

While 3 is technically the better game, you'll be spending the bulk of your time in 4's multiplayer so you might as well experience the originals story in the correct order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 16:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here comes Red Dead Retribution. 

"I'm John Marstons boy!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 16:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been saving for an elite pack, so is it really better just bring horde packs? I can buy like very nearly 9 horde boxes for the price of one elite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 12:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Toby Fox. 

I won't go into how good a game he made, most here will already know that. What is the achievement and what has proven a point is that you don't need to spend half a billion dollars developing a game to make it a success.


2. Cd Projekt Red. 

Again, there are too many others here posting this to go into details, but this is what happens when a professional outfit treat their product with the kind of care that Toby Fox gave undertale. 


3. Valve. 

People joke about it way too often, but aside from all their previous successes, refusing to put out a sub par Half Life 3, even when they know the game could be terrible and it would still sell a whole bunch proves to me again that Valve has their finger on the button. 

Edit: I'm not sure why Reddit formatting hates me so much it wint let me number a simple list correctly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 21:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's still a quality of life change imho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  PC-XBONE Let us set a default loadout. I constantly forget to switch to my Hammerburst.

Yeah, that one is pretty annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Murray is like the video gaming Batman. He knows what's up in the industry and wanted to educate folks on why you shouldn't preorder. 

By shafting people that hard on an overpromised and under delivered product it's turns out that while he isn't the hero the gamers deserve, he is most definitely the hero we needed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 12:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People can upvote things they think are more important, making more sought after changes nearer the top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PC-** Is there any reason why text chat is locked during match results screens? It's prime time for people to use it, and just seems a bit silly that it's disabled for the brief period where folks arent shooting each other in the face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PC-XBONE** Can we have a toggle when choosing skins for weapons etc that automatically changes the others to the chosen skin? Having to scroll through a bunch of menus three times to change the two pvp setups and the horde setup is a minor gripe, but one that I seems to be pretty simple to fix. 

On that subject, a random toggle would be nice too, so each match you had a random unlocked set of skins load from your pool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PC-** Can we please be able to bind the same action to two different keys? I like using my mouse four for melee, but it's really hard to spam in the event of a chainsaw duel. Having a second key on the keyboard in this event would help me in these situations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PC-XBONE** At the end of horde or versus matches where we can see accumulated credits, could we also be able to see the current total we have instead of just what we just earned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PC-** When choosing loadouts between rounds, could was have the A S D keys be used to select things instead of the arrow keys? It seems kinda weird that the menus allow for this but it doesn't here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quality of Life improvements thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks,

Thought I'd make a thread about minor gripes with the interface and stuff that while doesn't effect the mechanics of the game, might be a bit of an annoyance. Hopefully someone from TC will see it and bring it up with the the folks who can make the changes. 


Please note: i'm hoping we can have some *constructive* suggestions on quality of life improvements for the game. This isn't a complaints thread, for instance don't post about packs themselves, but if you wanted to suggest changing to layout of the screen or something like that, this would be where to ask.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how much have you spent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 09:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had one of those on my mac classic. 

Ahh the memories. Having to daily clean the slightly sticky rubber ball in the bottom of it was such a satisfying thing to do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's magical isn't it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently repeatedly swapping between the Undertale soundtrack, and How To Train your Dragon - Forbidden Friendship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. The first time i unlocked it I finished it (i was level 40), the next day when they announced double rewards I could get to the final three nodes, but then the enemy team are all 7-11 levels higher than me and in purple gear.

Did the game lull me into a false sense of security or something??

My A Team is Ackbar (lead), Leia, Chewbacca, JC, and Moff Tarkin (I have him at 6 stars, where the others are 4-5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also what happens when your wife and ex wife are in the same room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
