<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject610</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the gay person. Doesn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is pretty damn cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got it in 2009 when he was in office for less than a year. He probably thinks he doesn't deserve it. This stupid ignorant babble about the drones is so annoying. Stop reading Noam Chomsky and think for yourselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kids did it, leave them alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am deeply annoyed by both, but it would effect me about as long as it takes to notice it. The guy in the grey was annoying as fuck but he was also right.  When he is not putting on a show, he is probably cool to talk to. Either way, it would effect my life so little to interact with him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't disappointed. Then I couldn't buy it. Was disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the weirdest obsessions on the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pride... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I am already down voted lol. A joke on the shield placement was too edgy for Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, first off, life savings? No. Second of all, how do you know any of these things about any of these people? We can be sure the OP is totally isolated from "corporate profit centers" right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she pregnant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No fucking way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 years later, South Park sums up 2017 pretty perfectly. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [So courageous.](http://southpark.cc.com/clips/104225/acceptance-speech) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   a bunch of people started saying she was so brave and she was a hero.

South Park jokes have come to life. We live is bat shit crazy times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it would be some cartoon, but they got actual footage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh-oh say can you see... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people fall for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nahhhhhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One per week? It is not even mentioned if they were murdered BECAUSE they were trans. (not angry caps) There is so much misinformation out there to push a false narrative, which almost always hurts the group they are trying to protect, I am incredibly suspicious of any statistics that are vague. These types of beatings things are sanctioned by theocracies around the world and done in broad daylight. The comparison is laughable. If it happens here, immediate action is taken and the vast vast majority of people would help, even those opposed to the identity and lifestyle.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They serve a purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But wait, someone in America was not referred to as "zer" while attending their Ivy League school. We have to organize for that first, sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She can go away now. Neither side wants to see her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Now try this. READ IT! The opening fucking line proves my point. I mean, you might have to think. If you cannot do that read up how it is debunked. I am not spoon feeding it to you. It is right there.  Good luck in life. Wow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just proved you care about is less than the 30 seconds it takes to look it up. I am not doing your homework.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> St. Vincent. A review I read summed it up, "really well made cheese".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been debunked so many times, now you are just lying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times does this have to be debunked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite movies. Denzel, classic Walkin and the relationship between Denzel and Fanning made it so damn emotional. I think it one one of the best bonds in cinema.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh shit, he had to go to the infidels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It grew up and bit the head off of a baby seal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck in life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So stupid what people are doing to society and now children. I heard on NPR today twice that there is a gender wage gap. How many times does it have to be debunked? How much is enough? The current climate ignores the violations of women over the world for the exaggerated and slight and occasional minuscule transgressions. True liberals got lost somewhere in a pile of shit coming from the mouths of insecure douche bags trying to outdo each other with how virtuous they are.  I hope that child learns how to think for themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a proponent of female nudity since it is punished violently in the countries she is bringing attention to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the comment? I wasn't aware of that. Never even saw it. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck modesty for International Womens Day on March 8! (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously didn't read it. It is supported with evidence and written by someone who experienced a lifelong involvement with the issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just NSFWed it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, too late to do nsfw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Reddit, where do you find all your straw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic that they get to choose. Fuck the majority of the women in the world that are forced to wear it.  [If this issue and women's rights matters to you, then you owe it to yourself to read this.](http://freethinker.co.uk/2017/03/07/fuck-modesty-for-international-womens-day-on-march-8/) This is not a symbol of empowerment for the majority of women in the world who are forced to wear it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or? No, the insult still stands to the rest of the world by a corporation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting try. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To SJW's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit here we go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here we go. No, there have been established hoaxes. The fact that a single person can be so sick to do that, someone apparently on the side of social justice, means there are other that are not being caught. Unless there are witnesses, physical evidence, or a video, go the fuck away. I don't think it is on the rise, the insistence that it is on the rise is on the rise.  Did hate crimes go from 1000 to 1050 in a country of 350 million? You have hoaxes and you have people just trying to piss off people like you. Then all you idiots allow the actual racists to go undetected. You all make me sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is total bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority of women in the world who cannot take it off hate it. But fuck them, your virtues need signaling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was fucking hysterical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because fuck the majority who cannot take it off if they choose.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is stunning.  Specs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To counteract the effects of having a sex life and not being overwhelmed by ordinary women in the spotlight? Nah, keep yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also associated with high rates of adult addiction. I am leaving for work soon but I am sure a 30 second google search can help you find it. Something like the high 80's or low 90's percent of people who are alcoholics drank before the age of 18. Many other factors involved but if you have a genetic predisposition to have your reward center be hijacked by alcohol, your fucked if you drink at a young age.  If you have alcoholism in your family, you are really asking for trouble. Take it from a recovered addict who thought their will power ruled all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it, don't do it, she does nothing for me, not even a wiggle down there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did this stop being a thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dismiss any opinion of yours that may deviate from the norms of Reddit and start jerking the community off by pandering to them excessively.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How is calling someone a racist helping them?

What the fuck are you talking about?  

How are SJWs the best friend of racists?  

Use context clues, think, rinse and repeat. 

Telling racists they're racist helps them identify a flaw in their logic, ability to reason, and education I suppose (because most racist people have no idea that they're racist).  

They have to be racist. Ding ding!!!

SJWs help racists find one another I suppose, by giving them a common enemy.  

What the fuck are you talking about?  

Were you drunk last night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you come one here? You have no balls or self respect. I guess you know where to start?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this fucker get bowl obstruction and go away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best way to break their neck, they never see it coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously the motherfucker doesn't because they articulate a misunderstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walking side by side blocking the sidewalk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, again with this? This really has to be explained to you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because you have "social anxiety". If it has to be explained to you what is meant by "how are you" then you should probably just stay home.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you live? First off, they are just not as emotional as women, second off, no man gives another man a hard time for being emotional. That is a bullshit myth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think about what you say when you talk. Be aware of it and practice omitting it.  It won't happen the first time you try it, you have probably been doing it for years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's a filler that is just part of someone's dialect

It can be, the majority of the time it isn't. People who use that excuse are probably making...well excuses.  It is used in different places as "um" and for different purposes. It's a habit and it is fucking annoying. That is as far as my criticism goes so do not try to demonize me for dismissing someone character over something trivial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we need people with degrees for this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't read lol.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure you don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people calling others racist have zero evidence that they are, in turn, helping actual racists. The biggest friend to the racist is the SJW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not saying it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people calling people racist wont admit that they aren't.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was I waiting for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a history of missing these.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a weird is stupid image to live up to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  Nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because you watch movies for adults and have an attention span.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moonlight. 

The plot was disjointed, clunky and had no arc. The characters had almost zero development.  The intimacy was cheap and shallow and I see as an insult to the homosexual community. The third act was outrageously bad. It was stagnant, pointless, emotionless, meandering, and boring. It did a terrible job highlighting the humanity of the characters because of all these amateur film mistakes. It was outrageous that it got best picture.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Like" over and over and over and over and over in every fucking sentence they utter. I am talking about motherfuckers with jobs, well paying jobs, they sound like ignorant 12 year old children.  It is exhausting and takes so much time for them to dribble out a thought about something meaningless on facebook. Stop it! Just stop it!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see, this is so encouraging. I had a similar experience. Mock court proceeding and I had to argue for something I was ideologically opposed to. Depressingly, I did a really good job and we won the decision.  That didn't hurt things though, I made some points that I kind of agreed with and like always, it was a complicated issue with many nuances. 

I don't have an allegiance, but the reality is that the left aligns with what I believe in the most. It is the system we have. I have been called a Trump supporter so many times for showing the slightest bit of criticism of the left or not getting mad over something insignificant. I supported motherfucking Bernie! 

I just want to crawl in a hole and hibernate for 4 years and hope the fucking pendulum swings the fuck back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect your outlook but I was not being serious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem lonely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am, and always have been a liberal, it is way more over represented on the left. Even advocated for. I am disgusted with the left. My political opinions didn't change, but I guess I am center now because the left is something vile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because of Trump everybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laugh because this will actually effect people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda wanna say "Fuck". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insult them, call them stupid, call them bigots, call them Nazi's, and you will be one step closer to 8 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a little head dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made my day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it obvious what he is doing? People are on to this right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh, post it either way, you're a lot of fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is executed beautifully. Love Asian Jesus too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was Piss Christ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not pizza.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These comments are going sexual fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say the exact same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kidding, I don't want a wild animal as a pet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddammit, now I want a fucking prairie dog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cultures have stereotypes, you are not a bad person, or a fucking racist if they bother you. It makes the world go round. This hyper racializing will go away soon enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's cute as shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have the right idea. You have a good eye for texture and perspective.  [Here](http://imgur.com/OnKVZwL) I cropped it for you.  The nonsense in the bottom of the picture is gross and out of focus. You should check out "The rule of thirds", get really good at it, then break it artistically when you like.  I added a little blacks and corrected the white balance a tad but mainly it looks more pleasing because you get the texture of the wood as a feature and the framing is more pleasing.  Your depth of field is really shallow. Not necessarily a bad thing. Keep taking pictures!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bunch of postmodern babble. Don't listen to this person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The criteria for records are getting funny. "In March".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of these I could give a fuck, but he lost a me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That title is fucking genius.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will not only get down voted, but you will probably be called a bigot. 

People are terrified to criticize a movie about a black gay person. We are in a climate where normal people are being called fucking Nazi's by major news outlets who are so far removed from being a Nazi I feel like we are in an alternate universe. I am not going to patronize wither culture and be honest about it. To the movie. 

The plot is clunky, disjointed, and undeveloped. I don't have any time to feel anything because nothing is developed. There is so little time to feel a relationship between the boy and Ali. The exaggerated gushing over how stunning and beautiful the story is boggles my mind. 

The third act was stagnant and useless to the story. It offered nothing to the characters relationship and had nothing to do with furthering the plot. The movie had no arc and the third act fell below zero on a level of interest.  

The intimacy was cheap and shallow. I feel it is an insult to homosexuals. A wet dream? Really? Are we really watching him roll cum around in his fingers? That is how you tell us he is sexually attracted to his friend? Grow the fuck up. If that were a white heterosexual couple and he rolled cum in his fingers because he came over a woman people would be outraged. 

It was just lifeless. It had so much potential in the beginning with the characters relationships but they fucked it up. It went nowhere. It was saved by good acting, decent cinematography (although many parts were overdone and made me dizzy distracting from what was happening), and really beautiful music. The music was the best part for me.  

When "Fences" was out there, this movie getting best picture was a travesty. The human experience in that was unreal and brought to life by unbelievable performances. It was dialogue driven and I understand that being tough for some. I didn't see Manchester but it must be better than this movie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are You Threatening Me? (Tim Hagans/Stephen Hindman) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is pretty interesting. Check out some of his funkier stuff from back in the day. I used to go see him in the city with Billy Kilson on drums and Bob Beldon on sax. They had insane bass players I can't remember. I was pretty high or drunk lol. [Good old Youtube, found something damn near close.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H_uZ0f4oQgE)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banned from what? Fucking internet has something new every week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every check out [Tim Hagans](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o3RI8844JEU)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear screams and see the camera shake but what the fuck happened? I watched it 3 times and can't see anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you should read what I said? It applies to the current moment, you are not doing anything here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, you sure it is me that is missing the point? Good luck with that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you defended her, you should defend him, if you demonized her, you should demonize him. Of course none of this will happen because it is assholes all the way down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn clever graffiti.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How bad is 47 "Ronin"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this fucking guy Tom Hanks nice? I think he might be Tom Hanks nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck. You'll need it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sold the shit out of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you think that white privilege is about feeling guilty or less proud of your accomplishments because you're white you have absolutely no idea what the concept of white privilege is. 

That is funny, that was not my argument. Does this ever work for you?

Because it isn't that. At all.  

I am quite sure you are responding to the wrong person. 

I'm white, I acknowledge white privilege exists  

You are wrong, part of the problem, and virtue signaling. 

Let me know when you have a rebuttal, until then responding only makes you look ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You lose again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well shit, who can argue with that. Seems you dismantled every argument I proposed. Wait, no you didn't. Enjoy your day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work on your confidence. Become comfortable with being uncomfortable approaching people. You only do that by allowing yourself to be uncomfortable a lot. If you can afford it, a GOOD therapist (shop around for one that is right for you) can help you find strategies and work through failed attempts. 

We always wait for the future to come to confront things like this, only it's always the present and the future never comes.  It's not one thing you do to gain confidence, it is 100. Start today!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't. White privilege is the most divisive, racist, and devious term of our times. It is a broad brush of guilt that gives license to be racist and suffer zero consequences and ironically be praised for your righteousness. It is a fundamental misunderstanding of civil rights and what a privilege is.  


A civil right is guaranteed to everyone. Nobody is privileged with civil rights, we all get it. People who are good looking, free from genetic predispositions to disease, born into money, or born in a wealthy country have a privilege since it is not something we guarantee to everyone. Having said that, these people did nothing wrong and they owe nothing to others who did not get the same. They are not malicious and the others are not oppressed.
If a civil right is guaranteed to everyone, and some people have it taken away, the people who were not wronged, are not privileged. They did not receive a "a special right, advantage, or immunity granted or available only to a particular person or group of people" because it is guaranteed to everyone.  


When that is taken away, the answer is to give it back, not find malice in people for not having their rights taken. Or shamelessly imply that they have some sort of original sin for the transgressions of multiple generations past. The playing field is not evened by committing the same atrocious acts as an act of retribution. That does not make you right, it makes you guilty. If something is ethically wrong, it is across the board. We fix the wrong, we don't perpetrate the same act as punishment on parties who lack guilt that share the same skin tone as past transgressors.  


You can be damn sure that someone is on the wrong side of the argument when they start screaming, not addressing your points, and calling you racist when there is zero evidence in your life for being so. I recommend you don't engage with people who use this term if there is the slightest bit of dishonesty, yelling, or derailment. There is nothing to gain. You will spend your time in a trap of telling them why you are not racist. You will never come out of that happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever it takes to get them to help and that depends on the situation and the person. The big picture is that you are there for them. Knowing the science behind a brain disorder helped me with addiction and recovering from it. Your brain is just telling you things that you cannot will away. When you know what is going on, it is easier to identify it as some sort of outside influence you need to let pass. With anxiety especially, psychotherapy and better habits can retrain the brain.  Exercise is huge and takes time. People will not work for anything, try it for two weeks and then demand medication. Medication has it's place, but it's place is disgustingly over represented. It can also be used to facilitate change and be taken off of it. It is a chemical balancing act and that is why a doctor is important and finding the right one is even more important.  

I cannot emphasize exercise enough, intense cardio every day but probiotics are huge. Not the magic fix, but a piece of the puzzle. Look into research on them. There is stress tests done on rats that have staggering results. A quick google search can find those studies. THere is a good Radio Lab on one of them too. 

I have a high stress job and take "Garden of life: Mood" probiotics. When I am confronted with high stress, the edge is taken off without a doubt. If it is a placebo effect, I'm cool with that!!! Research suggests otherwise.  VSL #3 is way more concentrated but I don't feel the results as much. That being said, gut health is huge. 

It is complicated but attacking it from every angle is important and a therapist helps. Something as small as changing the decor in your house, the lighting, and keeping things clean can shave a level of stress off. Home is more welcoming instead of depressing.  

Shit, I am rambling. Good luck to any of you.  It seems to be quite an epidemic lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is pretty damn special. I wanna say she is a little young for that movie, but I didn't see it and saw rated R movies like it was my job at that age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His complaint is with Amazon. It sometimes takes it days for it to "leave the warehouse". They told me it is two days after it ships and getting it out of the warehouse is added to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are serious, aren't you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just wonderful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This word MUST be the most misused words on the planet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am brainwashed because I am critical of my own party? Fantastic then. 

Riots to prevent lectures, safe spaces, micro aggressions, 100 gender pronouns, fining people 250K for not using the correct of 100 gender pronouns, white privileged, calling all trump voters (many two time Obama voters) racists, calling everyone racist, bigots, islamophobes, homophobes, and now NAZIS!!!!!, halloween costumes, deplatforming speakers, openly advocating against free speech, punch a Nazi, and distorting facts on police violence to push a false narrative.  That is what I can ramble off the top of my head without stopping. 

That is rational? The left is irredeemable.  Nothing they do or stand for is for liberal principles. They need to call themselves something different. Real liberals need to reclaim the name "left" or re-brand themselves. What is happening is fucking disgusting. 

Criticizing the left is not an endorsement of the right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *slow shutter speed ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, this comment is spectacular. Bravo, fucking bravo man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! How do you do that without overexposing all the lights? F 100,000? 

Edit: It just hit me, a filter. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lose some weight they said. You'll look great they said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Criticized Moonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is the President of the United States he doesn't have time to fuck around on...oh, wait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I explained it in my fucking comment, try reading it!  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on the left and you cannot be fucking serious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its not even close to sexual assault lmao

Substance from the start. 

worst thing the person did was mislead you he was a woman.  

Why did you bother to respond? That is assumed in the fucking question lol. Yes, that was bringing on sexual activity I did not want. 

And no, violence would definitely not be an appropriate response.  

But why? You just simply assert it. When is violence ever justified. I see sexual assault as having consequences where a physical retribution is not unreasonable if someone was knowing deceived into doing something sexual they did not want to do. I don't think I would be violent, but I am not sure I could fault someone for doing so. I definitely would press charges. 

Edit: Including "lmao" really added substance to your argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you learn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the few times where you can use the word "brilliant" and not be exaggerating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you put the link in again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knots in my stomach when I see these ignorant slews of people shitting on their own rights, something as precious as speech. They are free and begging for chains. Worst of all, they have no argument. Obviously, since this issue has been settled hundreds of years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question for people out there. If a person like that, went on a date with a man, gave you every impression they were part of the [99.7%](https://www.google.com/search?q=transgender+population+percentage oq=transgender+p aqs=chrome.1.69i57j69i59j0l4.7326j0j7 sourceid=chrome ie=UTF-8) of women out there and never told you that they had a dick, and then decided to be intimate with you, what do you call that? I think it is sexual assault. Would violence be an appropriate response for such a devious thing to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens - Freedom of Expression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me more about what I don't think without asking me. Fucking Reddit and straw men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By having sex and not consulting the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what this fat man does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have difficulty with "transgender" claims from children who didn't even go through puberty. I have to imagine it is influence from their parents.   

That being said, false narrative and they are using a child as a political prob. Both sides are fucking disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not even taking sides, rational discourse is like porn for me now days. The left and the right are disgustingly dishonest on any issue when they discuss. When I see people, even talking about hunting, disagree like adults, I feel like I can cum.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's impossible to criticise, it's just so typical of people to break out the (overused) word 'overrated'   


Pretty sure you just proved the point my sarcasm was suggesting. Thanks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> k
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you cannot think of anything, or not being honest about the reality, the both cases make us too far apart for a brief conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought I would see the day the left were the worst offenders. I am liberal and pretty disgusted by it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, so annoying that someone has an opinion about a movie about a topic that makes it impossible to criticize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously this is in controversial. Spoiler alert. 

I got shit for suggesting that it only received the acclaim because it was about gay and black people. It had great acting, promise in the story that was not fulfilled, and some moments with cinematography. 

The gushing and overemotional reviews seemed to be about a different movie and it is the only reason I could come up with. The third act was stagnant, meaningless, disjointed, and lifeless. The concept of a gay black person in the ghetto was not profound enough to make up for the clunky assembly of the story. The intimacy moments were cheap and emotionless, I see them as an insult to the gay community. The camera work was beautiful at times but over the line in others. The introduction to Ali's character had a spinning camera technique that has been done before and was distracting, overdone, and had nothing to do with the scene. That is all I can remember off the top of my head.  There was no development of any character in the movie. It was a clunky mess. It was in incredibly flawed movie and had no business being best picture. I didn't even see Manchester but Fences was better acting, better story, more emotional, in depth view of the human experience, and better dialogue. On a different planet. I feel like I am taking crazy pills.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The facts are that millennials are in more debt, work longer hours for less reward and with less stability and less opportunities than baby boomers.

Found your problem. This is true for every generation. They just feel more like victims because it is happening when they are young.

But I'd be happy to introduce you to my friends who work every hour they can on zero hours contracts  

You mean the ones I acknowledged? It is almost like, dare I say it, you didn't read what I said? Nahhhh.   

for whom buying a house is a kind of distant pipe dream.  

Not just millennials. But fuck everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sometimes we say what we have to, not because it is true. Fact is, he is trying to motivate a stagnant and weak generation who make excuses for wanting everything given to them and refusing to work for anything.  Granted, much of that is their parents fault, that doesn't absolve you of the responsibility for hardship and working your way up to things. This will be passed off as the age old "young people are lazy" but don't make that mistake. I have full confidence that the generation that follows this one will laugh at this one and look past it to find a seed to discover new things and find new ways to do things.  Trust me, it is not young people.  I feel sorry for the significant portion of this generation that don't look for excuses and doesn't want everything given to them and want to acknowledge them. I am sorry there is a stigma and you don't deserve it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd dichotomy, it is statements like these from Democrats that will make them electable again and statements like these from Trump that will make him electable again. Doing the right things is difficult. In the end, you have adults acknowledging the good in someone but their image is not juxtaposed with a pile of shit and incompetence. I wish people would be adults. Good on Van, he said it perfectly, and most importantly, honestly. Try it!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, just let it happen, it's part of life.  Experience it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because people want to be racist against you and find an out to absolve themselves of responsibility. You are being judged on your race and being chastised with a type of "original sin". If the people who are doing what is wrong, the racists, make themselves the victim and associate guilt to you by past aggression of people you have nothing to do with, the very act of objecting to even being called a racists is seen a racist. 

Oddly enough, and this is speculation, but I feel it is motivated less by racism and more by virtue signaling.  Only because it extends beyond race. The addiction to creating victims where they don't exist so you can see as the defender of the weak. It is also an addiction to creating malice in people where it doesn't exist. You do not have a victim if you don't fabricate people of ill-intent. 

White privilege is the most divisive, racist, and devious term of our times. It is a broad brush of guilt that gives license to be racist and suffer zero consequences and ironically be praised for your righteousness.  It is a fundamental misunderstanding of civil rights and what a privileged is.  

A civil right is guaranteed to everyone. Nobody is privileged with civil rights, we all get it. People who are good looking, free from genetic predispositions to disease, born into money, or born in a wealthy country have a privileged since it is not something we guarantee to everyone. Having said that, these people did nothing wrong and they owe nothing to others who did not get the same. They are not malicious and the others are not oppressed. 

If a civil right is guaranteed to everyone, and some people have it taken away, the people who were not wronged, are not privileged. They did not receive a "a special right, advantage, or immunity granted or available only to a particular person or group of people" because it is guaranteed to everyone. 

When that is taken away, the answer is to give it back, not find malice in people for not having their rights taken. The playing field is not evened by committing the same atrocious acts as an act of retribution. If something is ethically wrong, it is across the board. We fix the wrong, we don't perpetrate the same act as punishment on parties who lack guilt that share the same skin tone as past transgressors.  

You can be damn sure that someone is on the wrong side of the argument when they start screaming, not addressing your points, and calling you racist when there is zero evidence in your life for being so. I recommend you don't engage with them and keep living your life.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame she wouldn't matter if she wasn't hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that this is an issue shows how stupid both sides are. There is no sanity left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Behold, the albino rationalist. The rarest creature on the political landscape. They often act like adults and act reasonably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOW!!!!! I did an edit, I linked the wrong book. You must have checked it before I fixed it. The book had the same name and I was in a hurry. I can't possibly imagine what the other book was about but you are a child with this reaction. The book I meant to link was by David Sheff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not. That is another discussion. I am simply commenting on the first level effect of each disease. The outcome of giving into addiction is to use, the outcome of giving in to pedophilia is to rape a child. The effects of what happens after that can be discussed.  

You seem to have a very deep misunderstanding of addiction. This comment is clear evidence. 

from withdrawal-induced rages  

There is so much ignorance in that (I am not calling you an ignorant person) I don't even know where to begin.  There are so many books I can recommend, but I think from what you are saying [this](https://www.amazon.com/Clean-Overcoming-Addiction-Americas-Greatest/dp/0544112326/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8 qid=1488281423 sr=8-2 keywords=clean) offers a good balance of science and anecdote.  If you want more, let me know.  

Edit: Oh no!  I had the wrong book in there.  I will switch the original linkas well. . [This](https://www.amazon.com/Clean-Overcoming-Addiction-Americas-Greatest/dp/0544112326/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8 qid=1488281423 sr=8-2 keywords=clean) is it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty sure this one wins and you can all go home now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty sure that sky video was bullshit too. Source: I live on earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in the most compassionate view of looking at it like addiction, a disease of the brain, the consequences of an addict do far less damage than a pedophile if they fall off the wagon. Just not the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially the intensity levels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one in my fish tank. He is the coolest fucking thing. He actually makes plasma! That was contingent on it being a liquid though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I despise Trump. But here you morons are playing a numbers game with the man who won the election. Jesus Christ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have ad-block and it does nothing with youtube ads. Help?

Edit: Wait, maybe that is just at work. I actually use youtube for work. Is that actually my problem??? Now I cannot even remember if I get them at home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucker. Not cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times is this exact joke going to be recycled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said "like" in every fucking sentence. Not full proof, but pretty damn close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uggg, I can't even.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said I wouldn't reply, but I didn't leave for work yet. Thanks for your opinion, I knew it, and can see already this will get down voted into nothing. That is a shame, I really wanted to hear some honest critique. I have heard virtually none.  I feel like I am taking crazy pills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhhhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Respectfully, Moonlight only won because the characters were black and gay. Hear me out. (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First and foremost, being black and gay in the ghetto wasn't profound enough to elevate the story to anything interesting and the third act was meandering and lifeless garbage. The actors in the first act were beautifully connected and it could have been something special, but it just wasn't and the story fell short. It fell short as a love story, it fell short in plot development, and it was disjointed and clunky. The intimacy was cheap and emotionless. 

The acting was great and it had real potential in the beginning. It could have been so many things, but it wasn't. I am 100% certain people are terrified to criticize it because they are scared to be called racists and bigots. This is the world we live in, groups went from marginalized to patronized. 

Would love to hear your thoughts but not here to debate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still gotta love Justin. Well, love to hate. Funny, sings, acts, attractive. Ugg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, actors are getting old. Wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
