<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject348</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck, this subreddit is delightful! I've just found it and it genuinely saddens me that its dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd you take your cat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit, really? As a MASSIVE matt hughes fan this makes me so happy haha even more excited than i thought could be possible for such an awesome show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you a Dick about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he's too old, he's going to like die in a month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooray! It's someone who actually read the article! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of (great) examples from more recent cards, so if you wanted to dig a little deeper UFC 92 main card was one of the best cards I remember watching, especially if you give a little context for the fights beforehand. 
Same for UFC 113 I think from memory.

Otherwise Silva v sonnen 1 will surely produce a great narrarive, though might be a little submission heavy especially without he context of who Silva is (could maybe show them the griffin fight and leben and franklin fight first?) 

If they'd be the ones keen for a brawl the recent cub v choi fight is perfect! But if they're likely to appreciate crisper and more technique, Edgar v Sherk is sure to impress or maybe shogun v griffin 1 (but that was a really long.time ago and so maybe it was shit or a brawl, I can't remember!) and if you wanted a more varied matchup with a good mix of standup and ground courier v nogueria is jumping to the top of my mind for some reason but I havent watched it in a long time so maybe it was shit also! :p 

Lastly there's a bunch of pride fights you could show them fedor v cro.cop, nog v bob Sapp (for the freak show fight fan in all of us), rampage v arona etc.

The fight that actually got me into MMA though was gsp v Hughes 1 which is unfortunate as neither is really.fighting right now. But just the variation.of the fight and then that finish oooh! :p

 but that's a personal fave, everyone has their own and for their own reason, so is really recommend any suggestion from this post, all are great. and just show them some of your favourite ones too, that way its easy to give context and create a narrative for them to invest in (like I remember getting my so interested just by explaining.to her on a pretty long bus ride the career of Frank Mir, becoming the champ, losing.the belt, over.coming real adversity to finally beat nogueria and win back the 'title'etc - but.now I'm just rambling!!)

Any way, hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i totally agree!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah same here! I never really cared for her character, and exactly as you put it, she was 'an extra' but this season she's probably become one of the more interesting characters, who's also a complete badass. 

and her story is cool, like genuinely cool! Her wanting revenge after losing abraham, and both before and after negan, and losing her friend in glenn, and now going to be dealing with her actions leading to Olivia's death and Eugene's misfortune is one of the more interesting character stories going on right now and im very very excited and intrigued to see where this badass character goes next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dwight probably makes the most sense, from memory he was surprisingly absent from both the survivors and alexandria wasn't he? i'm probably leaning a bit more towards it being dwight now after thinking about it

is also always the possibility of it being a brand new character, from an entirely new group though i'd feel that wouldnt really be as exciting (but thats just me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be, i think kirkman said it was the dude from the boat on talking dead though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The boots guy surely has to be an original character, who's obviously followed rick and aaron, saw them beating aaron, and negan killing everyone, and is going to give (and work with maybe) rick and co to beat negan. could also possibly be the kingdom member who was talking to morgan and carol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
