<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't play yasuo anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in promos for d5 twice and i attribute it to playing yasuo. Now he's perma banned because of a reddit post on r/leagueoflegends and i demote to p3 and don't get to play him anymore. Can't wait for the nerfs so i can start playing him again. Anyone else mad about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget abyssal and mastery magic pen and magic pen from runes! (Even though abyssal reduces magic resist i consider it similar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rip :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im plat 1 failed diamond promos twice. I dont compare myself to anyone below the ladder i figure if im good enough to carry d5-4 players then i should be diamond myself which is infuriating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sivir spell shield bug? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing braum and i q'd her and exhausted at the same time and it canceled them both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Carol not cause she's a bad actor but because they just throw her all over the place emotionally which doesn't make a lot of sense. I don't like Glenn because he's always been a self righteous preaching goodie goodie who avoids death all the time. I like Daryl but i hate his fans cause they praise him to where i think i can actually hear the female fandom's vaginas screaming his name. Rick is my boy. Rick can kill anyone in his group and i'd be on board.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 21:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plz riot dont listen :(. Dont be giving people at riot ideas about how to nerf my favorite champ. Just nerf frozen mallet since it seems to be the problem with yasuo and gnar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk i liked it. Idk why everyone complains about music. No one is ever satisfied :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No cure for fools Yasuo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gave me chills :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Renekton. If he dashes at you to trade you'll win it 90% of the time (made up statistic). Make sure to charge your fury and don't waste your cd's csing minions, if you do make sure you're out of range so he can't capatilize. Use empowered w to stun him and unleash your combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't want to come across as cynical but, how do you know? Sources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complex of a pre-teen girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm P2 now thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because i know my capabilities and am confident in then and i don't need to warm up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about when you enter a custom game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but there was a tournament a while ago if you won it you get the clan tag yasuo and a prize. Been searching r/yasuomains for another tournament post but no luck so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zephyr for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, fuck off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice flair. I can respect that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My guide for Lee Sin Plat 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys I have a really nice build for lee sin that I hope you guys like :D.

Runes: 2 Armor Quints, 1 AD Quint, 9 AD Marks, 9 Scaling Health Seals, 9 Scaling MR Glyphs.

Masteries: 5 Unyielding, Explorer, 5 Veteran Scars, Insight, 5 Swiftness, Strength of the Ages, 5 Savagery, Runic Affinity, 5 Fury, Expose Weakness.

Items: Warrior Trackers, Merc Treads, Triforce, Deaths Dance, Steraks, Dead Mans Plate.

Lee has a lot to do with early game so if you get ahead then triforce is what you should get. If not you can switch it out for a Sprit Visage or Guardian Angel if your team relies on your engage. Deaths dance is pretty essential for the staggering damage which helps with more bursty comps so it should be prioritized after triforce.

Build path: Hunters Machete 3 Health Pots- Trackers - Warrior - Boots - Phage - Triforce - Merc Treads - Deaths Dance - Dead Mans Plate - Steraks.

You can switch these out as i said before but I believe this to be the most optimal build.

Anyways, enjoy :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright cool thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as long as the restriction isn't in effect at the end of the season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season rewards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure each season is different on how to get them but if you were chat restricted do you get rewards still? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 05:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you worried when your team went to relegations? Did you talk to your coaches about the performance of your team and what needed to be changed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 01:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayyy that would be cool. They definitely need more client based game types that are actually fun. Like when they made the poro game for phones that was cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else notice that Procxin sold his jungle item? After he bought Tiamet he should have finished his jungle item into cinderhulk and just go straight tank after what happened early. But he full on tilted and kept buying full ad and then just sold his jungle item. I was puzzled :D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gotta save them for later tonight :D! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the whole thing and didn't see that. Thanks :).
Edit: Wow it was in the beginning the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is QC a combo? When i press C it brings up a stat menu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought given the 50% w/l ratio it implied that i've been here for a while but I can see your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually i had plat at the start of the season. I've just been stuck here :o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a smurf that's gold 3 that i used to play ranked with my silver cousin. He doesn't play anymore and i don't play on that account. I probably have like 100 games on it. I probably could get to plat if i was winning high plat games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
