<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  ,  "-2017"    </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devin Nunes Met Intelligence Source on White House Grounds (before his statement) - The New York Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pic is worth... Murza shaking hands with McCain which he calls "fighter against dictatorships" ...and on the top pic left - the King of KSA and McCaine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the one w/ the donkey, haven't seen that one, with the goose. Anyway I'll take it down. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  ,    ,    </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Presidential Candidates Financial Status </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  .       .       30%  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exhibit A: https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7300fhXQAAe7rQ.jpg

exhibit B: https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7301BJW0AEfYTh.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remembering who Navalny is indeed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it did, kind of. Good to know, haven't been back 10 years already. Thanks and my apologies for the outdated info. Then you in fact didn't break the law. Damn kids, man, left with no chance to break the law, that's sad. :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, dude, 'cause Sofia is not Bulgaria /s You can tell me whatev you wish. What if I call BS on that one? I know how kids wanna-be law breakers and shit but I don't buy it. You can tell that to s/o who hasn't spent 40 years in his life in that same country and have seen quite a lot you haven't dreamed of as runs with the law and other shit. Save me the teen and post-teen enthusiasm. How about if I tell you I have ordered alcohol during the short-lived 'dry' law period, of which you probably don't know shit (USSR Andropov times), in socialist Bulgaria (serving alcohol before 12 at noon was not allowed) in Troyan and it came in a tea cup? Does that make me a member of the Resistance, a dissident and anti-totalitarian fighter? No one is gonna risk his relatively hard to get license just to make a couple of levs more. Some joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1915 Satirical Map of Europe drawn from the Russian perspe x-post from /r/europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, cut the asinine BS and learn to read or go back to school as you don't impress me much. You can fucken drink as much as you want. Anyone can! Establishments are only banned to sell alcohol on election day within the hours mentioned by the law. Period. **YOU DIDN'T GET DRINKS IN AN ESTABLISHMENT DURING THE BAN** How is this difficult for you to understand? Now post a selfie, a pic or whatev or take a hike. Damn kids, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [" "](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YFStV1SWbcg) -'72 ' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Corruption Protests in Russia, 2017 - Album on Imgur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  after midnight

Is tomorrow in my book, in the law book and in the book of Nature. So put simply you DIDN'T get drinks in establishment on election day. Just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  ,    !!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read that. But anyone can link to such a source if it was "so many times", I guess.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess there is, that's how I view it. It's called AdBlock Plus extension for Chrome users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not sarcasm but disinformation on your part. Selling alcohol in Bulgaria is banned ONLY on election day, not on the day before. That's the law and it's there for a reason. Anyone can drink as much as he wants on the Day for Decision Making or whatev is the translation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that one too takes a lot of pounding without falling apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  don't really care about the law very much and it won't be difficult to find pubs, bars, etc. who are willing to violate the law.

You wish. No pub or bar will sell you alcohol for sure, especially to a bachelor party bunch and I deeply doubt any establishment will host such a party on that day, so better buy your drinks the day before and as it is the local tradition have it in private setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some caveats though. The official (right or wrong) unemployment rate in Belarus is ~ 1%. (WiKi) though "Many unemployed people in Belarus are trying to avoid registration, because of obligatory public works..." So basically the law does not target ppl registered as unemployed as I understand but the ones who don't work and don't register as such which already gives some better perspective on why the law exists. It's interesting to have some opinions from Belarus ppl. Also in confirmation that it is bad journalism I can say that from what I saw Belarus does NOT struggle to quell the protest, they (the Govt) shut down the protest in no time and without any hesitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just glanced at the chart and didn't pay attention he was asking about Armenia as they are next to each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The subtleties of soft power: China is spending billions to make the world love it | The Economist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Historical Photographs:Russian pilot Valentin Privalov flying under the bridge over river Ob. June 14, 1965 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Against All Odds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fights erupt at pro-Donald Trump rally on California beach | US news | The Guardian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italys Struggling Economy Has Worlds Healthiest People </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine honors nationalist blamed for anti-Jewish pogroms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine honors nationalist blamed for anti-Jewish pogroms - Haaretz - Israel News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. judge grants Singaporean blogger's asylum request | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhh, how else we gonna make the EU, our greatest economic competitor, crumble? Gotta keep them separated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.cia.gov/library/readingroom/search/site/resistance%20factors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1957 CIA SPECIAL FORCES ACTIONS in UKRAINE Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airstrike monitoring group overwhelmed by claims of U.S.-caused civilian casualties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed the first part of my post. One is enough :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France's Marine Le Pen visits Moscow and urges end to Russia sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all guinea pigs, bud. Just get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's banking system has SWIFT alternative ready </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, OK. I didn't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ', ,  - ,  ...' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be surprised: http://nymag.com/thecut/2017/03/vibrator-company-fined-usd4-million-for-tracking-user-activity.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ..? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also nyash myash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "CRIMEA COULD HAVE BECOME US NAVY BASE IN 2014. UKRLIFE TV (Ukraine) https://t.co/wafPh1qKEO @inabster @marcelsardo @inartic @Tiago477 https://t.co/7VtRC8Hj0v" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
