<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6782</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 05:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will try, cheers!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using a controller, so not an option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using a controller, so not an option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if this will ever be fixed. It seems like some stuff was fixed but I think they seem to fix the things that are easier to fix and simple "bandage" things up instead. I also wish there was a GTA4 style HUD for the in-car weapons so it'll show us what gun we have selected. I hate shooting and realising I'm using the garbage Micro SMG, then going for the AP then scrolling past it, then having to go full circle again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I think we'll be forced to anyway...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not like they'll actually fix it permanently, it'll be gone the next patch, then back (probably worse) the next lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad for people like you with expensive cards, a 980Ti being unplayable is just downright wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been getting these small stutters here and there since launch, but absolutely nothing like this. It was more than playable before and I could easily hit 80+ fps and keep above 60 at just about all times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I think you're right, I highly doubt it will be ever fixed. Why on earth would Rockstar even bother since they've already made the money?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a bloody joke, the online integration with SP is absolute garbage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I hope we won't have to put up with this until the next full patch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea honestly, haven't been keeping up with it. All I know is that it only supported some earlier versions and I really don't feel like having a separate install just for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would leave you restricted to offline only though right? More a temporary "fix", if you can even call it that... Maybe there will be some weird fix possible with some random setting in game or something, who knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's definitely a shame that there aren't private servers. I really hope that FiveM mod turns out to be good, it looks kinda promising so far, even more so than the actual game servers. Plus modding looks super fun and it sucks that we have to miss out since we want to play legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 3 new horns make up for it. Right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good old xliveless, I'm kind of glad I only got into GTA4 super late as all that stuff was fixed up. I miss that game. I miss private servers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it unplayable at the Ammunation? I'm getting a definite hit in the store but it isn't nearly as bad as some others seem to have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really sad right? I wish all these little issues were pressed out, it would make the game so much more enjoyable if it simply worked. Couldn't even play the entire day since it didn't even launch properly pre-update, and now we're stuck with some stuttering garbage and some mostly useless new cars. I mean I understand (to some extent) if the game was broken at launch, then fixed, but to be broken, then fixed, then broken again? Not to mention how easy it is to completely break someones game by pressing a few buttons on a script?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 17:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played this on PS3 a lot, and trust me, it ran so badly to a point where just driving a car would make the map disappear since it wouldn't load in time lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I could help you... that said the game doesn't seem to stutter as much in SP. At least for the few minutes I tried it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I'm running a 960, haven't had this issue either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know what they do to make it worse every update. Why they even change something that wasn't broken is beyond me. I get the armour stutter as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This too, the shadows pop-in super late now compared to before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it's fixed too, it's awful and near unplayable as is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it seems like the av. FPS has almost halved. Doesn't help that it actually looks worse too...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely, it seems like my aliasing is a lot worse than before too. On top of this the shadows seem to pop-in a lot more obviously? No idea how they've managed to make it worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awful micro stuttering after update and lower performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm experiencing terrible stuttering after the update and a lower FPS on average. Pre-update I was getting about 80fps which keeps the game silky smooth, now I'm just barely hitting 60. On top of this the game is micro stuttering all the time and it feels like I'm getting like 20fps. It's almost unplayable honestly. Anyone else having performance issues?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 here, on top of this the game seems to runs worse too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 11:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully yeah it will, I just hope it won't be closed before the actual removal. I'll miss the (relative) exclusiveness though haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Dorothy Avenue underpass (midway between Ormond and Glenhuntly) will become pedestrian/cycle only.

There goes my favourite route to skip the wait, damn. 

Very good info though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind Mischief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just sold, sorry! :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are currently full, but we may be doing another run later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Pacific Standard Setups   Heist - Hard - 40/20 Split (Right Now!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for 1 player on PC right now for the Pac Standard (all setups + final heist). Will pay 20% of the final cut to those who join. Please add us on RSC and send a message there if you would like to join. We would like to finish this as soon as possible and we have plenty of experience. Our R*SC names: timoloney   ThickishTunic15

It is expected that you have all relevant heist gear (Heavy Vest + Helmet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind Mischief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, I'm actually having someone look at the keyboard tomorrow and they seem very interested. There's a few other people who have also showed some interest too, but I'll let you know what the outcome is. Sorry!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 03:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind Mischief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elephant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 10:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elephant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooler Master CM Storm Trigger Mechanical Keyboard with Cherry MX Black Switches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 11:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SOLD**

I've got a used **Cooler Master CM Storm Trigger** Mechanical Keyboard for sale with **Cherry MX Black** switches. It has switchable red backlit keys which can be toggled into different modes.

The keyboard itself has **some wear marks** from general usage and will **only come with the original gold-plated Mini-USB cable**. I do not have the original boxes or documentation, the extended wrist-rest, or any charging adaptor for the on-board USB hub (as far as I know, this part is not included when new either and only enables charging). 

http://imgur.com/a/YRJOC

Looking for **$60 negotiable**. I am open to offers and maybe swaps. I don't mind swapping for another part but would obviously prefer cash. Swaps at my discretion only, and I am most interested in any low-end LGA1156 CPU with cash adjustment if you do happen to have one. 

Pick up in 3165 or willing to bring to you within reasonable distances. Not willing to post. Please PM me here if interested! 

You can find more about the keyboard here: 

http://gaming.coolermaster.com/en/products/keyboards/trigger/

http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B009FTWL2C/

**SOLD** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [VIC-MELB] [H] Cooler Master CM Storm Trigger Mechanical Keyboard with Cherry MX Blacks [W] Cash $$$ OR Swap for LGA1156 CPU + Cash Adjustment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a used **Cooler Master CM Storm Trigger** Mechanical Keyboard for sale with **Cherry MX Black** switches. It has switchable red backlit keys which can be toggled into different modes.

The keyboard itself has **some wear marks** from general usage and will **only come with the original gold-plated Mini-USB cable**. I do not have the original boxes or documentation, the extended wrist-rest, or any charging adaptor for the on-board USB hub (as far as I know, this part is not included when new either and only enables charging). 

http://imgur.com/a/YRJOC

Looking for **$60 negotiable**. I am open to offers and maybe swaps. I don't mind swapping for another part but would obviously prefer cash. Swaps at my discretion only, and I am most interested in any low-end LGA1156 CPU with cash adjustment if you do happen to have one. 

Pick up in 3165 or willing to bring to you within reasonable distances. Not willing to post. Please PM me here if interested! 

You can find more about the keyboard here: 

http://gaming.coolermaster.com/en/products/keyboards/trigger/

http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B009FTWL2C/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 10:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, I'll get back to you in a few most likely since I've also got some other things to sell. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elephant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Price Check] Adaptec ASR-5405 2258200-R RoHS Single 256MB SAS RAID Controller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone, just checking to see approximately how much an **Adaptec ASR-5405 2258200-R** RoHS Single 256MB SAS RAID Controller is going for these days. I have the original box and all the documentation that originally came with it (instructions, quick start guide etc) as well as a single cable and some screws. Prices seem to vary online a lot and I really can't find much about it either!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 01:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be Above It </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She Just Won't Believe Me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [VIC-MELB] [H] 2 x Corsair XMS3 DDR3 1600MHZ CL9 4GB (2x2GB) RAM/Memory Kits [W] Cash $$$ OR Swap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SOLD**

I've got **2 x Corsair XMS3 DDR3 1600MHZ CL9 4GB RAM (so total of 4 sticks, 8GB) kits** that are now unused since I just upgraded to 16GB RAM. None of the 4 sticks have ever given me trouble and have been running at 1333MHZ since I purchased them from Centrecom. They are both part number: **CMX4GX3M2A1600C9** 

http://imgur.com/a/WunM8

I'm willing to sell **everything here for $70 (4 sticks) or $40 cash for one set (2 sticks). I am open to offers and swaps.** I don't mind swapping for another part but would obviously prefer cash. Swaps at my discretion only. Please note that I do not have the original boxes. 

Pick up in 3165 or willing to bring to you within reasonable distances. Not willing to post. Please PM me here if interested!

You can find the exact same model for sale at: 

Centrecom here: http://www.centrecom.com.au/corsair-ddr3-4gb-pc-128001600-2x-xms3-2gb-cmx4gx3m2a1600c9-ram

And a StaticIce link: http://www.staticice.com.au/cgi-bin/search.cgi?q=CMX4GX3M2A1600C9 amp;spos=1 

**SOLD** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
