<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone experiencing weird Server lag and errors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 07:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird lag but not on my side. Others in my game were complaining too. Boost pads weren't coming up but still gave you boost if you went over them. Anyone else? Im playing on Oceania servers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 00:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found all juj eps, jonwaynes 'the wayniac' lp and all four of his 'from the vault'. Cant remember the others but there was more. Heaaps of groundislava, shlohmo.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 03:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> download soulseek qt man. that program changed my life. i did a few searches on that thread through soulseek and theres A LOT of that stuff on there. downloads are usually slow but yeah theres so much shit on soulseek. probably the first place i check when looking for music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 22:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends if he is playing live or not. Regardless, when I saw him dj i had a very good time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 14:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [1800KILLURSELF](http://imgur.com/p5ftWF4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> niiiiiice howd you get this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 00:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the first one is really well made. Great acting, solid killer with an awesome mask, and the tension is insane. You get such weird and unsettling vibes from the whole town. 

Not too sure about the sequels and the recent tv show, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 06:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks lads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 01:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that absolutely sucks. was it mid show or earlier?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 00:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 00:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did baauer cancel?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 00:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too sure. Event showed like 1.2k people were attending, I think about 40 people showed up. I saw 1/2 of Loudpvck walk up to the stage, stop, and then walk backstage, if that helps with anything. 

Still a really shitty thing to do regardless! What are the good outcomes of cancelling a show that way? Reputation? Ugh, idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to see LOUDPVCK tonight.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they cancelled literally last minute because of a bad turnout. Cheers guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have the original Shlohmoshun EP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 03:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the deluxe. Shlohmo recently said on twitter there is an ep before the deluxe version. He said it was still unreleased but I just wanted to ask in case any of you guys had it / spread the word. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Henry From Outer Space (Shlohmo) - Hummus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 11:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 08:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> private tune "stickupkid" (got this tune if you called wedidits number)

swim (oh no shlohmo remix) 

the bait (shlohmo remix) 

most of his remixes you can find on youtube anyway !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, i remember following sam at the beginning of this year and he had like 3000 followers. It was around the time when Diversa and Flow-Fi reposted him. Fucking insane how far he has progressed this year. Soulection are doing pretty well ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 11:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this edit/remake was made by quix. not a legitimate studio 320. probably the best version that will ever see the light of day. 

sounds real good on a big system. use it in your dj sets or to impress your friends!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SOPHIE - MaybeSD (Good Quality) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 11:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 10:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 06:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah shlohmo remixes etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 06:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got more if ya need  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 23:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was truly disappointing because the story was so interesting in the first three. Also, in the ghost dimension, the second scene goes OUT OF found footage!!! It switches to proper movie format?!?!?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 16:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah that is all fucked up imo. which is why he would be screwed if he uploaded it himself cause technically its not his  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nina's Last Show (Soundcloud) - Diplo, RL Grime, Cashmere Cat, Flume, Swick, Anna Lunoe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 16:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 15:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he would get completely fucked up by the label (who is even releasing the gemini ep btw?). loss of sales, all the work the label has put in thrown out the window because its out there for free. 

on one hand i understand going through a label to release music. on the other, he made it, why cant he upload it whenever he wants to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 15:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably samples, tunes, actual projects etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 09:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yaaaaaaaaaaaaaay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 08:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emoh should just upload it for free at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 03:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Well, kind of. In this one, there is time travel except instead of a door its this weird cave in the wall. Toby is chasing her so she crawls through and ends up at the old house in the third movie. Then random crap happens and they all die. 

The story was not resolved at all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young Scooter - Columbia (Shlohmo Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show off your stats thread! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 18:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post and show off your stats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 04:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just appreciate the fact that they deal with, create, and manage their music themselves on their own label.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need inspiration for my beach campaign! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 02:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, first time posting here.

My group and I are doing a big campaign for a local beach. Our main idea is revolved around each season being full of things to do, giving people a reason, say, to go the beach during winter. 

We have a presentation soon, which has already been completed. I was just reaching out for help with some themes/one word ideas that really tie it all together. I was thinking something along the lines of 'compatibility' or bringing the seasons together.

any ideas/discussion would be great help. thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 02:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Yes. Death Grips do what ever the FUCK they want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 16:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly. It hasnt been worked on for a while now i am told.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 13:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silva is a boss gahd damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 03:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whys that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 19 and haven't seen any Star Wars films yet. Why should I watch them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be different for you guys but I think luca lush, and other similar artists, will hopefully just be a fad and sizzle out soonish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dads wedding ring finger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 12:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 06:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I GOT A MESSAGE FOR PEOPLE WHO LEAVE RANKED MATCHES FUCK YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 07:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have listened to the leaked version. vyzee will be on the album so whats the problem? theres no difference in sound quality between a single and the same song on an album.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the difference be..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 13:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its coming out on the album!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 04:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commentary of scott pilgrim is an awesome experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 15:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol dude you have heard one song out of a whole album.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 14:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre gonna be VERY surprised/shocked by LOVE. Vyzee is really cool and has a nice beat but Love is just so whack. Im really enjoying his latest from the album! Different but refreshing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 18:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooof. Youre right! Gahd damn i hope its kitty cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 17:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone over at /r/pcmusic did. the exclusive track is msmsmsmsm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 16:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a strong feeling that song will never see the light of day except for crappy live rips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 16:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this and the cashy edit of forever 1. today has been a fucking spectacular day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JUST LIKE WE NEVER SAID GOODBYE by SOPHIE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old Fashioned In The Rocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 08:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 02:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> goddamn amazing. check in the middle right of the picture and you might spot a nice record!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 16:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From an unreleased/really fucking old ep i downloaded from somewhere. there was also a nelly furtado edit and a few originals. 

another one that samples the "can yall really feel meh" song 

http://www1.zippyshare.com/v/v4lPHOjc/file.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drake ft. Nicki Minaj - Im So Proud of You (Arca Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 16:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> purient - in dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 14:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 2] Favorite moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 12:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would have to be the shootout!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 1 and 2] Favorite moments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 12:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite part of Season 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 06:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 02:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this! It is strange, right? How someone can intentionally write a batch of code, and then for some bizarre reason it works the way you didnt intend for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are bugs made in games and how difficult is it to find one and fix it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 01:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Discussion) How are bugs made in games and how difficult is it to find one and fix it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 01:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 01:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its explained earlier on in the movie and basically the witch would steal children, make one child stand facing the wall while the witch killed the other child. Its one of the more prominent stories within the film so you know exactly whats going in when its revealed. 

Was it just me or was the lore and stories actually quite unsettling? It was extremely well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who cant be bothered watching or just want the unusual highlights (everything I type is said by the "doctor" in the video):

Beginning - Sloppy explanation of what the method actually does. Talks about either being a 'left' or a 'right' and this can be determined by sitting down with a piece of fabric one at a time on each butt cheek. 

1:20 - The girl is a 'left'. Doctor explains her posture is like a car veering to the left. 

3:10 - Does a fucking bizarre super twist on her, pushing her legs into the window by accident. 

4:38 - Doctor explains that he can feel whats wrong with the patients back/body by touching a certain area and then feeling ridges in the neck that tell him if the area needs correcting. Explains that he adjusts the bones the body cant adjust itself.

10:30 - Explanation of her heart being compressed due to posture and the weather or something. 

They're all the weird bits of the video, overall its just total bs. Worth the watch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bizarre Chiropractic Method. "Your heart is being compressed....." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 16:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 10:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much info about the release of Gemini yet. Seems to be a bit of hype that can be seen throughout the interview. Only thing he says is: *Thank you to all the fans for being patient with Gemini and for coming to the shows*. 

Hopefully its coming soon ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with What So Not (October 8th 2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 10:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 04:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching footage. It definitely wasnt coop and there wasnt as much hud on the screen like dynamite cop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 03:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching more footage now. It just doesnt ring a bell, if you know what I mean? Hopefully it all comes back to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 19:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. Is there a possibility it could be a small mini game kind of thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 19:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not it sorry bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately this is not it! Thanks for your answer, though. It was a really great game! I remember playing it for hours on end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ive got to bang loads of men

know the bouncer, skip the queue 

fuck the list, its me and you

the club is bangin, so am i

bangin bangin bangin bangin bangin bangin

banging loads of guys

slip the trousers, wet surprise

in the bathroom, suckin dick

thanks for coming, that was quick

quicker than the other guy

its friday night, wet surprise

leave the club, 2am

bangin bangin loads of men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> get to the club at 2 am </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 12:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am get get to the club at 2 am get to the club at 2 am  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Dreamcast][IDK]Shooter on a cruise ship (not Dynamite Cop) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Platform(s):Dreamcast

Genre: Shooter, action.

Estimated year of release: I recall playing around 2001.

Graphics/art style: nearly birds eye view (cant remember), 3d definitely. 

Notable characters: played as a man (maybe a cop/spy?), i think you could choose between a few different ones.

Notable gameplay mechanics: beat em up of kind of game, could pick up weapons from ground. a lot of the environment was destructable (i think!) 

Other details: the game was set on a cruise ship. i recall the very last mission which was finding the main enemies home base on an island.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cheers bro
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just googled dreamcast game cruise and the main results were dynamite cop. watched some gameplay but it definitely wasnt it!! i remember playing the hell out of it too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also: game wasnt dynamite cop  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been searching for a while now trying to find a shooter game set on a cruise ship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was nearly birds eye view (from what I can remember). I also remember the last mission was going to the enemies home base on an island. It was a shooter game but you could pick up different objects on the ground. Any help would be appreciated!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 15:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone just totally shits on every aspect of the game. But what do they expect when the game is an enormous unfinished bug?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 03:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the switch between Alejandro is very well done! You're sort of tricked into thinking the film is about Blunt, but really her ultimate purpose within the story was to give their operation a certain amount of legitimacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 03:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a major turning point in the movie. The first time you see the supposed 'villain/biggest threat' is when he is eating dinner with his family inside his own home. And you realize Alejandro is Sicario! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 02:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I can remember, I got these from an old youtube channel that was tracked down by Numbers.

I got Fizz, Physical, Higher, Oops, and Oof. 

Definitely not 320. But far better than most copies out there. [Spek](https://i.gyazo.com/e508f67461b06f79417fba0dd06e1c37.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SOPHIE - FIZZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 02:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched Sicario. Wow. (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 01:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ending scene. A huge intense buildup to a man having dinner with his own family. Made my jaw drop. That whole scene was so powerful yet fucked up. Gonna go see it again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 01:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that really makes it interesting. Going to give it another watch soon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 14:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry guys. posted it on my phone. thank you ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Req] TNGHT - R U Ready (320) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 08:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 08:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk man. It just felt so...off. Im not too sure if it was the movie itself making me feel like that but it was just an extremely odd experience watching that movie. Almost surreal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 11:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> melonius drunk is nick melons old name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 18:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are essential mixes all done with cdj's or can the artist choose what they want to use for one? If so, its gonna be interesting hearing his dj skills considering he mainly plays live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 03:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah all good man! a lot of people seem to think that its actually a genre. 

their soundcloud: https://soundcloud.com/pcmus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SOPHIE - MSMSMSM (320) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 03:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 03:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pc music is a label </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 02:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go see sophie play live. He opens with this and it is magical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 01:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think this is from the pc music forums yeah?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you hop on stage while Rae Sremmurd is playing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 12:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 06:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Novation audiohub has 3 usb inputs and its a sound card. Works well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yah downloaded it directly from soundcloud so its whatever was uploaded  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh out of the oven: http://www48.zippyshare.com/v/8J5fp1f9/file.html

Edit: This is not a 320. I downloaded it from Soundcloud using SoundTake so the quality is whatever was uploaded. 

Didnt expect downvotes :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its 1am here and i missed this post by about 3 seconds 

good night  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An album bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 14:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8  ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 13:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guessing for wsn, something fucked up during contracts and stuff when flume left. Its not like Flume can just simply say im out and hes out, he's obviously contributed towards the production of the ep so technically its his as well as emohs. Its a huge bitch sorting out all that shit and takes forever going back and forth, conflicting schedules, emailing, etc etc. 

Emoh obviously has the finished product in his hands but releasing it for free on his own would fuck over the label and their already set up contracts (read up on shlohmo and jeremih's collab ep and their label problems. Death grips too!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is the brain capable of remembering pain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 07:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I explained it well. I can remember when I broke my foot and how much it hurt but not the actual pain itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 12:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bbe said he cancelled for the whole tour  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 01:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> miiaaoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 06:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes :((((((((((((( times a million </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 05:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will probably never come out lol. cashmere posted a snapchat story a couple weeks ago of him in a studio with sophie. he was showing cashy some songs i believe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 04:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally see where you're coming from. I was thinking to myself while listening that it is probably for his live set. Good luck tonight at jack rabbit!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 02:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also patiently waiting for sophie and cashy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 14:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 14:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ubi cain. Will give this a shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP. Am stuck in an endless update loop with Uplay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 13:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought the Tom Clancy Humble Bundle. Installed Splinter Cell Conviction. Uplay updates game, says my operating system is not compatible (Windows 10). Uplay continues anyway. Downloads and installs a ~1mb update. Tries to launch game, ~1mb update pops up again. Downloads and installs again. I CANT EVEN CROSS OUT OF UPLAG. IT JUST REOPENS ITSELF AND CONTINUES THE SAME LOOP

WTF do i Do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a song you are absolutely dying for but know will never get released? : ( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 18:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mannn all i can say is good luck :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 11:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan of this at all. Makes the original seem like a gimmick that can be remixed/screwed with. 

edit: expected downvotes :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 11:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still working bredda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 14:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely well produced. Hudmo and Lunice. May have to dig deeper and listen to their unreleased stuff (search on youtube: unreleased tnght/tnght id). Not too sure if its just me but I fucking love hudmo's discog so it was cool seeing him branch out. 

They were at the forefront of the whole "trap" movement and came in at the perfect time. They stopped the project when it became saturated as fuck with copycats and brickwalled bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 15:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not op but i definitely think that what i read about it before on here messed with how i took in the film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 15:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight from the FoF Five Year Compilation. I think it was made for a Youtube interview called Yours Trule (Previously called Places (Yours Truly Remix)). Great tune if you're into the lo-fi sad guitar bizniz.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shlohmo - Places (Shlohmo Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 15:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 14:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup exactly my point. Pretty good follow up album but the wait was just way too long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 14:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how'd you get this leak btw ?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 14:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About to listen in a couple of min, I'll let you know what I think. Do you think it was worth the wait?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 13:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow fuck yes wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 12:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesssss. Amazing shit. Recently got into him a couple of months ago. Definitely check out his remixes. His shlohmo one is siiiick. He made me look into pedal boards and guitars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op is a little bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we have a discussion about sound and ambience in games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 03:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im always curious as to exactly how much time goes into this area of a game. There is obviously a big difference between the sound in a game like Limbo and Far Cry 4. 

What programs/software is used? What types of sound files are used? How do open world games have different areas with different ambience?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Uplay is an unreliable alternative for any situation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 14:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 07:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting! so there wasn't much of a reason as to why they never saw each other again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched Melancholia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 18:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing film. Completely drowned me with anxiety and dread. My only minor question is...what happened to the husband after she slept with the new employee? I didn't quite catch what he said. Did he know about her quick little affair?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 13:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats all i got! its nowhere near done i hear  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 12:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here you go buddy: http://www70.zippyshare.com/v/pJcwtSiS/file.html

not too sure about spek but sounds better than most rips out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 12:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unreleased Quix, Silva and Troy snippet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 11:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a popular tourist attraction that isn't as good as people say it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 18:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> villa on friday !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 13:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turned out i had work at 6am the next morning so i didnt stay for him. Saw nlv and mssingno which was cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 17:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. To solve this problem there could maybe be like a minimum explosion that isn't too small for slower goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup! it would make really fast goals a lot more satisfying too if it ended in an enormous boom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Game Suggestion] The goal explosion size should be base on how fast the ball goes into the goal! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 14:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 17:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing Djemba Djemba tomoz night in perth. What should i expect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 04:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like james blake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who wants to hear a silva and quix collab?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 16:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What mixer do you use? Favorites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 16:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yess thank you. This helps things a lot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 14:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats the routing like? ELI5 because I am quite new to this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it easy to make a pedal board run into/out of Ableton? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 12:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Necessary gear needed? I am very new to pedals and such and I mainly want to use them for production. I want to be able to have a loop running and then be able to have all the pedals run over the top affecting the loop whilst it all being ready to be recorded with Ableton. Absolutely any help would be amazing!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 15:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot contribute to this discussion myself but can we PLEASE have some more varied answers than the usual? You can pretty much guess the top five answers before you even read the comments! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
