<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The advantages/disatvantages of using a PPO or HSA account for medical coverage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 17:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 28 year old diabetec who visits the doctor twice a year for a checkup and prescription refills. I take care of myself and would consider myself "healthy". 

I have tried to understand what the difference between these two coverages are and I just can't figure out which one would be the better option for my situation. I have asked questions and no matter how they explain it, I can't seem to figure out specifically how an HSA account works, so I default to PPO because it's what I know. Any help would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 04:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to get rid of dandruff? Don't buy a "2 in 1" shampoo/conditioner, or wash it out immediately. Just leave each of them in for at least 2 minutes so the chemicals have time to react.

Source: Had dry scalp for years until I figured out what I was doing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Thomas Mller riding a soccer ball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ...Now what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 16:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 23:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CreditKarma has a breakdown of credit scores based on their users' login domains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 18:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be saving mine for a future beard apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 15:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks! You are a saint, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exactly my face when I opened the package. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 15:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unfortunately, my plans have changed. Anyone looking for a dinner reservation for 2 at the Rattlesnake Club tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 00:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me if you're interested.

EDIT: I am not a smart man. I replied to what I thought was a message with my name and reservation time last night (was on mobile and didn't realize). I do have a way to ensure no one else uses it ahead of the person I intend to have take it; I'll PM people in order until it's gone and fix the issue from there. Whoops...

EDIT 2: The reservation has been taken. Good luck to anyone who is still looking!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 piece black wool blend slim fit suit (Express)

white button down

red solid color tie (eldredge knot)

silver tie bar

[Skagen watch](http://i.imgur.com/xRRJhHW.jpg), and 

of course my Scooby Do heart patterned underwear.

Setting: riverfront dinner at one of the best restaurants in town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillbilly-esque secretary that does not stop talking about things that no-one cares about. I can't exaggerate enough: does.not.stop.

I sent [this](http://i.imgur.com/vc1uPNw.png) to my co-worker when she was talking to him in his office and I heard him burst out laughing uncontrollably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 21:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;dr Engineering graduate from a college in Flint. Moved to the suburbs and got bored, so moved to Detroit and partied daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "O"s in the Timehop feature on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 20:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiger Woods PGA Tour '09. I missed a short putt to win a tournament and proceeded to throw my controller through my wall. Once I pulled it out and realized that the controller stick was broken, I walked out onto my third story balcony and threw it as far as I could into the parking lot below. It felt pretty good watching that thing shatter into a million pieces after missing that putt, not gonna lie.


That was the last time I played Tiger Woods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 19:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be looking into this; thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 19:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Stickman Golf 2. Been playing it forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 19:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cunnilingus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For future questions like this, I would recommend posting them on /r/outoftheloop. They are very good at answering these types of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely pay a mark-up for inhalable insulin. I have used needles for 21 years and I still hate it. Any idea when this is supposed to be commercially available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 05:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see you from my apartment OP.


Signed,

Super Creepy Detroit Rob Lowe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing the sound of a carbonated beverage of any type opened and/or poured through speakers. Radio commercials, TV, anything. I have to mute it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 16:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same "squeaky metal door opening" and "semi truck honking twice while passing by" sound effects that have been around since what seems to be 1985. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 17:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/titlegore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 16:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maria Brink from In This Moment.


Sample: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5ZF5m-vmDzM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 19:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hah, well at least there's that". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not true if you are talking about a 2D plane, IE a piece of paper (I realize a piece of paper isn't exactly a plane, but an accurate representation).

d and p are a reflection of b and q, not a rotation; pending we are referencing it in the correct context of actual usage.

Sorry to nitpick, I can't help it sometimes...carry on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 14:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [So do I.](http://i.imgur.com/AWW0RTk.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 18:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This exact same situation happened to me as well (grand opening weekend). I went in to check it out, got one beer at the bar. Though I was the only person sitting at the bar at the time, the bartenders repeatedly walked past my empty glass without asking if I could use another. After a half hour of no offer for a refill (I could have asked, I know, but I was in the mood to see how long it would take; so sue me), I was told that I had to cash out and leave because there was a private event about to begin.

I went back the next day with my girlfriend hoping to get a more positive and lengthy experience, and was told that it was booked all day again for a private event.

They should have opened to the public the weekend after their private events; I can't depend on this place being open when I'm looking for a spot to eat/drink. Why would I want to make plans with people from out of town (for instance) to meet there only to have it closed to the general public?

This place needs to clean up its act. I'd give it another month once the new hires are broken in and the initial crowd wears down, then maybe it'll have a chance to be a solid spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Best Monday of the year"; implying that the Cowboys won't advance any further.

I'll take solace in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 17:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Lions fan, this WILL be the worst Monday of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 07:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Automotive accounts program manager in Detroit, 95k salary, 28 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 07:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [...I tried?](http://www.reddit.com/r/DIY/comments/23m5re/reddit_i_present_to_you_my_project_that_kept_me/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 00:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a company funded trip, fortunately. The skyline here is gorgeous, so this particular view is definitely somewhat infuriating regardless of who funded it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This beautiful view from my hotel room. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/Zz36JBq.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 21:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Hitler didn't win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 21:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to post this; you beat me to it. Have an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 18:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as getting the sleeves up higher to show a watch, what I do is pull the swatter back far enough to reveal the second button, undo the top cuff button, fold it back once and button the top cuff hole to the second button, then push the sweater underneath. As a skinny guy, this is a fail-proof way to keep the sleeves up and looking neat with minimal effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 19:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this. Wearing mine right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 00:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/ZgEE3xN.png

The shame in hindsight. 10 man PPR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Always great to have a comfortable amount of cash for the biggest bar night of the year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was definitely surprised to see this headline. This is a legitimate article. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 18:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Reddit community formed its own physical country, and the laws are to be created by the users. What law would you institute? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 15:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, that's quite unfortunate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My co-worker is really, really into Christmas... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The girlfriend's kitten is warming up to me, I'd like to think. Planted down right here as soon as I sat down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for the translation, Bing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The name of this beer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 23:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the Stott building. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DCA...? Looks to be the sky deck on the top floor, south side, shooting north... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the dumbest shit I've ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessir!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look closer, the door goes right over it. It is stopped by the wall, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This doorstop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The trees still in the sun haven't lost their leaves yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 21:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 21:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> QB: Drew Brees

2WR: Odell Beckham Jr., Sammy Watkins, Kelvin Benjamin, Brandon 

LaFell, DeAndre Hopkins, Allen Robinson, Andre Johnson, Josh Gordon

2RB: Le'Veon Bell, Denard Robinson, Lamar Miller

TE: Jimmy Graham

Flex: See above

K: Shaun Suisham

Def: Arizona, Houston

Edit: PPR league
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 17:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need Beckham to score 57.33 points in my PPR league.

[The situation](http://i.imgur.com/fTkwBxq.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This baked potato was not happy to be left at my house last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 23:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 17:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both know that's not healthy; but yeah, you're not exactly wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 16:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend and I used to love Steel Reserve in college. We made what we called the "Steel Curtain" in a month span. 

Evidence: http://i.imgur.com/5XCo6Id.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 14:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, it's like carrying around a big bag of slow and painful suicide when trick or treating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All that candy and cake I never got to eat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 14:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For context, I'm 28 years old.

I ask myself this question: "When I'm a grandfather and sitting around a campfire with my grandkids, would I have anything interesting from my life to tell them?"

I live my life by this mantra. I look for new ways to get outside of my comfort zone, live in the moment, etc. constantly. Honestly, living this way has given me many great stories to tell about my life. 

I had a good friend who has traveled the world, works in Detroit politics, can captivate a room with his words, and seemingly has seen it all tell a group of his friends, "I have stories; but subject5813? That guy has some REAL stories". It was a sign to me that I have been trending in the right direction.

But for now, through all the heartache and mistakes, struggles and successes, the horrible and the wonderful; the love, friendships, and experiences I've had would make me say that I am, in fact, satisfied and fulfilled with my life to this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 21:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is more than mildly infuriating to me. Being a fantastic GM product (sarcasm), the clock resets to a completely random time every time the car is started. I would set it correctly, but I'd have to do it every time I started the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This shit during my hour drive to work this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #MIAvsJAX - Looks like this Bortles kid is a miracle worker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 00:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to Yahoo!, Asiata will be shattering records this season... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice night for some riverside biking in Detroit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 01:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 15:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was disappointing. Time to try again next week. It's a shame, considering that pick 6 by the Broncos with 15 seconds was a gift from the betting gods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't believe in jinxes. Hopefully your day is going as well as mine. Special thanks to the Broncos defense. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 22:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's your day going /r/NFL? Mine is going quite well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 22:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've played hockey nearly daily for 20 years. The skates have rubbed nearly all of the hair out of my ankles, creating a boot line out of my leg hair. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a reference to the fact that Pontiac, and subsequently the GTO, was axed during GM's restructuring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This poster at work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 00:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you the part costs less than a dollar to produce, if that makes you feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 00:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a "stuffer". It's an acoustic silencer that's crammed in random orifices in a vehicle to deaden unwanted sounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 00:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The correction asked for a dodge dogeball, that's why I left it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It arrives every fall, and my opinion never changes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 23:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 23:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I didn't realize puffins were banned. Time to find a different meme to make the same point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's here every fall, and it doesn't change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 23:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 22:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source post for reference: http://redd.it/2ir9fe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone mis-typed "dodgeball" on one of my posts. Fixed their comment with an updated picture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 22:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 20:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real-life Photoshop is as good as I get at any sort of Photoshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dogeball it is.

http://imgur.com/5FJV0uz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 15:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work at CTC in Auburn Hills, as soon as I saw it I had to buy it. Not any cheaper there either, unfortunately... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picked this up at Chrysler, now it's a decoration in my office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 15:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix must have a new employee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 14:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So we're doing best Halloween costumes now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 03:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
