<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4125</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 14:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title adapted from [press release](https://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-10/e-dof100716.php), which includes quotes from the authors.

See also related [expert commentary](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e21263) for more insight into findings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See also related [expert commentary](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e21263) and [press release](https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-10/e-dof100716.php) with quotes from the authors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Abstract](http://dx.doi.org/10.7554/eLife.18313.001)
Metabolic studies suggest that the absorptive capacity of the small intestine for fructose is limited, though the molecular mechanisms controlling this process remain unknown. Here we demonstrate that thioredoxin-interacting protein (Txnip), which regulates glucose homeostasis in mammals, binds to fructose transporters and promotes fructose absorption by the small intestine. Deletion of Txnip in mice reduced fructose transport into the peripheral bloodstream and liver, as well as the severity of adverse metabolic outcomes resulting from long-term fructose consumption. We also demonstrate that fructose consumption induces expression of Txnip in the small intestine. Diabetic mice had increased expression of Txnip in the small intestine as well as enhanced fructose uptake and transport into the hepatic portal circulation. The deletion of Txnip in mice abolished the diabetes-induced increase in fructose absorption. Our results indicate that Txnip is a critical regulator of fructose metabolism and suggest that a diabetic state can promote fructose uptake.


[eLife digest](http://dx.doi.org/10.7554/eLife.18313.002)
Fructose is a type of sugar that is found naturally in fruits, and it is closely related to glucose. The amount of fructose in our diet has increased dramatically in the last few decades. Growing evidence suggests that excessive amounts of fructose contribute to several metabolic diseases, including fatty liver disease and diabetes. Fructose is absorbed in the small intestine via transport proteins called GLUT2 and GLUT5 and then travels to the liver where it can stimulate the cells to make fats. However, it is not clear how fructose uptake is regulated in the small intestine.

Glucose is taken into cells by a transport protein that is closely related to GLUT2 and GLUT5. Another protein called thioredoxin-interacting protein (Txnip) interacts with the glucose transporter and regulates glucose uptake. Here, Dotimas et al. investigated whether Txnip also regulates the activities of GLUT2 and GLUT5 to control how cells absorb fructose. Initial experiments in cells showed that Txnip binds to both GLUT2 and GLUT5 and increases the amount of fructose taken up by both mouse and human cells.

Cells from mutant mice that do not produce Txnip absorbed less fructose than normal cells did. Furthermore, the mutant mice had lower levels of fructose in the blood and less severe metabolic disease after consuming fructose regularly for six months. Mice with diabetes absorbed more fructose through the small intestine than normal mice, and the loss of Txnip from these mice abolished this effect.

Together the findings of Dotimas et al. suggest that Txnip plays an important role in regulating fructose absorption and indicate that, at least in some circumstances, diabetes may lead to more fructose being absorbed in the small intestine. The next steps following on from this work are to understand the molecular details of how Txnip regulates fructose uptake and to determine if other forms of diabetes also show increased fructose uptake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fructose is fast-tracked through the gut in diabetic mice, contributing to metabolic diseases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This related expert commentary gives some more insight into the advance brought about by the Mesolens.
https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e21072 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The videos in this article are definitely worth a look.
https://elifesciences.org/lookup/doi/10.7554/eLife.18659.015

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For hundreds of years, optical microscopes have had to compromise between resolution and field-of-view. Now, a newly developed microscope lens called the "Mesolens" offers imaging large volumes (i.e. entire embryos) with sub-cellular resolution throughout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
