<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many ground-up apricot/apple/cherry pits would cause fatal cyanide poisoning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 14:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painful and horrific but not that slow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 00:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nembutal or Cyanide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 09:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. We live in the same town and we don't really see him or talk to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have bad memory to, but I don't know if that's the PTSD or BPD.
I've got great memory when it comes to certain things like train schedule, bands or music, suicide statistics and methods ect but when it comes to anything else it's like a sieve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, got the same thing from my boyfriend.  He can understand most stuff, but he doesn't know that much about mental health. He said he never understands me with some of the stuff, but he's here for me too.  
It doesn't feel the best, but as long as you have someone to talk to,  it can help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phyisically tried: I'm guessing like 5, but if you include the times I got stopped, as in pulled back, I'd say 7 or 8, most likely 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Mum didn't actually want kids, she just got pestered. She said she's glad she had kids, but I wish my Bio Dad didn't pester her, because I wouldn't be here. Oh, and he didn't even stay around to raise me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, but how would that happen?
What would cause it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would someone get fatally electrocuted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 10:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 09:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you might be intersted in /r/sanctionedsuicide  
They don't give advice like get help and they are non-judgemental  
Anyway, fave genre of music? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knows pretty much everything. 
He knows my mental health is bad, he doesn't know how bad.  
He doesn't know that my most recent attempt was 3 weeks ago and that I got stopped by a random stranger.  
He doesn't know that the last time I went to a spot where I could die was a week and a half ago.  
He knows I've scratched myself recently, he doesn't know how bad that could possibly get, or the cautery pen I ordered. And he knows I don't sleep right, he knows I wake up in the night but he doesn't know how often I wake up with nightmares.   
I'm also worried about  when we go away because I won't be able to hide things so easily, and I could wake up with my heart pounding because of a nightmare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you trick it?
Is there another way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't got angry in years, I get a little bit annoyed or frustrated as stuff. I can't get angry, I don't know how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So probably not that painful, unless it gets pressed down.
One other question, what does it do to the skin?  
That is correct, but I did have help and I should of already learnt how to handle it by myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not insensitive, he doesn't complety understand mental health issues, that's all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you self induce a heart attack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would someone do that, and what if the person was healthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, and a few others, one of them being /r/MadeOfStyrofoam  
But I have started hurting myself again and that helps me have less suicidal thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on your defintition, so I'm really not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Survival instict. It's primal, so it's always going to be ther, and that means it's never going to get easier, just going to have to bite the bullet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never tried it but I'm curios now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd just say order a bunch of stuff and sneak it out, they shouldn't send a receipt, they didn't with mine but that was from eBay.
Luckily I ordered something and it came yesterday with another parcel I ordered, I didn't tell my parents and they didn't check it either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How painful is using a cautery pen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how would I make sure the wound doesn't get infected? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 23:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often would I have to manually clean it? 
And this might be a stupid one, would it set off the smoke alarm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't dark jokes help? 
The thing is I hardly get angry, I'll get a bit annoyed or frustrated but I haven't been angry in at least couple of years.
It feels like I'm not capable of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the more scarring, as it is used in scarification. 
Is it a more infection risk because it's burning mostly? 
Also, can you explain the smells bad bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faint scratches with nail scissors...only problem is me and my sister might be going swimming soon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boyfriend said to me that surely that my PTSD wouldn't be bad if I was over what had happened, and I do see his point, it does make sense. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 09:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knows I won't talk about my feelings, he knows stuff that has happened to me, he also knows I use humor to cope.  
Not gonna lie, I make pedophile/rape jokes and all sorts of dark jokes, but really only in front of him because he has a dark sense of humor to, but he's said that mine is quite a bit darker, and I joke about things he wouldn't touch.  
He said that these things that have happened to me must bother me if I'm like this, and I do really see his point, and I'm not sure if he's right or not.  
He said I act like it's no big deal, it's normal (it kinda is for stuff like this to happen to me), but he knows me extremely well and that he can tell that it does bother me a bit.  
I'm not sure if it does it not. It's just something that has happened, I can't really change it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a cautery pen to self harm? Is it safe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 08:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone done this?   
I ordered one on a impulse a few days ago, but I've never used one.  
It's a surgical one. What should I be careful of?  
I understand if this is against the rules, and if so I apologize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 08:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a dark sense of humor anyway, so I will share stuff from Nihilist Memes or stuff similar to that among other stuff. People just think it's my humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep you can, ordered one!
Have you used yours yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot, I did do some research and apparently it cuts and burns at the same time?
And that's confusing, and it's used for scarification too but the one I ordered was a surgical one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you ever used a cautery pen to self harm with? What's it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered one a few days ago after seeing a post in here but I've never used one before. So what's it like? 
I also have to explain to my parents about a package so oops but oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had something wrong with me. I didn't want to eat since I've been born. Had terrible nightmares as a kid, I've always seen shadow figures that weren't there.  I've accepted I'm never going to get better, I just have to handle this as I am now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 12:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My arms do get so itchy sometimes, that's when I tend to get the urges. It just makes me want to do it more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 12:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone I've told has the same reaction, says I should go to the Doctor, get help, and tries to give me advice and says to think postive. Or overreacts and says I need to be with someone at all times (My parents)  
My boyfriend has been the same, but I told him I would never act on this (LIES) but he says that he's here for me to talk to, but I don't want to worry him. But at least he's being non-judgemental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 12:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most weird recent thing I've done, is order a cautery pen online so I can burn myself with it. I have NO IDEA nhow I'm going to explain that package. Oh, And I've gone to a bridge 2 and a half hours away too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 11:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! I have never fitted in anywhere, always been classed as the weird kid. That's just who I am. Can't change it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 11:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm the same. I bottle it up, don't get mad, don't overreact ect.  
I just hide away, make sure not to let anyone too close, I haven't cut/burnt in a while but my recent suicide attempt was like 3 weeks ago, and the people that know are on reddit.  
Just because you don't act like people think you should act, doesn't mean you still dont have it. People act in different ways. My Mum used to overreact, I don't react at all. 
There is actually another subtype of BPD called Quiet BPD, all the same symptoms, only difference is how you act.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 11:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is so much stigma surrounding mental health issues, espelly BPD. The main reason why I didn't tell my boyfriend untill a few days ago (Going out 6 months at this time) Was because I was scared that he heard all the bad stuff about it. He heard about it, but didn't know what it was, so I told him what it was in a simpliefied form.  
Luckily he knew I have had issues, so he just accepted and said he might not be able to complety understand it, but if I ever need to talk he's here. He's very supportive.  
My Mum has BPD too, my Dad knew someone was wrong within a year of meeting her, and accepted there will be some issues later on, he handled it well, when she went into hospital, he called her every night and visited her twice a week, she moved to a high-secure 200 miles away, he drove 4 hours there, visited for 4 hours, drove 4 hours back. All while raising a 2 teenagers, one with a anger mangement issue, with a weed problem and an eating disorder, and me. I went into hospital a month before my Mum, got out 7 months later, she stayed for 3 years.  
But he's supported everyone, my Mum is so much better, same with my sister, I'm the only one still having some issues.  
On the other hand, my bio Dad thought she was using it as an excuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 09:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you do it?  
I have BPD but I'm having a bit of trouble at the moment and would rather not go back to the Doctors.  
Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 01:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you can. I'm used of not being wanted, or being ignored or talked over. I don't have any abandonment issues, but I'm scared of scaring off my boyfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I got diagnosed with this back in April but I only knew about my diagnosis last week.
Do you think BPD can be left untreated? 
Do you get any self harm or suicidal urges/impulsivlty? 
How do you deal with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't do the chemo, wouldn't tell anyone and maybe suicide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would that work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep sure and thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not on any prescription meds, these are a family members that she doesn't need to take anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, I didn't know about the psychotic break. Yeah, that's what usually happens to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I haven't, what's that like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I only do quite small OD.  But I fucked up the picture and I'm not thinking straight atm.  Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started up a couple weeks ago using these tablets, I know it's not harmful but it's comforting and I can't cut, but I have ordered a cautery pen. These meds aren't my prescription and they make me groggy and my muscles hurt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I felt a really massive urge to self-harm, and I impulsively bought a cauterizer pen. I have no idea what I'm going to do. I just can't handle myself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that was smart...oh why, WHY did I do that?  
The urge have been getting so much worse, but I've been getting by taking tiny overdoses (less then 5 each time) and I've only done that 3 times. I can't handle my massive moodswings, impulse, self-harm and suicidal urges.  
Also me and my boyfriend had like a couple hours chat on Saturday about my mental health, I've told him about my 2 diagnosis (C-PTSD and BPD) so he knows I've got some issues. But I got stuff of my chest, he gave me some good advice (One of them was stay away from depressing/dark/morbid stuff, and to stay away from one particular subreddit. He doesn't know my account, just that I'm on Reddit) That lifted my mood for a few days, but now I'm back to this. And I keep putting myself down, which he's really not happy about.  And I just want to say sorry to him but I'm good at stopping that.  
Him and my family want me to go back to the Doctors, but I really do not. I've been in treatment for just under a quarter of my life, but I wasn't getting treatment for BPD, where they did offer me therapy for it, but I decided to get discharged instead because I was doing so well. FML </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not wrong, everyone should have a right to choose when they want to die. You might find the subreddit /r/sanctionedsuicide interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know pfft we don't have rights, we are just trying to pretend that we do! 
How dare we!  
I know that will instill some order but to make us really happy,  we should listen to Pharrell Williams,  that's just the latest song of brain washing, works for the rest of the population 
Oh silly me, I'm only 21, I don't have any opinions or anything till I'm 25...how stupid of me :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much, but a portable one. 
I'm ordering something else too for my camera and my parents won't check mine luckily, but me and my sister go swimming at east once a week so I can't cut. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's easier to hide, but a bit harder to look after.
To be honest I've only burnt a couple of times, I prefer cutting but burning is so much easier to hide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ordered a cautery pen, yay! :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them apply to me. I've had a really weird eating pattern since I was a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I feel that way, nearly every goddam day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/morbidquestions could help, but don't mention yourself,  refer in third person.  
There is also a website which has the statistics and effectiveness, but I can't mention it here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 12:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the UK, no one I know has a gun apart from one person but he'd all the way in London,  and I know roughly the area of where he lives. 
I don't have and ID, so I can't buy fertiliser and I don't know how to make explosives. 
Oh, and there's something called the Survival Insitinct. Look it up, it's really fucking annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20, 21 in 2 days. While I haven't cut in at least a year, and I've never really burnt myself either, I do take small overdoses and I hardly eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What on earth is a cautery?  
That looks like it could be satisfying. I WANT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say that really won't be severe enough to be admitted to hospital.   
It's really common for people to self harm and you'd have to be classed as an immediate danger to yourself.
I think the severity of cuts they would consider hospitalization is the very deep ones that go down to fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I didn't have thoughts to this extent when I was a kid, I had really bad nightmares and would beg for them to stop. But I'd say my first proper one was when I was 12.  
That was also just wanting for it all to stop as I was getting bullied,  but I was thinking it would be better if I disappeared.  
They were on and off, more on then off for years. I did go for a few weeks without them a few months ago and it just feel strange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Mum had untreated and undiagnosed BPD until back in 2012, and she has never, ever abused me or my sister.  
Agreed, we did have to be careful about stuff but she was a good parent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This also caused my C-PTSD. 
Sexual Abuse when I was 3 for a few months, and again through ages 15 to 20.  We also had to walk on eggshells around my Mum to avoid her reacting, as she had undiagnosed BPD due to a neglectful and emotionally abusive Mum who was also an alcoholic, she's had some sexual abuse too and my biological Dad was abusive.
And I was bullied ruthessly in school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have both of these diagnosis. 
I was 16 and got diagnosed with PTSD, Severe Depressional Episodes, Psychosis and Eating Disorder NOS.
A few months ago the diagnosis was changed to C-PTSD and BPD.  
I'd say that the BPD is more the emotional side, like mood swings and insecurity. My C-PTSD manifested like normal PTSD, with flashbacks, being overly anxious, but with the added symptoms of derealization/depersonalisation (Which overlaps with BPD) and hearing voices.
But I also thinks it really depends on the person and their individual symptoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 10:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/suicidemethods is banned and /r/sanctionedsuicide doesn't allow discussion of methods, but there's a couple of google groups but I don't know the names.  
www.lostallhope.com has all the statistics of the effectiveness, time and painfullness, but not how to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 10:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't go too deep! One-way ticket to Psyche if it happens too many times, luckily I never needed stiches. You can head to /r/selfharm for care techniques and advie, and /r/MadeOfStyrofoam  
takes it a lot more lightly, it's usally memes or anecdotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 09:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the person. My sister's boyfriend has had drug problems, problems at work and he's living in a neglectful household and he's not suicidal. He's happy, he gets stuff done and he just puts up with it.  
With me, I'd say I have no real problems apart from my mental health, and my most recent attempt was just under 2 weeks ago, and then you see those really happy kids in poverty in 3rd world countries. There is actually more mental illness in the 1stt world countries, where people have better quality of life.  
It all depends on the person and their perspective.  
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 09:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fast was the train going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 09:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a quote that someone on this subreddit made, I can't rerember who even if it was only a couple of days ago, but here it is.  
We may be catching the bus alone but at least we can walk to the station together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 09:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D:  
Gotta decapitate yourself, unless someones got a macabre sense of humour and carts around my head haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 08:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might not be here by the end of today but I can help for the time being :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 08:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Function properly.  
For me I can't escape it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 07:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough,  I'm usally very good at not violating the rules. I think in the 2 years I've been on reddit this is the 3rd or 4th post I've had removed :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 01:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a website called www.lostallhope.com  
It has lots of suicide stats, most painless is gun. But I'm in the UK so I don't get that luxury. I'd say the second is train, although scarier, but that's the method I've chosen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, it may seem scary but everything will be ok. You will learn the best ways to deal with this and if you work well with the professionals and tell them everything, and I mean EVERYTHING, they can help you in the best way.  
DBT is a great therapy, it has done my Mum wonders. It's very intensive and can be quite draining, but it's so effective and you will cope fine. And I'm sure the people in this subreddit can help with anything too. And I aso suggest looking up mindfullness too, could help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree it's fucked up, but at the bridge I was planning they'd keep an eye out for me because of last time when I got stopped. This is literally my only option. I'd rather not involve anyone else but no other methods are available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok fair I see your point.
What if they got hit by a train or it was a suicide in a public place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've found out that the Network Rail website in the UK, you can search for level crossings on! And it says how busy they are and the speed of the trains! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 10:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get any. And with one of my mental health issues, it's likely to make that way worse. And I get confused with bitcoins and I don't trust the darkweb not to be Law Enforcement.  
I'd love me some Xanax or Diazapam to take away some of the fear though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do the Police do with someones phone after they've died in a public place? Will they go through any accounts linked to it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a satantist either, I'm a nihilist, and I love Slipknot. They used to be one of my favorite bands, and I do love Black Metal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know some medication makes people have a very low sex drive, I'm not sure if it can be done naturally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if I get depressed anymore, but I'm certainly not enjoying myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat!  
I want to move out for College and come back on the weekends, so I'm living in the College dorms for the week. They won't let me, saying I can't look after myself properly and that I NEED to be at home otherwise I can't do the course!  
Like what the fuck, it's a least an hour bus journey :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What groups are they?  
You can PM me if it's breaking the rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't feel like I belong anywhere. I always feel like a black sheep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 10:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on meds for a few months, did help, but I stopped them cold turkey about 4 months ago, which you are not supposed to do. Did ok for another 3 months, and then I started going downhill, fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 10:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no responbilties or obligations too.  
The main thing which gets me through the day is music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 10:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this has been removed, but you might be able to ask at /r/morbidquestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 10:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not leaving a note. My family knows that my mental health isn't the best, but to them it seems alright at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 00:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was like that. They went away for a few months, but the past week they've crept back in. It's hell. I just want to make it stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to post here, but I don't cut anymore. It was somewhere to document it and to relate to people, but I didn't do it as deep as most of the others, I went for quantity. And some of the others intrigued me and it helped me not to cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always listen to music and walk quite briskly,  look at the fastest exits and something else which can work as a distraction is Pokemon Go, as it needs me to walk and it keeps me distracted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything to do with suicide and what causes mental health problems.  
I used to be into serial killers and school shootings,  as well as torture methods. But it's really about suicide now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm like 95 percent am, I would accept it but I'd still be a bit scared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, without so much of a second thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 12:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've honestly never tried it, but I've heard it's very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 12:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this done to me many times. It's hard. The thoughts that come with this, they can be overwhelming but you can cope with them. Grounding and distraction techniques can help.  
Remember: Your experiences do not define you as a person, they do not make or shape you. And most importantly, it's not your fault. It's NEVER your fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you would need more to kill you, that doesn't seem like enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, always either jumping or train. I gives me time to prepare and evaluate. More of the jumpers tend to regret it more then the people that jump in front of trains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't sleep that much anyway, I like sleeping but I can't because of racing thoughts and I tend to struggle more at night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried Seven Cups Of Tea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what you think really.
I'd say monitor the frequency and intensity. If it gets any worse or worrying I'd say talk about it, but it's great that you don't want to act.
If it gets overwhelming try some grounding techniques.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say that's entirety possible. I've been more suicidal then I've been in months, got the closest I've ever got to killing myself then got stopped by a complete fucking stranger last week.  
Anyway besides the point,  I have self harmed in the past but that's been like a year.   
Unless you count taking pills that aren't yours but it's only really a couple at a time and that's just really to relax me, they just send me to sleep and I've only done it twice in the past week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is me, right here. I said sorry like 3 times to my boyfriend after bringing up something he does which I don't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 11:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well maybe blah blah blah blah blah 
And doctor but blah blah.
Things will get better - (but they won't )

Every post and comment on here ever.

(If this isn't a joke post let me know and I'll delete this)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The luckiest form is death! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 09:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I actually have no idea why your getting hate for this post.  
Some of your others are a bit insulting, but you can make good points and you can be supportive, and this is one of those times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seen it before.  
I've been this way for years, nothings changing for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems fair to me. You should be able to die at any age, and if someone wants to die, let them.  
You might enjoy this subreddit called /r/sanctionedsuicide  
I'm quite active there, it's for people that do not want to live for various reasons and belive we should have a choice and it's for discussion of suicide with other people that understand the dilemma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old are you all and what is your reason for feeling the way you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 11:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20, so I think I'm one of the younger ones.  
I have mental health problems that I have had since age 12, I've got help in the past but they've never gone complety away.  
So what's the point if I'm always gonna need help? 
This has changed my philosophy to existential nihilism.   
And another question because I'm being nosy, music taste?  
Mine is Metal and some Rap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. 
It so frustrating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!
I always look at aftermaths of suicide or gifs/videos of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 17:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! I've got a very sick sense of humor and it can be silly too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I'm not the only one who noticed.  
I'm not sure why it is, I think they think the way we think, because it is different shouldn't be allowed.
And that we are selfish, haven't gave help a chance ect.
It's terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did actually mean Paramedics haha.  
Yeah it's about 6 hours away.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl actually but yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has more information on those methods too on that website. 
You have to be careful not to be spotted too, but I know a place near me where you can access the tracks via a slope, and it's not a station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either jumping or train.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had trouble so I've turned to a different method, I'm physically uncapable of doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has at least a 95% success rate.
I can't do it because I can't tie knots properly because of my dyspraxia.
There is a website with more information about different suicide methods called www.lostallhope.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
