<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 15:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have to upvote this. got so annoying for me that i ended up just playing ranked (my server doesn't have normal draft) even though i knew i was tired and tilting and^now^i'm^back^on^0lp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quinn's new blind mechanic feels 10x more frustrating and oppressive to play against than the old one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 08:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riot removed the old mechanic because they felt it to be a low counterplay frustration feature, but it feels like they replaced it with something that just makes that frustration worse? Previously the blind only stopped you from autoing, the new blind *still* stops you from autoing because unless the Quinn player is an idiot they're not going to remain in your vision range, so you can't click on them. But now you can't even use targeted abilities, aim skillshots, anticipate incoming skillshots or abilities or get a feel for what your team is doing and hers is around you (which arguably makes this one of the most powerful forms of CC as even when you're stunned, you can anticipate what's coming and make decisions as to your next move accordingly)...or do anything really, until it wears off (at least in the case of Graves's smokescreen you can walk out of it unless you are chain cc'd). It's extremely frustrating to play against and I'm not sure what Riot was thinking when they took away the old blind for the reasons stated and then replaced it with this. 

I understand that it's in the form of an avoidable skillshot so that exists as counterplay, but the old blind was too so what's Riot's logic in saying that that was unhealthy to the game and this isn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 09:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that low elo games tend to be messy bloodfests with a lot of kills because of the way people greed and bloodthirst - it's actually not that hard to stack devourer in low elo by ganking or just playing in the same way a low elo ganking jungler would do. That's why it's so strong in low elo. Best way to balance it would be to remove devourer stacking off kills altogether and make it a purely farm stacking item, enforcing the "farm for your reward, punish the guy for farming by ganking early game" playstyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 04:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah true, her win rate might go down with duskblade's launch we'll see. I still don't think she's as vulnerable in laning phase as she's said to be though, people who run a defensive summoner and know how to abuse her range and manage the wave won't be overextending or susceptible to ganks too easily unless the enemy can well coordinate dives. In lategame teamfights maybe she can be picked off but the general Lux pattern seems to be to just stand way back and poke until something worthwhile hits. It's hard to get in and assassinate her without it being a 1v5 suicide mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lux currently feels like old Nidalee to play against. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 03:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how they used to say "it doesn't matter how many thousand Qs she misses, it's the one she hits" about Nidalee before they reworked her and she was unanimously considered one of the most obnoxious champions to play against? Same thing goes for Lux right now (this is speaking as someone who both plays against her and abuses the freelo when I do get her) - you can miss all your Qs but the nature of her combo and scaling is that the moment she hits one on you once she's level 6, that's the lane lost, or later in the game, the entire game lost due to the long as hell death timers. She just seems way too low risk high reward right now, hence the high win rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 13:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryze used to be even more braindead than Annie before the rework, all his abilities being targetted. That said she still would have been a better choice since learning how to burst and fire at least some skillshots is the core of playing pretty much any mage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
