<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5311</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made my first book, i think it turned out alright for a first try </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When sewing signatures into a text block(I've been using the kettle stitch if that's important), how can I keep the spine flat? 

The signatures start jutting out toward the front the further into the middle of the book they are, and that makes the spine arch inward. 

Any tips on how to make that NOT happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like the name is written on a piece of scotch tape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The earth Barry is in now, after he returns from flashpoint, isn't earth 1, it's earth 19 or whatever number you wanna give it. Same with earth 2, only its turning point in the timelines was way earlier. 

Earth 1 and earth 2 in the show could've both been the exact same earth 200 years ago, but in earth 1 Abraham Lincoln got shot at a play on Tuesday, but in earth 2 he got shot at home on Thursday, and because of that one change, everything is different now, although still the same in many ways. Both earths still continue to exist, neither knowing there's a different one.

Same thing with earth 1 and earth 19, except the timelines are just now changing instead of 200 years ago.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time changes don't affect any other earths that aren't involved, because a new earth/reality exists for every decision. That was confirmed when earth 2 Harry and Jesse came back right after flashpoint happened, and everything was different for them just like it was for Barry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 01:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made an educational infographic for anyone confused

http://i.imgur.com/kpFFxPe.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 01:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, just ended up in a different timeline that he thinks is the same because he never went back in time and changed stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz in this timeline, he didn't go back to flashpoint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 07:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think that Nicolas cage played both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flash and Arrow this week: "wtf Barry you can't just go back in time like it's nothing" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 07:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legends: "OH let's go back in time 5 times further than Barry has gone and kidnap an alien"

*Literally everybody in the room* "aw yiss time travel is so cool let's do this" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a few, but they can get pretty expensive, especially with huge prints </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't charge, but I'm not quite sure how to scale without losing its look. When I vectorize things to scale, it does it in such a way that it adds strokes to it, alot like a painting looks.

But I'm not sure how, if it's possible, to restore it back to a photographic look once it's full size </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a life size(105"x72") print file of Vigo in case anyone wants it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took some screenshots from the movie and measured the painting against Peter MacNicol's height, got a good size for it, then I took [trekkie313's high-res artwork of the painting from deviantart](http://trekkie313.deviantart.com/art/Vigo-The-Carpathian-123351887), vectorized it, and scaled it up to fit my size.

My next plan is to somehow print it onto canvas, and either go over it with oil paint, or just brush a bunch of mod podge on it to give it texture, then stretch it and frame it.

[Imgur link of a lower quality jpg](http://i.imgur.com/ErN9awd.jpg)

[Pdf for printing](https://pixeldra.in/u/H0wVgg)

[Illustrator file for editing](https://pixeldra.in/u/nD7v9B) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on mobile and wasn't able to link anything or edit, so i just deleted it and reposted it with links and good formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life size(105"x72") print file of Vigo the Carpathian from Ghostbusters 2, just in case anyone's interested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took some screenshots from the movie and measured the painting against Peter MacNicol's height, got a good size for it, then I took [trekkie313's high-res artwork of the painting from deviantart](http://trekkie313.deviantart.com/art/Vigo-The-Carpathian-123351887), vectorized it, and scaled it up to fit my size.

My next plan is to somehow print it onto canvas, and either go over it with oil paint, or just brush a bunch of mod podge on it to give it texture, then stretch it and frame it.

[Imgur link of a lower quality jpg](http://i.imgur.com/ErN9awd.jpg)

[Pdf for printing](https://pixeldra.in/u/H0wVgg)

[Illustrator file for editing](https://pixeldra.in/u/nD7v9B) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proud of you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atlantean, from the Disney Atlantis movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 02:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad i could help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like to write in ancient or fictional languages. Happy Thanksgiving! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 01:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy thanksgiving, in Norse runes, Atlantean, and Tengwar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 01:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I burned my foot with soup and now the scar looks like Abe Lincoln </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 01:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was enough light coming in from the lights outside, it's on a pretty busy road. We kept the lights off and parked in the back on the off chance that Sheila would drive by so she wouldn't see us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started watching Gotham and I didn't know Ian was in it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea, I'm assuming so, but he at least got a pretty good scare and probably won't be doing that again anytime soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got handcuffed in an alley at gunpoint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the title is slightly clickbaity, but hey it happened

Also I'm back for a new episode of the locksmith adventures yay

So our story begins a couple days ago, a guy comes into the shop, he's an old family friend, so we know him. He explains the situation, which goes a little like this:

Friend, who I'll call Bruce, went into business a few years ago. His business philosophy was that no matter how bad times were for people, liquor stores always do well. So he partnered up with one of his friends, we'll call her Sheila, and opened a liquor store.

Business was good for a couple years ago, but then Bruce found out that Sheila was embezzling money and gambling it away at a crazy rate, and they were losing a buttload of money. So he decides that it's time to change the locks on the store and keep her out(after lawyering up of course, this is all legal at this point).

So he asks us to come do it that night, but at like 1am, after they close and she's had plenty of time to leave. So here comes the fun.

1am comes along, I get there and meet him in the back alley of the storefront, and he lets me in to start pulling the locks off. I start at the front door and work my way back, but what neither of us realized is that one of the young employees decided to stay late and invite one of his lady friends over to have some fun in the back room.

Employee hears someone come in and start messing with the doors, with all the lights off, and he pulls the silent alarm.

Wonderful.

We don't know this, and I keep working on the doors.

I get to the last one, on the back alley door by where I'm parked, and as I'm taking it apart I see flashing lights and hear sirens. 4 cop cars block the alley and 6 cops get out with guns drawn, telling me to get on the ground.

And just a little tidbit, I'm a concealed carry holder just in case stuff goes down that might require it, so I have a gun on my hip at this time.

I put my hands up and they come and hold me down and put handcuffs on me, while I'm trying to tell them I've got a gun on me so that I don't get shot. 

After a few minutes of them talking to the employee, Bruce, and me, they figure out that I'm a locksmith, it's all legal and good, and they let us continue and apologize for the trouble.

That was fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither does his lamp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We sell locks. Not lamps. Locks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy today was a fun day at work

So the lunch hour is usually pretty busy at the shop, people coming in on their breaks to get keys and junk. Today was pretty slow, then right at noon people started flooding in. 

It was one right after the other, then we finally got to the last guy in line, and as I was making his keys, another guy walked in holding a big broken ceramic lamp.

I call my dad from the back to have him help the guy while I'm finishing the first guy's keys. It goes something like this:

Dad: "Hi, what can I do for you?"

Lamp Guy: "Yes, my wife was taking out Christmas decorations, and we were going to use this lamp, but the mice chewed through the cord, and I need a new lamp"

Me, my dad, and the old guy that I was helping are all just kinda looking at each other 

Dad: "I'm sorry, you need a new lamp?"

Lamp Guy: "Yes, the mice chewed the cord so I need a new one. And some light bulbs too"

Dad: "Sir, I'm a locksmith, I sell locks and keys here, not lamps. You can try the hardware store up the road though"

Lamp Guy: "I already went there, they can't fix it, this is my last place to check"

At this point the old guy that I was helping first is done, but he's still here listening to it and we're all trying to figure out what's going on in this lampy's head

Old Guy: "if you go down to the hardware store you can buy an extension cord and just splice the ends together, it's not a hard fix"

Lamp Guy: "But I already went there and they couldn't fix it"

Old Guy: "Well you can still get the parts and just do it yourself"

Me and my dad both just sit back and let these two guys argue it out for 10 minutes while they both repeat the same things back and forth to each other until they decide to take it outside for a few more minutes.

When they left we just kinda looked at each other like "wtf just happened" and went on with our day.

I wonder if he ever got his lamp fixed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
