<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 19:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using this, haha nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 19:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep telling myself this, haha! Go us for no life and way to busy! :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 19:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le Miserable... so epic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obligatory [*grumpy cat face*](http://i.imgur.com/KPbsUQw.jpg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bwahaha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome!  It shall be my next fb pic haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe gotta love the classic and that cartoon is awesome, I have a similar one set as my fb pic atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that is epic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir Grumpy cat I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This... is awesome haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rofl I am totally with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Thank you everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to let this sub know that not only have I immensely enjoyed gifting people things, the small gifts that have recently been gifted to me have helped me through my long weeks.

I am a full time employee with the State and I've just recently gone back to school full time to finish out my undergraduate degree that I failed to get before enlisting in the USAF.  Being that I have absolutely no free time and am constantly busy the small acts of kindness this sub has shown me brightens my day and makes me smile.

So thank you RAoA!  You are all awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Contest] Grumpy Cat! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a slight fixation on finding as many grumpy cat pictures as possible (which I use as my facebook profile picture).  

The contest is simple, find me what you think is the best grumpy cat picture and I will select 3 random individuals who post to gift!

Let the best grumpy cat win!

EDIT:  Contest has ended I am selecting winners now, sorry for the delay I was at work!

EDIT:  Congratz to jemiglio, xX_Justin_Xx, and watsoned!  Thank you all for the awesome submissions I now have a lot of pictures to use hehe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 18:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So awesome, thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 09:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He said, "Paint me like your French girls" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 00:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, Statikk Shiv is superior to PD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 19:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I have managed to carry myself from Silver III to Silver I using nothing but GP Top.  My build is Philo Stone - Boots I - Avarice Blade - Boots II - Statikk Shiv - Icebourne Gauntlet - Warmogs - BotRK 

Using this its almost impossible to be countered in lane as if you can't win the harass war you just farm with Parley combined with GP10 items and quints and you still farm money.  Even if the enemy stacks armor against you in lane generally by the time I make it to my Statikk Shiv they underestimate that 100 magic dmg that it procs.

In most cases so far by mid game I'm a terror that peels well, ults all over the map as needed, and can rush through a team to the carry or soak large amounts of dmg for the team.

This is simply how I've been playing him and its worked for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 23:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huzzah I'm glad you like them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 22:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes for this since this comment clarified instantly what I was having trouble grasping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes for use of the word salutations!  Welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings and welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 16:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've decided to make this a bi-weekly thing when I get paid.  So who knows who will be next! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIFTED] cmd405 Because its Thursday, I got paid, and the random wishlist said so! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 16:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 23:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm pretty certain a girl could do everything except tell me flat out that she likes me and I'd miss it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 23:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huzzahs for everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 22:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 22:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thought is what counts, I think I shall have to go buy some myself here on break :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 22:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes for Huzzah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 22:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel for you silverblaze92!  Until recently (just over 2 months now) I was single and had been for over 3 years after I filed for divorce.  

I met my current SO through a mutual friend and we all went to see Skyfall together.  Being the oblivious and socially inept individual I am I failed to notice the signs and didn't even ask for her number after the movie.  My friend being a bit more perceptive, called me the next day and said, "Here's her number, you should call her". The rest, as they say, is history.

I know how hard it is to put yourself out there so upvotes to you sir for making the effort! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
