<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8373</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm in Southern California.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 5'5" and a half, with a 29" inseam. I think it'll be on the small side, but it should work. 

If it's too small, I figured I'd be able to sell it. I'm located in Southern California, so hopefully somebody will want it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seller said they would sell it for $140 since they're about an hour drive away. I know the bike is in pretty high up there in the Centurion family.

Does anyone have some insight? Should I buy this weekend?

Also, please let me know if there is a more appropriate subreddit for this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found an early 1980s Centurion Comp TA for $160. Should I pull the trigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about buying it just to try it out. If it's too small, I might try and sell it as is to see how much I can get for it. Or I could try and fix it up a little and sell it. Not sure what to do exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 48cm. I'm 5'5" and a half, with a 29" inseam. I think it'll be on the smaller side for me, but it should work. (I hope) 
If it is too small, I figure I can sell it for a profit.  How much do you think it's worth?

I'm new to the bike community so I'm not too knowledgeable! Sorry about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seller said they would sell it for $140 since they're about an hour drive away. I know the bike is in pretty high up there in the Centurion family.  

Does anyone have some insight? Should I buy this weekend? 

Also, please let me know if there is a more appropriate subreddit for this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found an early 1980s Centurion Comp TA for $160. Should I pull the trigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice. I think I'm going to go with LED, that's what I've been hearing from other people I've talked to as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on first lighting kit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to own my first lighting kit for mostly documentary work and some commercial. As of right now, I don't do much feature work, but I'd like to buy something versatile just in case I do any other types of films.

Budget: $300-400 USD

Biggest question: Tungsten or LED?

I found a used kit on Craigslist for 3 Lowel Totas, stands, case, umbrellas, extra globes, and power cords for $350. (They said they're open to negotiation)

I could go that route, or I could buy a new LED kit. I've done some research, and it seems like my biggest problem with tungsten is high heat, which might not be ideal for interviews. Whereas with cheap LEDs, they might not produce accurate colors.

Is there an obvious answer here that I'm not seeing? I don't have much experience with tungsten lights, none with Totas actually. I'm used to using LEDs and Kino Flos. Does anyone have recommendations on kits in my price range? Or pros and cons of each type of light in the type of work I'll be doing?

Thanks in advance!

Also, please let me know if there's a more appropriate subreddit to post this to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on first lighting kit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to own my first lighting kit for mostly documentary work and some commercial. As of right now, I don't do much feature work, but I'd like to buy something versatile just in case I do any other types of films. 

Budget: $300-400 USD

Biggest question: Tungsten or LED?

I found a used kit on Craigslist for 3 Lowel Totas, stands, case, umbrellas, extra globes, and power cords for $350. (They said they're open to negotiation)

I could go that route, or I could buy a new LED kit. I've done some research, and it seems like my biggest problem with tungsten is high heat, which might not be ideal for interviews. Whereas with cheap LEDs, they might not produce accurate colors. 

Is there an obvious answer here that I'm not seeing? I don't have much experience with tungsten lights, none with Totas actually. I'm used to using LEDs and Kino Flos. Does anyone have recommendations on kits in my price range? Or pros and cons of each type of light in the type of work I'll be doing?

Thanks in advance!

Also, please let me know if there's a more appropriate subreddit to post this to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, not really. I film here and there, but it's hard since I work full time! I'm trying though. I've got a couple clips. I've been considering just posting them on here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular Speed - https://streamable.com/sk37 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Yeah I'll post it in a separate comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A kickflip I did yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is $350 for 3 used Lowell Totas with stands and bag a good deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 04:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a kit on Craigslist for 3 used Lowell Totas, with stands and a bag. 
I just recently decided to invest in my own lighting kit and I'm a little overwhelmed. 

I mainly do documentary and commercial work, and a solid lighting kit for interviews is crucial for me. I have worked with other lights on other projects, but I figured owning lights might be a different ballgame than using/renting other people's gear. Do you have any recommendations for a kit between $300-500 USD? Also, should I be looking for fluorescent, tungsten, or led? 

Does anyone have experience with the Totas? From what I've read, I heard they put out a lot of light and heat. Haven't read anything about their durability, however. 

Please let me know if I should be posting this on a more appropriate subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't get USB bluetooth transmitter to work with headset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USB bluetooth transmitter: http://targus.com/us/usb-bluetooth-adapter
Headset: https://www.amazon.com/Creative-WP-450-Bluetooth-Headphone-Invisible/dp/B005XPFYBM

I tried for about an hour yesterday installing different drivers and I could not get these to work together. :(

I tried installing Targus's software (http://targus.com/form/download.aspx?region=7 sku=ACB10US1), but that didn't work.  I also installed the WIDCOMM bluetooth software from Broadcom's website found here: https://www.broadcom.com/support/bluetooth

Is there a certain order I should be installing things? 
When I go to Devices and Printers  Add a Device, the headset popped up the first time I tried to pair it, but I still couldn't get it to work. Now, the headset doesn't pop up at all even after removing the device.  

Does anybody have any experience with this? Or know of a guide that could show me how to do it? I was getting really frustrated last night and would really appreciate some help!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy sold it to someone else anyway. Thanks for the reply! I'll keep searching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Needless to say, but..." 

If it's needless to say, then why do people still say it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to go check it out, and as I was waiting in the parking lot, I see a guy with the bike next to his truck. I went up to him and he told me that he just bought the bike from the guy. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About to go check out a 1975 Schwinn Continental for $165. Is that a good price? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://santabarbara.craigslist.org/bik/5689752706.html

Hi,

I'm very new to biking and I'm looking for an old bike to ride around for fun on the weekends. The seller is asking for $165 for this bike. What would be a fair price?

I'm about to go check out the bike in 30 minutes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got them with an extra 20% off so they came out to $69 with tax and free shipping. I'd say it's worth it for the price.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 01:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cole Haan Giraldo Cap Toes ($80): http://www.colehaan.com/giraldo-cap-toe-oxford-british-tan/C20087.html?dwvar_C20087_color=British%20Tan#cgid=outlet_clearance start=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 05:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish mine looked that clear. Thanks for the advice though. I'll keep that in mind when I redo them next time. How close were you spraying on the second and third coat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 04:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restored my 08 3's headlights this weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/XudGW

After being inspired by /u/kvior1 and /u/TeKiwiBird, I decided to try ChrisFix's method for restoring headlights. I spent about $20-25 USD on the supplies and about 1.5 hours total sanding and spraying both my headlights. 

As you can see in the pictures, my passenger side headlight wasn't looking too great but it looked much better afterwards! However, my headlights still aren't crystal clear. I believe this was either an issue of me not applying the clear coat correctly or not sanding enough after the clear coat had dried.  (I only sanded until the headlight was smooth and stopped because I was afraid of going overboard.) 

In the end, I'm still very satisfied with how they turned out and will do a better job next time! I'm curious to see how long they will last before yellowing/oxidizing again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 21:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll create a post with pictures. I wasn't sure if the sub would be interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to try this method this weekend on my 08 Mazda 3. My headlights look very bad right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 16:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, sorry to hear that! That sounds terrible. 
My 08 3 with 105K miles did the same thing (AT light and limp mode). I did a ton of research and figured it was probably the TCM. Somebody on this subreddit mentioned they got theirs replaced under the PZEV warranty so I took it in to the dealer and they diagnosed the TCM as the problem. Luckily, they had one in stock so it was fixed in the same day. That fixed the problem immediately. Hopefully they have one in stock for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! I'm just going to follow the guide on the Mazda forums, except I'm going to use 6 quarts of synthetic instead of 3 quarts of cheap stuff and 3 quarts of synthetic.  I still haven't decided on which brand to use though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 23:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I forgot to specify the last time the ATF has been changed. In the past, the ATF was changed at 30k and 61k miles at the dealer and I'm now at 108k miles. I bought the car last summer at 101k miles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 01:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it necessary to drain 100% of the fluid and refill? I still haven't decided if I want to buy 9 quarts and keep draining it all out until it's not brown anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transmission Fluid Choices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting ready to drain and fill my 2008 MZ3 S GT transmission fluid in a couple weeks and I'm wondering what ATF you have used and which fluids are M-V equivalents.  I've been reading and a popular choice seems to be Amsoil ATF and Mobil 1 ATF.  

Does anybody have any experience or knowledge on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to cross platform PC and Xbox One in a private match? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to figure this out with a friend who has RL for Xbox One.  I keep reading mixed answers everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to try cleaning my throttle body soon. I'm also experiencing this weak start (sometimes dying) unless I press the throttle a little bit.  My 2008 3 has about 108K miles on it so I'm nervous to see how much carbon build up there is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought my 08 3 S GT last July in California for $7800 with 100K miles and a set of enkei wheels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
