<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> join the club https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4jnocj/i_saw_your_burger_king_hotdog_and_your_bk_philly/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I saw your Burger King Hotdog AND your BK Philly Cheeseburger and RAISE YOU a BK Breakfast Burrito..or something... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 14:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe he said he was in the decompression chamber for 60 hours. This was from the Youtube video linked above: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CsZsHHOQx-Q feature=youtu.be t=143
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 02:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the one! I didnt say I wanted to hire him as a babysitter for my toddler. In my opinion, he's led, and continues to lead an interesting life. He created the first computer antivirus software when he was young (McAfee Associates, maybe you've heard of it), sold his company for millions, and has been traveling the world doing whatever he damn well pleases for the last thirty years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 02:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find John McAfee very interesting. I would pay good money for a John McAfee memoir...and I would definitely download a McAfee movie.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Douglas (the Antman character) could totally play John McAfee in the McAfee Bio... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 01:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 14:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely a Corinthians fan...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First two projects after teaching herself to crochet. Best girlfriend ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good site! thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vacationing Couple Discover, Remove, and Reverse Engineer an ATM Skimmer. Best article on skimmers I've seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 00:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally 12 minutes of some guy talking and 30 seconds of poor-quality cellphone video of the actual flight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ...because A Boy Named Sue was already taken.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 00:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the most fascinating AMA's I've read. Thank you for your time. My question is: Is it dangerous inside the windmill? Are all of the working parts of the machine exposed? Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend's eight-year-old daughter winning at hangman...in a reddit sort of way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 11:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am surprised no one has mentioned Cerberus. Its an anti-theft app, but has some other uses if you're creative. It lets you find and track your phone, take pics with front and read cameras, capture screenshots, list text messages and call logs, record audio on the target phone, open a terminal on the target phone. Basically, anything you can do with your phone it lets you do remotely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 03:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate to hear this. I was an early adopter and have used my wallet card almost daily. This is going to be a huge inconvenience for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 17:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a compatible router install DDWRT. It's great at  displaying realtime bandwidth usage for individual devices...plus a LOT more. It's free and very easy to install.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 17:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second time in my life I've heard that phrase. The first was in Jimmy Lerner's book, You've Got Nothing Coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know or have had experiences with someone like the dipshit in the back seat. Fortunately for us he'll probably be in jail within the next five years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is, BY FAR, the stupidest one there. Seeing the driver stomp the shit out of him would have made my day. I like to think thats how it ended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay Porn Actor or PetSmart Cat Toy? SFW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 13:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full view jpg http://imgur.com/CtL3p44  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 12:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> simply change the file extension from MKV to MP4. Seriously. Try it.

We have a Sony TV that doesnt play MKV's, but a lot of the movies and TV that I "obtain" is in MKV format.  I am familiar with video converting, but only as a last resort since I learned that when going from MKV to MP4 most of the time I can simply change the file extension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I actually thought I might die watching this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 17:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATE: incoherent man identified as....John McAfee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 20:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crappy situation for you both. I have been on both ends of that scenario. I had to fire a fellow IT professional and was forced to think about it from the malicious point of view- how would I get into this network and screw it up if I wanted? I was also fired from a great sysadmin job about ten years ago. Although I had no malicious intent I knew exactly what precautions my boss was taking probably even before I was fired...and it hurt. The loss of trust is what hurt the most...besides my wallet. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change your IP address, but remember he if he can connect to your wireless network then changing the IP wont help. Change your wireless passwords and the L/P to the wireless AP's. Change your RDP port(s). Look around for any common remote management software. Maybe run Wireshark for a while and examine the traffic report.  To thwart social engineering attempts, make sure all staff is aware that he is no longer employed... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 13:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gay, but twenty bucks is twenty bucks... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 20:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CEO takes over. Increases price by thirty-thousand percent. Go America! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 13:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty soon you'll be saying they should have their own schools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 12:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First laugh of the morning. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 12:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! Absolutely. As I come to the end of a book I find myself hesitating and procrastinating to complete it just for that reason. Its like that world will be gone soon and i will have to say goodbye to all of these characters I have some to know and love. It leaves an empty space inside me. I have tried to explain this to my friends, but they have no idea what I am talking about. Its good to know I am not the only one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 12:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> worked for me. Thanks for the info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 12:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 12:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cleaner is NOT to be trusted. I have a folder where I keep APKs to test. It wants to delete those. I have used EX File Explorer since my first Android phone many years ago. I was their biggest fan. Now I am looking for an alternative. Its too bad the devs dont read/listen to the user comments on their Play page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 12:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT, I thought I was the only one who did this! Awesome! The last one wanted me to download GoToMeeting so that he could access my machine. From past experience I had already setup files and folders on the desktop with titles like "credit card numbers" and "account passwords" and "pictures of credit cards" and "banking info" etc. I think I probably need a hobby also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 00:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The secret is this: there is no secret.  I am 40 years old since my late twenties I have been waking up between 4-430am every morning, weekdays AND weekends, WITHOUT AN ALARM CLOCK, and I love it. My secret is this- once I realize I'm awake I IMMEDIATELY get up out of bed and start my day NO MATTER HOW FEEL, and especially if I dont want to. I like to remind my body that I am the one in control. One of the reasons I think this works is because I absolutely LOVE life and am excited to see what the new day is going to bring! Anything could happen today! I could write a reddit post that maybe read by 5-10 people today or maybe I will meet someone new and funny or maybe I will make my coworkers laugh..or maybe it'll be something bigger. So, my answer is love life, be genuinely curious and excited for each day!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 02:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shentel in Radford City, VA does the same thing. I assumed I had unlimited internet. I woke up one morning and was browsing reddit, clicked an imgur link, but a Shentel page was displayed instead informing me that I was at a certain percentage of my monthly cap.  A cap that I had never heard of. That happened 6 months ago and has been happening every month since. It never happened before and we have had them for years. Shentel claims its to ensure that everyone has consistent bandwidth. Bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm off chicken for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So definitely not a brain. Also, that dark-colored protrusion was embedded in both halves. It's hard and flexible. Weird.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, Bear Grylls. Nice try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid to say. I think that would violate Reddit's rules and will earn me a ban. I will say that it was a grocery store chicken dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just became a vegetarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just threw-up in my mouth. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSFL Chicken brain I found fried into my chicken dinner today. At least I think it's a chicken brain. OMG I hope it isn't a rat brain! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 02:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> related events? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 16:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 23:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the best audiobooks I have ever read (yes I use the term 'read' to describe listening to an audiobook). The narrator, RC Bray, really does a great job painting the scenes. This is a great time to get an Audible account! I have been a member for about a year and have never regretted it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 23:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here. I also bought a Prius, but then I got tired of having my ass handed to me everyday on the freeway. So now I take the bus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 23:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit-on-a-shingle for breakfast again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I met you in the rain on the last day of 1972 (craigslist) xpost from hackernews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 13:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 17:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't exactly NOT work as a buttplug, I suppose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 12:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats BRILLIANT, and I WILL be doing it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 12:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. My bad. RIP, you big, beautiful, sausage-fingered man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hilarious. My junk looks like a Sesame Street puppet that left PBS, developed a crack happy, and turned to Fraggle Rock porn for extra cash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious either way...and a bit sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am painfully aware. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 06:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me of a story an ER nurse told me once. A gentleman walked into the ER holding a weight-plate with a coat draped over it in front of him. His penis was stuck, erect, in a 25lb plate with a round hole in the center, used for weightlifting on a barbell. The gentleman's penis had become erect once inserted into the hole and had gotten stuck in the plate. It was standard sized, not olympic, I assume. Anyway, the ER staff worked for a while trying to lube-up his penis, then trying to encourage the blood to flow out of his erect penis, but it was no use. Eventually, a surgeon "filleted his penis with a blade" to drain the blood. I will never forget that story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 05:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I've put my dick in it! It pinches and doesnt really stretch.  So thats a problem. I ended up taking it apart and taping the eyes to my cock.  Just in time for Halloween!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 05:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know why that wasnt my first thought. I honestly immediately thought "If I can squeeze that on to my dick....."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 05:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean currently or in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 05:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muffet. i LOVE IT!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 05:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...something like that, yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...thanks man. We have our moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure there's a joke here. My wife gave me the pack of Finger Spies that she picked up at the Dollar Store. When she handed them to me I said "Oh you know what I'm doing with these, right?" She replied, "Sadly, I know EXACTLY what you're going to do with them!" Without actually saying so, we were both referring to me placing the Finger Spies onto my penis and taking pics. Just like I did with the tiny top hot I found in the floor of the public library. Long story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! I'll use it to hypnotize her and have my way with her! Bill Cosby would be proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am awaiting permission to bring out the porn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shes something else....never met anyone like her before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL...thats perfect! Upvoted and send you some reddit gold. I'm not sure what its used for, but that was hilarious to me. Thanks for the laugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> autocorrect changes everything to dicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 04:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is crazy huge. It almost looks like one of the smaller 7.5oz Sprite cans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...my cocks got nothing on Edna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont even have to ask nice....she's into it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gachupito! Love it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If those eyes could talk... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUDE...NOT COOL...Hilarious, but still not cool. Couldnt you just say "penis"? Why does it have to be "small penis"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, EXACTLY! I cant believe no one else has posted that yet. Cock-eyed. Upvoted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd upvote the shit out of this comment if I could. Hilarious!  Also, no I am not Jared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, had it since June 30th and it really is the best phone I have ever had.  Its also the biggest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious! Upvoted! Also, does anyone know where I can register to be a sex offender? It looks like thats where I'm headed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They came from the Dollar Store, but they're available on Amazon also.  http://www.amazon.com/Finger-Spies-Colors-May-Vary/dp/B003F2OP3S
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted the Amazon link a few times. Just search the page for Amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah...uh...must be different than the ones I have. These things are GI-NORMOUS!...I'm talking the size of a bracelet! Yep, thats it....a bracelet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She just told me that when she saw it hanging in the store she knew exactly what I was going to do with it: put it on my cock, photograph it, and upload it to reddit. Shes half pre-cog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had myself a looksee.  I have never seen so many cocks in my life....all dressed up with nowhere to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but do you mean wearing them on my face? My wrist? Elbow?.........shoulder?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that was specific....lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I see that. I've created a monster...might-as-well introduce him to my peeps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bet you tell all the gals that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO....upvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit man. I wasn't expecting this. Ok...I've been responding to that request like this: if I can come up with something that isn't too NSFW and something she approves of I will post it. Standby all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol...no promises, but if she'll let me post something that's semi-tasteful and not too NSFW I'll do it. I'm thinking....a pic of her body with the googly-eyes somewhere in the background and out-of-focus, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, not since the fishing trip, but it was really just a big misunderstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm....a set of strategically placed googly eyes on my cock, pubes styled just the right way (think Michael Chiklis, but with less hair), and a cape. Epic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, do you want to see my penis because you're genuinely interested in me OR because of the circus-freak-man-with-smallest-dick factor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very tempting.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted the Amazon link here in the comments, but she bought it at the Dollar Store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted for "googly vag"...! That's now her contact name in my phone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the one. I'm not allowed anywhere near children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, they come in 2 convenient sizes: "aint it cute" and "grower, not a shower." Unfortunately, mine was the former. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drawings are HILARIOUS! Strangely, there isn't a drawing of how to properly fit it to an adult penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good observation! But the bird was for my wife. Posting on reddit was secondary. No offense fellow Redditors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, yeah, I totally didn't check the source url. I just googled Andre the giant + ring + egg and hastily posted the link. Good fact-checking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOXXED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try guy-who-wants-to-see-my-wife's-pooper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
