<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject251</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I'm getting it in. Should be several other players w 10 BBs on the other tables to bust some bubbles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that his range is super wide.  I disagree that vs a described villain a 4b w JT is good.  This guy sounds like a typical passive live fish who is stuck and wants to see flops w tons of holdings.  I think he flats way more than he shoves or folds and that puts us in really weird flop spots if we whiff and he can play the hand in position.  I don't see the need to go nuts against this guy who is going to pay off your value hands when you make them anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hero gets it all in vs fishy villain w top set and wonders if he played the hand correctly. 
r/poker everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea agree, I was just making a point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would expect these players to be flatting really wide and seeing a ton of flops.  3b could mean anything from 55+ to ATss+ imo...

I expect them to call way more than I expect a shove and I expect them to fold less than both of those options - again, this is strictly based on hero's read and what he has mentioned about villains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea but were talking about villains who are "bleeding and just having fun," who I doubt are there to fold after they 3b.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4b JTss it pretty damn bad imo, especially OOP.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  I don't see him open/calling w A9 as described.  This type of player prob folds 66 and A6 as well.  AQ/AK is most likely or air trying to make you fold pairs under Ax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure he has AK a lot of the time here too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You leave whenever the hell you want. Most players just play until their big blind and leave before they have to post again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like a fairly straightforward fold to me without any reads. We literally beat none of his value hands. 

Also, why are we betting the river? We never get called by worse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 00:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As played this is never a fold. Just flat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool report. I'd love to make that trek some day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 01:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I'm drunken that I thought I was  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 23457
How is this a question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try 2 new beers every week for a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> usually 3 to 4 buyins.  Try to stay at close to max stack.  ex) if playing 1/3 and I fall to like $200 I will top off to $300. 

Typically I will buy $300 in red and bring like 5-6 black in my pocket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> top up w 5's from your pocket.... Why not just get a handful of green or a few black?  Also wow @ waiting till down to $25.

Your preference at the end of the day, but seems strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 02:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol @ flatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raising hand 1 is suicide imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> overlay is not the same as HUD in poker terms.  I assume you mean HUD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> V1 should be folding imo but he's a drooler so there's that... I'd rather be in his spot so I can just fold the turn lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Sharpton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple vs PC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh gotcha. Misunderstood your post as you thought we should bet larger to fold out small FDs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tank jammed which in looking back I think is a mistake. V1s range was just too all over the place for me to fold. This guy is the type of dude to do this w J2 on occasion so I figured I'd get it in to at the very least scoop the side pot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your turn analysis is kinda weird... I want medium fd to call the turn.  I have good trips and 2nd NFD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> villain 1 has Q4cc and Villain 2 has ATcc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if bb pops to 30 we just fold without much thought to it.  Torching $4 by limp folding is fine by me in this spot most of the time. Tossing away 2 bb is sorta trivial to me when were playing in a game that is being played way bigger post flop anyway.  I think BB and UTG are more than happy to see a flop multiway for cheap (yet still inflated pot due to straddle). 

Open mucking here just seems so nitty... If this is your rule of thumb then what range of hands do you complete here with?  Are you really only ever raising or folding?  
Appreciate the comments, I'm not trying to come off confrontational either - this conversation is a healthy one and I look forward to hearing different thought processes.  That's why I posted in the first place, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell of a post. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friday's have been really solid too. Just sayin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like I said I considered a squeeze, but decided not to for the reasons you mentioned.  Being OOP is especially really bad and I doubt a squeeze to 35 takes it down w these particular players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um this is never a fold... not a chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to work at a pizza place.  They occasionally would cater weddings and events (not with pizza, but other nicer options).  Anyway one of the items was a large tray/tin of buffalo wings.  I saw the owner drop the buffalo wings on the floor of the kitchen.  He scooped them all back into the tray and gave everyone the "don't you dare fucking say anything" look.  

No one said anything, and out the door they went.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just visit this page:
http://treehousebrew.com/on-tap/

They update it regularly.  When the beer is done canning they will update the page with limits, price, and a description of that brew.  

Wednesdays are cans only and hours are 12-6 although they have been opening early to allow for better traffic regulation and parking.

Thursday and Friday are cans and growlers and open is 5-8 (early, same as above).  

Saturday is open for fills, whatever cans are left over, and sometimes a rare release of a Native (sour) or sometimes a pour permit where they offer on site pours.  

Your best bet is to just follow them on twitter or update the On Tap page. 

Cans range from $3.25 to $5 per can depending on release.  Limits also vary based on rareness, case yield, etc. but is usually 3-10 cans (most usually 4-6) 

Edit: If you have any other questions just reply or PM me.  I go every week and am about 45 mins out as well from the Hartford area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a particular beer?  I realllllly loved the C27 recipe that Tree House used.  Big ups to Nate over there, killing it day in and day out.  Also was blown away by BA Vanilla Shake from Mikkeller and the Wide Awake Its Morning from Funky Buddha (tastes like a freaking McGriddle and coffee breakfast)

For a brewery? Really pleasantly surprised with the stuff SingleCut in Astoria NY has been releasing.  They had a bourbon maple stout that was excellent and the 18 Watt session was insanely juicy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Line Check - live 1/2 Trips + 2nd NFD OOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> live 1/2, hero sitting on about 300.  I am a 29 year old white male, used to play in this room all the time when I lived in this city and some of the regs recognize me and are making friendly banter.  I think people see me as very competent but maybe a tad on the LAG side. 


Have history w villain 1 in BB.  He is a drunk in his mid 40s, usually also on pain meds or some other pharmaceutical. He has about 240 to start the hand.


Villain 2 in hijack is an unknown black male around age 40.  Seems fairly decent but limps too much and I recently saw him stack off on a 258r flop and muck to shown AA when he was 3b shoved on. He has about $180 to start the hand.


Hero sits in sb, there is a $4 straddle utg. 3-4 limps around and hero completes w KcJs.  I don't see any point in squeezing here as we get called in multiple spots imo.


Flop runs Jc8c2c.  Hero leads for $15 into $24 or so. Villain 1 and villain 2 flat, others fold.  Turn Jd.  I have a feeling im up against at least 1 fd so betting turn seems ideal.  I also have a fairly premium J as AJ I would expect a raise pre. 


Hero leads turn for $30.  Villain 1 min raises to $60, and villain 2 fairly quickly shoves.  


Hero???

I think its possible were up against at least one made flush.  V2 shows up w clubs here sometimes but I have a feeling that V1 probably has some Jx. 


So... Flat?  Shove? Fold?
Will post results after some discussion. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was really my line of thinking. Especially the last few sentences. I felt like there was no need to punt off a buyin w middle pair in a 1/2 game that will definitely present better spots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck this is a real thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hero folded. Maybe weak, but completely readless Im ok w this line I guess. 

Interestingly, I saw same villain 3b pre to like 45 and open jam for 200 on a 852r flop. He was called and villains AA held up. Idk why the huge overbet w that type of hand but it really made me think about the JJ hand over and over again. So weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. Ripping it is a bad option because villain can just instamuck his bluffs. The board is fairly dry and we can call off a lot of rivers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea I agree. This is a standard ship given these particular events.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird spot OOP w JJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hero has been sitting for maybe 5 hands and has $300 effective, villain covers. 

Villain is a reg, haven't played w him before but I recognize him. Has missing teeth, gnarly meth head looking guy but clearly capable of making plays and seems like a thinking player (ironic I know). 

Hero picks up JsJc in MP and raises to 12. MP+1 and cutoff call and villain on button makes it 41 to go. Hero flats and others fold. 

Flop Qs10h6c. Hero checks and villain checks back. 

Turn 2d and hero checks and villain bombs for $103... hero???

Sizing on the turn seems really very strange to me. I feel like most of his value hands should be betting like $50-75 and not a full PSB. Perhaps this is AK? Perhaps this is a weirdly played set? Really hard to say. 

We check the turn to allow villain to continue with bluffs and for pot control. I think if we lead turn and get raised it's a pretty gross spot. 

After a few replies I'll post some showdowns that I saw villain in that occurred after this hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea obviously you don't want to take this hand multi way. OP is really lucky that he was 4b and that makes this a super easy shove, but getting all the money in pre in PLO is always kinda LOL to me. This isn't NLHE, PLO is a post flop game. This hand plays super tough OOP if we get callers behind, we only really like flops w top set or nut spade draws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was thinking the same. Love people going nuts w bad aces, it's the best way to make money in PLO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check river and avoid all of this imo. Feel like villain will occasionally bet rivers w worse and you can find value in C/C here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha this was amazing. Love the dudes reaction when he scoops the first board. "YEAAAAAAAAA" *fistpump* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need a 401k? What does this even mean, seems completely irrelevant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Added  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao do not do this. 
1 dollar for almost all pots. 2 for pots in the like 200-500 range. 1k+ I usually throw like $10-15, $25 if I like the dealer and we're friends. 

Best times to play generally are weekend nights. Try 9-10pm and later on a Saturday night to get some drunks and random tourists.  If I cash an odd amount like $234 I'll tip a buck to the dealer when I leave, buck to the cashier, and keep singles for valet or drink tips.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea I've had their whiskey and would be down to go check that out thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how seriously you want to take this.  Are you going to have a separate roll strictly for poker or will you be a recreational hobby player?  If you plan on being a rec/hobby player then there is no shame in starting w a 10-20 BI BR (ASSUMING you can afford to lose this money).  If losing 4k is going to ruin your life, then no - don't even bother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome thanks.  Yea the Mormon thing is so weird to me... the 3.2% beer is the weirdest part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salt Lake City UT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey - East coaster here and big fan of hazy IPAs naturally, sours, and stouts - particularly coffee variants.  I am going to be staying in SLC UT (downtown) Jan 1 and 2 then heading to Park City for a few days for some mountain time.  Any good breweries directly in the city?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> serious question, are you autistic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Green Mile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat

57 runners * $90 going to prize pool = $5130 total prize pool

3rd place takes 18.5% of the prize pool? Was it like $3200 for first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Make sure you get your 8 servings of veggies today, son!"

"THANKS MOM!!!"

*Devours 4 boxes of EZ Mac* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heroin.

Kidding, but in all seriousness - lots and lots of water, hot shower, and a couch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the groom has to put up w the bride for the rest of his life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Holdem Limits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80s work out tape on VHS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see u/dcstix comment below.
In addition to that, a 120 min is HARDLY an IPA... Its super malty, dark, boozy.  Have you had one before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drank a 2011 about a month ago. It put me over the edge from slightly tipsy to pretty drunk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Persian lime Berliner hmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Autism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> had to look it up from my untappd.  It was Gubna, imperial IPA ringing in at 10% abv.  Ive had that BA ten fidy stovepipe and thought mehhh.  Need to get a hold of a java ten fidy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck to you and the shop man.  Im sure the Oil and Gas slow down has not been so friendly.  I used to work for Parker and since have left for the Aerospace industry, part of the reason was the declining O G business.  

Call on your local municipalities, advertise, and try to diversify your customer base if you think youre too focused on walk in business.  Always helps to have recurring business to keep the lights on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RAR had a can called Walk of Shame that was really strange - started off like an IPA and finished w strong coffee notes.  Really weird, but I enjoyed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man, I thnk it was called Gubna.
It was a malt bomb but super high ABV.  Had one when in Wash DC for work and it put me over the edge from tipsy to pretty drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously the typical player would tend to want to play against the fish, the drunk, the person who pays no attention to prior hands, etc.

Think about it; would you rather play jeopardy against a PhD candidate or against some drooler who can't read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its like the polar opposite of the "drunk loud guy"

No one wants to play w a person who is appears to be analyzing everything, for obvious reasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You def are giving off the vibe of that player who gets too emotional and has to win every single pot they play.  c/f is fine, who cares, next hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your own good, don't do this.  I can tell you from experience that a local reg would do this and he was labeled a nit by everyone within 100 miles of the casino.  No one would ever give him action.  It's not so much about the wasting time as it is about the "why is this douche recording every single action... its like he has a HUD" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok from what I have found on a 753 those are running a gear pump for auxiliary functions and a hydrostat for the propulsion.  So to answer your question - by increasing the speed of the engine you are increasing the output of the pump which is most likely increasing the speed of the motors.

EDIT:  The only benefit to this (completely a guess) is that you have enough HP to burn if you wanted to go full throttle on the propulsion and dead head one of the aux functions (ex. raise a cylinder at full speed) at the same time.  Its possible that performing both of these at the same time is putting the hydraulic system in an overdemand situation and it will stall or bog down the engine.  Again, without reading the article, maybe that's why they are doing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends: Are you running a fixed displacement pump (gear pump or vane pump or fixed bent axis piston)?  Are you running a variable displacement piston pump?

Your flow is a function of displacement and of speed.  So if you keep the displacement the same, and increase the speed, naturally your pump flow will increase.  However, some more complex systems with variable displacement piston pumps allow you to change the displacement of the pump as its running to achieve a desired amount of flow, regardless of the input speed.  For example, say you want a pump to run at a fixed 30 GPM but your input RPM fluctuates between 1000 RPM and 3000 RPM;  we can reduce the displacement at 3000 RPM to achieve the same output flow.  Hope that makes sense.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully I am understanding your post correctly...I assume you mean they are replacing the skid steers motor to drive the same stock hydraulic pump and motor?

If that is the case, the larger HP motor will obviously produce more power and can handle more torque.  The limiting factor on this would be your hydraulic motor.  Is it going to run at the same pressure and speed?

Assuming you use the same displacement pump and run at the same pressure, nothing will change.  If you run a higher displacement pump (or increase the RPM on the pump) the flow rate will increase (and most likely increase your motor RPM). 

Its really hard to say what youre talking about without a better description of the application.  
Sorry for the confusing response lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this 50NL or 5kNL?  People seem split on this...  at 5K then yea obviously.  50NL, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy but I think shipping $150 over a $12 open is inherently bad for more reasons than you probably considered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a phenomenal game... Need another player? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre is absolutely a fold.  Multiway this flop is a slam dunk call for me.  Raising puts you in strange spots on a lot of turns.  What happens if a heart falls on the turn? A lot of the time this Qh is not the best flush out there.

This whole hand seems fairly standard after your preflop mistake. As mentioned, 6,7,9 do not make your hand the nuts.  This is an easy way to torch a couple buyins - chasing non nut draws.  Fold pre and avoid it all.  Also pretty hilarious that bb minraises w top set on the turn lmao... Lighting money on fire... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For dailys I've found that 20 seems to be the gold standard. Higher buyins and special events seem to have larger levels (30 min or 40 min, sometimes even 60 minute) but I've literally never seen longer structures for dailys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a spew to me but what do I know, I don't play zoom or that low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.groupon.com/deals/ga-travel-by-jen-barcelo-aruba </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check like groupon and deal sites like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came to post Aruba.  Surely you can find some type of all inclusive deal for much less than $200 a night.  I did this back maybe 10 years ago when I was 19 and crushed PLO and 2/5 NL.  Parents cried when I showed them my stash of cash at the end of the trip lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mo1stVag1na lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to be a crazy good game on like 2nd and vine st in old city years ago.  No idea if its still around or not, haven't been living there in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raise to $2.22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think against described villain I'd be thrilled to get it in here. I think you played it fine but I don't see any harm in raising the flop either as this is a multiway pot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear fold for me. You often don't have the best flush draw here and your straight draw isn't clean as a K brings broadway. Shipping would be bad, flatting would be bad as you invite those other draws to continue as well. You can also add that you have 3 hearts in your hand. 

Edit: didn't see the double gutter but I sill find the fold  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm raising the turn here almost all the time. We're ahead of almost all villains range and get paid by worse hands often  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the right eyes, absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a thing? Or you just made it up? I have a '13 WWS I've been sitting on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suuuuper standard fold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super standard shove imo. 

Raise gives villain opportunity to stop and go and make us fold lots of flops. Raise call is meh. Raise fold is horrible. Flat is bad for obvious reasons. Fold leaves us in the BB with 6BB remaining and villain is shoving button w almost entire range. 

So yea. Fist pump jam  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes because tittayyys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great line you took there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always calling but I think we should be raising turn a lot of the time here. Need to make people pay for them draw 
Edit: didn't see clubs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw some like 2 weeks ago in Cromwell.  Doubt they are there anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys are the best, are you kidding me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want him to raise more than 7x pre? I'm not sure I can get behind that. There's more 6x that will call a raise pre than specifically 66 as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Villain is never shoving the river or calling a river bet w 77/88 imo. I would expect to see an Ax a portion of the time and a random 6 a very small percentage of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
