<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wind-Up Bird Chronicle is my favorite so far by Murakami, probably due to its extreme focus on the introspective. It's historical underpinnings with Lieutenant Mamiya's story was fantastic, too. I hear some criticize it for meandering a bit, and Murakami is certainly notorious for not making his purpose clear, but I think all the dreamlike qualities and lucid prose in this one have some sort of underlying theme that was fun to pick apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Shadowbahn, by Steve Erickson** and **At the Existentialist Cafe, by Sarah Bakewell**

Kinda of my first foray into experimental/speculative fiction with Shadowbahn, but it's deeply entrancing and a welcome reading challenge. Seeks to describe the state of the U.S., unnervingly prescient in its characterization of the nature of the nation. Erickson also employs music and its historical provenance with such remarkable precision.

At the Existentialist Cafe is a fun, well-chronicled account of existentialist philosophers; their lives, their ideologies, and the enveloping history that spawned the movement as well as the world that was subsequently informed by the movement. There's a passage about Franciscan priests and nuns doggedly working to subvert Nazi destruction of influential phenomenology manuscripts by smuggling them out of Prague. Having just recently read The Name of the Rose and A Canticle for Leibowitz, that part really stuck out as a poignant real-world preservation of knowledge situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going for Back to the Piast a few weeks ago and started as Silesia. Within 20 years or so I just happened to get a PU over Hungary, too. It was the easiest early games I've ever had the pleasure to experience. Ate Poland and become Poland in about 100 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always like to talk about the intended themes that the author weaves into the narrative. Finding what the author has to say about their intentions for writing the work is usually informative, and helps frame some questions by connecting certain passages in the book to the overall themes. Looking up critical reviews for the book also helps to familiarize yourself with what other people notice. Bringing up points that reviewers mention to those in your club is always fun for sparking discussion. 

For me, I like to prepare discussion questions if I'm leading the talk, so that I always have something to pivot back to if the discussion strays for too long. Note some things down that kind of stuck with you, or seem controversial, and ask for what people thought about those passages. 

Another technique for me running healthy, friendly clubs is to feel the vibe of the group and try to challenge their assertions respectfully with some of the research you've acquired. Laugh along with points you might not necessarily agree with and then pose an alternative idea. Probably won't be too much of an issue to maintain a civil dialogue if you're doing it between friends, but just something to keep in mind, and helps to contribute fuller discussion. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I commented on the other reply here, my problem isn't necessarily with not understanding how to produce an heir. I get the whole % heir chance. It's more trying to understand how to avoid getting a foreign dynasty to suddenly birth out an heir when marriage to a ruler of your desired dynasty. Is that prestige related? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The situation I just had was my Rurikovich queen, heirless, chose a prince consort from France from a typical royal marriage decision. In a couple years, a new heir was born. My Queen died and then her son, my heir, ascended, but to my horror, he was suddenly a de Valois. 

So I didn't die heirless or accept any event. But I got into this unfortunate situation where I couldn't control which dynasty the heir chooses when he's born, and I got to thinking maybe I was forgetting something. Should I not ever offer a royal marriage without an heir, due to the risk of that nation's consort placing their dynasty on the throne? Or is this prestige related, where I should only be proposing royal marriages with nations lower than me until I have secured the desired dynasty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tricks to retaining a dynasty indefinitely? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than the mysterious chronic game crashes that so often plague us, are there any tips to keeping your dynasty's reign unbroken? This most directly affects something like the achievement Kinslayer, but I'd also be interested in this generally. 

And can you know what dynasty your heir will be before they are born, based on the ruler and consort dynastic ties?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R5: Going for "Back to the Piast" as Silesia caused quite a bit of border gore, splitting Poland five ways. #Noregrets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think this is what historians think of when they hear of the Partition of Poland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's always the plan, but France guaranteeing them leads to some complications. Scotland never gets strong enough to become a problem later game, so taking out England early has its benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scotland and England were pretty upset, as well as the Irish minors. That was about it. If I took London in the first war, I definitely would've gotten some coalitions to form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R5: Got the 4 provinces needed to core and culture convert as Denmark in 1471. Of course, it took quite a while longer to core and change to Danish culture. I ended up taking London and Ireland and getting PUs over the Palatinate and Brandenburg by the mid 1500s. Felt pretty good about this, for being an average filthy casual.

Edit: Forgot the relevant strategy, if you can call it that. All I had to do was watch France take back their provinces on the mainland, ally them, wait for England to hit the war of roses, declare no CB and ship my troops over to a perfectly ravaged Britain. Their navy was sitting in the English channel the entire time blockade English ports while their 10k troops hid in London while rebels were sieging down the Marches. France and Aragon helped, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not super impressive, but proud of my 1471 conquering of the Danelaw region for the Iron Price achievement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meissner Porcelain is really annoying. You basically need to inherit the Lowlands from Burgundy or else you won't have the time or trade income to colonize fast enough to reach all the Asian porcelain provinces. Then you need to prevent the Netherlands from spawning in your provinces (which I think consists of culture converting). Also, Ming doesn't seem to break up so often anymore, which makes it a bit harder since China has a lot of porcelain provinces you need. 

Suffice to say, it hasn't been the most fun experience for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What have you done to Brandenburg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks to me like you may have just taken land bordering their provinces. If you check your ally's diplomacy screen, you can hover over your relations to bring up a display that breaks down the specific negative modifiers in your relationship. Oftentimes, taking land near their own borders is encroaching on that nation's provinces of interest. You can check to see what each nation has marked as one of these PoI's in the diplomacy screen as well, in the tab for Trust/Favors.

You can see in this image below from the EU4 wiki the menu that should be selected. The mapmode should switch, showing the selected nation's provinces in green, provinces with claims in yellow, and provinces of interest in red. If you end up taking one of the provinces that they want, they'll probably end up becoming hostile.
http://www.eu4wiki.com/images/thumb/1/11/Trust_and_Favors.png/800px-Trust_and_Favors.png

Otherwise, perhaps lend a little more context to your situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luck of the Irish is like the feel good achievement for those of us who aren't super invested in trying some of EU4's hardest challenges. I did Thomond into Ireland and got super lucky take the Irish isle without England or Scotland claiming any part of the it first. I allied France and Scotland and used their combined might to take London in the first war against England. Then began about 100 years of warring England, spitting out Wales/Northumberland/Cornwall, taking way too much land form England and firing a coalition war of European powers, appeasing the coalition forces by forcing France to release some small nations, then getting dragged into wars as Spain smelled a weak France and ate up its southern border, then using France's remaining manpower to finish off the rest of England, watching Spain viciously pounce on the struggling French, then dropping all my alliances to turn to fighting off a remarkably advanced Scottish military to finally eke out a domination victory in the English isles by 1630. It was a whirlwind of emotions, but this achievement was hella fun.

End game mutilation of the French state:
http://i.imgur.com/B9IovGL.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
