<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did The Fifth Estate fail? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fifth Estate was on TV yesterday, which made me remember this recent but already forgotten movie. Nobody seems to ever talk about this movie, either to praise any part of it or to mock it. 

What, in your opinion, made it fail both critically and commercially? 

I can't say how accurate it was, but I don't think it's a bad movie. The acting was pretty good, the direction too, it wasn't cheaply made, the cast was appealing...So what happened? Was it the subject matter? Bad marketing? Small release?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like it's going to be very different so even comparing them seems pretty pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a cool sequence but it was ultimately meaningless. There was no real danger, no real threat. Just a limitless amount of henchmen who all get effortlessly killed by the hero. It was like playing a video game on the hardest setting but with immortality cheat codes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That clip is in no way representative of the quality of the rest of the film, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to point that out. It's amazing how people confuse this church with the actual Kremlin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pizza is so delicious that I had to play some appropriately epic music for it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you think trailers give away too much plot, this website will tell you if a trailer is too revealing based on viewer votes. Join us and hunt revealing trailers - or help our programmer /u/Krzysztofik with further development </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that sounds cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you feel about the last couple of episodes? I finished DS9 about a month ago (maybe two) and I was kind of underwhelmed by the ending. There was too much focus on Damar, Kai Winn, Bajoran Dukat, the Pah Wraiths and the war and some characters just didn't have anything to do, like Miles, Bashir, Quark, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Shane Black movie is a comedy. He's in the original Predator for all of five minutes and he tells a memorable joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Full service during a movie.

How does that work in a dark theater with chairs in rows? Seems like that would be a major source of noise and disturbances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We can go faster if we have a faster engine." - Captain Obvious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Fellowship is by far the best one. While it doesn't really have an ending, it's the one that works best on its own and for me it has the most memorable moments and the least amount of things to complain about. Two Towers is the typical middle part with no real beginning and end and the cutting back and forth between Treebeard and Helm's Deep always irritated me. I get cutting away from action for quieter moments, but this felt like going from 100 to 0. Return of the King is getting too full of CG for my taste, I kind of hate how the ghost army looked, and there is too much good material left on the cutting room floor (or the extended dvd) for me to call it really great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't really seen that many movies with him other than the Marvel flicks - only Chaplin, Zodiac, Kiss Kiss Bang Bang, Sherlock Holmes, and The Judge - but the one thing that really irritates me about him is his strange diction or manner of speaking. I associate it mostly with Tony Stark. If he could get rid of that, I would take him more seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand the point of this article. Connery is 86, Hackman is 87. Why would you want fucking octogenarians to come out of retirement? Just because you miss them? Either that author is very childish or he had to meet this week's clickbait quota. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  so many casinos operate with huge profits without cheating

as far as we know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slovakia - and specifically I am taking about a theater chain called CinemaCity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they probably do that. I sometimes do. That is why the reservations fall through 30 minutes before the showing.

But yeah, their system is hardly perfect. I think this is because they had it before online purchases were a thing, and even before internet was really a thing they had phone reservations, and now instead of having one good system they have a bunch of remnants from older systems stuck together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If by worthy replacement you mean a place where people call you an idiot for having a different opinion, then I would suggest the rest of the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reservation system is online and there you have the option of either just reserving or directly buying. I guess this allows you to reserve and then not stress about changing your plans last minute because you haven't paid yet. And, for some reason, the online system only allows you to pay with paypal and nothing else, but paypal isn't really all that popular here, so not everyone has an account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my country the reserved seating is only valid up to 30 minutes before the movie starts. So you have to buy your reserved seats before that deadline, otherwise the reservations are cancelled and the seats are available for purchase again. This way you can't have a situation where someone reserves half the theater and doesn't actually buy anything. It also means you can still get good seats if people don't show up or if they are late.

EDIT: Also, these theaters are usually in shopping malls so it forces people to show up early and then they can kill time with shopping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 13:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this not surprise me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 11:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing stuff. I think I upvoted this everywhere you posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got Dr. Strangelove on first try in 28 guesses. Couldn't get Her at all and crashed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /s ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it Scott Pilgrim that had the tagline *An epic of epic epicness*? Ugh.

EDIT: Yes, I do understand the tagline was a parody of the epic trend. The "ugh" was in reference to the fact that such a parody was even necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you think trailers give away too much plot, you might find this website useful. It is designed to indicate if a trailer is too spoilery based on viewer votes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this movie will be just the kid half of the novel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The minute the guy turned on the drill my whole theater went batshit crazy. It's amazing how universally hated that sound is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This film was described as a bad Shutter Island, but a more accurate wording would be that it's an unsuccessful one. Set against the backdrop of the Swiss Alps and with some amazing interiors, A Cur for Wellness has beautiful cinematography and an eerie atmosphere to boot. The performances are all perfectly ok, with no one standing out either positively or negatively. The pace, however, can get excruciatingly slow. Normally a slower pace can create a creepy mood and is genre-appropriate, but Verbinski takes this too far. There is no reason why this movie needed to be 146 minutes long and filled with shots of DeHaan walking slowly on crutches. The plot doesn't really support this pace, either, with very little happening at one point, only to be replaced with an info-dumping conversation or a needless bar fight at another point. Speaking of plot, the movie spirals into increasingly fantastical territory and leaves you with poorly defined concepts and plot holes galore. The inevitable "what was the point" question arises in the viewer, one that even breathtaking visuals are not enough to answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 07:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's creepy and there are a couple disturbing/disgusting images. But it's not really horror. (Don't take her to see it if she's terryfied of dentists, though.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved it too. That doesn't mean I can't have problems with it as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad thing is that they probably won't let him have enough creative control anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you basing the assumption that she has no more kids and dies alone on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That title is a little harsh. Keanu Reeves' *emptiness*? Sound like he's somehow mindless or a psychopath  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was definitely digital and actually a lot of times actors are *not* filmed underwater for convenience but post production makes it look that way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I re-watched Arrival and I think it's a near-perfect movie with three flaws that really bother me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as the title says, I watched Arrival again. I really liked in the theater and the re-watch only confirmed that it's an amazing movie. There are three things that bother me about it, though. You might consider this nit picking, but bear with me for a sec.

1. Roughly a third into the movie there is a montage scene with a voice over from Jeremy Renner's character Ian. This scene feels very out of place to me. It's an info dump with no real purpose other than to move the plot forward by summarizing a few events and explaining a few concepts we'll need later on. I understand the need for it but I resent the execution. To me it feels like something from a completely different movie. Or it just doesn't make sense to me. It sounds like Ian is giving an interview on TV or like he's recording thoughts for his diary, except neither of those is true (or at least neither is shown) and so there's no reason for Ian to be giving a voice over narration that is pure exposition. It took me out of the movie both times I watched it.

2. The big twist of the movie is that scenes with Louise's daughter aren't flashbacks but flashforwards. But I think this twist was revealed (or at least made way too obvious) one scene too early. When her daughter asks Louise about that scientific expression for a win-win scenario, Louise tells her that if she wants science, she should ask her father. At that point it becomes obvious that she is talking about Ian, and since they only just met during the present events, it becomes clear to the audience that this scene must be in the future. But it's only until the next scene, when Ian in the present uses that word in a sentence and Louise is able to tell it to her daughter in the future that Louise figures out what's going on. I wish the audience and the character figured it out at the same time. I think that would have been more impactful, as we would be experiencing the same mindfuck as Louise at the same time when she is reacting to it.

3. I hate the digital hair. When Louise enters the ship towards the end of the movie, her hair becomes wavy and flows as if she were underwater or in lighter gravity - or I guess that's what it was meant to convey. But the effect looked terrible and once again took me out of the movie both times I watched it. All the other effects in the movie are great, displaying beautiful design and a measure of restraint, but the hair is just...terrible and pointless.

So those are my three problems with Arrival. It's still an ace movie, but not perfect.

EDIT: I seriously don't understand all the downvotes. What is your problem, people? Is it really so unacceptable to say one negative thing about reddit's beloved movie? Can you not appreciate that I took time to word my thoughts on Arrival in a coherent way and provide a real argument? I would understand downvoting something like "Arrival sucks" but this is just ridiculous. Thanks a lot for the conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've see in; great movie. Not quite what I'm looking for right now, though. It's more of a drama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it and I loved it. Replaced Fargo as my favorite crime infused dark comedy set against the backdrop of too much snow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for good European thrillers or crime movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for tense, intriguing, mysterious or exciting movies from Europe. I've already seen Headhunters, Funny Games, The Fourth Man, Borgman, Elle, The Vanishing, and The Sicilian Clan. 

They can be from any year, black and white or color. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shout out to Fassbender for lasting so long in the ring with her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It would be awesome, but it's somewhat unlikely. The only reason John Wick can hold steady, long shots of amazing action is because Keanu is a dedicated, skilled actor.

There is also the possibility that maybe studios should hire capable actors and build movies around them, not the other way around. Like maybe don't cast Liam Neeson in an action movie when the dude's in his 60s and doesn't have the moves. I'm sure there are more dedicated and skilled actors out there besides Reeves and Cruise. Maybe they're unknowns. But you don't need a star to make a good action movie, you need a badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets sucked out through a suction nozzle (basically a shit vacuum cleaner) that's inside the bowl. So you have to line up your anus with the nozzle. Astronauts train this on Earth with a camera instead of the nozzle and a TV monitor showing them how they are lined up. No joke. I read about it in either [this book](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/311504.Riding_Rockets) or [this one](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/311503.Do_Your_Ears_Pop_in_Space_and_500_Other_Surprising_Questions_about_Space_Travel) (can't remember which, since they are both written by the same astronaut and I read them back to back) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were going for an older Batman anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the mistake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really thought Affleck was a perfect choice. But since DCEU is becoming more of a joke all the time, maybe they should cast Bruce Campbell  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally get why they didn't do that, though. The way those Nolan movies are crafted, it would be really unbelievable that Superman exists in that world. ~~Also they probably couldn't keep Bale as Batman.~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should just incorporate the LEGO version of Batman into live action footage. And keep him to scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/iESWda0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then there will be the inevitable "pick ups and reshoots are scheduled far in advance and are a normal part of production" damage control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm suspicious of every video that is 4:20 long. Coincidence or a stoner editor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet you've spent (wasted?) so much time discussing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is basically the reason why most of the movies mentioned here get remade. Total Recall, Robocop...both awesome movies but they must feel extremely dated to a younger audience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My main problem was that it had no reason to exist- it was just a rehash of the original with some Americanization.

But that is the exact reason WHY it exists! It's great that you are interested in movies enough to have heard of this Korean film everyone else seemed to love and checked it out. It's great that you don't mind reading subtitles. It's great that you embrace foreign cinema. I do, too. But most people don't. Most people won't watch anything with subtitles because it's off-putting to them. Most people won't watch Korean movies because they seem too foreign to them or too unrelatable. And let's face it, most people have trouble recognizing Asian people and differentiating between them. And when I say most people, I mean the target audience of these remakes, which is middle class (probably preferably white) Americans. These are the people studious cater to. Producers take a good foreign movie, remake it with recognizable preferably white actors and in a relatable setting and these people pay to see that product. It's custom made for them. Even if you put "the Korean original is better" on the American Oldboy poster, most people would still not watch a bunch of Koreans in a foreign land talk in their incomprehensible language when they can watch a good looking, American-as-apple-pie actor and a hot young blonde. This isn't rocket science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this regularly in school or in my first temp job when I was bored. I don't own a kindle or any other ebook reader and it would obviously be unacceptable to take it out at work and blatantly read anyway. Same goes for reading the actual book. But take pictures of the book pages, download them into your computer, stare at the monitor and pretend you're clicking or writing every once in a while and presto! your boss suspects nothing and you can read.

Edit: Granted, this lady took terrible photos of her book. Must be pretty uncomfortable to read it when you have the pages curved like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it baffling? Because she's a woman? Or because you've never heard of an actress who in the past two years has received only positive reviews in a couple of high profile projects? Or because Reynolds had one big hit in the past couple of years so he's suddenly relevant again despite his at best average acting skills? You haven't even seen the movie. For all we know, Reynolds is a minor character and she is actually the true lead and should have been billed over Gyllenhaal too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think so, yes. I would much rather listen to the opinion of a studied, experienced critic, who knows what he's talking about and who has seen hundreds of movies from all decades and many countries, compared to a random person on the internet, who is probably a teenager and hasn't even heard of Casablanca. I'm not saying the critic's opinion is automatically better/true or that I necessarily adjust my viewing habits based on these pro reviews, but I absolutely think someone like Ebert was a million times better at judging films compared to you or me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  seemed to be what Cameron was most interested in discussing.

You mean like in interviews? I would understand why the director might want to talk about the technical aspects of his movie and leave other topics to actors. That doesn't bother me. And he was always pushing the boundaries. His first short movie was super effects heavy. And he utilized masterfully created puppets and animatronics. And he pioneered CG. But he did all as support for story, not as a main drive for story. If he is becoming Lucas (and that is a frightening thought) then I would say it only started with Avatar. What I find really odd and somewhat off-putting is that he didn't let go of Avatar for a while and do something else in the interim. Instead he decided to do four more Avatars in a row and took almost ten years writing them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think not because with text we are automatically wired to go from left to right because that is how we read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It relied more on visual spectacle than on building stories and characters. When we look back at Cameron's two best movies, Terminator was a pretty low budget movie that took its time to develop Sarah and give her some character development, and Aliens has almost an hour of time spent with characters before the action drops. Avatar has...uhm..colors and 3D. The visuals are the only reason why it made so much money. It was the first movie I've ever seen in 3D and I went to see it three times (though once was for free) solely for this reason. Not the characters, acting, or story.

In comparison, while Star Wars had groundbreaking visuals when it came out, nowadays they don't look so hot. But we stayed for the characters. And while Dr. Strange had those cool action sequences, I liked it for the humor, actors and the ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so?

A person who logs in to reddit and gives their opinion on a movie is nothing but a random person giving his opinion. A film critic is a professional (meaning they get paid for it) who probably studied journalism, has experience, and is good enough at giving balanced and well versed opinions that they were hired by a news outlet to do so.

Similarly, a person who runs really fast to catch a bus is nothing but a random person running really fast. An athlete is a professional (meaning they get paid for it - at least in sponsorship deals or prizes) who probably trained for most of their life and who is good enough at running fast that corporations pay to have their logo on tight shorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They call them phases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. In the same way that everyone who runs to catch the bus is an Olympic runner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I would get multiple tickets for a roller coaster but I wouldn't make any emotional connections to it.

That about sums up the whole issue perfectly. But it's a real shame because James Cameron usually makes stuff audiences connect with and care about a whole lot more than anything in Avatar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, that explains it perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? I guess I sound smart or something. I did actually research this whole poster billing thing a couple of years ago when this exact same thing bugged me on a different poster, but I'm hardly an insider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is every mentioning of a name part of the credits?

Yes, pretty much. You might even say that is the definition of credits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same could be (and probably was) said for Godzilla.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was in Mission Impossible: Rogue Nation and The Girl on the Train. Not a household name yet but definitely a rising star. Also a great actress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I found out how all of this worked, movie posters confused me as fuck as a kid too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan Reynolds most likely signed up for this movie and negotiated his contract (and thus his billing order) before Deadpool came out. At that time I don't think his popularity or box office draw were that high. Also, as I mentioned in another comment, you don't know how much screentime he'll have compared to the other two. 

I don't know what kind of box office draw Gyllenhaal has but apparently he plays the lead role and maybe he has a better agent who negotiated more money and top billing for him. I don't know what else to say since I'm not privy to the behind the scenes negotiations of this movie. But that is simply how billing actors works.

As a side note, Gyllenhaal is also a more respected actor in terms of his craft, so putting him first makes sense if you want to lend your movie more seriousness and gravitas. As for Fergusson, I can only assume that either her role is big enough to warrant her billing over Reynolds, or she negotiated her contract coming off of Mission Impossible, where she had a big role that was very well received. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what "it can sometimes" refers to in your comment, but as for the rest, consider these points:

* The order of names in the credits was contractually predetermined before the movie even began shooting, so nothing you or anyone else says about the poster will ever take precedent over that order

*  On the other hand, since the order is determined in advance, the artist creating a poster probably views the names as just another legal line, same as the blocks of credits that appear on the bottom. It's just something that has to be there and that's that. Why limit yourself creatively because of it?

* This poster will be turned into tons of various formats including web banners where the names might me too small to read, or billboards next to highways, where even if the names are big enough, you won't have enough time to read them when you drive by. So ultimately, the order of the names doesn't really matter so much in relation to the big faces, because you might miss the names but you are bound to see the faces.

* As I mentioned in my previous comment, usually you put the most important thing in the center of the poster, because people tend to view pictures head on and focus on the center of the frame first. Why would you disregard this natural human tendency and put Gyllenhaal to the left just because two years ago he signed a contract that put his name first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I think that's called double billing, where one actor is the first from left to right and the other is first from top to bottom. It's pretty common on TV, I think. For example, [Hannibal had Mikkelsen and Dancy appear this way](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kz3qclEk5kI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never know. He might die in the first ten minutes of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The order of the names on the poster reflects the order of names in the movie's credits, which indicates who has top billing. When you have top billing, your name is the first one. Usually this means the actor has the lead role, but it can also just mean the actor is the most famous, or the biggest box office draw, or the one with the best contract. For example, Marlon Brando had top billing in Superman despite appearing in it only briefly. If this were an Indiana Jones movie and Indie's face were in the bottom right corner surrounded by twelve other actors, Harrison Ford would still be the first name in the row.

As for the order of faces, who knows? Either it's just an esthetic choice, or the thinking here is that visually you should put the main actor in the center because that's where your eyes focus the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didn't this happen a year ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Theory of Everything

The Imitation Game

A Dangerous Method

Creation

Gorillas in the Mist

Einstein and Eddington (TV movie)

Shackleton (mini series)

Hawking (TV movie)

Fat Man and Little Boy 

Bogowie

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popstar: Never Stop Never Stopping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Deadpool levels of fourth wall breaking and pop culture references, this movie is a laugh out loud blast for audiences aged 15-35. It's a straight up parody of Batman, mocking his previous movie iterations and the inherent ridiculousness of a playboy billionaire dressing up as a bat with branded gadgets, while also getting the character right and exploring him in a hyper-meta kind of way. But it also mixes in lessons about family and team work that feel like they're taken straight out of a Disney sob story, which are obviously aimed at a younger audience. This creates a certain imbalance, where the movie tries to be entertaining for all ages but can't really balance the two tones without a noticeable shift from one to the other. This, however, is not a significant fault and doesn't happen too often to be overly distracting. Visually it follows in the footsteps of the first Lego movie with breathtakingly colorful and cinematic animation that often feels like stop motion on speed and is a joy to look at. Not only is this a great animated movie, it's also a hilarious comedy and a cool Batman flick that should be a real crowd pleaser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably learned that from Nerdwriter. 

EDIT: Why is /u/swoledabeast getting downvoted? It was a legitimate constructive criticism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So somebody forgot to put a lock on the minibar in Depp's hotel room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knocked it out of the park on the first try! She is sure this is the movie, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the exact same thing. But with all the popculture references, especially to previous Batman movies, I wonder how much of that could a kid actually get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [movie] Looking for a movie that takes place during one night (more details in description) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told my girlfriend about [After Hours](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0088680/) and she immediately thought of another movie that takes place over a single night. But of course she has no clue what it's called or who's in it. Supposedly it's a dark comedy (though she's not entirely sure so don't focus on comedies) and there's a murderer (or murderers - anyway, there's a lot of deaths) and it takes place in a small town where all the characters somehow know each other. It's definitely not [Identity](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0309698/) but could be something similar (genre, atmosphere). She's seen it maybe four years ago, so I think we're looking for movies made up to 2013.

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here's a video that actually talks about how it works](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kwLiY-J0bJQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Felicity Jones' evil sister? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Fincher usually has good opening credit sequences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Bowl was last week, right? I'm still waiting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAP of a highway built next to a cathedral in Bratislava </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all look incredibly peaceful and relaxed, which I envy them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but not with twenty more minutes of plot after it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is having your own garage rock band still a thing among teenagers nowadays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or is that more of a 70s or 80s kind of thing? Was it replaced with electronic music and that genre's much more individualistic, solo performer inclination? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the quality of this gif is crazy low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely fantastic until [they get off the bus and it explodes.](#spoiler) After that the movie just kind of falls apart for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah, the obligatory Browncoat

never back down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tribble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seeing that opening night, which is Feb 23 in my country. I can't fucking wait. If it's half as good as the first one it will still be better than most modern action films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You answered your own question in your wording. They *build up* the tolerance, meaning it's a gradual process. Don't think it wasn't painful for them at the start just as much as it is for you right now. Eat gradually hotter food, starting with little or mildly hot, and after a while you will notice that you are building up your tolerance just like everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Showing off a house is not a skill.

Letting people walk around a house and showing them the rooms might not be a skill, but *selling* a house is definitely a skill, and that's what those showings are all about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why did so many Nazis flee to Argentina after the war? (Or if they didn't, why is it a prevailing myth?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what the title says. Why specifically Argentina of all places and is it even true that they went there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered why nobody's bothered by stoner celebrities. There are all these well known, unashamed stoners in the business like Seth Rogen, Woody Harrelson, Jeff Bridges, Snoop Dogg, etc. I think one time Josheph Gordon-Levitt was on a talk show and mentioned meeting Rogen and how they got super high, and everyone just laughed. But isn't marijuana still illegal in most states and still a fucking drug? I mean, I smoke it too, so don't think I'm being a puritan or whatever. But it seems like these stoner celebrities get a free pass to do drugs and everyone just laughs it off despite the fact that they are pretty bad role models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think of that as a very random cameo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are all fine titles but you named 3 in the span of 10 years. Not much of a career, I think. At least not an A-list career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting as fuck dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much this. His performance is amazing regardless of his untimely death, but that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Descent into darkness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  as long as they make it their own.

it's based on a true story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> colleague is a former gymnast, she shows everyone gifs like this all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I saw The Dark Knight, and I don't understand the hype around it.

Same here, pal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, that make sense. I didn't realize there was green screen footage available. I thought you had to cut him out from the movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why would they specifically pick Tom Cruise using a shot from 16 year old movie? There must be tons of shots of actors falling like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this buzzfeed article](https://www.buzzfeed.com/briangalindo/45-amazing-vintage-polish-posters-of-classic-american-films) should paint the picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people in Poland must go "man, I'm sick of all these easily comprehensible posters, I miss the communist era" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somebody let a glove freeze in this open construction site, making it look like there's a body under the ice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a movie that is original and doesn't reference, homage, parody, or imitate other films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this movie more times than I should probably admit. And I usually discover something new in it every time. I remember the holy shit moment when I realized Jon Stewart is in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of liked the colors more in the earlier version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched this yesterday. I was expecting a movie about divorce, but that was not really the case. A Separation is mostly about the burden of taking care of an Alzheimer patient (and the filial piety it involves) and about the accusation that husband Nader pushed his father's caregiver down the stairs and caused her a miscarriage. This event is the real driving force behind the movie and takes up most of the plot. However, it's arguable how interesting this story would be had it not been for the setting. The movie's most intriguing aspect is the depiction of life in Iran and their oddly laid back criminal justice system. It's a world the western audience rarely gets to see and some of it may cause a culture shock that elicits various emotions. For example, at one point a character calls a Muslim hotline to find out if doing something would be a sin under certain circumstances, which is kind of hilarious, endearing and completely foreign all at once. Well acted as it was, I am not a fan of movies that are two hours of nonstop bickering and shouting, and I feel like the setting itself was the only (or major) reason why anybody even cares about this film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I not remember this? I hope I didn't read some sort of censored edition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
