<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7661</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London eye hotbox 420 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London eye hotbox 420 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 09:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big country mate. Sure you guys probably vary rolling styles state to state  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 02:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting way of rolling. I honestly think it's a very long way. I was about to say "normal" way is best. Guess this way is normal to the Danish. I like making sure weed/tobacco is evenly spread throughout joint. Think this method makes it difficult to have it spread evenly. I'm too high for this. All this talk of rolling is making me want to roll joint now. 
Maybe I'll try it the Danish way. 

I'm Surprised at lack of anti tobacco comments from the AmericEnts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orange diesel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 01:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Papastathopoulos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd one I've signed now. Let's hope something happens. 3rd time lucky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 01:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same same but different  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate of mine flys out from Southend airport   he books well in advance he pays 35. Has done the last 3 times his flown out. Worth looking into  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 01:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you burn the roach end. His probably bummed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried Thai or commercial weed?? 
High in cbd low thc. 
A lot cheaper than skunk
I used to smoke Thai daytime or if you got shit to do! Skunk at night when getting high is all your doing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous Brussels reaction video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 01:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 23:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really don't think that climbing up scaffolding, then getting high   trying to climb back down. While buzzing is a good idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 04:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1st time here. Just grabbed what I could.  I'm from London. the 2nd bag I got, was good. Got me to about [5/6].  The smell from rolling zoot in hotel room. Stunk up the whole corridor. Prices   amount was the same as there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 19:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just come back from old town part. Got bag of some weird lady. Smells good. Looks a lot better. Hope it smokes better too. 

  yeah considering I did buy off a 'lookey lookey' guy. Guess it wasn't that bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 in Palma, Majorca. I'm on holiday here, thought I'd try the local trees. It Wasn't good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 13:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 15:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must be very high! cause that took me way too long to figure out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 02:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uk ent here our 1p weigh 3.5g. Learnt that from a dealer friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got 2 options with that. 
Cheese  amp; pickle or mustard. 

In a sandwich that is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate! Will check that out now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna do some research into ordering off dark net but reading things like the link posted above puts me off. Can get good skunk. Just would like to get some import skunk at reasonable prices. So thought dark net might be the place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seriously considering trying to order off dark net. Not sure how to go about it. Will do my research 1st. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I'd expect to happen. if you was ordering skunk online. 
Was actually thinking off ordering small amount after reading a few post about it in this sub. 
Will give it a miss   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 18:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably does just think if they can get big bags of stinking skunk through customs. They could get anything. I can't afford to smoke this stuff everyday but for special occasions defo worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Import weed. It' taste lovely   is very strong but really don't think it's actually come from the USA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 15:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 00:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love rubicon mango sparkling but when I discovered Copella apple juice! Took top spot. That stuff is like crack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 00:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good vibes from east London. 
Just discovered this sub. 
Think my posts would be more appreciated in this sub. Communicating with them AmericanEnts can be difficult they use our language incorrectly lol. 
What we call a roach they call a filter or crutch And a joint without a roach is called a roach, baffling. Plus I get jealous seeing all the different strains they get out there, LEGALLY!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 18:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bhang". They give this out in temples. For shivrati. There was couple of post about this last week. It's religious Hindu festival. They mix it with milk, snacks   some priests smoke it straight. It's illegal but on that day most Hindu temples give it out as parsaad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie is brilliant! 
No reboot they'll just spoil it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 12:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lib dems said they wouldn't charge university fees or at least increase cost of going. Literally the 1st thing that happened when they formed coalition with conservatives. If it was another party then it definitely something I'd get excited about. 

But keep the dream alive. Sign the online government petition for it to be discussed parliament. Already been done before but someone started a new petition. 

I'm Too high to find link to post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Hindu can confirm this is true. Not just in Nepal but all over India too. My Dad told me they used to give out "bung bhajias" in temples when he was a kid. Basically onion bhajis with cannabis in them. 

He also had monkey brains for dessert but that's a different story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signed the last one. The email response from them was a load of crap. Signed this anyway. There's so many wonderful strains out there. Need to get them over here without having to pay through the roof for them. Also the medical benefits   how many people it could help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 23:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In uk we call them "roach", which is exactly what American ents call joints without roach or crutch or filter or whatever you want to call. I'm too high for this. But post it notes are not good roaches. Too weak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 12:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookies   cream is the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the uk it's always on Mothering Sunday. 4th Sunday of lent. 
I thought it was the same day all over the world before as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 12:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green crack is brilliant strain only ever smoked it once. Hard to get here in uk. 

Since no one else has commented. Congratulations on you SO. I can only imagine her crack is just as lovely as the strain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 12:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's brilliant. Your mum will get you through anything. They're the best. Love between a mother and her child is unconditional true love. No other type of love is so pure. 

I Lost my mum 4 years ago. Still hurts the same amount. She was a saint. I must've been her child to test her. She was best mum. I know everything would be ok if I talked to my mum. She would help no matter how bad I fucked up. 

Mother's Day March 6th. This Sunday just a reminder  for uk ents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Brother must've done something really bad to deserve that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 02:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh cool. Guess they might be good for people new to rolling. U.K. Ent here, we always use crutch but we call them roaches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 15:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure a new coffee grinder would beat an old one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 15:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any pics? Never heard of wire papers before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 15:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hope it is legalised here in the uk. They will when they realise how much  they government can make for the business side of cannabis. Over 10 years ago most of the weed was imported and actually cost less than it does now. However most of the weed in uk is now grown here in the uk. In 10 years box(1kg/36oz) has gone from 2,500-3000 upto 6500-7000+. Depending on quality of course. All this attracts a very nasty criminal element to business. As much as you can deal with good dealers you will always have to deal with some nasty scum bags from time to time. Police used to be so chilled when it come to weed. 90% of the time your let off with warning(verbal no record) but now they seem to want to give out police cautions for the smallest amounts. Although it's still fair, cautions can stay on record for up to 5 years. Think if they was to decriminalise small amounts 1st, then maybe they might start to think about legalisations. 

Signed government petition for them to discuss matter in the House of Commons but they didn't receive enough signatures. They also emailed a response in which they stated the reason they wouldn't legalise cannabis. They main arguments from what I remember where they felt that it has no medical values   it's the main cause of schizophrenia in uk. It was long email   I was high but sure they were main 2 points. 

Here's to hoping we can be smoking legally here in uk soon but best not wait   spark your joint anyway.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 18:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 18:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the correct Thai saying is "Same same but different" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 23:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/leaves  they seem like a good sub. Lots of people there will be able to give you more advice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 15:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether something is morally right or wrong is down to opinion. Everyone has different morals. I haven't been through it but you saying you don't remember it anyway doesn't mean it wasn't painful at the time. I think docking tails is morally wrong. Other people may not. Obviously we will not agree in this matter.  I could bring in female circumcision. Do you feel that's morally wrong? In Africa it's common practice but illegal here in the uk. Opinions   morals differ. I find the practice of docking barbaric. Feel same about circumcision. You said docking was a non issue because that's how you feel about docking. I'm completely against it   It wouldn't be illegal here in uk if it was a non-issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 01:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say it like that. You make me sound like the crazy person. I'm just saying docking tails for pure aesthetic purposes is wrong and the fact that you don't remember the pain does not make it acceptable. That's especially applies to circumcision. Unless it's your religious beliefs, no way can putting a baby through pain be acceptable. I'm from the uk. Only reason babies are circumcised over here is religious. I'm assuming your America where I here it's more common the other way round. 
Puppies   babies might not remember the pain but as a human being the thought of putting them from any type of pain. For aesthetic reasons only. Is unacceptable. In my opinion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 22:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good mate. Your Internet famous now. 
It got removed cause I used word fag. Which is just a cigarette here in uk but Usa ents. Have different meaning for the word lol. I've had loads of post removed. Mods don't like me in most subs. 
Appreciate the message bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 19:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You decide to compare docking tails to being circumcised. Should've realised then arguing with you would be pointless at the point. Good luck with cutting tails off puppies   chopping the dicks of little boys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
