<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the first person you ever fell in love with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dark Dick Rises. I shouldn't have to explain that one; pitch meeting's over, boys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What mild inconvenience really pisses you off without fail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What annoys you most about online dating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be snowed in all weekend. I live in Raleigh, NC, and one of the top posts on Reddit today gave me a brutal premonition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So happy for ya! I'm hoping the same goes for me. I have a big phone call tomorrow with the company I'm a contractor for to see if I can become a permanent full-time employee. Would be my first job after graduation - it's been almost 3 years. I need this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, everyone. After reading through all the comments thus far, I thought I'd recommend listening to podcasts. There's a podcast for virtually everything that's been discussed. I listen to Lori Harder's "Earn Your Happy" podcast and it really helps my anxiety/depression. There's a world of sources out there to help you, just keep digging! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, just let it all out - how are you feeling right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you trying to get really good at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Reddit classic available on Showtime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 04:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 05:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now calm down Skeeter he ain't hurtin' nobody." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men of Reddit, if you were going to contribute a chapter to The Universal Guide to Understanding Women, what would the title of that chapter be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat is a vampire bat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminded me to shower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow that'll become a hit tv show with a laugh track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That it smells like fish. Turns out I'm not entirely wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't like to beat around the bush. Would you like to beat around my bush?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American television in general, and I'm American. There's almost never a reason for a show to need 100+ episodes to tell its story. That's why Breaking Bad kicks ass - quality over quantity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What ridiculously exaggerated job titles can you come up with without giving away what the real job is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
