<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [POLISHED] addictedtochapstick   itjustintright have some goodies coming in the mail!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thanks!] New Mani with CG For Audrey and Rainbow Honey The Worst Possible Thing. You're the best Cinsare!!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 02:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 02:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're very welcome!! Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 03:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my For Audrey!! It's soooo pretty! Now to figure out what design to do next... Ooooh! Got it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 19:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw this!! Thank you so, so much!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 19:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it. Kinda along the same theme as medium. And the same actress as Dollhouse. It was good and I like Eliza Dushku. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 18:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Pushing Daisies

-Jericho

-Dollhouse

-Tru Calling

-Medium - Oh how I loved Medium!!

And I'm going to go on a rant and say that these stupid TV channel companies cut shows WAAAYYY too soon. They don't even give them a chance before pulling the plug! Some story lines take longer to get into than others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [POLISHED] anjjelikka - Just because. A random pick. ;) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 05:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 05:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Zoya - SOOOOO pretty!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 05:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want, I want, I WANT!!! Lucky girl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 05:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had long nails! Even if mine were HALF the length of yours I'd be happy. I'm using Nail Magic so I have some hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who works 7 days a week and doesn't have enough money to pay a decent wage? I'm a single mother and neglected to mention that someone in that area may be interested. It would require very little effort on their part, especially if their child is going to the same school. Of course if that were the case, I would get him ready myself. The area is upscale so most mothers don't work and I'm sure they'd enjoy some spare change. 

No need to be snarky about my request. Thanks for your unhelpful comment. I was very aware of the hourly wage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome idea! I'm stealing it! :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 18:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Post a pic of yours when you're done. I wanna see! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
