<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4680</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 10:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't really write all that often so I don't think it's a problem for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I keep playing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear r/WOW,

I have attempted to play WOW for three times in the past week because I have several friends who play. 

I simply cannot enjoy it, or at least the tutorial levels. 

Does the game get better?

Basically what I'm asking is, should I muscle through the tutorial area or should I give up now if I'm not enjoying it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pokemon war fan theory confirmed??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 03:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This card exists in a strange position of only being good because your opponent never expects it. If you play it in the late game, they're going to think its something else most of the time. 

If it became popular it'd be horrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait if he's a general of the old gods why are his stats three times higher than theirs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 03:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah shit card BGH counters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Blackrock or not to Blackrock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 05:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey!
I'm just looking for some friendly advice. 

I've been playing Hearthstone for a few months and I'm really really enjoying it. I have both Naxx and LoE and I was wondering if BR is worth buying. Some of the cards look interesting but I'm not entirely sure how useful it would be. Thoughts?
Is it worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 09:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but what about once you install it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to access shotgun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 09:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey!

I pre-ordered the game and can't access the shotgun and other things that come with it. Anyone know how to find it?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 08:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the many, many people who will think British coins have Harry Potter characters on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stable internet connection OP PLZ rebalance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 22:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 13:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe try reading books by authors renowned for their prose, such as Nabokov or Pynchon or Wallace. 

Reading nice prose helps people speak, generally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does essence affect artistic ability? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 00:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eiger Allan Poe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 10:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me this is a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 09:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello!

He is... Relatively speaking. Sadly, he's very anxious due to abuse from the owners he had before us, and so he has a habit of freaking out, although those have been getting better. 

We're not quite sure when we would need someone to look after him for a period of time, but it's possible we'll need a long-term sitter for him for nine months starting September of next year. 

Edit: Just realized I sent this as a reply and not a PM. Sorry. Respond with that if you'd prefer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 02:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We started dating my Freshmen year of high school. We both had some issues. I was suffering from severe depression and she was struggling with PTSD, so high school wasn't exactly easy for us, and neither was our relationship, but we managed to make it work so we could both take care of ourselves and wouldn't become dependent. 

We've always had each other's backs, I guess, and it's just kind of naturally evolved into something a lot more than a relationship. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I'm so impressed with your hip cynicism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 00:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a long story, but trust me, it's not as bad as it seems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: I think Stanley Kubrick's movies are dumb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 00:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone willing to help a young couple? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 00:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear /r/askportland, 

My girlfriend and I are young and are heading off to college together next year. However, neither of our parents are willing to take in our dog while we're in the dorms and can't have pets.
i know this seems like an odd request, but, if things go south, would anyone be willing to take him in?
He's an Australian shepherd named Frank. Relatively young, energetic, and the most loving dog I've ever seen in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone want to help out a young couple? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 00:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear /r/SaltLakeCity

My girlfriend and I are young and are heading off to college together next year. However, neither of our parents are willing to take in our dog while we're in the dorms and can't have pets. 

i know this seems like an odd request, but, if things go south, would anyone be willing to take him in?

He's an Australian shepherd named Frank. Relatively young, energetic, and the most loving dog I've ever seen in my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 22:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those things are everything bad in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 00:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree with that. NPC wise the game is really good about it. I guess there are just a lot of lore points that are sketchy. 

I agree. Lucatiel is the bomb-diggity. She sums up a lot of the themes beautifully.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 23:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not universal but a lot of the female characters are portrayed as manipulative and cold. One or two characters like that is fine, IMO, but it sometimes gets a little sketchy, especially with the daughters of manus. The emerald Harold is arguably among these characters, depending on your interpretation of the lore, Licia, Mytha, etc etc etc. just a lot of cold, spiteful women who fuck shit up for men and that's the vast majority of the female representation. 

Lucatiel is cool, IMO. And the daughter of manus in the ivory king DLC goes a long way to making up for the other daughters. Although the whole prospect of her needing a man to show her morality is a little weird, but that might be reading too far into it. 

Also Rosabeth. I have no idea what the implications of being able to dress her up however you want might be, but I think it's honestly too dumb to read into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 22:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 21:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the two games are VERY different. 

First off, in the lore department. In DS1, the story is centered around a macro-story, without too many sub-stories besides NPCs. DS2 is the opposite, with the stories of many kingdoms being told throughout the game. The lore is more thematically based and has a stronger human element as opposed to godly forces. That being said, the story occasionally has less strong bits, and also struggles with a fair bit of sexism, if you ask me, although that's not the case with every character. Also there's some dumb "dark edginess" that's occasionally eye-roll worthy. But once again, this isn't always. 
The story is also built around themes of disappointment, degradation, and loss. So expect the game to pull some crazy tricks on you. 

Gameplay wise, it's not as hard as DS1. It includes a lot of easy buttons for players that want them. Like NPC summons that make things incredibly easy. If you don't take those easy buttons, it's very intense and difficult, though. 

PvP and co-op wise it's a million times better. More viable builds. Faster and easier access. 
Well, except soul memory. Which is shitty. But you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can people in NG sunbro people in NG+? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 01:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep hearing conflicting things. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 21:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats, man. I'm happy for you for getting to visit her. Long distance is rough, man. Good job holding onto it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 21:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure? I've always heard you do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Havel-noob extermination? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 08:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone cool with exterminating the Havel-noobs?

Alright, cool, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Places to sunbro at the endgame? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 07:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, so, I'm at 2Mil SM and I was wondering where the best places to sunbro are, as I need to rake in sunlight medals. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 01:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey. Not sure if you're still looking, but I can get you that, friend. 

You have any twinkling titanite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chariot help? [x-post r/darksouls2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 08:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I'm SM 1mil trying to take down the chariot. I'm really struggling, especially with it being a shieldless run. Anyone willing to give me some help?

I'm on PS4 SOTFS 
Username: Spatialsnake904 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weapons for a cleric? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 05:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I've been building my first PvP build and good lord am I having fun. 

It's been awesome, but I'm still in need of a weapon. Frequently, players get too close and can poise break me before I can cast anything. I'm looking for a weapon that might solve this problem, and just a good offhand weapon in general. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 22:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously though!
I think I died more to him than most bosses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone willing to trade LITERALLY ANYTHING for wrath of the gods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 04:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making a faith build and I'm loving it, but I swear to god, it's pretty much impossible to level up in the blue sentinels enough to get it. 

My run is shieldless so any shield in the game, and most weapons I'm perfectly happy to give you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 22:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try changing out your equipment for better fire resistance. You can survive a couple fire breaths if you do it right. 
Suit up for your environment!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's old as shit now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I was in the same spot. 

Dark Souls sometimes makes you question your play style. Try to make it so you can roll well and learn to roll. 

You can beat it as a strength build but it's a hell of a lot harder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 00:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure nothing exists other than dark souls  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DS2 SOTFS PS4 SM860k Giants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 20:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I'm really struggling with the giants in the black gulch. Can anyone help? My username is Spatialsnake904 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To BlueBro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 11:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell do I get summoned as a blue sentinel? Are there any particular places or levels that work best? I am human and have the ring etc etc etc. I just can't seem to be summoned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Dark Souls] Solaire helped Gwynevere escape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 09:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This theory is pretty much blatantly wrong, canon wise, but I like to imagine that the reason Solaire (Assuming he is Gwyn's firstborn) was ousted from Anor Londo was because he helped Gwynevere leave the city with her husband, thus enraging Gwyn, who was desperately holding on to his daughter, and being exiled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4] [SOTFS] Sihn, The Slumbering Dragon SL 128, SM 2 Mil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 00:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pls help
SpatialSnake904 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 07:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to our club, friend! It sucks but it's worth it. I hope it goes well. If you ever need advice, feel free to PM me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And we're back... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a year apart, we had an amazing summer together. I just arrived back home... If we make it through this year we get to move in together. Let's hope this goes okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 07:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about all the commenters that can't recognize satire _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I drive by that every day!

Sorry. Just surprised to see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 01:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't wanna sound like a try-hard, but Gravity's Rainbow, as I recently explored Lot 49 for a class, and good lord, I've never felt so challenged by a book. Pynchon truly pushes rhetoric to its limit. 

I think it's very interesting how Pynchon explore the idea of Post-Modern spirituality, and genuinely seeks to empower his readers and communicate incredibly complicated truths, ideas, and warnings through fiction and words that he himself admits are worthless. 

Also it's just a hell of a lot of fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 03:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I thought I was the only one that did this. Every single time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friends, redditors, countrymen. Lend me your ears. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 02:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello friends! I'm /u/subject4680 

I've been modding this sub with /u/WastedUpvotes the past few days and I want to say a few things and ask a few questions about moderation. 

First of all, thanks guys! I didn't expect this sub to get more than say, twenty subscribers. Needless to say I'm shocked, impressed, and overjoyed that you guys want to find cool underrated games with me. 

As is stated in the sidebar, this sub is directly inspired by Extra Credits. And I would very much like to stay true to that inspiration, and so I would like this sub to be focused on two things: fun, and intelligent design in these games. That's what we're looking for. I would love this sub to act as a place to discuss these games from a design perspective as well. 
Furthermore, along with EC, I would like this to be a community united in the idea that games matter. That being said, no game should just be written off. Even the worst games are worth learning from. So no bashing in the comments please. And toxicity and elitism of any kind isn't going to be tolerated. That is non-negotiable. 

So let's love on to some questions. I have no idea how to run a subreddit and have very little time to moderate. So I'd like to turn to you guys when problems arise and hope you guys want to sort them out and make this a better subreddit. 

I guess the first problem we should probably take care of is what defines a "game you might not know"? Obviously, a few of us (or even a lot of us sometimes) will know about a game on this subreddit that nonetheless, deserves or needs more publicity. So we can't just write off everything we've heard of. However, we don't want this sub to become a shithole of wannabe hipsters saying "OMFG HAV U HERD OF MINCRAFT"...... Exaggerating of course. 

So I think it'd be best for us to come up with some solid empirical rules. 

Here's a few I thought of.

1. Games that can be seen on, or were recently featured on, the front page of Steam will be rejected. 
2. Games that have sold more than (no fucking clue what number should go here) units will be kicked out immediately 
3. Games that have been featured in a popular gaming magazine or review site will be terminated. 


Thoughts?

Oh also! If you read all the way to the bottom of this post I'm assuming this sub seems interesting to you. If that's the case, wanna help mod? PM me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 02:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I'm thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 02:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider myself a fairly middle of the road gamer. I hear about things that have become popular and the occasional "hidden gem" and indie games. Given that I have heard of one of those three, I'll allow it. I agree that a lot of things have no place here. If someone was to post say, Minecraft or Psychonauts, or maybe even System Shock, that wouldn't fly. 

And we shouldn't limit ourselves to indie games. 

Maybe the rule should be "if you know less than two people personally who know what this game is, go ahead and post it." Although that creates its own host of problems.... I don't know. I'll think about it. I don't want this post to become a circle-jerk of idiots that think they're hipsters, but I also don't want it to be something interesting only to the most hardcore of gamers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 22:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input! I considered the idea but to be honest I'm not fond of the way we label games by genre. They tend to say very little. I would try to come up with a new labeling system but I'm way too lazy for that. So until we get some good ideas on how to define game genres, I'll wait on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Risk Of Rain- A rogue-like... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 02:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rogue like... Thing. It's an action platformer focused mostly on getting resources, using them to buy randomized items, and learning to master different classes with unique abilities. The different classes feel truly unique and none of them feel quite like playing any of the others. 

I dumped a stupid amount of time into this and I loved every second of it. 

http://store.steampowered.com/app/248820/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I created a new subreddit for suggesting awesome underrated games! Please come join us in finding amazing games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 23:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 22:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike! I have come from the future to tell you something incredibly important! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 02:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second that. All of the fights in my LDR have happened because of miscommunication.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Gods does this very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a book like East of Eden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read EoE about a year ago and it changed my life and got me into literature. With almost a biblical epicness it is deeply compassionate, emotional and all around amazing. I've been looking for something like it every since. 

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 00:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladd Russo's personal hero? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 20:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...
Is that your roommate's skull?
_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 23:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like no book teaches compassion quite as well as East of Eden, or really most Steinbeck books. But preferably East of Eden. It's long, but worth every second of it. I generally have a horribly short attention span and I didn't struggle as I thought I would. 

The Sound and The Fury helped me with a similar problem, but you definitely have to be viewing it through the right lens, thinking about how being more compassionate and forgiving could help, by looking at really really cynical and pretentious characters. So it could work, but it could go either way. Either way, that's my two cents. Good luck, friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think a ghost might have talked to me at Ted Bundy's house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 09:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few nights ago my girlfriend took me to Ted Bundy's creepy little basement in the woods as she rather likes those creepy sort of things. We were walking through the woods for a while and it was not quite dark. The sun was starting to set. 

I was in my normal state of mind as we walked. I'm usually a pretty skipping-through-the-daisies person, living my life going along, a little bit dazed. 

We came to what just looked like a door into the mountain, steel with a window cut out of it. 

When I saw it I became alert, suddenly a bit confused. My girlfriend later told me I said "this is wrong" as soon as I saw it. 

I turned on the flashlight on my phone and peered through the window. I looked down it for a little while, staring down a cement stairway. I jumped, and shouted, and ran suddenly. "What's going on, what did you see." "We need to leave this is wrong something's wrong" I kept saying over and over again, dragging her out of the woods as she laughed and called me a pussy. 

I don't remember seeing anything. It felt like I did see something. But I can't identify it. As the pain faded another emotion took its place. Fear, but not "I'm afraid I will be hurt" sort of fear. It was a defeated fear, as if I knew I was going to die and there was going to be so much pain and there was nothing I could do about it. And I couldn't get the imagine of that stairway out of my head. I kept seeing it and dirty blonde hair falling in front of my face, in a few strands. I have short brown hair. I didn't have this memory, but it was as if I was vividly recalling being dragged down that staircase, crying. 

As we drove off I heard a noise too. I would have thought it was ringing in my ears but it sounded... Prettier I guess. It sounded like some metal spinning quickly on a machine. A power tool sorta noise. 

It moved in what felt like intentional patterns around my head and body. 

Time passed and by the time we got home I couldn't hear it anymore and I felt perfectly fine. Normal as ever. 

What do you think happened? Could I just have been very spooked?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 22:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I had a shitting technique named after me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 22:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timshel, friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 02:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Father VS Hohenheim! FMA:B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
