<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movies, songs, shows, chatting to a native speaker, school, practicing accent, thinking in English etc. Basically you have to indulge in the culture to learn as much as you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bitter gourd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just called her once. I don't know why it was such a big deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have given up on life. She was chatting to me and it wasn't bad. It was a friendly chat. Then one day I called...and from then on she avoided me like a plague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called her. She thought I was a creep. Blocked me from every social media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think women always have the option to marry a rich guy if she can't work for herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can piss you off without saying anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let the facts get in the way of a cool story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he would always eat too much food knowing fully well about tight budget. Most of my group members hated each other and we rarely hung out together. Safe to say I didn't have a lot of my fun at my second school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend that doesn't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pep-si is sex-y. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billie Jean is not my lover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'd drink Pepsi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just can't see others having what I want and take it for granted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writing "mate" in every sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you fucking mosquitoes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mom. She isn't picking up my call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating and enchanting. Because they're so....*magical* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a beautiful girl. I feel tingling in my balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube is your friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk for at least 30 minutes everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1- You will need your friends one day. You might not realize it but make sure to keep your friends close because they're your family outside of immediate family.  

2- Don't think you're invincible or perfect. More often you'd not be able to do things alone, make sure to appreciate the people in your lives. Many of us take them for granted.  

3- It's not necessary to be super talented or super famous like Harry Potter to get girls. You just have to express yourself and don't hold back. Confidence can take you far instead of fame.  

4- Love genuinely if you want to love someone.  

5- Remember one moment can change your life for the better or worse. Be humble.  

6- Last but not the least it feels awesome to fuck your best friend's sister! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insecurities. Everyone is insecure about something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No dude OP's mom is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who wants to have sex with their teacher/s, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who lie to get attention and be "famous". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loneliness, hopelessness, worthlessness etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those gigantic boobs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well for starters he hacked my facebook account few years ago and read my private messages. He then posted shit about me on a website and pretended he doesn't know who did it. When I  found out it was him I wanted to beat the shit out of him but for some reason, I decided it was a mistake and let it go.  
After maybe 1  or two years he DID it again but this time only read my messages and didn't post shit about me. I felt betrayed but I still forgave him.  
Then when I was having the hardest time in my life because of my alcoholic father I needed someone to brighten my day. He vanished and I was alone battling domestic violence and emotional pain. Turns out he had a girlfriend for 1 and a half year and he only told me about it when they broke up. So, telling me when it was all done and dusted was pointless and he used to vent about it in front of me because I listened. When I tried to talk about the REAL bad things that have happened to me, i.e, talking about job pressure at the age of 17-18 by my relatives(because my dad doesn't work and they're tired of giving us money), my mother being ill, facing the domestic violence, getting shit from teachers for not  focusing enough, getting ignored by girls, emotional and mental pain etc. he would say "let's talk about something else, something positive etc." Told me to think positive when REALLY BAD things are clearly happening to me.  
I told him about my crush and she obviously rejected me(who wouldn't because I have been through shit and I can't have "fun" and I am not "fun" to be around), the douchebag started talking to her and would show me their conversations( those were only friendly though) and would show me her pics deliberately when I was trying to forget about her.  
Once my phone got stolen when we were walking and he suspected that it might happen. What he does then? Instead of dragging me along he walked ahead leaving me behind and I didn't see it coming and it got stolen. He later told me thieves are stealing stuff with this approach these days in this area. If only he told me before or at least dragged me along with him and not leave me behind my phone would have been saved.  
He keeps telling me I am lazy when I am clearly down and depressed these days. The clown actually studies psychology and claims to "know" lots of things about it yet can't see it when a person is depressed(FYI I was a psychology student as well and people tell me I am a great listener).  
Lastly, he helps out the people who only talk to him when they need something but I have been with him when he needed someone the most and yet he always screws me up.  
I am currently enrolled in a course with him and I would like to get away from him permanently once it finishes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My "best friend" who has betrayed me a number of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A walk to remember, and Hardy Boys is a good one too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I stop feeling jealous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to stop feeling jealous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not comparing with celebrities. I meant do small musicians who don't really have a fanbase and are struggling. Do they have an easy time getting laid based on your observation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't either. Hence, asking the question for validation. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think being confident goes a long way and you don't necessarily need a talent to show off to get laid? Is confidence a bigger key than the talent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to see things from their eyes and you will realize that they suffer and those are no lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in that case every celebrity has a better chance to get laid. Do you think you can't get laid if you have no talent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does that mean if you're not a musician you can't get laid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaden Smith saying I was raised by the power of will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe 13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BQ: Does sportsmen get laid more than musicians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Why is it easier to get laid for musicians? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For someone who is craving the warmth of having a partner it was good to read and a reality-check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy everything in theory and nothing in practice. For example  I'd like to try more sports but in practice I am always a couch potato. At most I'd go for jogging or weight lifting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to be an adult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg! Same here. Can we be roommates? We'll support each other. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apathy. I just don't care about anything. I am a broken soul. Want a refund or a replacement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should a person do if only bad things happen to him all the time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am new here and after reading FAQ, rules, benefits etc. I still have no idea what I should be doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Reddit gold because I want to know what it feels like. And my biggest wish in life is to say "Thanks for the gold kind stranger".  
Edit: OMG! I got the gold. So, here we go..... Thanks for the gold kind stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that really sucks then. I don't know what else to say. I  say just  enjoy your own life and do your own thing. Just try to have a grand time because no one gives a fuck so why not just go batshit crazy and do whatever you want to do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are pretentious bastards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is ..depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't answer a question that is asked hundreds of times on Askreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play easy pranks on your friends,  ride a bicycle,  read a book, do  something you suck at(you might improve). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Why are Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram a waste of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you're still young and life is more than high school bullshit. Believe me, it won't matter once you graduate. Working out and going to the gym can turn your life around. Pick up an art as a hobby as well. People love art and girls like muscular guys. If you have both of them to an extent then you can lead an average life at least. That's what I think.  
People think I am a "cool" dude because I look somewhat good and I do artsy stuff especially poetry. I also run fast and I am somewhat fit but not muscular. It's just my depression keeps telling me how big of a loser I am but most people from outside think I am "cool". They don't mind talking to me. Depression is hell but having hobbies and working out will make you more presentable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's stay in contact and see where we end up. What do you say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you man. Talk to me. I want to talk as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk man! I am having extremely negative thoughts. They won't stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Society is selfish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to live but I have to because the society will be hurt by  my demise. My family will be hurt. My friends might be hurt. It is selfish. They're keeping me alive for themselves and no one is there for me when I need them. Why don't they let me go and end my suffering?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good advice. Real world often won't care about your dreams. If you want something to happen you have to MAKE them happen otherwise be reasonable and remember there's nothing wrong with choosing a safe path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't really go away I guess. It becomes a part of you. I think you can manage it to function in society but it doesn't go away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to watch music videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's creepy. Fucking a 16 year old? That too his cousin? When he's already married! What the fuck? Was it consensual? Isn't it rape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! That's  the beauty of well written stories. This is why you should  read  novels as well. You can feel as if you're there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drowning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't invest your time in social media likes. Rather build actual relationships with people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find true love, a job that I enjoy and me and my gf never cheat on each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also dropped out not because of depression but other reasons.  But depression is hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you dirty little cow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask about their regrets in life or what do they miss the most about high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you sleep so much? Bitch, I can't sleep at night so I sleep during the day. Why is it so wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel EXACTLY like you. Please be my friend. The real ones I have around me don't give a fuck at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS EXACT FUCKING thing happened to me last year in college. I have dropped out and I feel as if I am stuck now. I HATE to see people being happy. I hate it when  my friends are having fun. I want to see them having problems and NOT be positive all the time. I am so bitter. I am  disgusting. I fear I am turning into a sadist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/subject6388 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just can't move on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short I just can't move on. I had a rough childhood and to this day I am unable to move on. I am 19 and male. I see people around me having fun, going out with their gf/bf/friends etc., building new relationships and having a grand time. Here I am stuck in my mind. Lost motivation, lost my will to live. I don't enjoy anything. I am bitter and that drives people away. Apparently, no one wants a bitter guy in their life. No one gives a toss about me. Hell! I don't care. I myself don't give a fuck about me so it doesn't matter if someone else does.  
I don't know if I will ever be able to get out of this. It's 3:45 AM and I am typing this stuff right now because I can't sleep! I get ridiculed for sleeping too much while in reality I usually sleep in the morning and never at night. Why the fuck people don't understand that my father was an alcoholic douche who used to claim he was a "nice" and "innocent" guy?I have went through abuse and no one gives a single fuck! They just want me to pretend I am happy because they want only "happy people" in their life.  
At this point I have no friends and no one who genuinely cares. Please give me some advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What is your favorite book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you still in that house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some bad news buddy..some bad news.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact reddit is the last place we should take advice on. Pretty much the whole internet you can say because no one really knows what's going on in your life. You never know who is giving advice either. Whether they're actually intelligent or they're just here because they've nothing to do in their lives. So, I think reddit is just fun stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A beautiful place that was destroyed by criminals named anxiety, depression, low self esteem, self hatred etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shortcuts. Read, write everyday. Join forums or a community who share similar interests. Be determined. Be humble because you always have a lot to learn. You're never perfect. There is always something to learn. Remember, there are no shortcuts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That life struggles are a real thing and we can't always pamper you and treat like a fucking princess. Don't pretend that everything is always good and positive. Shit Fucking happens whether you like it or not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who did some bad shit to me as adolescents. I thought I should ignore it and tried to forget it. It's now 6 years of our friendship and I realize how miserable I feel. He keeps talking about him and I have faced real troubles yet he won't listen to me.  
The friendship sucks and I was right back then when I thought of boycotting him. My life gets 10x worse when I am with him. It's best to drift apart. In hindsight, this friendship has really sucked and probably one of the worst I have ever had. Funny thing is people usually think we're best friends(lol). The reality is it's the  shittiest friendship ever which has gone on to 6 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spend some. More importantly invest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what to do when your life is hell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, some people can't have their priorities right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend like this as well. He used to steal other's songs and claim he sung it. Now a days he keeps sending small audio clips of either music or him singing to impress people. He once said "girls love musicians". While I think that is true, another important thing to note  is that to build a relationship you still need to care about the other person and get to know them.  
All he does is send these clips on whatsapp and then proceeds on to ignore others. I have a project to make with him which we had to complete within 2 weeks and now we have taken over 5-6 weeks because apparently he's always "busy". Well, I think he has to set his priorities straight and do the work that matters. Sorry for the rant but I can understand how you feel. I hate pretentious bastards like that. I plan on to cut contact with this guy once I finish this project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College. I dropped out this semester and I haven't read anything for a long time except stories on r/nosleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you instantly lose respect for someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studying. I have lost motivation. In fact lately I have been pretty depressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the hobbies everyone should explore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to train your friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What if we are just a figment of someone's imagination? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk in the park is always a walk to remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend keeps sending audio files on whatsapp to many people. Well, I don't know his intentions but it comes across as showing off to me. It's okay to get feedback but sending your audio  every other day to so many people seems as if he's just trying to impress them. I don't tell him it's weird because he once said "My life, my rules" over something. So, I don't bother telling him much these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am doing well. Did some jogging with an old mate. I'd say I had my fair share of troubles today but I survived so I am not complaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, socializing, life stresses, high school, college etc. Gets hard to find time to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I wasn't expecting that girl to text me after not replying for 4-5 days but then I logged in my FB account and she had sent a beautiful poem written by her. Will see where it goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I used to read books late at night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dropped out this semester. I don't live in USA though. I can understand how you feel. I have been tired and depressed and what not for as long as I can remember. You should take comfort in knowing that there are truly broken souls like me who sleeps away at least 8-12 hours a day. I am really scared for myself because I don't have motivation for anything. You're better off as compared to a lot of people. Hang in there!  
Also, it will be good for you to relax once in a while. I suggest body massage or just a hot bath after a long day. You can try meditation if you want as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learning it the hard way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being one of the topper in last year of high school, my creative writing and my deep voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best advice you have ever received? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm yours by Jason Mraz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I am searching for the meaning of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I think in Asian and Indian culture, losing your virginity is not really a big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/nosleep
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teen years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Asian culture? What's their average? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
