<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9440</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what? You fucking assholes have done it.  I'm not buying the game now.  I'm done.  I was planning to buy it when it was on sale but im sick of being downvoted over this bullshit.  Fuck all of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lTzByQTeyJQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with Season 1 was that they didn't know what the show was when they started filming it.  They gave us two characters with identical abilities, and wrap them up in the main plot with the villain.  Which ended up bogging everything down because none of them were interesting.  BUT, Season 1 had moments of greatness.  There were several episodes that didn't deal with the hawk idiots or the main plot and they were just way better than they had any right to be.  I knew as a viewer that those episodes meant that they figured out what the show is, they just couldn't do much about it during the first season.  Then season 2 starts and [Boom](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w9X6R57WcUg).  
  
Season 2 will be on Netflix in 8 days.  You will love it, I swear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought Deus Ex Mankind (X-Box One) in January for $12 new from Best Buy.  That was six months from release.  
  
Edit : [Proof](http://i.imgur.com/TKDmBfp.png)  
  
Edit 2 : Also, I bought Titanfall 2 for $26.  Battlefield 1 for $28.  Mirror's Edge 2 for $15.  Horizon 3 for $38.  All last year, and all at a massive discount.  Hell thats $181 dollars that I saved by waiting under a year.  Don't call me crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harvey : Name 6 things that you like to do in bed.  
Contestant : Anal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course Mick grabs the waverider. lol   I really hope he is on the team next year.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember watching the trailer for this and wondering why the hell Adam McKay directed it.  It just didn't make sense.  Then I rented the movie [and it all clicked.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=anSPG0TPf84) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Years?  You either have no idea how games are priced after release or are very delusional.  Watch Dogs 2 has been out for 5 months and you can get it right now for $30.  I've seen it as low as $20 a month ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that would be funny.  He buys his first costume off of Amazon and he gets a bright pink shirt and pants on accident.  Daredevil going out every night wearing bright pink with literally no idea.  He finds out a few days later when the papers start calling him the Flamengo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt is more observant.  I mean come on, are you blind?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a man playing his mom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it might be playable in a year?  Cool, I'll get it for $10.  
  
Edit : Ok, well... point taken.  I'll just wait until its GWG.  Thanks, reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [But we've already seen Quake's arse.](https://gfycat.com/TanIncredibleBurro) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I learned anything from watching porn, you'd want that hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the same. :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed? 
  
Edit : Googled it.  Hot damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still bums me out.  The one show I really want and its so far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  They don't exist.  *looks around the room nervously*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Remember this from a few years ago at NBC?](https://www.facebook.com/notes/thisis50/wtf-nbcs-black-history-month-menu-exposed-by-questlove-on-twitter/287015733050/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its easy.  
  
They can do whatever they want, unless they are told they can't.  The only exception is if they have to do it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Patton Oswalt talked about doing Blade with him, and you all owe it too yourseves to read it.](http://www.geeksofdoom.com/2012/11/21/patton-oswalt-gets-brutally-honest-about-the-failures-of-blade-trinity) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't use that switch in the dock.  The heat from the overclocked processor combined with the enclosed nature of the dock is literally warping the devices.  The games and SD cards are also melting inside the device. This console is on the cusp of a massive recall.  
  
Edit : Seriously?  Downvotes for trying to help someone?  Its not my fault the dock is faulty and causing these problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The controller releases a 120 volt zap to one of players based on a complicated skillz algorithm.  Microsoft has already reported they will be implementing the skillz algorithm during solo play to help n00bs learn the ropes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The finale is tonight and based on the new netflix deal, the second season could actually be up next month.  Crazy Ex Girlfriend was up a few weeks after it ended this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how time works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best show on CW after Arrow this year.  Sara Lance fucking rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actors have PR clauses in their contracts.  They are forbidden from saying stuff like this in the press.  So he said something, broke his contract and Sony made him turn around and say that.  Thats how that works.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cnn.com/2015/10/08/entertainment/daniel-craig-james-bond-feat/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lost my shit like this over computer shit before.  In IT, you deal with a lot of stupid fucking people who all think they know more than you.  Hell the other day our secretary called me at lunch and demanded I come back because her computer stopped working.  Her fucking monitor was off.  Man that day sucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He turned down 120 Million for two more films.  I really doubt this is real.  He doesn't want to do it again.  Hell, you could see it on his face during the last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats all over his face?  Is that just shitty gif noise or did they spray some kinda motion tracking paint all over him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Playtest". Season 3 of Black Mirror on Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : The McRib is only available when the price of pork is low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next episode..
  
Rick : We need a buncha free shit from Apple Morty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the character model from Arkham Knight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait?  What?  Oh... you're talking about those weird comments at the bottom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats fucking awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Barrowman using a mirror for this?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got Darksiders this weekend which is great.  Never played it before and having a blast with it.  Just beat that douchebag dragon boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite was when you piss of Yenn and she teleports you into the ocean.  Close second is the fakeout three way between Yenn and Triss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Showtime : What are these?  
*holds out a pair of dice.*  
Ron : Dice?  
Showtime : You're hired! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can Confirm : Used it exclusively at the brothel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat would sit on my shoulder like a parrot every time I would have a bowl of ice cream.  She assumed I didn't know she was there, and would sniff every bite.  After she died I couldn't eat ice cream anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cinnamon Life cereal is the shit, dry.  I eat it out of the box as a snack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, I watched this video three times this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone said it was an ad for tape, so I replied to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't want to be hasty.  Having a means of destroying the spear could have potentially locked him in a terrible universe with no escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You named your kid tatertot?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vincent Donofrio owns that role.  He sold [that speech](https://youtu.be/vyqXwlkBjpA) at the end of the Second Season when he allows Frank to leave.  It was just so great.  Go kill my competition because you mean absolutely nothing to me.  Killgrave was very selfish and depraved, but he didn't really have a scene like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you do the frying pan mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of content this game has means that a lot of people haven't seen most of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Anne Hathaway started a new race of humans that evolved into the fifth dimensional beings that made the wormhole, tesseract and Copper Station possible.](#spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure.  Sometimes the mods out right ban users.  Other times they shadowban so the user doesn't know hes been banned.  Were you banned before?  Maybe you kept breaking the same rule?  You could message the mods and ask them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The torture episode.  Josh spent that entire episode with Stephen.  Amell tweeted it was a first for the series. He had no other scenes with the rest of the cast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand [This was one of my all time favorite fights on the show](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SqhIWNxUcPQ) on the other [Shit like this happens all the time on Legends](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5NpiggD54mo).  It's really a hard damn decision.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes playing someone who treats people with respect and dignity?  Uh...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and there were still people who didn't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the next season they are hiring younger doppelgangers for the cast for flashbacks and using the full cast together for present day.  Obviously the switch between past and present is being used to bridge the gap on the various actor's schedules.  
  
Also, this won't work.  They can't find younger people that can hold a candle to Will Arnett, Jason Bateman, David Cross, Tony Hale or Jeffrey Tambor.  It's impossible.  Their comedy timing is what made the show popular.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I saw that movie was in IMAX.  I got so nervous at the end.  I gripped the armrest and started looking away because I didn't want to see his fate.  Great movie, I wish more people actually got what the ending "meant".  I hate how everything has to spelled out or the general population won't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its probally bending because of the mobile CPU and no proper ventilation. I would assume that the mobile processor is heating up more in dock mode (because dock mode overclocks) and the heat is being trapped by the plastic wall.  This is very similar to what happened to the X-Box 360.  The chips got so hot that they literally popped off the mobo.  If the switch is bending after a month then I would assume the handheld will be rendered useless in a few months.  
  
It's odd that Nintendo didn't see this coming.  It would have been pretty easy to install a fan to blow up through the slot and suck the air out of the base.  Kinda makes me wonder if the Switch was something else and this dock TV station thing was added in the last minute.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And its building.  This showdown between Oliver's monster and Prometheus is going to rival the Slade vs Arrow fight.  Plus this year they clearly have money and they get Bam Bam to direct the major fight oriented episodes.  The finale this year will be epic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that chinese shit in his blood made him go crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't read the comics.  Is that a van full of gun toting nuns hes fighting?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its well worth it.  It's actually kinda funny, Ubisoft tapped into some "secret sauce" with this game that they have been unable to find in the last two games.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Crystal Dynamics ran out of money during the production of Rise of Tomb Raider and Square wouldn't help them.  This "exclusivity deal" was Microsoft giving them the money they needed to finish the game and loaning them their engineers to make the game better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garth Ennis said you physically couldn't adapt the comic book to live action.  There just too much stuff to process in a small amount of time.  It would be overwhelming. Thats why they stretched it out.  It was out of necessity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise would make a great Nathan Drake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have no idea why they killed Vass so early.  Should have been the main villian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you dip the fries in franch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a movie about that dude.  He mowed down an entire library with an ak47.  He was a bad ass.  One dude tried to karate him and buddha snapped his neck.  It was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've probably been shadow banned.  Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone said Watchmen was unfilmable and it was.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had a gun with two bullets and was in a room with Hitler, Toby and Bin Laden, I'd shoot Toby twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what im saying.  That game made them so ridiculously famous that they have to make another one.  They had billion dollar companies trying to buy their company.  They have AAA developers citing their game as *their* inspiration.  It's a much bigger deal than some people on reddit saying its great.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.  www.google.com  
2.  Type "cd projekt red isn't done with witcher"  
3.  [Pick one of the hundred fucking links.](https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant rlz=1C1CAFB_enUS644US646 ion=1 espv=2 ie=UTF-8#q=cd+projekt+red+isn't+done+with+witcher *) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was before it sold 25 Million copies and became one of the greatest games ever made.  Last week they said they might go back to Witcher and this week, new game.  Gee, that's a coincidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look funny without a face.  But good job.  I can't do that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't work, you will always been killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That girl is so hot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mom.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes it is.](https://youtu.be/wQ6A3GvEVo0?t=2m40s)  
  
Also im fairly sure the games take place after the novels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HBO has boobs.  *lawyered* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he calls someone an idiot, I miss that so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geralt isn't dead.  You could easily do another game.  Also Cyberpunk is a world Ciri Visited, btw.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's obviously a new Witcher game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love when Ron tells Leslie and she immediately wants to add seven meetings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking Bad.  While they were in their first season, Breaking Bad was cut short due to the writers strike.  The planned ending for the series had Jesse and Hank both being killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 is the shit.  It starts and you get sucked in by the villain and location.  The tutorial is awesome.   That game made the whole "learning new skills throughout the game" trope actually work organically. 4 starts and you're doing take downs with in the first five minutes.  Its bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has to do with drugs, grandpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a square.  It's gone now, [but I made it.](http://i.imgur.com/HbxJRFy.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You do the math -- Silicon Valley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She bought them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We doing pre-crime now?  Is Tom Cruise running the division?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 STARS!  
  
I CAN'T WAIT TO BUY THE REST OF THE GAME SEPARATELY! GAME OF THE YEAR! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try finding it, but if I remember right Sony went apeshit and got them all removed fairly quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They already released the theme song](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U1mlCPMYtPk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I watched this episode, I kept thinking his voice was trying to get her to kill herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even adapting the novels.  I still don't understand that decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the biggest issue.  
  
TOM ROTHMAN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The leaked trailer didn't look all that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Barry's phone rings*  
Barry : Hello?  
Oliver : Hi Barry.  
Barry : Hi, Oliver.  Hows it going?  
Oliver : I was just watching the news and saw that you opened a Hall of Justice with all these heroes.  
Barry : Yeah, we're called The Justice League.  
Oliver : So why didn't you call me?  
Barry : What?  
Oliver : Why didn't I get invited.  Im a hero.  
Barry : Yeah but you just shoot a bow.  
Oliver : Excuse me?  
Barry : Shit, sorry.  I'll send you an invite for you and your sidekicks.  
Oliver : Don't bother!  I'm going to start my own group, and you won't be invited.  And... we'll have cake every Wednesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get out of White Orchard?  The opening region and prologue serve as a tutorial.  The game doesn't open up and become truly amazing until after you kill the Griffin.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A set of leaked photos with full penetration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I thought you can't take the sky from me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speedsters have horrible peripheral vision.  They also occasionally forget they have powers until someone inexplicably reminds them.  Its their only real weakness.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's what that was?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also like how he had explosive knifes or something now.  There was no reference or anything to them before hand.  He just jumps through a window and throws something that explodes like it was normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : Seth Rogen sent Tatum an email asking if he wanted to do that scene in the movie around 3am.  Channing was "Drunk and on ambien" when he replayed to the email agreeing to doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thumbnail gave me a Metallica vibe.  Cool theme song, intro seems kinda long.  Reminds me of Westworld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he'll leave citing "Creative differences" in two weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else think he looks like George Clooney in this?  Not sure if its the hair or what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Humans need more animal blood. It keeps the spine straight." -- Dr Leo Spaceman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the first chick Ryan Reynolds kills in Voices?  
  
Edit : Just looked it up, [its Gemma Arterton.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JwKgme54_0g) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a TV show on showtime where the main guy got fired and spent three weeks in house just watching porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the season 3 story was utter bullshit.  This at least seems more in character.  We won't have a "SURPRISE!  I was working with the bad guy this whole time and totally faking it! LOLZ!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had his powers and a Speedster on his side.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the reviews for the first film slighted his performance because of his speech impediment.  Said it was annoying.  I thought it was pretty unique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Did anyone else notice this stunt man to actor transition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The action wasn't the best last night, but I really liked [this](https://youtu.be/Rgr3ZOwG0uk?t=1m) little technical thing they did.  Stunt guy starts it off, then Stephen takes over without a cut.  Kinda neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] I really like that he didn't put the hood back on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most TV shows have a magic reset button where everything is better by the end of the episode or season.  Its a common trope, sometimes its harder to spot but its usually there.  Anyway, I really like that they didn't reset Oliver by the end of the episode.  Going into the next episode he'll still be rattled from what happened.  It's very impressive and has me excited for the finale.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like you don't understand english. I know it had a way point system, I said its terrible and barely functional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People gave Sam Jackson's character a lot of hate for his speech impediment.  I actually liked his character.  It was unique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Heres a nice clip](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kdBa7VRwPqk)  
  
The stuff in court is just the best.  I can't wait for the trial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he went after the club and found that arm.  Such a great sub plot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes great in the show.  Every time hes in court he says the greatest shit.  I can't wait for the trial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a mess.  I couldn't play two hours during the trial without having to reset the game myself and a full on console crash shortly after.  I also spent around 20min trying to find an objective because the fucking waypoint marker is the worst.  I can't even fathom why someone would make an open world game and not have a functional way point system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have pretty bad osteoarthritis and these three hour movies are hell on my knees.  Would it kill them to put in an intermission? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pulled in the lot from lunch and the secretary starts knocking on my car door.  She said she needs help immediately. So I follow her into the building and head to my desk to drop off my coat.  She tells me again, its super important.  So I turn around and followed her back to her desk.  She said her monitor just stopped working in the middle of an important e-mail.  She had her coffee cup next the monitor and accidently hit the power button.  Its situations like this that make me go home and drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I flubbed the title.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't end with "Wally is more popular than me?  Better go back and fix this."    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore.  Last weeks was the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gavin and Jack are teaming up for the box.  Remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beginning of I Am Legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His script was two parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still bums me out that they got rid of Cary Fukunaga on this film.  They brought him on and he wanted to do an honest adaption of a King novel.  With actual characters and backstories.  The studio let him go because they just wanted a horror movie.  Normal character tropes and an evil thing killing them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pee Wee Herman got caught jacking off in a theatre full of people.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... 'This, Guy, Fucks,' ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew he deserved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He finds it amusing that these ants think they are his equals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  He said he got his powers back after he entered the new reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL The Mindy Project is still in production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was worried when Kevin Hart was in it.  Now I don't even care. I'll wait for Redbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was rolling at the con scene when he said he should of got him a hat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL The Whitest Kids You Know are currently back together and writing a movie.  
  
Edit : [Source,](https://www.instagram.com/p/BQZRyUYBwvn/) Since people who didn't know this apparently think im lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I paid $22 on Amazon for the 360 version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That part was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barrymore's schtick got old, but the humor came from Olyphant's inability to deal with the situation.  That guy made the show funny.  It was great seeing his comedy chops on display. I thoroughly welcome a second season of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might be trolling us again.  He did the same thing last week by showing off Felicity's mask concept art without any context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : When Warner told Nolan to shoot The Dark Knight in IMAX he pushed back the intended sequence because he didn't want to do it.  After he saw the first dailies of the footage he tried to shoot as much as he could in the format.  Thats why the second film is so such a hodgepodge of different aspect ratios.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats kinda his character.  The dudes a lovable idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with Season 1 was the writers didn't know what the show was when they started making it.  They shoved the villain and those coffee making hawk people into the show and made everything about them.  It was just wrong.  Season 2, they fixed that problem.  The hawks will never come back.  The villains are actually interesting.  And they have added an entire roster of characters that add to the universe instead of weighing it down.  It's a shame that nobody is watching it because of Season 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just him.  Legends has Darhk, Snart, Thawne and Merlyn.  They are all interesting as hell and actually have stuff to do.  Its great.   
  
Edit : Look how they [interact](https://youtu.be/NdAu2-HyWr8?t=41s) with one and other.  Its just gold.  And its not just them, the legends do it too.  The characters are just ridiculously on point this season.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would argue that since they are time travelers, her hotness remains constant throughout all of history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you need to look at the Teragigflops and how much unicorn blood is in the reservoir.  Also because both companies are outsourcing productions you also have to see what region the board was forged in.  The goblins in the north are just far superior than the other areas.  I swear people are so dumb just looking at RAM or speed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know its funny, Nolan spends spends a stupid amount of money on not doing things with CGI.  The beginning of TDKR he did that for real and Warner got very mad because it would have been a lot cheaper doing it on a soundstage. I heard he spent weeks on Interstellar scouting locations for alien worlds.  He spent the majority of the production trying to figure out how to build that room at the end.  Dunkirk, he bought a 3 million dollar plane and crashed it into a mountain. In Dark Knight the tumbler bike was so complicated they had to train the stunt guy for two weeks to learn to drive it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but when they asked him to get stuff he just walked too it instead of super speeding to get it.  Kinda took the air out of the whole scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a red box once that had a note.  It said "This movie sucks.  Just return it.".  I should have listened to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, Respawns cost money?  Ok, that explains why I have a few grand and my nephew is always out of cash.  I thought it was wierd, I always split the chests with him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that was Robert Downey Jr's doing.  He found out his fellow Avengers weren't getting properly compensated and he made Marvel give them all a pay bump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> passcode?  This is Eobard Thawne we are talking about.  Dude probally has some new fangled lock from the 67th century. Shit we wouldn't comprehend even if he explained it too us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its an alternate reality.  That said, they fixed Felicity on Arrow this year.  She's back to being a support character.  It's almost like Olicity didn't happen, they really don't talk about it or bring it up.  Hell, In the 17 or 18 episodes of Season 5 they only talked about their relationship once and even then it was handled with more care than Season 4.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legends of Tomorrow had the ultimate fan service last night! [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was?  OP she *IS* hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the two Saras make out with each other in the shower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Mirror is an anthology series.  So it's not relevant.  I'm saying the one director thing is what made it stand out and gave it that freshness.  Every TV show in the world is directed by multiple people, this one wasn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mick doesn't have his scars now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey neat Flash is back on my birthday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are spending a lot of money on this episode.  It's actually out of character for this season.  Something tells me something major will go down at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at Arby's like 16 years ago, we had to spray the fries down with lacquer so they wouldn't shine so much.  It was mandated after the fry guy looked directly at a freshly cooked batch and went blind for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see that Full Metal Jacket [trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vFkgHae7NH4) for this show?  It already sold me.  
  
Edit : Bonus [Coneheads](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5Vb5wSy1psQ) / [Speed](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7cZoRVcpkSQ) / [Snakes on a Plane](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Iq-rKZJcd0k) / [Mortal Kombat](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wbxFjTBOo4w)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
