<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5372</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What States Grew (and Shrank) the Most in 2016? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I misunderstood. Summer makes a lot more sense. More people drive in the summer. People are more likely to need to get things done before road trips and things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the article, but I'm not exactly sure how this is a good measure. I guess this proves it spikes in the winter, but there could be other reasons that happens other than procrastination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but this is an extremely childish comment. The system is the system. Everyone knew the rules and knew what they needed to do to win. If you don't like the outcome you either need to work to change the system or play to win within it. If you can honestly look in the mirror and say that if this would have happened in the opposite way and you wouldn't have recognized HRC's presidency, that then I will retract my comments about the child like nature of your comment, but otherwise you need to start to accept the world you live in or start to try and change it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toy Makers by State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 38% of US Households Spend More Than Income </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 61 shot, 11 fatally, over Christmas weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton refers to popular vote count in year-end message to supporters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil steadies above $55 ahead of supply cut deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about the thumbnail on Reddit or the website? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's survey data for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a suggestion on how you would display a two response category variable like this then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt Confirms Arrests of Al-Jazeera Journalist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Results] Is Die Hard A Christmas Movie? (All) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this refer to the filter? That was just the easiest way to filter by geography. If you try doing country it would have a lot of really small groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its actually a little more than ten percent of the US population that lives in California.

US has about 325 Million.
CA has about 39 Million
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked people if they think Die Hard is a Christmas movie using Google Forms to survey people in r/samplesize and people that follow my site on Twitter and Facebook. The data visualization uses Tableau and Google Sheets to display the results. The visualization will periodically refresh with new responses so be sure to take the survey to let us know what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Die Hard A Christmas Movie? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Casual] Is "Die Hard" a Christmas Movie? (All) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 12:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stats for Stories: National Homeless Persons Memorial Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Political Preview: GOP Expands Historic Control of State Governments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Political Preview: GOP Expands Historic Control of State Governments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maine electors vote for Sanders ruled improper, switches vote to Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump team asks State Dept. what it spends on international environmental efforts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four more officials charged over Flint, Michigan, water crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great job on this!  it would be much more difficult but it would be interesting to see the strength of  poker hands in different situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hate to see what it looks like if you change the threshold of upvotes to 5 or 10 which still have a pretty low number of views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Measuring America: Our Changing Landscape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the reason then EPA exists is to blow the whistle?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dollar hits new 14-year high, Dow sets sights on 20,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flint Water Crisis: Why the EPA is Partly to Blame </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looked it up.  The EPA knew but didnt make it public

Source:[Time](http://time.com/4190643/flint-water-crisis-susan-hedman-epa/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I am wrong, but wasn't the EPA partially responsible? people kept coming to them for help and they were ignored weren't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump calls Russian ambassador's assassin a 'radical Islamic terrorist' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber ignores Calif. threats, keeps testing self-driving cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Marshawn Lynch effect: A look at why the Seahawks offense has struggled this season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electoral college reform: What would happen if Congressional districts were based strictly on population? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon Girl Remains Missing 38 Years Later </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 13:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China said it would return a seized U.S. naval drone. Trump told them to keep it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aging baby boomers increasingly embrace marijuana, heavy alcohol use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clicking on the dots on mobile provides information about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I posted the data to my website if you are still interested in looking at the data](http://overflow.solutions/datasets/how-income-compares-to-rent-in-each-us-county-visualization-data/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to have to quibble with you on it being useless on mobile. I was able to find [San Francisco](http://i.imgur.com/F6lzJqY.png) quickly by just clicking on the points. Then again I am the creator so my opinion is 100% biased

As for the median rent, the Census Bureau reports that the median rent is around 1,500. I know there have been a lot of stories about the rent being that high lately, and I can't say how they come to that number.

I can tell you though that this data is from a five year sample so that could have something to do with it. It also includes all household sizes so maybe there are a lot of studios that bring down the number. Finally, it is self reported data, maybe a lot of people only report their portion of the rent when they should be reporting it for the whole household. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/sweaterfish and I explained this in one of the other comment strings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great explanation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can upload the spreadsheet later on tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They Said 'Never Again' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill admit, I was a little confused by this as well. These are three separate variables that the Census Bureau publishes so that likely has something to do with it. The best explanation I could find was from socialexplorer.com.

"This measure divides the gross rent as a percentage of household income distribution into two equal parts: one-half of the cases falling below the median gross rent as a percentage of household income and one- half above the median. Median gross rent as a percentage of household income is computed on the basis of a standard distribution. (See the "Standard Distributions" section in Appendix A.) Median gross rent as a percentage of household income is rounded to the nearest tenth. (For more information on medians, see "Derived Measures.")"

It doesn't say much, but it has got to be something about how they calculate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last 10 Weeks Of 2016 Campaign Stops In One Handy Gif </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where To Say Merry Christmas vs. Happy Holidays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of Canada's Poloz frets about protectionism: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To create this data visualization I gathered data from the American Community Survey. I used the 2011-2015 ACS 5 years estimates from Table B25064, B25077, and B25071 on American FactFinder. I then manipulated the data in excel and used Tableau to visualize the data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Income Compares to Rent in Each US County [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I hadn't noticed that. It is very slight, but maybe there is something going on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was interested in seeing how many times people get married and remarried through out their life. The best way I could figure out to do this was to use data from the American Community Survey. This Census Bureau program collects data that can be used to look into how many times people of certain age group get married. I used the 2015 One Year Estimates Public Use Microdata Sample, which can be found on the ACS Website. I then used Tableau to visualize the data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Many Times Have Americans Been Married by Age? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first Amazon PrimeAir drone delivery landed today, 13 minutes after the order was placed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and Silicon Valley look to smooth over frictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google spins out car project with mission to sell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make this data viz I downloaded data published by the District of Columbia on their open data website. I then took the data and put it in tableau to show the locations and the type of enforcement camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are the Speed Traps and Red Light Cameras in DC? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are the Speed Traps and Red Light Cameras in DC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokmon GO, Going, Going, Gone As A Physical Activity Fad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 12:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama Reveals Why He Won't 'Vanish' During Trump Presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 12:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science guy Bill Nye: Climate adversaries can unite around innovation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 12:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rants toward Terrelle Pryor raise issue of respect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 12:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Trump skews science, researchers must raise the alarm - Obama official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 12:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LAPD Crime and Collision Raw Data for 2015 | Los Angeles - Open Data Portal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To create this data visualization I gathered data from the American Community Survey on American Fact Finder. I used Table B25007 and the data from 2005 to 2015. I then manipulated the data in excel and used Tableau to visualize the data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whether You Own or Rent Your Home has a Lot to Do with Your Age [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hack of Quest Diagnostics App Exposes Data of 34,000 Patients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Brady once again makes MVP case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Trump's Twitter account a national security threat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To create this data visualization I gathered data from the American Community Survey on American Fact Finder. I used Table B25007 and the data from 2005 to 2015. I then manipulated the data in excel and used Tableau to visualize the data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are People More Likely to Rent or Own their Homes in Each State? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red means stop! Banking app cuts customer spending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Istanbul explosions: 15 killed, 69 wounded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump bashes CIA, dismisses Russian hacking report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands flee Syria's Aleppo as Assad nears victory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College fave Yik Yak suffers deep job cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German authorities probe VW's Porsche for manipulation software </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oakland Mayor Announces $1.7M Investment For Affordable Art Spaces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: No survivors in Pakistan passenger jet crash carrying 48 people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio 'heartbeat bill' abortion ban moves to governor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low Energy WaPo publishes story blaming Trump for stock "tank". Stock only drops two dollars and recovers by end of the day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. Census Bureau recently reported that the American Community Survey (ACS) estimates that 9.4% of Americans dont have health insurance coverage. This is an all time low because of the passage of the ACA. Like other statistics though, different groups have a different percentage of people that are uninsured. This visualization lets you explore the number of people that are uninsured for a number of different populations.
To create this data visualization I gathered data from the ACS on American Fact Finder. I used Table B27001 from 2010 to 2015. I then used Tableau to visualize the data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Percentage of Americans have been Uninsured Each Year Since 2010? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the White House Could Justify a Debt-Driven Keynesian Stimulus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Reduce Infant Mortality, U.S. Cities Adopt the Finland Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One day later, Earl Thomas still unsure about his football future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Klay Thompson's incredible 60-point outburst by the numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trump could save jobs but damage the economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trumps Carrier Deal Isnt The Way To Save U.S. Jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to nominate Carson as HUD Secretary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 12:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cam Newton: Rivera benched me because I didnt have a tie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 12:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Votes Miscounted? Your State May Not Be Able to Find Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After completing a post on the unemployment rate in each state, u/Kotebiya asked I publish the interactive tool to explore the data. This tool lets you see the unemployment rate in each county, state, division, and region in the US for the last 26 years. I used the latest 2015 data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics to make this visualization. The data was cleaned in Excel and then Tableau was used to create the timeline. The data published by BLS is the average unemployment rate for the year. I then strung them together to make the timeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Highs and the Lows of the Unemployment Rate in Each State and County Since 1990 [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. jobs report: 4 facts to know before its release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 13:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carrier incentives stir debate over 'rewarding' offshoring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How these five undecided voters made their choices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Foreign Secretary underscores commitment to NATO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the size of mobile screens and the differences in them, no, i don't think that it is possible for the whole visualization to fit. When you look at most screen sizes the bar chart does fit in the full screen which is what I think is most important.  As for the advertising I think there is an appropriate amount and haven't heard any other complaints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American FactFinder Health Insurance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 03:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the idea. That should be pretty easy to put together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, Tableau Public is free. There is a row limit and a space limit, but you have to have a farily large data set to run against them. The row limit is around 25 million I think and the total space is like 10gbs but Tableau puts the data in their format so it is fairly small.

No problem. I really appreciate the advice I get in r/dataisbeautiful so I always try to respond when I can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 15:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really strange. I haven't come accross that issue so it is very hard for me to explain. On all the screens I have used the width is displayed when the browser is at 100% view. I did try zooming it in and their is an issue at around 120% but bumping it up or down changes that issue. I wouldn't know how to go about remedying that tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!

"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. "
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get what your saying. I think it may have to do with legality across states. While some states you have certain labor laws that allow this, in other states it isn't legal. It is likely easier to have an overall rule instead of multiple regional rules with such a small number of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you are having issues with the website. Do you mind if I ask if I ask what you are using to access it (Mobile, Desktop, Tablet)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic violence callout leaves officer and suspect dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that anytime something comes up as zero, it isn't that it was never reported, but that the situation is so rare the census decided it wasn't able to provide a reliable estimate. 

The difference between unemployed and and not in the labor force has to do with if you were looking for work. Thanks for your questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Israeli ambassador arrives in Turkey amid improving ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion, I am going to work on putting that in.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!
"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably my favorite thing that the data show. It is extremely interesting it is that people start moving so much in that range, after, for the most case parents have settled them down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question. I am going to look into implementing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words. I appreciate it. As for the hosting, I use Tableau to create most of my visualizations. Tableau has an online hosting tool called Tableau Public which allows you to share the visualizations that you create. Let me know if you have any other questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great suggestion. I will look into doing that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you had such a bad experience on the mobile version. Did you maybe have any suggestions on how to make it better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are thinking if each sex had its own chart and you could look at both and compare? That would be a cool idea. I will look into doing that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!

"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!

"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!

"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!
"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. "

That being said, I don't think you can say the data has anymore problems than any other survey data. The Census may not plan on data being published this way so they prob don't attempt to smooth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be interesting. I used Census data so the government doesn't have an interest or think they could pull off such a question, but it would be cool to look into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way the Census currently asks this question they ask for whether or not you have Hispanic origins and then ask your race. They do it this way because there used to be more of a distinction, but people don't look at it that way anymore. If you are interested in learning more about changes to this [Pew published a story about it](http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2015/06/18/census-considers-new-approach-to-asking-about-race-by-not-using-the-term-at-all/).

Since the data is collected this way it is tough to create a visualization that incorporates this. That is why I have a Hispanic filter on the visualization, but it is not worked into the race variable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you could compare them, but I would give you some advice on the wording. All the people in this are individuals so it isn't a comparison of people when they are 31 v when they are 71. It is a comparison of 31 year olds and 71 year olds currently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed this as well at work. From my experience it feels like everyone should be like you, but that isn't the case in some circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input. I will def look into incorporating this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!

"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten this question a few times so I am going to just copy my response. Thanks for asking!

"Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ACS differentiates between race and ethnic origin. That is why I added a filter for Hispanic Origin, but the way they collect data, it makes it difficult to show it within the other race categories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was fairly certain it was white Hispanics that made up the next largest group.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-white Hispanic/Latinos should be in the other race categories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works great now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting this /u/kotebiya. I'm glad to see you were interested in looking into this trend. Very cool graphic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is by age, That is what the 26 refers to. If you hover over the graphic there is a statement about the exact stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @kotebiya I am excited you did this. I was thinking about this because I saw that trend as well. I am having trouble seeing it though. Did you make sure to switch it to public view? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since this is weighted survey data I think it is people that are estimating age and then the weighting kinda expands the effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the last few months, I have done some work creating various age distributions that show different demographic traits. I wanted to create something though that was able to show age distributions with multiple demographic traits all in one place. This graphic is my attempt at making this tool.

In the data visualization above you are able to take various demographic traits and apply them to the population pyramid of the U.S. You can then use the filters below to adjust the pyramid to only show certain populations. If you want the visual to only show one characteristic or exclude a trait, simply click it in the legend and keep or remove it.

The data for this tool comes from the Public Use Microdata Sample (PUMS) published by the American Community Survey.  It then utilizes Tableau to display the data.You can find information about the ACS PUMS at the Census Bureaus website. On the site there is information about the survey, summary level data, and how to use the PUMS data.

I plan on updating this tool throughout the year. If there are any traits that you are interested in seeing, let me know and I would be happy to set it up. Also, since this is an ongoing project, any suggestions you have on how to make the visualization better are welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Do Americans Differ by Age? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if a data viz is the best way to present a group of events happening once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney not a done deal for Cabinet post, says Reince Priebus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you go about downloading it?

edit:spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Messenger launches Instant Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would make the graphics bigger within the blog if you want them to be the focal point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrelle Pryor says he's 'part of the reason' the Browns are 0-12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't all of these countries still stable  democracies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump can keep his company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet Archive putting database in Canada to keep it from Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Trump and Romney's Jean Georges dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Half-Century Of Learning: Historical Census Statistics On Educational Attainment in the United States, 1940 to 2000: Detailed Tables - Educational Attainment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three miners dead, five missing after tremor hits Polish copper mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 12:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate leader hopes to have several Trump nominees confirmed on January 20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Is Tearing Itself Apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Kellyanne Conway hates Mitt Romney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defense a no-show in Eagles' first home loss of season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryant guard, trailing by 1, dribbles out clock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Peters is going to demand focus from Eagles down the stretch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Much Education do Americans Have? - Visualized by Age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wealth Gap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Trump join the GOP's voter identification push from the White House? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump announces selection of Tom Price for Health secretary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wells Fargo Pushes For Its Day Out Of Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conway plays the outside game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lone OSU officer stops 'lone wolf' attack from being worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to check that out. I am not very good with R but this may be a good excuse to learn more about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes there is. Acts has been complted every year since 2005. It would be interesting to look at it that way. It would be a lot of data though. Idk if Tableau public would take that much data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was interested in visualizing how the highest level of school completed differs based on someones age. To do this I gathered data from the American Community Survey which is completed by the US Census Bureau. I used the 2014 One Year Estimates Public Use Microdata Sample, which can be found on the ACS Website. I then used Tableau to visualize the data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Much Education do Americans Have?  Visualized by Age [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump 'furious' over Kellyanne Conway comments on Sunday shows about Romney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election recount process to begin in Wisconsin after Green Party petition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Trump team wants Romney to apologize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Time did you have Thanksgiving Dinner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Results][Casual]What time do you have Thanksgiving dinner?(US) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Respost][Casual]What time do you have Thanksgiving dinner?(US) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 22:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Casual]What time do you have Thanksgiving dinner?(US) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 12:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this is a % of the population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried including it, but I couldn't find a way that didn't look clunky on this particular visualization. If you are interested in it there is a link to another visualization that has it on the page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice side by side. Thanks for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Moves Toward a More Diverse Cabinet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cities Closely Watching Chicagos Version of a Fitbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For this visualization I categorized people 15 to 34 years old are as Millennials. I found that almost 27% of people in the US fall into this age group. While Most states did not significantly differ from this I found that their were a lot of variation in the counties, especially smaller counties. This visualization lets you explore that with the ability to filter by gender and highlight by geography.The data used in this visualization is compiled by the US Census Bureau. I used Table PEPAGESEX from American FactFinder to determine population counts by age. Once I had the data and the age groups I was going to use, I cleaned the data with Excel and used Tableau to create the visualization.

In addition to using Tableau and Excel, the website Codepen is used to host custom CSS and JS coding. The idea to do this came from Ben Sullins website. In a recent blog post, he explains how to use this coding and Tableau to create 50 state maps. I used this same idea to create the maps for how many Millennials are in each states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Many Millennials Live in Each County of Every State? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK's Mr Brexit says no vacancy for ambassador to United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon explores live sports streaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Md. board approves building new $765M Harry Nice bridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye West Cancels Remaining Saint Pablo Tour Dates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 39 percent of Americans would give up sex to never worry about hacking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global Abortion Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Pivots to Economic and Domestic Policy Posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch out: google.com isn't the same as Google.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good idea. That would be an interesting analysis.

Thanks for pointing that out. It should be fixed now.

edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The data used in this visualization is compiled by the US Census Bureau which produces the American Community Survey. I used the 2015 one year estimates from table B12001 from American Fact Finder. I used Excel to clean the data and Tableau to create the visualization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What States Have The Most People that are Separated? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Settles Trump University Lawsuits for $25 Million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney, Secretary of State? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
