<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5027</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah more like this.

Fact: Immediately bought the complete edition of Witcher and the new Hitman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnnnndddd it's gone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks for clearing up what I thought! Aren't you just wonderfullllll for telling me what i think, you circle jerkin pudding pop eating toaster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not your banana, kidney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One is functional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha this whole thread is cancer, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you. Way to clear this cancer up sweet heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take yourself a bit more serious. Good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha lighten up. Take yourself a bit more serious, good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah bouy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We get it, you got one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendork downvote party in here it seems. Enjoy the joke. (The console that is) *ooooohhh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Street Art that speaks to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yeahhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it funny how people keep saying it's a response bias, when this is a thread asking directly for people with a perfect system. Now that's response bias! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King of trashy still </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horse to pasture, put er down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude or dudette I had a great time playing this. Totally recommend buying it, but try to get it on sale. But I'll say that for every game.
Open world is fun and a bit zaney, missions are not the most varied you'll ever see but there's many different side missions that help improve your character. Racing, climbing, flying, wing suit "falling" etc.  
I still love it, never finished it because of the grind aspect, but I just finished resident evil 7 and it's my go to in between game. Highly recommend having it in your collection regardless of any moderate grind aspects
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh reaaaalllyyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently you knew how to smile like a god damn boss!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After finishing RE7 I feel this should be their slogan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post has been removed for violating Rule#3 on this thread.

No Lets Plays.

To quote the rules of this subreddit and help you with future posts that may support your channel (Hey we all gotta make a living),

"If you make an imgur album of your base and link to a video of you making it, people are less likely to be critical of it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must admit I hate losing screen space. Give me a pull to reveal menu any day. The r/all link is gone to push r/popular. The post link is in an invisible glitch. I really dislike it :/ best recommendations for a replacement are welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate losing screen space for a menu honestly. Makes sense though coming from the iOS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the same place but invisible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mobile Redditors, do you like the new design for the official Reddit app, why/why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the big TD babies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we just control our dashboard fully already. So many people argue it's a huge deal, but truly just let us add/remove what we want. Let us use screenshots as backgrounds, let us have shitty icon packs, it's really not a big ask Sony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to think this is happening

https://youtu.be/FxNvUWN3vYk

The wrong people are buying the front page of Reddit to discredit it and confuse the legitimate arguments. Of course that's a conspiracy and really I'm not interested in living like that. But I can suggest that Reddit will no longer be worth its weight if this continues. Voting manipulation needs to be understood by all Redditors and we need to be clear on our moderation of fake news, it's no good for either side of any argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the tri-tip. Yep another good point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it's just increased popularity due to restaurants using it, and using it because it's cheap. Sous vide, braise, and butter poach have been around long enough that it's very hard to believe the price of flank is a direct result of methodology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I laughed at that also. Like really now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're faded black too. Poor fucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bowling championship stripped, 7-year-old for wearing black-ish pants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah dude I seen some of the hacking and basically gave them a "*go fuck yourselves*" and peaced out. I guess it would have come up sooner or later to be dealt with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another atmospheric screenshot. Same rad storm. Equally rad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, gonna post another one here now too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It follows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha this guy knows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame press like this barely put any effort into writing let alone fleshing out the story and looking professional. Increasingly I see stories like this from magazines or websites that actually read like a thirteen year old girl wrote them to piss off Jenny so she can have Luke all to herself.
This is a very significant and serious issue and the Donaldites need no help to minimise our concerns so please for the love of Job try to do your job right, or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some stuff has become more pricey because of general interest and new markets. Chicken wings alas are one of these bad boys. I always point to flank steak. Before we started serving that in restaurants it was outrageously cheap, because honestly it's a shit cut only worth braising. But now with it on every other menu it's popularity has increased and we're paying so so so so much more from a shit cut. Way more than the average beef price increase year over year. Damn trends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm actually not ok with the tease at this point. Shut the fuck up and get it done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very surprising when you consider it was understood to be a bottom feeder. Where I'm from my grandmother still considers lobster to be a poor person food (along with mutton and rabbit). As a bottom feeder they feast often on dead and decaying matter, and that was considered beneath the privileged class. Funny enough whole wheat or multigrain bread was considered beneath the privileged class as well, since it wasn't the fancy bleached white shit, and now look at us.
I've always found it funny in food culture poor dishes and dishes of preservation have been elevated and served to the rich and well off. Lobster, whole grains, rattatouille, duck confit, smoked salmon/trout, cured meats, etc etc. 
It used to be to survive the winter hardship, now it's $39.99 a plate suckas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to grab those situations right away. I'm not a big dude but I'm a little ridiculous and find its best to go further than someone else at the drop off a hat. Granted you need to know when to fold too less you can get stabbed pretty quick. 
But in this particular situation you need to loudly proclaim, "I don't give a fuck what you'll say you can't just grab my dick! What the fuck is wrong with you! Your cousin was right you need to get fucking help!" Then look to other people and immediately get them involved. If they escalate further you gotta be ready. This is not good advise for normal people haha but I refuse to let people walk on me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I feel like she's missing the true experience here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you about to drop the hottest rap album in the Commonwealth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sing Tuesday's gone when he leaves the kitchen.
Chant Tuesday when he enters the room.
Definitely over all just fuck with em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. But the steaks?! That's a dead give away.... Get it. *Dead* give away. Har Har har </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerky is good. That's a damn fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. *Scene. Haha better? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it! Spread the *love*
https://youtu.be/HzSUo8iPp4M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good god. The Sharper image selling Trump steaks. What... What have we done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha my buddy always says that during a bad service. "They're gonna taste the hate on that plate!!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The animal paid for it with his life I like to say. Eat it right or eat a hotdog. Then the whole vegetarian side of the table starts piping up. Ya can't win I tell ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally figuratively. Also are we still doing phrasing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is brilliant. I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seen this on a different sub and hadn't seen it here. Seemed like something this sub would enjoy excuuuuse me princess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is all the evidence I need to know where I stand with this guy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that's how they decide how to run such an astronomically successful business, by five minutes limelight at a time.
 Forget their award winning cuisine and books, forget their contribution to eating movements. It's through news plugs. Mmhmm. Yeah they totally need help staying in the spotlight, you jealous little girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gnarly. I absolutely love it! Good work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screenshot I took. Feel that atmosphere [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man. I have another one I'll post tomorrow. Less atmospheric. But God damn that game is gorgeous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fallout 4 Screenshot Wallpaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your gardening store is on point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying he going to be a multi millionaire that has every politico's dream resume. Dang , justice will be served.

But on more serious matters this picture is amazing and we can never let it die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's heading straight for us!! Shoot it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't finished Skyrim or Witcher 3 and I don't know why
What's wrong with me!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see more activity too, but I think with the flurry of titles that have come out in the past few months it makes sense why a small, still under-developed game like this isn't the talk of the town.

It's a fucking great game though and we all know it. They've come so far, from a few months ago with a team of just two now they're running with fourteen members.
 
I seen some people hacking and cheating and they've addressed this recent as well. Ruins the game but apparently it's also stalled their development weeks as they develop and implement anti-cheating ideas. 

I look forward to the next big update which they're potentially dropping during or around PAX East conference, and that's just over a week away! They've said it's their biggest update yet so I'm pretty excited, and I'm sure we'll see more talk about the game if they do well with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping it's revealed in a later update but as of now just for show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sesame Schezwan Chicken Thighs [1920x1920] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Sesame Schezwan Chicken Thighs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just one lie. Can a gif master put together at least a dozen lies and we get that to the front of all for a month just so Donny can choke on it a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey happy to see a new player in the community!

First just to let you know the devs are very active in the steam community, last posting Feb 21, and you can see for yourself what they're up to and talk directly to them here:

https://steamcommunity.com/app/402710

You will start to die of dehydration when you run low on water. Ideally drink water before this point ha. You'll need it but generally only after a few days active, lots of running, etc

Creatures do not level up with you currently and are set at the difficulty chosen upon launch of the game. They are not more difficult further from your spawn point either. The difficulty usually lies in returning to your base with materials and the like.

They are planning to open up more of the universe yes, but to my understanding neither planet is finished yet. Aziel is a very recent release so expect to wait for a third planet. 

I hope this helped a bit and again stay close to the steam page these devs have been great with the community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the most expensive city in Canada either. You said you don't understand these articles but truly I believe you do. Toronto does run this risk and I'm sorry you find that difficult to comprehend. Other cities in Canada do as well, particularly Vancouver. They have different standards than a different city in a different country. I'm not sure how you don't understand this article and yet try to come off like a dickhead "making it simple" for me. Read the article slow and mouth the words maybe that will help you buttercup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you not understand this view when you're leaving a city and referencing it's high cost as you leave? Not being a dick but that's exactly what they're talking about.
After you compare economies and living standards, average wages etc there's really nothing here you don't understand. And further more London is currently under going what this article warns of.

http://www.viralthread.com/london-is-dying-and-its-too-late-to-do-anything-about-it/

www.standard.co.uk/news/london/more-people-dying-penniless-and-alone-in-london-official-figures-show-a3125956.html%3Famp

I personally can't understand how you don't understand but are capable of citing all the high costs associated with a city you're leaving? The article is warning of the time when you leave Toronto and say the same thing about it that you have London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered why people like Dugin who are so into ending it all don't just off themselves. I mean lead by example loser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like you have an ugly sweater thing going too. 10/10 would wear sweater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eggs have room to expand and can be frozen. Source: I do it on occasion. Thaw in the fridge before using.
The shell however would almost definitely crack upon being thrown at a window. No source but will try on my asshole neighbor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not entirely unheard of but is very much indicative of the current political situation. Some background for those who don't know what this is. 

White House Correspondents' Association(WHCA) is an organization of journalists who cover theWhite Houseand thePresident of the United States. The WHCA was founded on February 25, 1914, by journalists in response to an unfounded rumor that aCongressionalcommittee would select which journalists could attend press conferences of PresidentWoodrow Wilson.

Its most high-profile activity is the annualWhite House Correspondents' Dinner, which is traditionally attended by the president and covered by the news.

Many annual dinners were cancelled or downsized due to deaths or political crises. The dinner was cancelled in 1930 due to the death of former presidentWilliam Howard Taft; in 1942, following the United States' entry into World War II; and in 1951, over what PresidentHarry S. Trumancalled the "uncertainty of the world situation."

I would like to just suggest the president openly skipping this is again an "uncertainty of the world situation". Please support real journalists and ignore party politics for the safety of all, this man may be so dangerously out of touch it could ripple out for a long time to come.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that Cheetos mother fucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *brutally bludgeons father with cast iron pan* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I live in the North Atlantic and got handed a layoff for the first time in my life! Ten years solid work though I'm gonna take a rest for a few weeks boys ... but also fuck extended patio weather. My fingers are crossed for at least one Friday storm for ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This! Is my boom stick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the facility but you have to remember that some kitchens are attached to hotels, boutiques and otherwise. Meaning even after closing some moronic client may wander in or through  somewhere they shouldn't.
Alternatively having a busy bar that goes on for hours and hours after kitchen closing leaves many bodies with access to the walk in, and it can just be safer to lock up for those hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno sounds like this boss knows everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean they're controlling access to information. Not scary at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming Nintendo ultra-64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Ultra-64 reveal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend dropped by with "some magazines". Stoked!! Stack of em!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'all got any honey nut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask not for a lighter burden, but for broader shoulders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Renaissance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it!!!! My bit. It's just a little wet it's still good, it's still good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BBBQ the extra B is for BYOBB...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear cocaine fixes everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eastern Canada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's right too. Advice I often give out I should listen myself. Also, fuck em haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. Brilliant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah true enough. Getting older I'm not as ballsy as I used to be with well paid employment but truthfully I've never had to fight to hard to get work. Best to trust the gut. Thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much. Truthfully I was very much frustrated with the place. But it's someone getting one up on me that bothers me haha anyways thanks for your kind words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this guy needs to get out of his current arena.

 He wants to safely play with civilized people because it's comfortable and not dangerous to run his mouth. Civilised people tolerate him and get frustrated.

If he wants to dance on the edge of civility, and advocate such discrimination and hate, I'd like to see it happen in a back alley where people still use more than words. An arena more fitting for such big talk from such a small little human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kid vid. My fucking rival... We meet again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm here thinking, you got savings? I can barely afford a fucking pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would quit my job and take part time work as a ranch hand. I would volunteer my cooking skills and contacts (from my current career) to feed people that need it. I would not do this as much as I currently work though because I feel I'm a bit more selfish than altruistic. And also I'd buy a bitchin' over sized Nerf gun right away and run around screaming,  "Dream moderately big bitches!!" While shooting soft arrows at people in business suits. Heck I might do that payday... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NES rentals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negative. But it was in Canada eh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting coffee at 1pm today I sighed at the barista and said, "Mornings, am I right" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were not made like that. 

A "barely simmer" will allow the first and second membrane to pull away from the yolk so I definitely disagree with that. In my experience you will end up with "tails" of whites. A rapid boil is not best, but just below it, particularly if adding enough egg to lower the temperature of the water. But I can not suggest a barely simmer for this result.

Acid is important to help, generally cover the bottom of your pot with a thin layer of a soft flavor vinegar, in this case pomegranate. 

The single biggest thing to get this result is to control the water, and thus the eggs, direction. By creating a whirlpool in your hot water (stirring in one direction nice and steadily) you create an environment where the white membranes naturally wrap around the yolks center of mass. This is absolutely imperative to consistently shaped poached eggs.

As long as the egg is dropped quickly and steadily it is irrelevant where it comes from. They can be dropped from their shell as these were. Often we use ramekins to drop eggs in a steady rapid fashion, but only when trying to take advantage of the whirlpool effect and when doing dozens at a time. Dozen ramekins, big whirlpool, begin dropping, cook for a few minutes while cracking the next dozen. But then you have a dirty ramekins so that won't be happening at home on my day off.

And truthfully for me the egg must be pulled out of the water with carry over cook in mind, dried gently, and then served.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hollandaise and mushrooms added later. Just wanted to show the testicular shape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like we should all get a fuck ton delivered to a remote island that costs more than five bucks for OP to ship to so he's out money for his mild misdirection. Mean? Yes. Over the top? Probably. But it'll be like sending OP a proper fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zelda one has a spot on my wall ready to go! Fingers crossed there's one left for me in the next few days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha right?! They always think that and after a twelve hour shift I'm like, "can you lift the burger to my mouth babe I'm tired" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are literally, the most fun I've ever seen in a person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got it eh. Sorry guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twenty bucks at EB. Doing it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your poach game is your only feature to offer a girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah captain buzzkill. Just cause you broke up with your left hand doesn't mean this guy will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
