<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9437</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia Uncovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>    </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Saudi Islamic teacher once told me that Muslims should sleep only 4 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 09:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember, as a child, being told by a Saudi Islamic teacher, that Muslims should only sleep 4 hours so they can make sure they wake up in time for fajr prayer. He also said that sleeping 8 hours a day is not good and it's something the West made up so they make sure Muslims sleep in and don't make it for prayer. He said its their plan to bring Muslims down..He sleeps only 4 hours a day because of this, lol and says he never missed a fajr prayer

Sounds absolutely ludicrous but this is exactly what he said. Utterly stupid but this is yet again what religion will turn people into. I'm glad I left this country (Saudi Arabia) a long time ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>     </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 07:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 09:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ask him if he seriously believes that an ignorant cave-dwelling carpeneter created the universe with all its stars and galaxies. Or, if he walked on water. Or if he turned into wafer. Or whatever nonsense that is in the bible. It is you who should be upset at your Dad's mindset gullibly believing ridiculous nonsense and taking in traditional claims at face value without questioning them. Religion corrupts people's thinking abilities and reasoning faculties. 

EDIT: Actually, don't do that if it will make problems escalate or if he will take it seriously. You can pretend you are religious for the time being and lie to him and tell him you do believe in this carpenter fuck named Jesus, while in fact you dont to avoid any serious consequences.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi religious police receive training on 'how to fight magic' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 08:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the West continue to turn a blind eye to Saudi Arabia's heinous crimes and odious laws? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 04:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 22:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> posted it to highlight the stupidity and delusions of some people in the world and how religion can corrupt minds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 22:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> translation below video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes I should. If it  is a nonsensical fairy tale founded upon ignorance and superstition, then I can damn well mock and disgrace it. Why should religion be immune to ridicule?! Why not politics, why not astrology?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Saudi Arabia such a backwards regressive country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translation below video. Yeah didn't act out in a technical sense. But pretended he was dead and looking for good deeds he did in his life to escape god's punishment. Its really stupid and funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim acts out what will happen in your grave. Advises to do good deeds before it is too late. LOL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women in Saudi Arabia "need not apply" to Saudi-based Canadian colleges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 08:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> up your ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sign at restaurant door in Saudi Arabia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 22:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
