<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right ? sticking it to the matriarchy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once thought that my inner monologue was insanity, kept it secret so no one would find out and put me away. So I would talk to my self more often but I've made a habit of not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you hate about yourself the most ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or we could just let hunting and fishing go unregulated and have the ecosystem of cherished land scapes destroyed in the process. XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...in the california you also have to have a fire arms saftey certificate, a registered fire arm, a license to drive a vehicle to get you there, insurance for that vehicle, ect... ect... I can list meaningless specifics too XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why our proprietary netflix has a huge list of foreign movies ? XD Good for your friends but the companies that made it our american companies. Sure they make movies in other countries with people from other countries but the fact is the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, no, that's my point. You can hunt in third world countries. But you have so much else to worry about that you don't here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into it, i'm not wiki hahaha the country of origin for production of the film is a the United States. Inglorious Bastards wasn't filmed entirely in the US but guess what ? it's a US film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not without having to worry about roaming gangs of fucks that rape pillage, and murder the local populaces on a regular basis. Rule of Law still reigns supreme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the beauty of holly wood compadre, it has a long arm that reaches the world over and invites the rest of the world to join in. It is actually an incredibly american system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two things simultaneously, first, In some way shape or form they are useful, so i try my best not to piss them off. The most unlikely of strangers has saved my bacon on more than one occasion. Secondly, that no matter how that person appears, they have the power to hurt me, another lesson I have learned on sever occasions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing with Rogue One, I saw it in London.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airsoft technicians, and airsoft players.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zack Snyder remake of Dawn of the Dead - had a dream that all my friends became these viciously homicidal maniacs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So powerful though, great series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This road is a hard one, if you ever want some guidance. I've carried that cross for seven years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you'll fuck anything, man, woman, trans, and everything in-between. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be premature, but Logan was pretty rattling too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Max Fury Road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that i can take a .308 caliber rifle and kill a wild pig. Clean, dress it, cook it, and feed my family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> traveled to other countries, and they still show our shows and play our movies in their theaters. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aztech Death Whistle, it's a hand molded skull with a spout you blow into that makes a loud sound comparable to a lady demon screaming. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> going to leave the country at the drop of a hat ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For local laws ? or you prefer not to use a blade ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most others also do tho   :/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides my wallet, keys, and phone. I rarely leave the house without my baby multi tool, sometimes a flash light, and a decent sized folding knife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you carry daily that most others do not ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flashlight, level two med kit, water, multi tool, cs shovel and toilet paper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leatherman cs4 rides in my pocket daily, and I have a gerber dime that lives in my center console.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a local Coffee Bean, instant connection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> put on an orange shirt and an orange hat, shock resistant goggles, and a lower face mask to protect my teeth. I then proceed to Shepard children ages 12 - 30 in objective based team death matches. They attack each other with an arsenal of plastic spitting assault weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know that the history books are going to paint you to be the biggest joke of a president to date, right ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way Putin would be the bottom. He'd rip trumps rump up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could definitely see where you're coming from. I think woman are also allowed to feel more, the term "man up" certainly doesn't help young girls but I think it hurts men more than we know.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in all honesty i'd be happy with less whine. This topic has better defense than the raiders XD
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like watching a powder keg XD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> knew someone would get triggered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I piss like +3 times a day. I shit twice, tops. At the very least stop crying about the toilet seat being left up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very true, I know plenty of people that have deep seeded issues that would be best suited for a mental physician that go unchecked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a lot of solid points here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally think it has a lot to do with the way we were raised by society. I mean, sure girls have to deal with the preassures of being pushed towards barbie, and baby dolls. But they gave us GI Joes, they gave us nerf guns, recruiters paid a lot more attention to the boys when they came to our schools. Playground fights seldomly involved the girls, and our cartoons often depicted men as warriors. Make a kid think he's a warrior and man grows up with nothing to fight, then boom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not expect this to become a trigger pile, sensative redditors are going to have to navigate this thing like a mine field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there might be something to that, columbine duo, virginia tech, santa barbra shooter, oregon theater shooter, and i'm sure others all seem to be pretty sexually challenged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't agree with it entirely, but for what ever reason it does seem that woman have been groomed to be less violent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> false, it's at least equal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shots fired
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you leave the toilet seat up for me ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are almost none of the US mass shooters female ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> accept when walking over grass, cobble stone, gravel, ect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear of the Dark - Iron Maiden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can, a girl that can roll out of bed in a t-shirt, jeans, and some sneakers looking hot is more like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song would you like to be the last one you ever hear ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still though, it's like make-up. false advertising. Like talking the sweater you saw on amazon you thought would look killer on you, till you get it and the stitching makes it fit weird, it's two sizes too small, and doesn't look like it'll survive a rain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conclusion of that chapter with the brothers got me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto, lover to death and it's really nit picky to improve on what I feel is perfect. But a little insight only helps me help her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a girl hurting her feet to.. look taller ? maybe make the butt look slightly perkier ? doesn't change the fact that the vast majority of guys do not care even a little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plenty of cunts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, if he'll bend over and let me show him where the wild goose goes while he eats her out. thumbs up XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like others here I was very angry and didn't understand how we all went to school learning about MLK Cesar Chavez and other civil rights advocates and still ended up getting discriminated against. But if a civil conversation can be had I like to let them know that there is nothing wrong with me. My skin is brown and my relatives come from mexico. But I was born here and have the same rights that you do, I am not the problem. You on the other hand chose to have a mental defect, some one born with a mental defect can never chose to not have it. But you choose to be racist, you choose not to accept me. Though I am peaceful, despite my law abiding background, in spite of my community service and blood that i have given for my community you choose to discriminate against me. Even though at any moment you can choose not to, you are the problem. not me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Last of Us, play the game with a fresh box of tissues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heels, you all look like baby giraffes once final call happens. Looking like you need help navigating easy terrain is not hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if she was more into masturbation. Watching her please herself gives me more insight as to what she wants subconsciously. That and occasionally inviting the random adventurous friend into our bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The devil and god are within me, hell and heaven are here. Where I am is because of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chick that can make a mohawk look sexy. Not just with physique but having just the right amount of fuck you to make +10 inch mohawk work gets me. Only ever been with one but man that got me going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> phone or computer ?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brother has autism, I know the struggle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for what kind of trip ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most crucial item you forgot, and absolutely needed them for a trip ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She said she got in a disagreement with he room mate and needed to find a new place. Turns out she threw her room mate through a glass door and broke two of her fingers till she agreed to pay the back rent that she owed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His ex told me she was falling for me, I asked for his say before I pursued the woman. We dated and the day after I told her I was falling in love with her. (just under 11 months of dating) She went to him for advice, they fucked. She came to me the morning after right after I'd just got off work to surprise with breakfast and an early morning fuck. I don't even know if she'd showered between her coming from him to me given the time frame. She went through a tearful confession about what she'd done and I haven't spoken to them since. There's a good chance I've tasted his cock through her pussy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, I'll look into it. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of the art subreddit and have already tried there, just trying to get a quick response so I can start on a craft
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm absolutely awful at capturing shadows and shades in my sketches. Having something that can crank up the contrast and exaggerate it for me would be nice to help me sketch some photos that I've been procrastinating on. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have any recommendations for a cheap or free image modifying program ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a program to modify photos and images for free or cheap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm absolutely awful at capturing shadows and shades in my sketches. Having something that can crank up the contrast and exagerate it for me would be nice to help me sketch some photos that i've been procrastinating on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie, i'd occasionally dab the end of a spoon in a frosting jar if I really liked that specific flavor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you alive... ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend was having pretty intense cramps a while back. So I decided to stop by the cheese cake factory on the way home and get her a treat. I called in what I wanted so it would be ready, I had ordered two slices of Reese's cheese cake for desert. when I arived I paid off my bill but they didn't have my order ready so they apologized and got someone on it. Some newbie server fucked up the order and boxed up a whole plain cheese cake. "Why should I correct him ? We'll have fancy cheese cake for desert all week.. ," I thought to my self.

and we did...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fat decision you've ever made ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apreciate the offer and advice friend, I'll seriously keep it in mind. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try, just making it through the day and trying to be as happy as the circumstances allow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do that, using people typically comes back to bite you in the ass. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little people are good for a lot of things, a good friend is tiny but He ended up being perfect for a role in a tank crew in afghanistan. Hundreds of men trembled at the tiny feet of his crew and the behemoth they manned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to lose myself first, I spent too much time worrying about trivial bull shit. What strangers would think about how I dressed or if I displayed (an appropriate amount of) emotion in public. Trying to patch up relationships with people that realistically didn't care about me because they were well received by others. Than I lost some one very close to me and it really put into perspective what I should be focusing on and who I should really be spending time with. 

I had to break apart pretty bad before I formed who I am today.  I recommend doing it the easy way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is wrong with you ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most rude stranger you've ever encountered ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What purchase did you deserve more than you needed ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 00:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 00:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want randy savage ? Because I can summon randy savage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
