<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5238</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know who is stronger, trans women or gay men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If someone is trying to achieve something and they share that they've made a big step, let them enjoy it by not reminding them of the end-goal. They don't need more pressure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is starting to sound like russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah keep paying for deadpool like it isnt corporate funded satire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people don't understand that China's leaders really do think they must do right by the people to keep their "mandate from heaven" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so where's zetsu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from Amy Pascal who brought us the gender-swapping blockbuster, Ghostbusters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are mods on Reddit able to mod and make a living? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://ktla.com/2017/03/05/man-fatally-stabbed-at-metro-station-in-koreatown/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Deadpool movie mocks the system while being paid for by the system (and making lots of money for it) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to Descanso Gardens for the Japanese Cherry Blossoms and I highly recommend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In La Canada.  Trees, beautiful.  Japanese folk singers.  Walkable in two hours with variety of plants.  Favorite was the cherry blossom and camellias.  Air is fresh, mountain view, reminds me of Yosemite.  Only this weekend and next weekend for cherry blossoming viewing I believe.  9 bucks, no fee for parking, come casual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my friend got robbed there at night in the restroom, be careful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> short apocalypse ruined it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Train to Busam was nonstop.  Watch it in blu ray at least and on biggest screen possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eater la recommended this crappy shawarma place a while back, and anyone who likes tsujita ramen is a shill because the ramen is awful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The super rich are modern day pharoahs who will take their wealth with them when they die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "leaked".  reddit is a disgusting cesspool of stealth advertising </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8.2 average critic rating which is a bit more accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so are old men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like any Angeleno, I am all for deporting the bad guys but his dui happened a decade ago.  On top of that, the taxpayers are getting screwed because now we're probably on the hook for the kids' welfare.  Trump is a racist coldhearted idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIDEO: Undocumented dad taken by ICE while dropping kids off at school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it's the critics and users average that should be cited along with imdb, although the latter two can be gamed

edit: thought it'd be interesting to see the average critics ratings vs their RT score for recently talked about movies.

Get Out average critic rating 8.3 vs 99

Split 6.4 vs 76

Moonlight 9.0 vs 97

Manchester by the Sea 8.9 vs 96

La La Land 8.6 vs 93

Rogue One 7.5 vs 85

Arrival 8.4 vs 94

I find the average critic score much more in line with the percent of my enjoyment/quality of the movies
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sick and tired of seeing Rotten Tomatoes' scores being viewed as a percentage of its quality rather than the percentage of critics who liked versus disliked it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Rotten Tomatoes tells us is the percentage of critics who liked or disliked a film.  That's it.  That scale can be 0-59 or 60-100.  It bugged me most with John Wick 2.  I liked the movie but it's not a 90/"A".  It had big problems including the redundancy of action and some illogic like at the ending, but it's still a solid "B."  Yet Reddit talks about it like that 90 on RT means the movie is infallible.  No, an actual 90 and above action movie is The Raid.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think of them as Star Wars movies.  It's as if a studio started making Tarantino movies without his input.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Walls Yin and Yang: Cautionary Tale Or Building Block? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely no one in this thread badmouthing the movie talks as if they've seen it, it's all regurgitated generalities.  I saw it a couple days after it came out and it was fun!  Here's my review.

The Great Wall's situation reminds me a lot of Edge of Tomorrow in that it got a lot of initial hate because of Tom Cruise but the movie itself is pretty darn good. Reading the comments on Reddit, I went in expecting Dragon Blade or Warcraft quality but it was much better.

The first few moments I was apprehensive. There was a short chase we'd all seen before, then some fireplace banter, and the make or break moment where the Matt Damon and Pedro "Oberyon" Pascal first meet the Chinese at the Great Wall. It could've gone really cheesy and nationalistic but it didn't and soon we were just watching the story about a mercenary and his friend happening upon a crazy situation.

There were many things it did right and I'll jot each one down.
The relationship between Matt and Pedro was the highlight for me. Like Edge of Tomorrow, it's a shame the commercials didn't feature more of the banter between them because we were laughing each time they were together. Pedro defintely has a future in action comedies and Matt Damon's accent could pass as Brad Pitt's brother in Snatch. Also, for a blockbuster, the characters were well defined and rich with conflict.

The visuals were absolutely amazing. Someone compared it to watching the opening ceremony of the Beijing Olympics and it's a good comparison. You'll get to see the Great Wall, inventive battles on it, the monster cgi was actually not distracting and look better than World War Z's zombies, the costumes are gorgeous and the colors help to organize the different groups of soldiers. Please don't watch it online because its visuals are such eyecandy.

For anyone worried about Chinese propaganda, the message of the movie is cooperation and trust over greed. There are both bad and good Western and Chinese characters. I never got the sense they were good or bad because of where they were from but because of who they were. Both Western and Chinese characters kicked major ass and equally saved the day. If scenes of Chinese people kicking monster ass unsettles you, then it's just you.

The marrying of Western and Chinese elements were really well done. We got a tight Western structure and the most Chinese things invariably were the dressings on it. So there's really sweet archery from Matt Damon and kung fu and Chinese battle tactics, Lord of the Rings-type pacing and suspense and monsters and a Chinese Forbidden City-like capital. My favorite scene was the singing and lantern scene because it was very Chinese and appreciated the filmmakers respecting us enough not to cut it.

I'm a big Hong Kong cinema fan so seeing Matt Damon and Andy Lau together was awesome (they starred in their respective versions of Infernal Affairs)

So those are my two cents on TGW. It's a fun quality blockbuster that I wholeheartedly recommend. Grade: A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same news, different take

http://deadline.com/2017/03/the-great-wall-box-office-china-hollywood-analysis-future-coproduction-xxx-1201938044/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you havent seen it have you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let's see any video of you then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is just mob bullying.  celebrate diversity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an industry that, according to Blum, doesn't change by the day but "by the minute," he believes the only way to survive is by taking calculated risks. He sees the success of "Get Out" as the perfect example of what Blumhouse does best, and it's miles away from the major studios' thinking.

"Jordan's script had been around for quite some time  no one wanted to make it, and I understand why: It's bananas," Blum said. "We did it because I read the script and I thought it would be amazing. If you make something on a respectable budget, you can make weird stuff. Did I know it would be a hit? I had no idea. But I loved how weird it was.

"At studios, filmmakers have to come into a room with comparisons. I don't want that," he continued. "If you can compare it to something, it's less interesting to me. The most excited I get is when someone says, 'I just read something and I've never read anything like it before.'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the company behind 2 of the year's biggest movies is blowing up the Hollywood playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best grounded supermarket coffee brands [MISC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a fan of JBBQ in the early days, but I've since converted to KBBQ.  JBBQ is too soft, too expensive, and not enough sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Oscar Pundits Got It Wrong This Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Resident Evil' sequel scares up big business in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Working with researchers from Trent University, the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation conducted DNA tests on meat samples from Subway, McDonald's, Wendy's, A W and Tim Hortons to determine exactly how much chicken was in each sandwich's patty.

 The meat from every chain but Subway was found to contain between 84 and 90 percent chicken meat. Those looking to "eat fresh" at Subway, however, are only consuming 53.6 percent chicken meat, the analysis found.

After an initial round of testing, the team was so surprised at Subway's results that they returned to run additional tests on five additional samples to confirm their original findings.

It's important to note that the restaurants' samples were not expected to have 100 percent chicken DNA, as processing, seasoning and marinating procedures will bring down the overall ratio of chicken to other substances in the patty.  In Subway's case, the researchers said that soy protein comprised the majority of the mystery DNA in the chicken patties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subway chicken only contains 53 percent chicken meat, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Keanu's become more popular because he represents us against the system, in the roles he's played in The Matrix and Point Break and John Wick, and in real life with how the studios treated him with replacing him on Passengers, a movie he brought to life and basically as if they single handedly decided he'd no longer had a career but he came back with the John Wick series.  Also in his personal life, having a mixed background and personal tragedies but man, he's still standing and doing his thing.  Fuck you life and fuck you system! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now replace "asian" with "human" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Too often, a narrow group creates an echo chamber in which outside voices fail to be heard. That group consists of a few hundred people  awards campaigners, along with older and less diverse Academy members  who appear and re-appear at the same screenings and cocktail parties, along with the journalists who engage with them and repeat what theyre all saying. As with any opinion poll, we need to sample a bigger crowd. Minority members, foreign members, younger as well as older ones, all need to be canvased  and not just by reporters who bear an unhealthy similarity to the people theyre currently canvasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Too often, a narrow group creates an echo chamber in which outside voices fail to be heard. That group consists of a few hundred people  awards campaigners, along with older and less diverse Academy members  who appear and re-appear at the same screenings and cocktail parties, along with the journalists who engage with them and repeat what theyre all saying. As with any opinion poll, we need to sample a bigger crowd. Minority members, foreign members, younger as well as older ones, all need to be canvased  and not just by reporters who bear an unhealthy similarity to the people theyre currently canvasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> living in this era has made fake news possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay Nostradamus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know Steven Spielberg said that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he acted, nothing spectacular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hes the one next to JC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is what it means: bernie will work with the dems by being a party within the party.  we should do the same, keep the pressure on the dems because theyre the only party we can work with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Box Office: 'Resident Evil' Astonishes With Huge $94M Weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brutally Honest Oscar Ballot #4: 'Moonlight' "Everything I Think An Oscar Picture Should Be," 'La La Land' "A Piece of Shit" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's an excellent series by Dr. William Neidinger on Amazon streaming called The Rise of Rome and another series called The Decline and Fall of Rome.  According to it, we are close to failing as a democratic republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't let U.S. become next Rome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paxton was awesome in this and I see this post more as a tribute than what it is which is nihilists without a life trying to bring everything down to their level of no value </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny how wikileaks never goes after trump or his minions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL "Nihilism" labels all values as worthless, therefore, nothing can be known or communicated and associates itself with extreme pessimism and a radical skepticism, having no loyalties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember liking the music then hating it because it was nonstop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think Netflix should have a "Coming Soon" section so I can get excited especially for their originals [ALL] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> common got ktfo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too many nihilists on r/movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol how many "marketing reputation" companies are on r/movies?  just try posting anything bad about la la land, moonlight or arrival </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dems over trump any day.  wake up people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dems over trump any day.  wake up, people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brutally Honest Ballot #5: "Loved Emma Stone and Ryan Gosling Together," "Gimme a Break" About 'Arrival' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you meant that as a slam but note the variety of influences.  whereas tfa was influenced mostly by new hope and a dash of episodes five and six.  thats one of the differences between artists and hacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the sense of cultural superiority here is nauseating.  how much crap have become hits here?  res evil itself was crap from the beginning and we had a bunch of those successful here before china even saw one, so what if youre suddenly too hip for it now, not to mention derivative crap like star wars tfa, jurassic world, arrival, and more mindless blockbusters like transformers.  id take the mermaid which is hilarious over your picks any day. you all are a bunch of movie nazis who lack understanding of other cultures and your own.  and by the way, if it wasnt for china, we'd all be getting fewer movies because you steal movies and dont even go to the theaters anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> welcome to adulthood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you both have points, but just looking at the movies op is watching, they do have a dark undercurrent.  so why do there seem to be so many, my guess is like the others, the country has had a long history of oppression and only recently came out of war and a dictatorship through a capitalist mentality which has left emotional and psychological development to be placed as secondarily important.  so people are going to watch movies that speak to or satisfy that and makes those movies more popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this movie shouldve won an oscar.  it's bullshit prestige titles that get it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hulu honestly right now offers a better deal than netflix because its tv and anime library is superior.  and once youve seen netflix's must see stuff, theres really no reason to have it as most other stuff is not worth seeing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree with op on action, it became repetitive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> collider has a good article, jw2 was a typical sequel in a bad way by favoring plot over character. and like you mentioned, john wasnt very sympathetic.  he goes back on his word and the ending was dumb, only designed to setup the next sequel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you nailed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jerry maguire, he did take that walking escalator kinda fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's that mel is just a very good director.  it takes time to tell a story visually.  rapid cuts like new michaelbay (I like old michael bay) is like that oscar ballot voter who criticized denzel's performance in fences where he didnt let his dialogue breathe.  mel's style shows assuredness, skill, and respect for the audience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> favorite manga of all time.  naruto's creator is said to have been influenced by its beautiful two page layouts.  like the anime, movie doesnt get the experience of reading the manga completely right, but still excited to watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, a guy gives his opinions and instead of discussion, everyone namecalls the guy.  real classy, r/movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt see all the nominees either because I wasnt interested.  And he said a lot more about La La Land which I agree with

 I did not like La La Land  I thought it was imitative and I did not think the leads could sing or dance. I am of an age where I saw [1953's The] Band Wagon and [1952's] Singin' in the Rain, so how could I give this one an award that they never got? Yes, the music is good, but the fact that it got 14 nominations makes me wonder about my colleagues' opinions. I really felt it was a piece of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a guy giving his opinions

to all those downvoting me, I bet youve never been told your opinions are garbage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol that's what I've been saying and was downvoted to oblivion for.  glad to see honeymoon's finally over

dug up my old posts for anyone interested:
https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/57eam0/birthmoviesdeath_offers_an_insightful_analyses/
https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/3z2bxk/star_wars_episode_two_was_a_good_movie_three_was/
https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/5kr69n/with_it_being_known_that_the_new_star_wars_are/
https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/3xwk6g/i_have_no_interest_in_seeing_star_warstfa_the/?ref=search_posts
https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/3z5m2y/star_wars_the_force_awakens_backlash_has_begun/?ref=search_posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great points.  personally I felt like the movie was slapping me in the face the entire screening.  walking to the car, I was so angry.  then after reading other's praise, it's been pissing me off for months.  but im glad the honeymoons finally over and we can view it more objectively </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wonderful, im gonna try that this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sound mixer is 21 times an Oscar bridesmaid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watching tfa was like watching someone try to reverse engineer a masterpiece </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and also Contact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> prequels had flaws but was original.  this is why you dont see tfa being requoted and memed on reddit because theres the ot for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because theyre original.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I bet that's how they did it.  it's like they took every element of star wars into a machine and out the shit came </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give every one in a nursing home a tablet since they're not mobile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very well thought out points. I could see the reasoning behind your pics winnng  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPR is a classic, also check out Hacksaw Ridge, battle scenes take the next step  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love apes series, excited to see what he'll do with bats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh great, more stupid stereotypical characters, animal abuse, stupid hybrid dinos, and high heels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, I looked up the El Super near my places and found 2 dollar salsa like you said!

http://elsupermarkets.com/el-super-california </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only tried Southern California and Texas, both are great, but now you've given me the idea to try NorCal, Arizona and New Mexico's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont want my salsa, I want their salsa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, red's the best :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> red </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's everyone's Oscar Best Picture pick? Here's mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La La Land - too light and navel-gazing, the leads' problems are shallow exacerbated by their lack of talent. Compared to other musicals it pales. Feels like the Academy will regret if they choose this like The Artist.

Arrival - too similar to Contact. Run it side by side and it's the same movie with a different "dress" and doesn't acknowledge it unlike Fast and Furious which everyone knew was essentially a remake of Point Break

Moonlight - appreciate the introspective look into black and gay life in America, but stylistically if I wanted to watch a Wong Kar Wai movie I would watch a Wong Kar Wai movie. Plus, he already made an American movie called My Blueberry Nights which renders Moonlight redundant

Manchester by the Sea - a surprisingly fluffy drama that gives a great look into life in blue collar New England and with a dour ending that may be consistent with the attitude there but is a huge downer. It felt like it should be better and got halfway there. Love Michelle Williams' acting the most but she's barely on screen.

Hell or High water - like Manchester, it's a great look into the West Texas life though doesn't feel really lived in. The story about a pair of bankrobbing brothers is fairly generic and it doesn't leave anything for you to feel or thinkabout after. Hollywood hardly makes action pics with drama anymore so perhaps it feels more special than it is like Argo.

Hacksaw Ridge - first half is dopey but forgivable since we tend to view everyone back then as simple and corny. While I dislike what Gibson has said in the past, the story of Desmond Doss, young man who stood by his convictions despite everyone being against him, is more timely in the age of Trump. The movie presents the drama of Desmond's life stirringly and it is a movie that cannot be forgotten.

I haven't seen the other nominees because they don't look interesting to me

My best picture choice is Hacksaw Ridge

edit: if it was nominated, hands down Silence would be my pick. It was a thorough gutwrenching experience, deeply moving, with no flaws in any category. Pure cinema and just a huge oversight.

Captain Fantastic would be a distant second. A fun but thoughtful criticism of capitalistic modern day life, felt rushed at the end but overall, was refreshing to see a new slice of American life.

edit2: why is this being downvoted?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I get salsa like from the taco trucks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got some extra salsa from the truck yesterday, eating del taco with it and it's making all the difference, and don't want to keep asking them.  Maybe a Mexican supermarket?

edit: found some salsa (red and green) in plastic containers being advertised online at my local supermarket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I buy salsa like from taco trucks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got some extra salsa from the truck yesterday, eating del taco with it and it's making all the difference, and don't want to keep asking them.  Maybe a Mexican supermarket?

edit: red salsa.  green's okay, sorry green! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you mean but it lacks any real exploration of that moral dilemma to be anything other than a simple action romance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian Last Names Lead To Fewer Job Interviews, Still </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree that it's a morality tale.  it always was a romance but marketing, and look of the film made it too glossy and took away the weight of pratts choice and played up the romance too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jokey frat boy wakes girl up, creep.  sad loner who eats with pigeons on benches does the same, wrong but understandable.

tldr: chris pratt was likable in guardians and the POS that was jurassic world, but he's no keanu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you Speed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> time to reboot Passengers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like La La Land and Moonlight shills are working overtime in my post for my best picture nominee that currently sits with 0 upvotes.  I refuse to believe most users on r/movies would downvote the post meant to encourage discussion, but shills on the other hand would find my dismissal of those movies as threats

https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/5vz0br/my_pick_for_best_picture/?utm_content=title utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reddit is the biggest commercial in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's in Brazil isnt he.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> intercept is a rightwing propaganda site, dont believe it's got any of dems' interest in its heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no it looks like one of his guys from the movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this should have an oscar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ask me if I want to have sex again.  always nice to be offered seconds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like an old man, ive known this for a while  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still play but I plan on quitting after I finish my eggs and level up this one pokemon.  after the update I just realized this game has no end, that ill never get the sense of satisfaction of catching all the pokemon before they release more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldve been happier if they made rare pokemons more common so we could finish catching them before the update.  now I just feel overwhelmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silence was the best picture but wasn't nominated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with her on Hacksaw.  Imo, it is the best of the nominees for best picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha I just rewatched it yesterday, what a classic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passengers would've been a hit with him in it.  Hollywood thinks they know everything but passion wins in the end.  I'd love to see him in more action movies,  or any roles where he stands in for us against the system like in Point Break and Matrix  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't leave it until you set out, or else the heat will cause the plastic to seep into the water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only brisket is korean brisket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off-duty LAPD cop pulls out gun and fires while struggling with teen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off-duty LAPD cop pulls out gun and fires while struggling with teen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's vital and estranging them is a surefire way to defeat, however if grassroots could ALSO raise money that will only give us more of a say so I support it in tandem with raising corporate money  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> newsflash, even kings had to get support from the business community. you think dems are gonna fund every election out of their pockets? how many are even participating in elections anymore? theintercept is a bullshit conservative site trying to divide dems by separating the far and moderate left. we have trump after 2016 because of sites like it. wake up before it gets worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try to win everything and we will all lose just like we did. better to pick our battles.  you draw up a list of everything dems as bad as they are (and they can improve or else bernie and ellison wouldn't be in the positions they're in with them) and that repubs support then choose your side wisely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do girls actually like to cuddle after sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> newsflash, even kings had to get support from the business community.  you think dems are gonna fund every election out of their pockets?  how many are even participating in elections anymore?  theintercept is a bullshit conservative site trying to divide dems by separating the far and moderate left. we have trump after 2016 because of sites like it.  wake up before it gets worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same story, different name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> arrival is like westworld, it sucks then the ending tries to convince you otherwise  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep if you hate a movie you can go on but she didn't because she had respect for the alloted time for the interview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen Contact several times, it's one of my favorite alien movies.  Run it and Arrival side by side, same things happen in the same order with very minor variation.   Arrival's literally Contact in a different "dress" with sign language and a new but stupider tragic past for the main character.  Movies are influenced by other movies all the time but Arrival crossed a line and you cant copy one of the great sci fi movies without having to at least acknowledge it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol look forward to their breakfast and southern food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well Arrival ripped Contact off so it can't have been that bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she made an effort to watch all the movies, she just hated Arrival because it's a Contact clone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watch Contact and see Arrival outright stole every single scene, except for the stupid kid sickness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only original thing it added from Contact and it sucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, just saw all three a few months ago, they are classics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everybody should just watch Contact on Netflix which Arrival ripped off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure if I can do the peppers but love idea on extra toasting the bun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, fixed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shake shack has a better brisketlike patty than habit which has too much pepper, but habit you get grilled onions.  I prefer in n out overall which has a great patty and grilled onions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL "Ramen" comes from the Chinese word for pulled noodles, "Lamian", and was changed from "shina soba" due to its association with China after Japan lost WW2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good burger that has a korean bbq brisket taste but overpriced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bans are to create your own echo chamber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love the bankrobber singing scene

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V8LBHemGpjk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> warcrap was awful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American writers fyi, did World War Z and Michael Clayton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can agree with that.  I went for Keanu and he did not disappoint and it's refreshing to see an action movie in that vein in theaters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people like me generally liked it which is the minimum those ratings say, but for me it's not a 90 percent, that would be an action movie like The Raid or Train to Busan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an honest headline and article http://www.boxofficemojo.com/news/?id=4269 p=.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is Edge made more domestically than Great Wall and hadn't begun its global run before critics stuck a fork in it, and also did not foresee it'd have domestic legs.  With The Great Wall, it already has had a successful Chinese run which critics/journalist are ignoring when writing about its performance.  Journalists should report the truth, and reporting that it's "crumbling/tanking" ignores the realities of the movie business as being global.  An objective headline would be "high expectations, performed well in most markets but below average in America, may serve as a model for future coproductions".  

Sounds like you have a nice setup, hope it's fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used the links as examples of the negative reporting on its box office, which the authors acknowledge and are responding to.  When I say critics, I mean journalists in this respect.  And there were a fair amount of critics on Reddit who blew the movie off at first but I and others defended it and now on Reddit it could be considered a "hit" in terms of quality so I want to defend a movie I enjoyed.  

The theater I went to was a midday showing and was still two thirds full, people laughed at the jokes and while I was waiting outside after it ended, people had smiles so I can only speak for what I saw myself. 

I want to see good movies first and second, for good movies to be seen.  I'd love to hear what you think if you see it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm criticizing journalists who write articles to grab clicks and ignore the facts.  They can't evaluate a movie's performance on just the American market.  Edge defied critics and had a good run to 100m domestic despite a similar "low" opening and made money, perhaps Great Wall will break even and eke out a small profit in the end, but journalists pronouncing bombs is just clickbait  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear your reasons why Great Wall is rubbish. I posted the links of critics hating on Edge of Tomorrow based on its box office each week elsewhere in this post and I having seen Great Wall, see they're casting the same spell of doom  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> articles like these came out every week DURING its run.  people have a short memory I suppose

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/quora/why-did-edge-of-tomorrow_b_5564752.html

http://www.cinemablend.com/new/3-Reasons-Edge-Tomorrow-Fumbled-Box-Office-43390.html

https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2014-06-13/after-edge-of-tomorrow-is-tom-cruise-still-a-movie-star </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great Wall was a fun movie.  Critics hated on Edge of Tomorrow saying each week it wasn't a hit but it made its money back in other markets and Americans who saw it made sure it did well in home video.

check out my review [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/5v38ve/the_great_wall_is_a_lot_better_than_its_critics/?utm_content=title utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you forgot to mention she's also your half-brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asian Americans are getting more role models though, Glenn on The Walking Dead, that korean dude from Lost and Hawaii 5.0, Hiroyuki Sanada and Ken Watanabe and John Cho have been in a lot of movies, pretty good for only 5 percent of the population if you count Indians. I agree it'd be cool to see an Asian American Denzel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damon is not a side character.  He is the hero and the actress Jing Tian is a close second but still second.  It's dishonest of the media to play up a whitewashing issue when it's a US-Chinese co-production that like Hollywood and its increasing casting of Chinese actors, is trying to make money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Edge of Tomorrow got savaged by journalists too partly because of casting Tom Cruise in a Japanese character's role.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen The Mermaid?  Monster Hunt?  Journey to the West?  Those movies performed tops in China and had cg but valued story first.  If you're interested the latter two are on Netflix.  

Also, I think it's ignorant to say because movies like Warcraft do well in China that the audience's have worst taste.  It ignores the cultural phenomenon of Warcraft there and smacks of cultural superiority when we have many movies that are horrible and do well because of cg and IP like Jurassic World.

I think it's amazing that Chinese audiences will see mainstream American movies and I don't think it's because American product is that much greater but different and shows an open-mindedness.  Americans will watch foreign movies in small numbers but we could do more to be as open-minded.

Also, The Great Wall has a Western narrative structure and is a fun action movie and far from "shallow and over the top" if you've seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we watch the same movie?  Andy Lau had a lot of lines and significant role.  Matt Damon's accent and its similarity to Brad Pitt's isn't really noticeable in the trailer, it's something you notice after hearing him speak for a while in the movie. And asking Pedro and Dafoe to change is like asking Blunt or Paxton's character to change.  Though if you saw the movie, their ends are incredibly satisfying.  Matt and Jing's arcs are simple but clear which is better than many blockbusters.  I address EOT in another comment in this post.  

I'd honestly love to hear your own review of it to have a discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lot of bad buzz from EOT's box office performance during entirety of its run and people hating on Tom Cruise which extended to the movie.  I think critics can be right and wrong, in this case I feel like they watched a completely different movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
