<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4049</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 07:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he/she is just stating an opinion and suggesting medical help. I would suggest the same thing seeing as this is how I was when I was depressed, well I guess I'm still kind of depressed but besides that you could've suggested something helpful instead of calling someone arrogant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 21:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I honestly believe you question your own attraction to these really skinny women and you want the opinion of others to determine if it is right or wrong. I like skinny women,  but not like Nicole Richie, it's hard to look at women like that because they are so skinny and I can basically see their bones. It isn't wrong to be attracted to these types of girls. If you're attracted to it so be it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've dealt with the same thing, well still dealing with it kinda, but when I opened up to people,  I found out that people are nicer than they may seem. When I was in class, I would try to speak up as much as I could without trying to sound annoying, doing this relieved anxiety for me. After answering or asking questions people became comfortable with me as well as I did and eventually the idea of just randomly talking to someone wasn't scary. If you aren't in school, I suggest trying to get involved with something outside of your house. I thought sports would be the best thing but I don't do well with most sports so i just started in a bowling league (I'm part of a family full of bowlers) these things have helped me gain more friends and kill most of my social anxiety. I hope this helps you like it helped me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 19:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe whatever you like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 03:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Did you go to a university? If so what did you major in?

2) Did you think you would be working at BB? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 18:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure his wife has friends, but he can't pinpoint who has been telling her his posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 21:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how did you feel about seeing Slenderman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 16:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that would be a great arc. I just imagine him getting the kitesu destroyed because of its low weapon grade so he'll get a new one but the sword has to have some significance so I thought the supreme kitesu would be perfect. Which ever way the story goes, I hope it's a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 07:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are you saying he might eventually use just one sword?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 07:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there isn't a reason to have 3 even if they get imbued somehow, the two swords he has without Kitesu has their own special value. With two great swords it seems the Wazamono graded kitesu will be the first sword to get replaced, and if Zoro wants to be the greatest swordsman he'll need a supreme sword. So I believe if he still wants to prove that he has enough luck to overcome the cursed kitesu swords and he wants to become the greatest swordsman he'll pick the supreme kitesu. Or if the story goes in a different direction,  the cursed kitesu he has gets destroyed because its grade is lower than his others and he finds a supreme sword or gets one custom made from a famous swordsmith. 


This is also an 'if' question so I'm not exactly sure what is going to happen I can only make opinions, deduce the ones that seem over the top, and come up with logical explanations to what will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 01:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a hard question but I believe I would start from how many people are dying in a specific area and go from there. If the killings stay local that would be easier to find out who was doing it. Most serial killers like to watch a person die, especially If they don't have to get their hands dirty and some like to come to the scene of the crime. If I had advanced computer skills I could try to find out who has been looking up criminals because I mean how many people spend their free time just looking up local criminals? But if they watched the anime, that might be more difficult, they would most likely stay hidden and not go public seeing as that didn't really work out for light. Honestly I would know what to do if someone had a death note without seeing the anime, but with it, I'm not so sure unless I had better resources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 00:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think zoro will replace the kitesu he has now for a supreme kitesu. I mean the one he has now is only Wazamono graded. I think he'll keep shushui since it's such a great sword.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some random images of women celebrities in relation to double-standards and I think self-image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so how do you get to the 16th floor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 21:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit new to programming, can someone explain this to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 01:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you're here, ive been waiting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I'll keep an eye on him. I'm taking him camping next week. /u/EnlightenedAddict suggested it so I think it'll be good for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 07:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he's 14 and pretty healthy I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 23:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I'll do that. I mean he's my friend but that's something we wouldn't do to each other, especially since he already moved out of his parent's house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 23:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll try to give him some time, but I'll keep contact with him as much as possible. I don't want to blame her, but this doesn't seem like something he would do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a computer science major like I am. We both have a passion for computers. Yes, school is expensive but we both enjoy it. I'm also sure it's worth it to stay in college.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I deal with my friend's toxic girlfriend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 20:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back story: My friend recently got out of a 2 year relationship. We hung out to get his mind off of her (will call her woman A) by going to see a movie with some friends (we're all 18 and 19 so we can't get into bars) he met this girl (woman B) and instantly connected with her. Since then we don't talk much, but when we did he explained that he dropped out of college because woman B asked him to and now they're moving in with each other. WTF?

Edit: I wish I could give more details but, I can't get much out of him, he pretty much cut contact with me and everyone that we're friends with. 

Edit 2: These are all good suggestions,  I appreciate the help. I recently talked to him and we're hanging out tomorrow, his girlfriend is coming along. Hopefully it all goes smoothly. 

Edit 3: I'll probably post an update tomorrow. If anyone else wants to give me anymore advice feel free to post here until then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 19:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a double standard.

Men do pretty "unmanly" things, but we tell no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 19:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women in glasses.  

It's not all women, and I'm pretty sure it isn't a fetish of mine I just kinda like it.

I love it when my girlfriend underdresses, I'm not exactly sure why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 19:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone takes food out and never puts it back. I see the boxes of cereal or bags of chips on the counter, pick it up, *empty*, proceed to get pissed as I throw it all away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 19:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it a habit to go outside, maybe even exercise to relieve some stress. I went through the same thing as you and it helped a lot to change things up a bit and get out of limbo. My brother is actually doing something similar to this, he stays in his room all day and when he comes out he acts like he's in 'Auto-pilot'. I'm not really sure what to do to help. I would give him advice but he's stubborn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 18:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to read more of your poems, if you don't mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What happens to our bodies during sex? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 00:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold up (hold up) hold up (hold up) Hold up (hold up).... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh......no! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 14:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How come you don't have a girlfriend?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 08:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so awesome! I watched all 3 of the videos and subscribed. I think it's awesome she moved away from the U.S. all the way to Japan, I wish I had that much dedication to a dream job. After I'm done learning Japanese I hope to visit and maybe move there some day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 19:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some hot celebrities, but I can't imagine them sitting on my face...but if I had to choose I'd say Natalie Portman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 10:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to become the next most downvoted redditor on Reddit? You seem to only say negative comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 03:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm great pick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your other two? Are they from this list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, this is such a great list, I started watching Hajime no ippo a few weeks ago and I'm almost finished with *the fighting*. This series has seriously inspired me to get back into the gym and maybe learn a martial art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok Katie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 23:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like frosting too but that can get pretty repetitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 19:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Dr. Who. The concept is ok but it's not appealing to me at all. I don't understand why people like this show. It was exhausting just trying to get passed the first episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People named Brenden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The taste and you get the feeling that it's just too much for your liking. I don't like Nutella for this reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she realize you were having a seizure?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be jealous of hate being with love. I wouldn't understand why love likes assholes like hate and doesn't like me. I would stay jealous until they split apart, then I would be ready to take on love in my life, but I'm the type of person who gets nervous and never really makes a move. And then love finds another hate before I even tried and I just sit here being jealous until the day comes when they split apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking forward to new and better technology, specifically from Google. And new DC and Marvel movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't sound too pleasant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 07:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I tried to find it I really did, I spent hours looking and listening, if there was a better way to find it I would've had an immediate answer. I love the soundtracks for Death Note, but it wasn't enough to find what you were looking for. The closest I got to something, if anything, was mikami concertino. Down vote me if you want, but no one can tell me I didn't try hard enough. I hope someone has your answer soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 23:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a virgin. My parents are very religious and don't want me to have sex until I'm married. I think the worst part about all of this is that my dad is more strict than my mom.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
