<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 15:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish that you're wife had found out. I feel like she deserves better... You must be low as anything to cheat on your depressed wife, because you weren't getting any sex. :( 
Why didn't you suggest fertility treatment sooner? What did you do to help your wife? Etc.

Edit
Your wife agreed to get help to get better, so you probably could have done that without cheating at all... Maybe more effort was required on her, instead of wasting it on other girls. Just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, for a start those links refer to making false reviews to help sell products. This post is about posts on a self help website, no money involved. Hiding posts that break rules on that site is totally different to what you have posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 10:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not ganguro girls, that trend is so unattractive 90% of the time haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that this is relevant here, it's an entirely different thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 14:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is though, while those things are true.. It's not a universal truth. 
In order for something to be bad, there must always be a good to compare it too. Otherwise nothing would be good or bad. It would just 'be'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 14:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have tried like, snore strips or something first. I wouldn't have jumped right into cutting my own mouth out. but, that's just me. 

My advice is to put down the knife and scissors and call 911. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 14:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my lord.. Run boy. I would not sleep at home for weeks. Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 09:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phew, I'm so glad I'm not the only one. It took me a while to work it out, I felt so daft! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 04:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good! Bravo! I loved this tale, I'd love to know what the beast is or where it came from. What a mystery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 03:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't put my tongue on it is a phrase I've never heard ;) perhaps, you meant finger? Or are there different variations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 03:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I read this, I was really confused. I thought that you meant you had two extra fingers on one hand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 11:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you ok op?! Could you get help?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 11:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, that scary op. Is the news for your area updating? There's been nothing on my news.. Maybe try going out, but don't make eye contact with anyone? Or try contacting friends or family to see if the problem spread further than the plaza?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 11:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi haven't read the whole story yet, but it took me ages to realise that it was man in the plaza, not man in the pizza. Wow, I nearly read this whole story in a really weird way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 11:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that I heard a story about this once, people and fog. I don't remember, but it's ringing bells.

This was awesome, because it's a real mystery. Did any people go missing that week?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 10:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old hospital might not even have cameras though, or yet have operating ones in the new part. The footage op talks about came from the link right? And maybe the spirit only goes there when it follows someone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 10:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is retardation still a typical description in mental illness? 
The 40's wasn't a great time to be a mental patient but we did learn a lot from that era. Electric shock therapy and trepanning (drilling of the skull) is still in use today, but obviously more regulated. 
I don't want to be mean, but your intro made it a bit hard to feel bad for you.. Because you don't seem very caring about the sick people you work around. Maybe it's just the way I've read it though. I would be careful when going back on rounds, mark definitely knows more than he is telling you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... I see. My bad then lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 16:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now, the stoner kid is the one trapped? That sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 16:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds pretty similar to 'the entity', except I don't think that the creature in that loved the woman. It just enjoyed hurting her... And it was way bigger. It's a movie btw, kinda old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One light bulb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 02:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a child I often had strange thoughts, as I'm sure most children do. Having unusual thoughts floating through a childish mind isn't immediately unusual, and parents only show concern when a child becomes vocal about their weird flights of fancy. No one ever really asked me about my thoughts, and even if they did, some things are best left unsaid. Even as a child I knew that I probably shouldn't share some of my crazy thoughts.

It all began one day, when I was in the toilet. At the tender age of 6, I was minding my own business, my brain decided to ask me 'what if flushing the toilet too much, brings a monster to life?' 
Hmm. Then I was stuck, truly stuck, sitting on my porcelain throne. Should I flush the toilet? But what if not flushing the toilet will unleash this beast instead, what if it's just a trick? I remember crying, sitting bare bottomed over the dilemma that I had found myself in. I think my mum saved me, somehow. But every trip to the toilet since then was an inner torment, a grim reminder of the terror I felt that day. The fate of the world had seemingly rested in my chubby, 6 year old hands.

Over the years, other strange thoughts have come and gone. With some lingering longer than others, but always following the same theme. A singular action, carried out by me, ending the world or unleashing some terrible monstrosity upon mankind. Whether it be something small, like never knocking three times or less on a door. Would two knocks complete some ancient, yet unfinished ritual? In turn summoning a demon forth from hell, burning all of the world alive in its wake.
Or whether it be something ridiculous, like closing my eyes until the fluorescent lights finish blinking on in my office. If I have my eyes open, I might see into another dimension. Everyone knows that seeing something like that creates a pathway between the two dimensions, right? My brain was always providing me with these little instructions, it was always there to pester me with these warnings.

'Don't kick that plank, it's loose. It'll definitely cause a building collapse.'
'Don't look behind you three times, we are walking at night! Don't you remember that story? The one about raw head? I know it was fiction, but these things can happen!'
'Don't tap that wall, the ceiling will totally collapse. Might even cause an earth quake.'

The thoughts died down with age, which was so good. I couldn't stand always feeling so responsible, all the time. Having that weight on my shoulders was draining. I suppose that I also like the normalcy, most people don't think such weird things. I could have moved on, I could have just left it all behind. If not for the light bulb.

You see, I've lived in my home for 10 years now. I keep to myself, I don't know my neighbours but I see them now and again. My home is nice, it suits me fine and I'm happy here. Behind my home, there is a row of houses that directly mirrors my street. Our houses are separated by a dirt path and our mirrored back yards. Nice wooden fences; matching council house windows, hopefully you get the idea. Each on my street has a direct view to the back windows of the houses on the opposite street, and visa versa. Everyone was just close enough to see when people were home, but far enough away that you were fine if you liked to hoover naked. 

For ten years; the house behind me has been occupied by the same person, or people. I know that someone must live there! Lights in other rooms go on and off during the evenings, blinds go up and down in the windows. But, for ten years, that one light bulb has always been on. Always on, never covered, never hidden from view and never, ever off.
At first, I assumed that it was a bedroom, in the same place as mine. I too prefer the small comfort of the standard 'box' room, rather than the king sized room at the front of my house. It wouldn't be too unusual to assume that there was a child, or even an adult, using that room as a bedroom. Perhaps our schedules were just too different, and I missed the bulbs' off times. Besides, it was their electricity bill after all! What did I really care? 

After a long while, it became a curious fascination. How odd, for someone to leave a light bulb on for so long. How strange, that they don't even have curtains in that room.

Over time, it turned into something more than a fascination. I would look slyly out of my window now and again, just to see the bulb hanging from its wire. Doing nothing other than lighting up an empty room. Why was the room so bare? From my vantage point I could tell that the room was empty, no furniture, no curtains and not even a light shade for the poor lonely bulb. What was the point? It boggled me, truly. I often thought of the bulb, it seemed wasteful really. 

Years passed, and my obsession grew and grew. Sometimes I was angry, angry at that damn bulb. It was just there and I wanted to know why! I had never, ever seen a human in that house. The lights still alternated in the other rooms, as if people were living a life in that place. But I never saw any other signs of life there, the windows and doors remained closed. No sounds of children, pets or even the tv ever floated on the breeze over to my home. I never smelt freshly cut grass from the garden, yet the grass always seemed well trimmed.

The bulb was on, just on all the time. I realised that it must be there for a reason.

'It's to keep the dark away.' That's the logical reason, and I knew that my brain had been wrong before. All of the stupid obsessions I'd had before had been wrong, but this one just felt so right. I became the unofficial watcher of the bulb, it had to stay on. The darkness would swallow us whole should it ever go out. It can't go out, never has in 10 years. That was my motto, and I was the proudest member of my own little fan club. 

What does it really take to keep monsters away, to keep demons sealed in their realms and to keep evil away from our homes? Light! Light has kept us safe. None of the other things I've done before mattered, none of those childish games were the true saviour of us. The light bulb is! The the protector of the bulb! 

For the first time in 10 years, I saw the darkness. It took over my light, in the space of one blink. I knew that I had to save the light, I knew that I had to get that bulb back on before the world was swallowed whole by the inky darkness. I tried my best, and that why I'm here now underneath the shattered remains of our old protector. I'm here, huddled in the suffocating darkness and I can feel it inside of me. The darkness is killing me, I can feel the cold tendrils seeping into my skin and tearing me apart. But I don't regret trying, I don't regret jumping my fence and leaping into the creepy ever cut garden. I don't regret smashing into this strange house, with its sentient light switches. I don't regret slaughtering the demons that I found in here, pretending to be surprised at my entrance. Their bright red blood splashing onto me, as they screamed and gurgled in broken english. 
I regret cutting myself on the glass of the smashed back door, maybe I'd have been faster. Maybe, I could have gotten here quicker. I regret not being able to save the light. I regret not locking the door as another demon knocks, telling me to come out. It's calling to me in perfect english, telling me that it's 'the police'. What a joke, the world is ending and these demons still want to play games. I regret that the darkness won't kill me, before the demon does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 02:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but it's clear in the story that he still wants to leave.
And he must be fairly mobile to move around and find new potential suitors now and again. So I was just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't even see the dodgy part, you killed him for nothing man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, he was playing hide and seek but got stuck, or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got that, but I didn't really get the ending. In my mind, it seemed to fold back around full circle and it left me confused. But I might just need to re read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always nice to see urban legends still going strong. Not!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure that I'm following?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thank you. I've never read / seen that :) I do understand where you're coming from though, with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing that op buried the body in the neighbours yard, and the neighbour was about to unearth it by digging a pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, dick move bro. He died, because you were scared of getting in trouble.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, wonderful writing. This called me back to read again and again. 
I'm so sorry about what you went through op, maybe you could post your lab results to other families anonymously. They might not believe you, but at least you gave them the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 11:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What keeps the men around once they aren't in the cage? Clearly the husband wants to leave. 
What keeps this cycle going?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might have been there before, don't try to smash something out of existence with out even giving it a chance :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 years fixated on someone else wasted. Do not answer the door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it was on cctv.. Usually stories like this end with the op seeming crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, don't kill him.. You should scoop up your new kids and mosey on down to the cdc or something for umm, safety reasons. New children are prone to all kids of illnesses... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, maybe it's just looking for somewhere to call home. Try to talk to it? It seems vaguely intelligent, from the way it seems interested in you and it watches. The cats are aware of it, so it's not just in your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just call the police some more lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will adopt you mister otter. I will look after you.
No one deserves to be treated that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get that pillow, your brothers pillow and all the ones your dad bought and burn em all. Yup. Burn them.

Or maybe take the pillow to the living room, where your girlfriend won't hear and talk to it. It might turn out to be pretty chill. Just don't sleep on it again, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. So, what you do now is call 911. Enough evidence right? Or, leave your hotel room and drive to a police station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 01:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so maybe now and again the 'sky' gives birth, but before hand it clears out the area using radiation. I'd be careful, there might be hundreds of those things by now. Especially if gwen has seen it before.. It must have happened more than once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 11:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it just happens. Our old dog managed to kill a litter once, she was a sausage dog and we had locked her out of the room where the kittens were nesting with mumma cat... But she clawed through the door just to get in there and kill them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 11:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irresponsible pet owner right here. Buying from breeders, not spaying animals, leaving newborns with a dog, 'we were going to sell them anyway'. Jeez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 02:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it can't be your mental health causing this... There would surely be evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting braver, be careful op!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was his plan to kill the entire family, including himself then? 
He should have just picked you all up and high tailed it. It seems like he does really love you.

I got a bit confused by the 'becoming a nuisance' though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr tickle should raise his own damn kids. That's so unfair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat has white paws, and I love her with all my heart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed that it was something in the coffee, but for some reason the elbow scratching threw me off lol, as op said the blood tasted good. Someone was saying that the coffees might have been different drugs for each one as well. 
Is it possible to get high from many drugs just by mixing them into a drink? I don't honestly know much about that kind of thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 11:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 11:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to report you to the foundation! Damn op, don't you worry about what the cult is planning?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 11:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just a slight mistake in the story to be honest. Otherwise it doesn't really make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 11:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, was he taking drugs the whole time? But like, blocking it out? 
Or was it the coffee with something extra added?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 17:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did take me a while to realise it was a doll not a person, I guess it was a little vague on purpose for the twist.
I also thought that the parents were arguing because of the doll, and the gifts... Not because of neglect. Then later on, the op makes a slight reveal about that as well. I enjoyed the way that this was written. 

Op I wish you luck with things, confiscate that doll and contact the police. Please keep us updated on your safety!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 10:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angry? Why angry?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 10:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought it was a person who was wearing a glued on hat haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 10:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you cheat on a werewolf? Self preservation lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 10:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, do you think it happened because they weren't a native boat? Like, being native protects them or something from the creature there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 10:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then it also said that the people who have been around technology forever are really susceptible to it. It was worded really strange. So I'm not really sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 03:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to hear more please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the drink was the problem, he had... A friend staying over, keeping him awake.
Which is creepy lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm horrifically scarred, and deformed, please call my parents to fix this mess I'm now in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, suicide isn't really the Cause... It's population control. What a mad idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hardly fair, you were a blooming foetus.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 13:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what? What are you then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 12:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you escape? At least you could still see, hopefully the blindness was temporary!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
