<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7095</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta be this. This fight would be slick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a 10 across the board for me too. 
Sidenote, my former japanese teacher looked a lot like her. But I never noticed until after I left that school. Needless to say I can never go back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that was the point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 10:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.mmafighting.com/2016/8/21/12572478/nate-diaz-vs-conor-mcgregor-2-scorecard-ufc-202 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 07:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find the thread but another user here explained really well why conor gets the pay and treatment he does. He's obviously a great fighter, but he's also the best salesman in the ufc right now. Not only is he better than everyone else at selling fights, mostly everyone else sucks at selling fights. Michael Bisping is the only other UFC fighter that can showboat, like McGregor, and even he's only getting a chance to do it recently. Not everyone likes the trash talk (bit WWE, I get it) but McGregor is making the UFC more money than anyone else on their roster. That's why he gets overpaid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 07:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lets thank SpiritOCE for bringing the math </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 06:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McGregor landed a LOT of clean leg kicks, I think Nate managed to check maybe 2 of them (could be 3, anyone know for sure?), reversed just about every clinch, knocked Nate to his back several times, successfully defended 2 out of 3 take down attempts. 

it was a great fight but i don't understand confusion with the win. close as fuck for sure but Conor definitely deserved that margin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 06:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic fight. Both guys gave it their all and the respect shown at the end was great to see. Conor definitely deserved the win though, hopefully now the guys who like to rag on him needlessly will let up a little. How much more does have to do to prove he's not overrated?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 15:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hobgoblin in shibuya always show ufc if mcgregor is fighting. Sometimes even if hes not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 11:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah i remember that now. Nothing was said about shady methods though, is that just speculation on your part? 

For the record john kavanagh didnt want him to take the nate rematch either, so idk if his coach will necessarily get what he wants. I really cant see him simply vacating that belt. Losing it, sure, maybe. But i don't think he'll choose to lose it without a fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 09:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you got a link for his coaches saying that? Ive never heard it before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 06:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive heard a lot of people saying he wont go back to 145 but his whole ambition was to be a dual-weight champion. If dana is like "defend or vacate" i reckon he'll defend it. Win or lose, then is the time to move to 155. That makes more sense to me. 

Why are so many people sure he'll vacate the belt? Ive never heard anyone on the inside say that, and he explicitly denied it at the presser anyway. 

Sounds to me like a lot of people WANT him to vacate the belt. Which is a different thing entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
