<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8764</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 08:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most underrated important play of the game was the wild pitch by Hunter Strickland. Salvy had two weak swings before the wild pitch, which moved the runners over to second and third. I think Perez was afraid of hitting into a double play and after the DP was taken out, he had a strong swing on the next play. 

That pitch also started the unraveling of Strickland and was huge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 08:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tim Hudson wins the World Series MVP after the Giants win the series in 6. I hate picking against the Royals, but I hate how they've become the favorite of sorts when it comes to Vegas and "expert" predictions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cowboys are the obvious answer.

I'll add a couple items:

- I didn't think Seattle would three games all year. 

- The Chiefs defense is much better than I thought. They had the toughest six-game start to the season and I thought 1-5 was very possible.

- Jason Garrett FINALLY commiting to the run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 19:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of respect for both of those guys and the Giants organization in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 10:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of great ones, but I'll add one I haven't seen: Hitler declaring war on America shortly after Pearl Harbor. 

There were possible scenarios for him to defeat England and later the Soviet Union. If the Nazis don't shift the bombing efforts to London, they could have wiped the Royal Air Force. Had Hitler's race views prevented the Germans from arming and welcoming the Eastern Europeans who initially viewed the Germans as liberators from Stalin, perhaps they could have knocked out the Soviets. 

There was no possible way Nazi Germany could have defeated the United States, Great Britain AND the Soviet Union. America's economy was a war machine by 1945 and its production dwarfed anything Germany could have produced even at its peak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 07:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost forgot that Marshall Faulk was once his teammate. Crazy how long Manning's played in the league at the high level he has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 07:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not racist. The commenter was also referring to her past relationship with Brody, who was a white guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 07:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of negative press about this upcoming World Series. Someone on ESPN wrote it was the "worst World Series" ever. 

I guarantee you that if an 88-win Yankee team was playing an 89-win Dodger team in the World Series, the manufactured storyline would be considerably more positive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 07:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with the crying scene, one part that makes me think he was bitten was the "one more" kiss scene. It felt like a good bye of sorts. 

I could be wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 03:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respectfully disagree. Joe Montana or John Elway were better. They played in an era where defenses were allowed to be physical with wide receivers, allowed to hit the QB at full speed and both played outside of a dome and when most stadiums had grass. 

Peyton's a great quarterback for sure, but he's played in the most friendly era when it comes to quarterbacks. I'd take Montana, Elway and even Dan Marino before him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 01:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props to the Chiefs on the win. It's no doubt they're a better team from last year. They already more "great wins" this year than they had last year. AFC West could send three teams back to the playoffs this year. 

And of course, my Raiders are the fourth team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 09:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's gotta be the tallest photographer ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 08:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2007 and 2008 Florida Gators teams would make for an interesting 30-for-30 on how some of those players turned out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 07:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed this play a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 07:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the day I stopped investing emotions into my sports teams. That was a great win for your program! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 07:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, usually Missouri is on the other end of fluky things like this. Muschamp will be a solid defensive coordinator somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 06:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florida State would finish fourth or fifth in the SEC West this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 05:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two best teams so far this year are from the State of Mississippi. Incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 05:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Jameis Winston, Florida State got away with one there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 06:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May God damn these people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 05:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who takes part in a lot of "Pick'Em" contests and occasionally makes small wagers on CFB games, I dislike Clemson and Virginia Tech because they are my betting kryptonite. No matter how hard I study trends or look at the match-ups in a toss-up game involving one of the two teams, I lose. It feels like my all-time picking record with them is 3-97. 

Just last year, I picked Georgia to beat Clemson, then picked Clemson to beat Florida State and then picked Ohio State to beat Clemson. 0 for fucking 3. I picked Clemson to beat Florida State this year and they meltdown and choke. Clemson upsetting LSU a few years ago in a bowl game hurt my chances at winning a Bowl Pick'Em I was in. 

The best way to become a millionaire is to ask me who I'm picking in a game involving those two teams and bet the opposite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 16:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 95 percent of baseball experts picked the A's and the Angels to knock off the Royals this postseason. Most will consider the Giants the favorite in the World Series. 

That's one heck of a West Coast bias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 09:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly enough, this is the type of face I made when watching Quin's offense when he coached Mizzou.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 05:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mathenied  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 01:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From 2003-2006, the National League Championship Series were awesome. Some terrific series in that stretch that were overshadowed by the 2004 Red Sox comeback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 01:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest problem with those who had the biggest issue with steroids is I bet they would have done the same thing. If there was a magic pill, cream, ect., that could help me  become a better salesperson and double or triple my income, I'd do it in a hurry. Baseball writers are very political and the fact there hasn't been an unanimous first ballot Hall of Famer speaks to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 01:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this will be unpopular with some baseball fans, particularly "traditionalists," but I miss the guy. I'm not a Giants fan, but whenever the Giants were on TV from 2000-2003, I'd watch to see Bonds hit a few times. Every at-bat, excluding the intentional walks, was filled with drama. He had the most beautiful swing I've seen and it's a joke he's not in the Hall of Fame. Each era had asterisks attached to them and steroids don't account for Bonds' amazing hand-eye coordination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 12:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the greatest "what if's" in NFL and NCAA history. There's a pretty good chance Nick Saban doesn't leave after two years. The Alabama dynasty never happens and the Saints would possibly be in San Antonio if not for Brees and Sean Payton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 07:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially after the 1996 ALCS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2010's Giants remind me of the 1990's Yankees a lot. They find a way to score clutch runs and haven't really done it with power. Their opponents also have a habit of imploding and beating themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 08:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. He's got a script and he sticks to it. That's both good and bad depending on what type of situation he has. His handling of pitchers during the season drove me nuts, particularly with bringing Aaron Crow in during in a crucial game against the Red Sox late in the season. Some of his substitution moves when it came to pinch hitters were mistakes too. All managers make bad moves, but Yost's come in the most important times. He's lucky the Royals came back in the Wild Card game.

The over reliance on bunting bothers me too, but to his credit, it's worked in the postseason. I thought Moose bunting in the 9th inning of Game 2 in the ALCS was a terrible mistake. It turned into two runs. The buttons he's pushed --- even the wrong ones --- have worked since the Wild Card debacle. 

That said, sometimes a manager looks smarter depending on the team he has. Joe Torre lost a ton of games with the Mets and the Cardinals, only to later win four World Series with the Yankees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 02:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in 1985 and he's the best player I've seen in my lifetime. I don't care how much stuff he put in his body - he should be in the Hall of Fame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 10:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the general theme is New Blood vs. Establishment. Either way, you'll have a match-up of a team looking to snap a looooong World Series drought vs. a team that's won a couple the past decade. The Giants are also looking to become a dynasty and three titles in five years would qualify them for that. 

Also, if the Royals get the Giants, they'd have a chance to eliminate a third California team from the playoffs. I'm guessing that's never been done.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 10:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter King of SI tweeted that this year's Royals team would be a good candidate for Sports Illustrated "Sportsman of the Year" and just give the entire team the award. If they come out of no where and win the World Series, they'd definitely be worthy of any award. 

That said, it's far too early to bury the Orioles and the winner of the NCLS will bring a ton of postseason experience. Royals still have a lot of work to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 08:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss the days when the biggest NCAA football scandal involved coaches covering up tattoos. Jim Tressel, who I think got a raw deal, is an angel compared to all of this stuff that's come out on Penn State and Florida State the past few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 08:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking of this exact scenario, though I think the Royals have had more of a magic carpet ride with all of these wins. 

However, I still think the ALCS will go 6 or 7 games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 06:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, if he keeps this up, ESPN may suspend him for three weeks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 05:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moneyball. I'm a big baseball fan and while I enjoyed the book and the rise of Billy Beane's Oakland A's, I thought there was no way the movie would work out. 

It did and it's one of my favorite 10 sports movies of all-time. Brad Pitt was great in that movie and you actually feel sorry for him as his team loses and gets criticized no matter how great they've been.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 23:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if they underwhelmed in 2004. They had the best record that year, but the Red Sox or the Yankees weren't exactly chopped liver that year. I recall most people picking the Red Sox before that World Series, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 02:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. With the Nats rotation, I'm not ruling out a comeback. 

However, I guess the most appropriate ending for the Nats would be to win the two games in San Francisco and blow a late lead at home in Game 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 02:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least Los Angeles will get St. Louis' NFL team here in a few months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 08:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, although the way he's been giving up homers this postseason scares me in a ballpark in Baltimore. 

I have a feeling there will be more scoring than expected in this series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the Tigers running off their manager after one year. I know they had a disappointing end, but that bullpen was a joke last year in the postseason and Dave Dombrowski deserves blame for that.

The Dodgers ,on the other hand, should hire him. Mattingly might be the one guy that Yost has an advantage over in a potential World Series match-up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kershaw is due for a playoff gem. That's the one thing I'd stay confident about if I was a Dodgers fan. That guy is too good not to pitch one great playoff game, even if it's against the Cardinals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Boston's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 07:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, they are. I'm probably the only Barry Bonds fan who lives outside of the Bay Area. The K and PacBell would make for two awesome ballparks for The World Series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 01:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iowa State has been screwed multiple times by officials in football and basketball over the last few years. There was a KU-Iowa State basketball game a few years back that featured horrendous calls in KU's favor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is why LeBron only signed a two-year deal with Cleveland. That next deal he'll get from the Cavs will be a monster deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 01:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, at least Kap's dumb interceptions happen in the postseason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 01:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking forward to next week's "Team Hates Harbaugh" leak in order to fire up the 49ers team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 08:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is reminding me of the year 2007 when team after team was upset. So many upsets happened that Missouri and Kansas played one of the most important regular season games. More upsets happened, which allowed a two-loss LSU team to win the championship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 08:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alabama. They get Auburn and A M at home and I honestly don't see them losing to any one else. I think those three teams are the best three of the bunch and they'll start pulling away from everyone else in the next few weeks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 08:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scioscia's a class act...very complimentary towards the Royals in his press conference . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 08:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a great comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 11:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why I loved him when he pitched and loved him when he destroyed Yost tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 03:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Cavs-Wizards will be great this year. The guards from both teams are snipping at each other in the media. Add the Pierce element and his history with LeBron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 02:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cavs/Wizards played some great series the first time LeBron was on the Cavs. Hope that rivalry is reborn, along with the Bulls/Cavs. The NBA needs more rivalries and less buddy-buddy stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 07:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were a lot of rumors late last year that Gruden was interested in coming back to the Raiders or going to the Falcons if that job opened up. I think they'd need to fire McKenzie and offer Gruden full control to make it happen. 

Should they? I don't know. Gruden didn't do a good job with full control after winning the Super Bowl with Dungy's roster. I love the guy, but full control rarely works in the NFL. I think Andy Reid and the job he's done in Kansas City the past two years is proof that when a coach only coaches, that's good. I think that's what doomed him in Philly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 05:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this. It reminds me of the Gruden situation in his last year as Oakland's coach, though it didn't get this bad. The stage is being set for a divorce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 05:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I'm wish Bill Simmons wasn't suspended right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 05:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best I've seen the Chiefs play since the Vermeil era. WOW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 23:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My obvious bias aside, Jim Harbaugh and the Raiders are a match in heaven personality wise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 20:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's unfair to pin ALL of the blame on Mickelson, but I think Brandel's point about the US not being a "team" is dead on. And he is accurate about what Mickelson did before the 2004 Ryder Cup, changing clubs and practicing at a different course before the event. It seems like for Europe, the Ryder Cup is a competition and for this generation of American golfers, the Ryder Cup is an interruption of their offseason. 

I think Phil is the embodiment of this generation of American golfers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 04:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, great. That means the annual "Jon Gruden back to Oakland!!!!" rumors will have legs for a few extra months this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 12:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Kansas (we don't play them anymore, though)

2. Illinois (ditto)

3. South Carolina ---- After the last two years, I think this is turning into Mizzou's best SEC rivalry. I could see Arkansas fill that void down the road, however.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 11:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Lavin's run at UCLA is the perfect example of this. Bad regular season, but they'd win a few in the tournament and he'd survive it. Then, the bottom fell out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 11:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, some big time jobs may open this season. I think Muschamp is close to toast if Florida loses to Tennessee next week and I could see that happening. Also, if the Cowboys gig opens up, Jerry Jones may go the college route again and perhaps poach someone like Bob Stoops, Gus Malzahn or Sumlin. All three of those programs are in better shape than Michigan right now. 

If Michigan axes Hoke, they get a jump start to a potentially busy offseason. 

EDIT: Also, if they really want to make a move for Harbaugh, they may be competing against other NFL teams too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 05:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually Mizzou leaves me dumbfounded about how they find a way to lose a game. Tonight, I'm left dumbfounded about how they won that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 02:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in here to say this. I was born in 1985 and they and the '07 Patriots are the two best teams that didn't win it all. We were robbed of a potentially great Super Bowl between them and Elway's Broncos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 02:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll never happen, but the Internet would break if Michigan hired Jim Tressel as head coach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 23:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we were a little late to do that whole "let's beat Hitler and fascism thing." We are even now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 21:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lowest common denominator for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 20:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Every employee must be accountable to ESPN and those engaged in our editorial operations must also operate within ESPNs journalistic standards. Bill Simmons did not meet those obligations in a recent podcast.

---- Statement from ESPN, the same network that recently did a story about Michael Sam's showering habits and ran a graphic of the women Derek Jeter dated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 00:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And as a libertarian, I dislike him because of ALL these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 04:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ESPN is already trying to suspend Matt and Trey for three episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 01:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet Ray Lewis is still on the air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 01:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. Just wishing out loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 01:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protecting the shield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 01:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish Simmons would go independent. He's the one sports writer in America that could pull it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 02:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note to ISIS: When you align the US, Israel, Iran, Russia and China into the same column, you're doing something wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS is screwed. Vladimir Putin is the one world leader who doesn't care about perception in the international world. Russia won't fight ISIS with one hand tied behind its back like The West has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 03:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason a lot of people are complaining about the rules today is Peyton Manning was on the losing end of them. 

I'm 100 percent OK with the current rule as it is, although I like the college deal better. If your defense allows a team to go down the field on you, that's their problem. 

I understood the frustration of a field goal ending things. But a defense should do its job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 00:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But to be fair to Fox, Manning has always struggled against great defenses, whether it be those early Belichick teams or these Seahawks. At some point, Peyton Manning deserves criticism and Fox shouldn't be scapegoated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 00:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah....I wonder how Montana, Marino and Elway would play in this era where you can't hit quarterbacks too hard or grab WRs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 14:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excluding the usual suspects like the Patriots and 49ers and the teams on the rise like Carolina and Cincinnati, my dark horse is Buffalo. Solid running game, a dangerous group of wide receivers and their defense can stop the run. 

Admittedly, E.J. Manuel needs to get better in order for them to become a Super Bowl contender. 

But man, I really like that talent they have. Plus, they have the sentimental stories of the owner dying and Jim Kelly's health improving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 09:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've went back and forth, but I'm leaning towards "work" for these reasons: 

1. Everyone benefited. Bret got the big contract from WCW and had the best entrance into WCW possible. He was the most famous athlete in the world. Shawn Michaels got heel heat you can't buy and the title. Vince McMahon got more attention to his company and Bret's exit opened the door for Steve Austin to rise and for "Mr. McMahon" to become a great heel. Heck, even the ref is famous because of it. It was the perfect end for Bret Hart's "Hitman" character. 

2. Vince had MANY opportunities to take the belt off Bret. Also, if I remember the timeline right, the contract negotiations were going on even before Bret won the belt that year. Why put the belt on him in the first place? Also, why not take the belt off of him before Survivor Series? Vince is too smart of a guy in my opinion to get himself into a jam like this, especially after the fiasco of the female wrestler who trashed his belt on Nitro. 

3. The fact Owen stayed. I know Bulldog left, but if someone legitimately did that to my brother, it would be tough for me to work for Vince. 

4. For years, Vince refused to let outside cameramen take photos around the ring. Somehow he decides to let a documentary film company go backstage, interview wrestlers, ect.? Come on. 

5. The fact multiple wrestlers, including Lawler, Kevin Nash and others, suggest it's a work is telling to me. Lawler was part of the greatest storyline ever with Andy Kauffman and they kept that secret for 20 years. 

I see both sides of the argument, but those are my five reasons why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 03:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeBron James. He was hyped up as a high school kid and he's the greatest athlete I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
