<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2574</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level of surprise: 0

Level of schadenfreude: 1000000000000000000000000000000000000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF are "clad women", or, GamerGate doesn't even read their own posts before commenting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://np.reddit.com/r/KotakuInAction/comments/3d67oa/goal_were_back_baby_operationazureorbs_message/

From the sample email:

 And The Verge, ironically libelled a respected Scientist as a 'misogynist' for wearing a T-Shirt of clad women. This incident has now become infamous, yet how can a Vox property slander men for liking clad women yet SB-Nation covers sports which have cheerleaders? Who's primary goal is to look clad for men?

It's pretty funny that as far as I can tell, with 94 comments and 451 upvotes at the moment, no one has called out the egregious typos in the sample email (wtf is just "clad", "who's", "SB-Nation" vs "SB Nation").  

Also, missing the irony.

My only conclusion is that GamerGate, in grand tradition, doesn't even read their own articles and posts before commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 09:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW the patreon link is always there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, whoever Manabyte is, they've got an axe to grind against Polygon. He's *still* going on about it on Twitter.  Just give it up, guy.  Not even KiA believes you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's just his hypocrisy - he likes his T A in one place, what's wrong if someone else likes their's in a game?

There's nothing wrong with that.  If that someone else wants to write their review of the game, they can score accordingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vagrant Story also did it pretty well, IMO.  Same with the original Parasite Eve.  Borderlands' "playthrough 2" was also quite enjoyable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, left out a word.  one of my favorite authors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a tough call with Martin and asoiaf. The sexism in his world definitely adds to the flavor of the settingsand arguably to the realism. But in the novels at least, IMO I think he's handled it mostly respectfully.

Anyway, with the larger issue of realism in fantasy, one of the best responses is also from one my authors, Scott Lynch: http://scott-lynch.livejournal.com/159686.html

 What you're really complaining about isn't the fact that my fiction violates some objective "reality," but rather that it impinges upon your sad, dull little conception of how the world works. I'm not beholden to the confirmation of your prejudices; to be perfectly frank, the prospect of confining the female characters in my story to placid, helpless secondary places in the narrative is so goddamn boring that I would rather not write at all. I'm not writing history, I'm writing speculative fiction.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a couple of years since I played the game, so my memory is not super sharp on plot details, but IMO, I didn't notice any egregious stereotypes.  And of the ones that were used, it felt like they were used as pretty obvious homages to Hong Kong films and the overall Hong Kong gangster/triad film genre.

Which isn't to say those films don't have issues with sexism or diversity, and that those issues didn't also carry over into the game.  Just pointing to them to provide context for the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even a Western idea of sex positivity, unless you count Japanese otaku culture promoting essentially a teenager's view of sex and sexual organs as positive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think he's just stressing people don't usually try to convert homosexuals in Japan.

Most people don't try to do it anywhere commonly, but it's troubling that the game has that subtext, and "it doesn't usually happen" isn't really an excuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 08:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just once, just once I'd love it if the person saying "that's just Japanese culture" actually lived in Japan for long enough to truly have a grasp of precisely what "Japanese culture" means.

Too often, "Japanese culture" is a shortcut word for "Japanese otaku culture" which most of the time is shorthand for "Japanese otaku culture for this specific media subtype".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> importantly:

 The doors are all opened by fingerprints, pretty cool haha

I mean once you go into many company's main entrance, it's not like there are regular security checkpoints.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reporting on a deleted Reddit comment about information not so much leaked as explicitly illegally obtained.

On one hand, yeah, newsworthy info should be publicized.  On the other, is this news worthy info?

Like I said, I got mixed feels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 22:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the same article I did?

 The doors are all opened by fingerprints, pretty cool haha. But I just followed some tattooed dude into the door after he unlocked it. He didnt even ask me any questions. 

"Following someone through a locked door" happens frequently, but it's not like they had their gates wide open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mixed feelings: Fan of game studio sneaks/trespasses into studio, eats their lunch, discovers information about unannounced game, is republished by Kotaku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 21:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely noticed this too.  I felt pretty gross doing it, but the most "efficient" way I've found to play the game is to have a single male i the living quarters with a bunch of females.  Fallout Shelter implements pregnancies, but not monogamist relationships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like trotting this one out whenever GamerGate tries to encourage advertiser email campaigns. 

It's like, c'mon y'all, if ethical publications actually did bow to advertiser pressure to change coverage (even if it is a change to something more favorable), that is precisely the breach of ethics that you are supposed to be against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure I see the problem with saying "the people I talked to have been mostly respectful".  It's not an pledge of support for what those people represent, or even a suggestion that everyone in that camp is of similar respectfulness.  

She also said: https://twitter.com/GWillowWilson/status/614811643998920704

 I disagree w/their politics+tactics, but if they want to have a respectful convo abt marriage equality, i'm all for it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Critical favorites are not always commercially successful.  Welcome to every consumer market on the planet, GamerGate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 10:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, my enjoyment of both Chuck and Firefly is significantly less bright and cheerful after getting more acquainted with Baldwin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 10:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously Host Europe is mistaken because don't they know that GamerGate self identified in a shoddy poll that they were left leaning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As with most things, the ethics concern is not in the action, but in the disclosure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right -- the material itself probably isn't that much cheaper than just using Codura (might even end up being a little costlier depending on sourcing).  Tho there's no arguing that Freitag charges a hefty markup due to brand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right -- sorry, that last part in my post was poorly worded.  I didn't mean to imply that every of a certain age or maturity is able to afford those things.  What I mean is that KiA's tone seemed to take pride in not owning an expensive packaing ("my backpack was $5 from goodwill!") while at the same time, mostly likely owning game consoles, games, and gaming computer parts that easily add up to more than $400. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, remember 2013's E3 badge?

http://cdn.destructoid.com//ul/255748-crown.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 07:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. The Freitag backpack (even at $400) will likely outlast and be used longer than a $400 graphics card, or a $500 console, or a $400 phone, or any number of disposable electronics that most people buy today.

(I think Freitag way overcharges due to their brand.  Their construction is superb, but the patterning and designs are a little staid and impractical)

The fact that so many people in that thread can't even comprehend spending $400 on something like a backpack (that's likely used regularly) speaks volumes to their age, maturity, and general understanding of the world.  I hope they never find out how much fancy watches cost, or actual fashion brand bags and clothing cost.  They might die from shock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 06:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people on NeoGAF are experiencing it too:

http://www.neogaf.com/forum/showpost.php?p=168214749 postcount=3585 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think TB is pretty open with regards to his complete and utter pandering to his perceived audience.  I mean, at one point, he specifically said "don't forget the hand that feeds you" in the same breath as something stupid about ethics.

The best thing I can say about John Bain is that he knows he's ultimately a sponsor and viewership mouthpiece, and seems to revel in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 01:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RGB Topres with a relatively low weight and cherry stems.  it's basically just them directly taking money out of my wallet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article makes a specific point to make exceptions for articles about Game of Thrones it considers to be "newsworthy".

I take this to mean that they won't be posting obvious promotional things like regular recaps, teaser hype posts, etc.  I think there's a fairly clear line between those posts which are primarily promotion (recaps, trailers, interviews) and those that are critiques. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Condolences in advance :(


(I did not like Powers the show all that much) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pilot MYU/Murex family of pens

http://stutler.cc/pens/murex/index.html

http://stutler.cc/pens/sales/images/m90.JPG

http://www.stutler.cc/pens/murex/images/four_diagonal.JPG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even compromise.  It's accepting that things you love can (and almost certainly are) imperfect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 11:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like Dresden, check out Luke Daniels' narration of Kevin Hearne's *Iron Druid* books.  I actually rank them equal to Dresden in terms of how much I enjoyed the voices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I take some glee in Alec Baldwin's cousin Adam Baldwin (/sarcasm) projects failing, I admit that I was _really_ hoping this would be a good game.

Because I typically love the games that Intelligent Systems put out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 04:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC, William Usher is the guy who loudly declaimed that Intel was back advertising on Gamastura *despite* both Intel and Gamasutra saying so.  He kept saying "NO ITS JUST RANDOM ADWORDS" and used some incredibly rudimentary (and incorrect) source code digging to justify his claim.

And then, of course, promptly forgot all about it once it came out that he was absolutely incorrect in his claims.

"ethics" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 05:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But one of the most legendary knights in the history of Westeros taken out by a couple of nobodies with masks and knives? Uh, ok.

TIL "couple" means 10+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TV ASOIAF is canon for TV, Book ASOIAF is canon for books.  It's that simple.

It's like comics.  There is the Marvel Cinematic Universe, there's the universe of some comic runs.  They are all "canon" in the sense that each is an accurate reflection of events that happen in that universe.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The calculus in the Barry fight is ultimately pretty simple:  10 guys vs 1 guy in an enclosed space where the 10 guys have daggers and the 1 guy has a sword  means the guy with the sword is probably dead, no matter how skilled.

The logistics of that encounter just means that the 10 can flank/surround/attack together without worry about each others weapons getting in the way each other.  Daggers, particularly, can be debilitating in close quarter fighting.  They are hard to see, quick enough to be hard to dodge, small enough to be hard to parry, and just in general, really fucking annoying when you have a number of them going at you from multiple angles.

This is also what happens when a group of 10 people _don't_ use standard tv/movie logic and attack one at a time.  

In fact, I give high props to Barryand his legendary prowessthat he managed to survive so long and kill so many given the power imbalance.

For all the magic and dragons and undead in Song of Ice and Fire, I've always felt that the violence and fighting and overall physicality of combat hew pretty close to the grimdark formula of _yeah, these characters are good, but they are still human_.

He _might_ have done better with armor, but historically, in enclosed fighting, daggers are also pretty adept at fighting open gaps and joints in armor.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really.  I've read all the books, and I've kept current with the show, and the biggest, most important point that you need to accept is that **the show is not the book**.

Accept that, and you can enjoy (or not enjoy!) each separately.  Because there are things about the books that infuriate me, and things about the show that infuriate me, and they are rarely about the same people or scenes.

Granted, if you're worried about book spoilers from the show (even in a form that's twisted because the show is not the book), then yes, you should probably stop watching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 19:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love hidden badasses who get underestimated or are unrecognized. Examples: Belgarath, Ninefingers in Red Country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 22:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people criticize GamerGate for having a 12-year old's take on "objectivity" as a concept and in the nuance of its application as a word.

This isn't even getting into the fact that for many GamerGators, "objective" really means "article agreeing with my world views". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing I actually appreciate the most about the Hugo controversy is that SF/Fantasy authors are *not afraid* of speaking their minds.  Many of the greatsand most of my favoriteshave spoken openly and honestly about what they think of the whole mess.

I don't always agree with that they say, but it just refreshing to see an actual responses by creators instead of the relative stonewalled silence we saw from the game industry at large with GamerGate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 12:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate hardcore vs casual camps in any field/hobby, because I can guarantee that however hardcore someone thinks they are, there's is someone else who is more hardcore.  

It's a pointless metric in most arguments, and an especially dumb one when used to talk about the "depth" of someone's love for an activity or discipline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 19:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of his early work has neat ideas, but in general I found him incredibly uneven.  Some good concepts and plotting, but generally mediocre writing. 

(This is without getting into how batshit crazy he is as a person -- and one that isn't afraid of using his megaphone to drive home his personal brand of insanity) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 09:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Marsters' rendition of Harry Dresden is *the* voice of Dresden for me.  Even when reading the prose, I hear his voice in my head.  I'd highly encourage all of the Dresden audio books.

Luke Daniels does a great job with Kevin Hearne's *Iron Druid* books.  His portrayal of Oberon is probably in my top 10 faves.

Neil Gaiman also narrates many of his own books: Neverwhere, Stardust, Ocean at the End of the Lane.  Having the author narrate a book is always a special treat for me.

BBC Radio 4 also does dramatizations of some greats.  They recently did one for Good Omens that was superb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 09:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donating to charities is the modern day version of indulgences. You-can't-say-what-I'm-doing-is-bad-because-look-I-donated-this-money-to-charity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, touche :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like some of the subsequent tweets have been deleted.  Next time, should archive.today the last tweets or storify them, since people can easily claim that screenshots can be doctored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 07:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from DC!  

Unfortunately, on that day, I'm going to be in NYC and then Delaware :(  Otherwise I'd go and report back on the crazy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tolkien is still the gold standard for me, here, in terms of sheer breadth of maps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Run your own high-end cloud gaming service on EC2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 07:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doris Egan's Gate of Ivory https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/884583.The_Gate_Of_Ivory

Guy Gavriel Kay's Lions of Al-Rassan.  https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/104101.The_Lions_of_Al_Rassan

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final section is great, but ugh, that feeling of having to wait years for the next one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding the Vlad Talotos novels.  Gritty and funny dialogue is Steve Brust's bread and butter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To continue what AllWrong74 said, I'd personally put _Armor_, _Starship Troopers_ and _Forever War_ as my top 3 favorite military sci-fi novels that also happen to be standalone.

(There was never a sequel for Forever War, There was never a sequel for Forever War, There was never a sequel for Forever War) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 19:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually found *two* copies of The Wizard  presumably because at some point I forgot I already owned it and bought another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there's a key bit of information missing: was Milo **invited** or was he **accepted**?

ie, did ESA/E3 reach out to Milo to tell him to attend, or did Milo apply for a press pass?

Because the former implicates ESA/E3 in some behavior that's kinda gross, but the latter is just evidence (that I've experienced first hand from my E3 media passes) of the relatively low bar of entry for E3 Media passes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started cleaning up some old books from storage since my parents are moving, and finding treasures I forgot I owned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by the statements he makes in the response posts that have been linked, I mean, its obvious that not all of his statements are uncolored truthor even remotely true in some cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worldcon *never* claimed that the Hugos represented all of fandom.  But then, breadth of representation and prestige are not strongly tied.   Some of the most prestigious awards in the world are selected and given by a relatively small number of judges in proportion to the size of the industry: Michelin stars, Academy awards, the Nobel Prize, etc.  Correia seems to believe that a prestigious award must necessarily be a "people's choice" award.  **That's false in nearly every single industry that gives awards.**

The Hugos are famous and carry prestige for one reason and one reason only: history.  They have been around a long time, counts among its voting membership some industry greats, and has, through the decades, mostly recognized the right people for their works (though maybe not at the most ideal time in some cases).

That Correia is incapableor more likely, unwillingto recognize this fact speaks volumes about the cogency of his position, and the integrity of his position.

At the end of the day, I cannot help but think this is yet another conservative trying to open yet another front in the great left/right schism in America.  (And in this specific case, I don't think Scalzi/et al are helping stem that schism, though Scalzi has certainly been less harmful to the Hugos than Correia) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be different if the founding SP members vigorously rejected the more rabid commentators, but I've never seen them do that.  At most it's lip service "they are not us" all the while giving the sly wink and nod to those people who just "want to stick it to SJWs".

That kind of behavior severely undermines the integrity of the cause.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The **real travesty** of Sad Puppies is that it has made George R.R. Martin spend at least several hours on these blog posts, thereby delaying Winds of Winter YET AGAIN.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be fair, it's obvious that writing lengthy rivers of prose runs in GRRM's blood, and not just for his novels :)

(Though I'm fairly certain that even if the post was 140 characters, GamerGators would read the first 10 and then make up the last 130) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 06:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you... miss the part where that statement was in quotes and is attributed to things that people shouldn't think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 19:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the joke was in bad taste in retrospect, and I can see how if you _didn't_ know that "lego dimensions" was already a rumor and wasn't some kind of embargoed confirmation, it looks pretty bad.  

it's a bad joke, mcwhertor turned it off

btw using my sekrit gaming industry connections, i figured out a possible new game and just bought http://bloodborne2.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 08:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hugos **matter**.  Not to everyone, perhaps.  But to the industry, as one of the most prestigious prizes awarded in sf/fantasy fandom? Oh yes.

Growing up, finding an unread sci fi/fantasy book with the "*Hugo winning*" or even "*Hugo nominated*" badge in the new arrivals section at the local library was like finding a treasure. Theres legacy to the history of the Hugos that lends its nominations and its winners weight.

What the Sad Puppies have donethis year especiallyis to tarnish that legacy. Through bloc voting for an agreed upon slate of books, theyve diminished the Hugos as a metric for judging quality science fiction and fantasy books as voted on by Sci Fi/Fantasy fandom.

That last part is important: **fandom**.

The greatest crime of the Sad Puppies voting contigent isnt to nominate authors that I think have despicable personal views on politics and other issues. The greatest crime of the Sad Puppies is weaponizing the culture war going on in the U.S. right now to sabotage what the Hugos have always been, and always should be: a reflectionsometimes something good, sometimes something disgracefulof the taste and judgement of science fiction and fantasy fandom.

Fandom. Not people only interested in seeing SJW tears. Not right-wing conservatives only interested in opposing progressives in yet another front of the great left/right schism in America. Not even those extreme progressives who blindly vote for diversity without regard to quality.

/u/randomthrowaway102 links to a great comment by GRRM about this that I think is extremely relevant to *why* the "many new voices" brought on my Sad Puppies is so damaging.  These new voices *are not* sf/fantasy fans.  Frequently, they don't even pretend to be.

Commenter:

I honestly don't understand why you're upset about increased participation in the Hugo Awards. Isn't inclusion, as represented by these many new voices, meant to be a liberal value?

GRRM:

 But is this inclusion?

 I want worldcon to grow and thrive, and have tried for many years to encourage new people to attend, volunteer, become part of it.
Are the Sad Puppies joining the worldcon community? I sure don't get that sense. Reading their posts, especially in the comments section, suggests that a good many of them (not all, I hope) want only the rockets... oh, and to discomfit and upset the people they call "SJWs." They talk about buying popcorn to enjoy the show, and savoring the taste of our tears.

 That doesn't sound like someone who wants to sit down and have a beer with me and argue about Robert A. Heinlein.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 06:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few other subs have a mod created and pinned weekend thread along the lines of "what have you been reading/playing" etc.  I think having that for /r/fantasy would be super. 

On the weekly thread for /r/games for example, I've found many games I wouldn't have otherwise played or heard of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodgamer.us, the GG affiliated gaming site, shuts down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 21:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/goodgamersus/status/585439383710498816

 We at goodgamers regret to inform you that we have, in fact, closed our doors. At this time, there wont be anything else from us.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used a Fictionary for Malazan, and it definitely helped with the experience.  Thanks for the service! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular reminder that if you are reading on the Kindle, The Fictionary can be invaluable for books that contain a ton of characters/names:

thefictionary.net </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are those green cables in the container behind the sofa or... are you making a gigantic salad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a mix between scifi and fantasy, but in practical terms, it's fantasy with overtones of sci fi. There's no "magic" in the world, only advanced technology believed to be magic.

It starts off pretty good, I enjoyed it.  I've read all but the latest.  It it felt like it wasn't going anywhere for awhile.  A lot of meandering plot lines, and loss of focus.  

I've heard the latest entry focuses more, however, and brings the series back to some semblance of momentum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard there's this great series called A Song of Ice and Fire that you should start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read the Chronicles of Amber by Zelazny?  It's not super intricate, but is a romping good time with plenty of intrigue to go around.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch the movie version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The fact that /u/MichaelJSullivan blew every penny of his new Del Ray contract in one huge Vegas weekend, filled with blackjack, peyote, and a drunken night of crocheting that left the Blue Man Group unconscious and yarn bombed from head to toe.

I dunno about you, but I assumed that's how the First Empire managed to fall into Rhune.

*rimshot* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correction: GRRM announces he's putting A Song of Ice and Fire on hold to focus on his new HBO series ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - *Bas-Lag* series
- *House, MD*
- *Dresden Files*
- *Lovecraftian horror*
- *Thieves world*

By *Max Gladstone*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will almost always do my actual reading on the Kindle, but then go back and buy hardback/paperback versions of the books I really enjoyed for "keeping".

There's still nothing quite like having a shelf full of books you love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now, I love the Hugos and everything it represents. My apprenticeship as a novelist has been a steady diet of Hugo-winning novels since I was just a baby bookworm. 

I fully admit I've let this year's Hugo noms get under my skinand I probably shouldn't let itbut an underlying reason, I think, is that I still *place value* on being "Hugo nominated".  I'm not a novelist, but I grew up reading Hugo and Nebula nominated and winning books, and I remember always feeling a great twinge of excitement whenever I saw an unread novel at my local library bearing a Hugo or Nebula blurb.

I *don't want* the Hugos to go away.  But I also don't want the focus being only on Hugo winners.  Being nominated for a Hugo should be a huge honor, and I think the slate voting this year (and last, to an extent) severely undermines what being nominated for a Hugo should mean.

(I mean, there's not a snowballs chance in Hell that Vox Day is going to win his categories, but it's still disconcerting that Vox Day is able to count himself among the list of Hugo nominees due to the Hugo vote process) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oberon fron *Iron Druid* books

Eshrahaddon from *Riyria*

Silk from *The Belgardiand* and *Mallorean* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edit: Further in, around 6 minutes, is he really claiming games press is "buddy buddy" and don't criticise each other? What? Does he not actually talk to different outlets?

Did TotalBiscuit just... sleep through the entire backlash from various members of games press at Polygon's initial documentary launch trailer?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Often talks about "remembering the hand that feeds" you in reference to his audience. As if the audience is always right and SHOULDN'T be criticised.

The best part is that "the hand that feeds" is actually not his audience, but *the advertisers* buying ads that run against views by his audience.

TotalBiscuit is literally saying "hey, don't forget about your advertisers when talking about video games" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But at the very least, you could read them. I don't generally like Tom Kratman's work. I hold him solely responsible for the mess that Ringo's Aldenata series has turned into. But I read Big Boys Don't Cry and I think it's actually probably one of the best novellas I read last year.

That's part of the dilemma, I think.  Some of the work on the Sad Puppies slate might actually be good, but the nature of the slate means that some *other* good works probably got knocked out of the running due to the voting bloc.

(Some think, for example, that Cixin Liu's *Three Body Problem* [a great novel that was honestly a great example of the sort of sci-fi I think many people of all views would enjoy] might have garnered a nomination if it wasn't overran by on-slate nominations for Sad Puppy approved works)

It makes it so that if I don't want to reward bloc voting via slate, the only real choice, imo, is "no award".  Because even if Kratman's work is good, the advent of the slate means that the novella's competition in that category is severely crippled.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Meanwhile none of this, at all, has anything to do with whether the book is worthy of being considered "The best scifi or fantasy written this year."

Sure -- and in cases like best novel, I'll still vote as normal, by reading the works in the nomination list.  (I've already read most of the best novel nominees anyway, except for the single MH entry)

But in cases like best novella and others where the evidence for an author or work being listed solely because of the slate is obvious?  

I mean, I've read some of John C Wright's work (The Hermetic Millenia), and while I don't think it's terrible (unlike his personal views), I highly, *highly* doubt that his writing ability has improved such in the past year that he landed 6 hugo nominations on his own merit.

In cases like that? Yeah, I'm comfortable voting "no award".  Not because I dislike their personal politics (I reserve that for my personal purchases), but because "no award" is the only choiec in some categories that *doesn't* reward slate voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I can see that.  But that also make it funnier because it feels like Gators always lead with that argument.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, I don't take "you might be part of the problem" to be a personal attack, in any real sense.

Now, if you followed that up with language that many of authors of the Sad Puppy slate reserve for LGBT people, then, maybe :)

(And I think a separate thread on artistic merit of creation vs objectionable traits of creator and the intricacies of support in cases like that when it comes to both awards and personal spending choices would be an interesting thread, assuming the comments don't get super awful) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If someone writes a good scifi novel, does it matter what their politics are? 

Insofar as saying whether or not the scifi novel was "good", no, it doesn't.  (I actually read the first couple Monster Hunter books and enjoyed them as brainless pulpy fun before stopping the series after I learned more about the author)

But as it relates to if I would want to purchase that work and read it, or recommend that author to friends?  Oh yes, definitely.  

(And in this specific case, I'd feel perfectly fine voting against works on the slate not because of their chosen ideological pedastal, but because they got there via voting bloc shenanigans)

(The Best Novel category does give me pause though, because I think most of the works on that list could feasibly get their on their own merit.  So I'd vote that category as normal by reading everything and voting accordingly)

 The root of all of this is the desire to maintain ideological purity or to make a fan voted award for the "best" scifi and fantasy of the year be representative of some political goal. It's just as contemptible when employed against people like Vox Day as it is when employed by them.

There's a difference here.  Vox Day and John C Wright *actively reject* certain opinions and ideologies as anathema to civilized behavior.  (eg, Wright's reaction to the end of Korra).  In most cases, the so called SJW tendencies ask that other viewpoints and authors simply be considered. 

The rejection of viewpoints that encourage active rejection is not, in itself, some kind of contemptible rejection.  Down that way lies madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?  I highly doubt Sad Puppies are against not liking something who is attempting to (legally) game the Hugo voting process. And if they are actually against that, then they have an interesting way of showing it.

If you mean judging a work on its own merits rather than my views of the author, sure.  You can read like that if you want.  In my personal consumption of media, I like to know that the person I'm supporting with my purchases is someone I'd feel good about supporting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a perfect world, the Hugo's are about the works, and not the author. The Sad Puppies voting bloc, however, invalidates that approach. As such, I feel perfectly fine in disregarding works represented on that slate when voting (I'm a supporting member), assuming the author/group/etc in question knowingly accepted being on the slate.

More importantly, I'm also talking about my personal reading choices, and in my personal reading choices, I can use whatever criteria I see fit.  And yes, how much I like the creator plays a role into my personal consumption choices (for all media, not just books). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a pretty great point.  Another example:  I devoured Heinlein during my middle school and early high school years.  Read nearly every book he put out. To my middle/high school brain, they felt free of politics.  Obviously, they weren't.  But they *seemed* that way to me back then because (1) I wasn't looking for it, (2) I wasn't aware of many of the politics that were running through his work, and (3) I also privately agreed with many of the things I *did* notice, and hence attributed to good writing/storytelling resonating with a reader what would've otherwise been politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 08:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I feel bad for Andromeda Expressways as well.  But they've also gone out and clarified their stance on the matter.

With the publicity that this year's Hugo awards have been getting (especially in the circles that Kloos and others run), I'd find it extremely suspicious for any Sad Puppy nominee to continuing being "surprised" at being included, and to use "I wasn't aware" as an excuse to not make a statement one way or the other on the slate.

I'm willing to admit that the Sad Puppy slate put forth some works that possibly deserve a nominationbut at the same time, being willing (or at least, expressly not against) to be used by the slate as a hammer to get nominations is a character flaw that I'm not sure I can support.

But this is why I'm seeking clarification.  I'm more than willing to give authors/publications/editors/etc on the Sad Puppy slate the benefit of the doubt wrt their involvement, assuming they state as much, like Andromeda Expressways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 07:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If this continues, I will be forced to look at other streaming options

I love that this is always the very first threat out of any GG supporter's mouth.  Ah, if only.  If only they'd actually follow through with the constant threats to JUST GO AWAY. 

"If Polygon continues to publish this kind of stuff, I am going to stop reading"

"Why are you still here?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 07:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends what you're using. Self-hosting a wordpress blog?  It's possible to overload your site by posting comments, but 20 in 10 minutes probably won't do it.

Even 200 comments in an hour likely won't overload your blog.

That said, if you're worried about comment overloading, using something like Disqus should help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 07:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audiobooks have honestly been a lifesaver to me.  I probably average about ~1.5 hour commute every work day, and given that time, I can usually finish 2-3 audiobooks a month.  (I've recently just caught up on Kevin Hearne's quite excellent Iron Druid books narrated with amazing performances by Luke Daniels)

Otherwise, I do most of my reading on the Kindle.  For a long, *long* time, I was a give-me-paper-or-give-me-death kind of guy, but over the past several years I've changed my mind.  I still buy hardback and paperback versions of my favorites "to keep", but otherwise, I've shifted all of my reading to the Kindle.  It's just too convenientand light weight!to use.

(I've also recently started listening to *Welcome to Nightvale* while at the gym, and its episodes are actually perfect little morsels for 30 minutes on the treadmill) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 07:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you thinking of John Ringo's Council Wars books perhaps?

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Council_Wars

(Fair warning if so: I've tried reading the first few, and while the premise is interesting, the writing and themes are... not particularly to my tastes.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supposedly, every nomination supported by the Sad Puppies group gave explicit permission to be used on that platform. Is this true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 06:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking because if so, my opinions of people like Jim Butcher are going to change drastically (there's a difference between being used by a platform because of your views, and explicitly agreeing to join a platform that included the likes of Vox Day).

At least one party claims to have given no explicit permission: http://www.sfsignal.com/archives/2015/04/finalists-2015-hugo-award-with-free-fiction-links/#comment-147655, so it's possible that there are others who, likewise, were nominated by the sad puppies without their knowledge.

Does anyone have any links or confirmation/denials from the various Sad Puppy nominees with regards to their complicit approval? 

EDIT:

Other authors that I've enjoyed reading that I would... have issues continuing to read if they willingly accepted being on the Sad Puppies slate (https://bradrtorgersen.wordpress.com/2015/02/01/sad-puppies-3-the-2015-hugo-slate/):

- Marko Kloos
- Mike Resnick
- Kevin J Anderson
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indiana amends 'religious freedom' law, Gen Con responds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Breitbart either, but the title is a little misleading.  Brietbart didn't want the game censored (insofar as they didn't explicitly ask the game be censored).

This is like Polygon writing about Hatred and saying "look at this gross shit".  

We rightly defended Polygon for being able to write about Hatred without being accused of wanting censorship, and at least from what I'm gathering from the article, Breitbart is in a similar situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 10:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A good, if janky, strategy is to pause the game, (spacebar) issue commands to all of your characters, unpause until they are done, pause and repeat. I do this at important and large encounters: easy enemies I usually hack through without using many spells and abilities.

That's not janky, that's the way the game is meant to be played!  Hence all the various autopause options, etc.  You're supposed to give some orders, unpause and watch the action, and then repause and evaluate for new orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, Richard Lewis is the same shitty "journalist" who responded like this when someone called him out for using an uncredited photo in one of his pieces:

https://twitter.com/dz/status/390553131735875585

http://i.imgur.com/pdA30ty.jpg

"Faggot melodrama"

Classy guy, him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 06:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there anyway we can put a stop this?

If this subreddit doesn't want those threads, people on this subreddit will stop upvoting it and that thread won't hit the front page.  

It's pretty simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think it's great that you purchase materials that you've already pirated. If everyone paid for all the content they pirated (edit: replaced "purchased"), then I might think a bit differently about piracy, but from my anecdotal knowledge, that's not happening.

Even if every pirate paid for their content afterwards, it's still unethical.  If I steal something from a store, and then go back and back later, that doesn't invalidate the original act of theft.

I have nothing against piracy: I think it's unethical, but whatever.  People do unethical things every day.  What I find most amusing is the mental gymnastic that frequent piraters go through to rationalize and justify their choice as not unethical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And i am saying that people who wanna make money out of art should rather try to find a way where the risk is reduced instead of stating what you just did.

Things I'm going to guess you don't do:

1. Go to restaurants and ask for a sample of their entree before ordering.

2. Go to concerts, and ask to sit in for 15 minutes.

 Don't jugde people who pirate

Why not?  Pirating normally-paid content is wrong.  End of story.  All justifications are people who are unwilling to accept that they are engaging in an unethical act.  Just face it: you are doing something the creator of the content you enjoy finds immoral.  Nothing is going to happen to you if you admit it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I want this thing but I can't afford it, what are my options?"

These are options an ethical person would evaluate:

1. Decide to not get the thing.

2. Save up money and get the thing.

3. Investigate avenues of making more money, and when you have the money, get the thing.

And guess what?  This actually works for everything!  Cars, houses, electronics, jewelry, books, that fancy restaurant down the street.

There's also a 4th option: admit that it's stealing, accept that it's an unethical action, stop trying to justify it, and get on with your life.  You're *never* going to get approval from a content creator for stealing their content.  Exasperated acceptance that it's unavoidable from some, maybe, but not approval.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you also go to restaurants and ask for a sample of their entrees before agreeing to order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the "let's talk to our lawyers about this" stage should've happened before the original letter about SB 101, where they said it "will factor into our decision-making on hosting the convention in the state of Indiana in future years".

Unless "future years" meant "after 2020" all along, and they specifically neglected to mention it to gain some positive PR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is.. disheartening, I guess.  It basically makes it look to me that GenCon was bluffing, had the bluff called, and now is backpedaling into some extremely warm language about the city of Indianapolis:

 We believe GenCon attendees will receive the same great service and hospitality in 2015, but an even warmer response from the city.

This looks especially spineless in the face of what Salesforce did when they pulled all travel.  

Granted, GenCon says they have a contract with Indianapolis through 2020, _but they knew this when they wrote the original letter about SB101_.  So when they said they were going to reconsider holding GenCon in Indianapolis, did they mean "reconsider in 5 years" all along?  If so, that's very disappointing and facetious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GenCon decides to stay in Indianapolis through 2020 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 14:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salesforce cancels all travel to Indiana, wont subject customers or employees to discrimination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 20:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To quote TotalBiscuit:

 It's pseudo-intellectual at its worst.

That basically summarizes the essence of most of his "rants" and "screeds" and "deep thoughts".

https://twitter.com/totalbiscuit/status/578521366162464768

 I like how all these pseudo-intellectual hitpieces also always attack an audience of 2 million. The sheer arrogance of that, mindboggling.

I like that all of his pseudo-intellectual pieces always rely on having an audience of 2 million to imply authority.  The sheer arrogance of that, mindboggling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 05:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with "neutrality" is that it implies that there are two sides. There aren't.  There's GamerGate, and everyone else.  

A typical GamerGate "neutral" is someone who shares many beliefs with GG, but is unwilling to publicly proclaim support for GG.  You see this commonly in comment threads and seal lions the world over.  The "I don't know much about GG, *BUT* I think regurgitates previously refuted GamerGate talking points".

There's no such thing as a "real neutral".  The closest thing is an uninvolved person who not only has no knowledge of GG, but also doesn't really care about video games.  In this case, they are not so much neutral as completely tertiary to the controversy.  

(Notably, they also won't be commenting on GG-related threads.)

And then there are the "neutrals", people who just want the status quo.  Sometimes, this is couched as a positive: "Why can't we just go back to how it was like before GamerGate?"  Sometimes, this is couched as a plea for peace: "If everyone would just calm down, GamerGate would already be over."  

The common thread of "neutrality", as I've seen it, is that the status quo is seen as a positive balance.  

But as well all know, the status quo is anything but a positive environment for diversity.  Anita got harassed plenty before GamerGate.  Females in gaming faced challenges way before GamerGate.  The general tone of diversity in gaming has been a rising tide of criticism for years and years.  

GamerGate did not cause these things.  **In fact, seen another way, many GamerGate supporters are merely an extreme, militant, radical idealization of the classical "neutral"**:   They want a return to a status quo as well, but engage in abhorrent tactics and rhetoric in that pursuit.  GamerGates have an internalized utopian view of gaminga perverted concept of what "real gaming" or "pure gaming" or, ultimately, the status quo of gaming should be and, in their minds, has been.  

The self-proclaimed "neutral", meanwhile, also wants a status quo (that is perhaps more grounded in reality), but won't put any effort towards that goal beyond stating "wasn't it great back then?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 05:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard GamerGate thinking that is also, sadly, all too similar to the kind of dumb YOU-TRAITOROUS-FLIPFLOPPER sentiment that happens in U.S. politics.

There's this super strange idea that many subscribe to that (1) companies/publications are unified entities in organization as well as thought, and (2) a single person should be crucified for changing their mind or holding two different opinions at two different points of time.

It's baffling, and frankly, a shitty way to expect someone to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 15:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really horror in my book, but yeah, it's definitely weird.

And... what's wrong with "speculative fiction"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 08:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China Mieville and his Bas-Lag books fit right up your criteria:

https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/68494.Perdido_Street_Station

Perdido Street Station is also, incidentally, probably in my top 20 favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mdo, who comments on the thread, is github staff.  apparently what they should do about the repo is under conversation internally there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given how many of Final Fantasy's female characters to date _haven't_ been like FFXV Cid, it just feels super strange to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The changing looks of Final Fantasy's Cid: fashion experts weigh in  lol at the reactions to FFXV Cid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://github.com/letsgetrandy/DICSS/pull/16#issuecomment-84146824

 The beginnings of an Orwellian society in the making and it scares 
me. You might not see what you are doing to be hostile, that's besides the point though. There are many people who DO find this behavior to be frighteningly similar to behavior straight out of 1984.

"Hey, maybe we can stop with the dumb jokes that a lot of people find offensive"

"OMG THIS IS LITERALLY 1984" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't strictly related to gaming.

But laughing because **of course** there's a GamerGater in the comments about making women and others feel more welcome by not engaging in stupid over the top dick jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gators in the wild: It's really about ethics in Github Pull Requests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethics is an American concept, I dunno why TotalBiscuit cares so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 07:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Seriously, the motion blur is [fucked up](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S2-yS4_dr1c)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just starting playing Final Fantasy Type-0 and took a few screenshots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 07:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't understand how Danny could turn on his own audience like that.  I'll remember, and I know they will too." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 09:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that they are convenienatly ignoring that Gamespot, one of the top 3 gaming publications in the world, gave it an overwhelmingly positive score of 4/10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, at least it's better than Tobal No. 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [media] For me, the best feeling in Destiny is when you land a knife throw in Crucible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CcVB_ufx8_k

Last Iron Banner rotation, I feel like I finally upped my knife game and general golden gun game.  It was the first long stretch of PvP where I exclusively used Gunslinger over Bladedancer, and it was great.

I run with the two knifes + burning damage perks.  

(Also, Hawkmoon.  Praise to Hawkmoon.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this in Nighfalls and Weekly Strikes, but in Roc, I just say fuck it and go ham.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 18:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean James Marsters (Harry Dresden) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 19:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  our first conversation consisted mainly of some 'hardcore' video game dickwaving where he kept trying to hold up his 'obscure' taste and put down my taste, but whatever, I can handle a bit of hazing

You call that hazing, I call that someone who is unable to stop being an asshole even to someone he just met. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 16:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world lost one if its very best today.  I have every single Pratchett book on shelf at home, and re-read them regularly.

He was one of the rare ones that transcended genre.

RIP, Terry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 15:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agents of Academia has a nice ring to it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haters gonna hate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 05:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 22:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Majestouch 1 was, but the Majestouch2 is easily available from Amazon in the US: http://www.amazon.com/Filco-Majestouch-2-Switch-FKBN104MRL-EB2/dp/B007VAFWN2
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
