<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until they hit the cable networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And they're not all rednecks and they're not all conservatives.

Well, no, because technically, Tallahassee is in the panhandle (although actually more in the Big Bend), and it is a huge dot of blue, as are all the areas in the state with major colleges and universities. I was talking more about everything west of the Big Bend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes feel like I'm in the middle of the UFSA (United Fascist States of America) instead of the USA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, Rick Perry wants to shut down the EPA. This is going to be an ongoing battle, with them picking it apart piece by piece. I'm sure the EPA scientists have been backing up this data from day 1 of Trump's win, because they aren't stupid. Even if it comes back up as a paid site, that's better than losing it all. 

What worries me is losing NOAA. Living in FL, that is completely vital to our survival during hurricane season. The EPA is pretty popular down here too, since we are one of the most environmentally sensitive states, so we're in the fight for the long term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why I didn't move to Pensacola. I wanted the beach, but I didn't want the religious freaks trying to convert me all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, we're talking about Sarah Palin here, not a normal woman. She's a female Trump. She's going to do whatever is best for her, and all other women be damned. She just gives lip service to caring about them...or anybody, for that matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire South of dominated by Democrats until 1964, and even after that, it took a long time for the conservatives to take over. My home state of SC still occasionally elects a Democrat as governor, but with a Republican legislature, they don't get more than one term of getting nothing done before they are replaced. Yes, the Tea Party changed things, but even the Republicans are getting sick of them, so their 15 minutes is about over, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it got that name because Florida was giving away land to homestetaders after the Civil War and a lot of Alabamans who had pretty much lost everything took them up on it. Hence, FloriBama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ETA: Really? FloriBama, Redneck Riviera -- never heard either of those? Strange. Not entirely (not many places are 100%), but pretty damned redneck conservative. If I move 10 miles outside my little dot of blue, the difference is night and day. 

Of course, I'm not talking about the snowbirds, who have their own little enclaves. I'm talking about the natives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That also sounds like ever Christian troll I've ever known. I love to play with them by knowing the Bible better than they do, calling them out when they misquote, take things out of context or when I can point out a contradictory passage in their precious book. I love to very innocently say something like "Would you care to explain who/where/what/when --insert absurdity here-- when the bible says --insert verse here--? Perhaps you should actually READ your bible instead of just spouting off what your preacher says." They never reply.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying hateful things and then claiming "it was a joke" is one of the first signs of a sadist mentality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please -- I love Keebler. Do not put those names in the same sentence. Poor little elves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FL panhandle is called FloriBama, and trust me, it's hick country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine that not having a sense of humor would be infinitely better than not having any morals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they'll just clean house and become a REAL news network. I now, pipe dreams and fantasies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of when I briefly worked at WalMart for extra money one Christmas. There was this one cashier -- older guy -- who was a real racist. He evidently thought because I was a southern woman, I was racist too. He started saying the most horrendous things to me one day standing right out in front of our registers about our gay supervisor. I reported him. They fired me, not him. Never even called him in for a "talk."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  one of these allegations should be enough to get you fired.

If that were true, Trump would not be President. That audio tape would have killed his presidency for once and for all. It just goes to show how low a country can sink on the morals chart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Failing newspaper. Unfair coverage. Very unfair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or even be in a room alone with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far, I've seen some pretty fucked up families on that side of the aisle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Embrace the rainbow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all shades of brown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certifiable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.K. That makes sense. Once the brain of an organization rots, the rest if right behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought they rotted from the inside out, and I'm a horticulturist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking it's trickle down penisonomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never read about this, but in some states, pointing a firearm at a person, whether it is loaded or not, is a crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palin won't come out because once Faux News goes down and has their big shakeup, she wants to go back to them. THEN she will privately meet with the new leaders and say "I kept my mouth shut when all that shit happened. I want my job back." It was well known that Ailes didn't like her, but never known why. It's not like he doesn't have a  dozen less-than-intelligent women in that network, so that couldn't have been it. Maybe she told him to stick his raw red meat into a grinder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then there is Megan Kelly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could handle that! Getting rid of Faux News would be the best thing since canned peaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I doubt they will learn anything from it, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this news? We all know he doesn't believe in climate change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she sue them? I would have. Seems like wrongful arrest and imprisonment is worth a lot more than $30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What scares me about that is that it will eventually go to the Supreme Court and get voted into law, so there will be no recourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's an INS problem, and INS doesn't have the resources to deal with all of this. It's not just techies, either. There are thousands of undocumented Caribbeans, especially Jamaicans, living in S. Florida. I've been trying to get INS to kick one of them out for years, to no avail. They've had him up on tax evasion several times for not paying his business taxes, and he's running a chop shop out of another town. The local LE says they don't have the resources to chase down every single one of these people. I can understand that, so I don't know what Trump thinks he's going to do about it. 

There are supposedly about 10,000+ Canadians living and working here on expired work visas too, and God only knows how many Europeans. People with white skin can get away with it much easier than brown and black people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember it too, and it was insane! No, we have no such fighters for truth in this administration. They will all protect him. I believe he and the Russians have something on every one of them, and he only appointed people they could control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of this the other day, and how much it is like the coverup with Nixon. Much worse than Watergate, though. We need a "Deep Throat." There has to be someone who is willing to try to save the country. I'm wondering who Trump's John Dean is going to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read that business owners are complaining that people cannot get to their stores because of the exclusion area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in a town in SW FL where there was a large community of Ukranians. One would get a work visa and the others would come over and work under the table as housekeepers, yard crews, whatever they could get that paid cash. Some set up illegal roadside produce stands, and some just sold drugs. It happens all over the country. People who want money are not going to let a few little laws stop them. 

They also would give custody of one or more of their children to a legal relative, so they could get benefits for them. If you think the Indians are not doing the same, you are naive. I'm not saying all of them, but I know of a few who are working under the table at convenience store/gas stations and hotels owned by relatives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe they shut down one lane of it in the block where Trump tower is, didn't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have definitely outlived their usefulness, and the way McCain flip-flops lately, I think he may have dementia too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HA! No, I take too many meds. Whoever ate me would likely die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a number of years that they cannot, but it's not indefinite, and any children they have here are eligible for assistance from birth. 

ETA: Also, their children are eligible for education and in some states Medicaid. Not sure about free lunches and breakfasts at school, but maybe if they are born here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of when police departments were confiscating the property and money of alleged drug dealers and refusing to give it back when they were exonerated. I remember the feds in TX once confiscated a man's airplane   $10,000, and it cost him thousands of dollars after he was exonerated trying to get it back, and thousands more to undo the damage they had done to his plane when he did get it back. Took him years to get his money back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about Manhattan. I just remember reading that people were complaining about being re-routed because they couldn't walk or drive in front of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's o.k. I don't use those poisonous little popcorn bags, and I only use organic butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, and my son is in tech, so it worries me that one day he will be replaced by one. There is a very strict rule at MS that if you discuss salary with any other worker, you can be fired and people have been blackballed for it. Don't know about other H1B companies, but I'm thinking it's probably true of all of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. I read about it many years ago when the service workers union was trying to get into WalMart. It was on their website. It may not be true anymore, but it was then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll probably call in the SS and his generals and lock himself down in the oval office. We'll have to smoke bomb him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, you can walk right up to the gates of Buckingham Palace and even mess with the guards to try to get them to move. True royalty is not afraid of anything. Kings of England regularly rode into battle, and it's a requirement that the heir apparent serve in the armed forces. We need to make military service a requirement for our Presidential candidates so they wouldn't be going around trying to bomb the shit out of people every time their daughter cries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the street in front of Trump Tower has also been closed since he took office, causing even more of a traffic jam than ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he had more legitimate death threats than any other President in history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad but true, but it had everything to do with his race, and no one will ever convince me differently. I just wonder what he could have accomplished is the lazy-ass dems had actually gone out and voted in 2010. It makes me so sad to think of all that lost opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that makes slightly more sense, but not much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make America Greasy Again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True fake news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Obamacare in danger of appeal, he had to do something to help the opiate addiction problem. I hope it works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually heartbreaking that we are in a country that is still so mired in racism that this could happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait -- this happened in San Francisco? Are you fucking kidding me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer is very amusing, but I'm getting fat from all the buttered popcorn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when is the UN going to charge Trump with war crimes, or at least with violating the charter? That is grounds for impeachment right there. 

In the immortal words of Toby Keith (Yes, I know he's a Republican, but he writes damned good songs): 

I know somewhere amid all this distraction is a little less talk and a lot more action...
Let's get on down to the main attraction with a little less talk and a lot more action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just tech, it's everything. Trump has visas for his maids, etc. at Mar-a-Lago. These visa workers can get special visas to bring their families over, then they either take people's jobs or get on assistance and cost us more money. 

I'm just sick to death of talking to people I cannot understand in customer service or tech support. After holding for 20 minutes for CS one day, I literally could not understand a word this Indian girl was saying, and she spoke such poor English that she couldn't understand what I needed, just read from a script. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  EB1/O1

Exactly. And as soon as a qualified American is available for the job, these companies MUST hire them and the foreign worker's visa is not renewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they are already cutting Pell grants and making loans more expensive in the new budget, so how do they expect us to do this? It would be nice if the tech industry could fit the bill for a few scholarships instead of shipping in people from overseas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it didn't cost so damned much to go to college, we'd have all the tech workers we need. I honestly think we do have enough. Tech companies just don't want to pay what they're worth. It's a disgrace to our country that we can't make a pointed effort to train more tech workers like we did when we gave free degrees in nuclear engineering back when the nuclear energy industry first started. 

We have so many brilliant kids that will never have a chance to get a good education. If they did, we wouldn't need workers from anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, dem voters who didn't vote for whatever reason in the primary will show up in force for the runoff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because voters are fickle, but I don't think it will work. They are expecting the GOP to pull some shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but if we want to get millenials to the polls, Ossoff is the best choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidently. They did that to make dems not vote, because they should think he is a horrible candidate. We can't let voters fall for this bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For example those Indian workers you're disparaging above look for opportunities abroad because there aren't enough back home and because India has no welfare system for the jobless.

Yes, but only the higher-class of Indians is allowed to go to college, so they are the first in line for good jobs there. Their social system is much different than ours, and even though they say there is no more caste system, there is an "unofficial" one. The poorest people in India do not get to go to college, or even to school sometimes. Only those who can afford it get to go, so those techies are not poor kids we need to help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Los Angeles, there is a food stamp office just for WalMart workers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, for awhile, but Trump is destroying most of it now. The GOP wants nothing more than to destroy everything Obama accomplished and wipe him from history. It's so terribly sad that they are that hate filled, and yes, racist. They have never done this to any other President, not even Clinton, so don't tell me it has nothing to do with race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine a Presidential campaign is not the most exhausting thing, even for a healthy, young person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't we do that with Obama, and then the old farts in Congress sabotaged him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a type of dementia that explains a lot of his behavior.

http://memory.ucsf.edu/ftd/overview/ftd/symptoms/single </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if you have hardening of the arteries from too much McDonald's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. That's how I saw it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother told my mother that my father was a bad man and she should leave him. She thought he was her husband (same name), who I hear abused her (he died when I was 3). My father was the gentlest man you'd ever hope to meet and never raised his hand in anger to anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which explains why he repeats the last thing he heard someone say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not lying. They honestly believe what they are saying is true. My friend's grandma was sitting outside when the new preacher came to visit. She told the preacher (who knew none of them from Adam) that her son (coincidentally also named Donald) was a thief, that all his tools in the garage were stolen and all the clothes on the line were stolen, and that he had stolen all her jewelry and sold it. When they explained to the preacher that she had Alzheimer's and showed him all her jewelry safely tucked away in a safe so she wouldn't lose it or give it away, they all had a good laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm telling you, the man is going senile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now it seems like they are just talking to hear themselves talk, and to convince themselves that they didn't make a mistake. It's pretty sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demand was my one big mistake, and I never made another one. I write for several different sites, have private clients and also have my own blogs I make money from (but not much -- yet). Am now seeing the content mill business going a little whacko, so I'm trying to move more into other revenue streams like ebooks, content marketing (outsourcing) and affiliate marketing. 

Freelancing doesn't have to be feast or famine if you set it up right. I have friends who make six figures a year freelancing, and not one of them only does one thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As sad as I am? I think not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to argue with you over this. If you live in New Orleans, by all means, use "prolly," but if you don't, even urban dictionary thinks you are "really lazy..."

http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Prolly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's just that no self-respecting attorney will work for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my answer to the last person who said this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but some are made up to replace real words, because stupid people are too lazy to say the real words or type the real words. "Prolly" is one of those. I hate them, and I will always call them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, well when you learn to spell and speak something other than ESL, I might consider registering. If you aren't professional enough to get a native English writer to do your site for you, you aren't professional enough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. I used to put pill bottles full of skittles in my medicine cabinet, just to piss off people trying to steal drugs. Thieves never look at the dates on bottles, and I had a few opoid bottles from when I broke my leg and had pins in it for awhile. 

My friend's dad had a frigging loud-ass alarm on his medicine cabinet. Scared a shitload of his daughter's teenage friends nearly to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he's undone almost everything Obama did, which was the GOP's agenda all along. They want to wipe Obama off the electoral map, as if he never existed. 

Trump has done a lot of damage in less than 100 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Agreed. ~~Prolly~~ Probably Russians /s

FTFY - sorry, pet peeve is made-up words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a long way to go to get to $4,000 a month. Most of the better mills are not accepting applications right now. Yes, there are people making good money on Textbroker, but most of them have specialized degrees or have been there for years and have many private clients they write for. I've been there 5 years, and have never had a private client. I don't work there much, because I have better options now, but it's not a place to get rich quick, by any means. 

Do you know how to write in AP style? If not, learn it quickly, because all the mills use it, and some are very strict about it. Textbroker has a comma fetish, and they will demote you over comma issues.

In short, freelance writing is not a "I don't want to work a regular job, so I'm going to freelance" income. Most people started out part-time and worked thier way up before they could quit their jobs. Not trying to be mean, just telling you the absolute God's honest truth. I see so many people in here who have bought the hype that freelance writing is a gold mine, but unless you have some sort of specialized degree like law or tech or finance, or you have experience writing in those verticals, you aren't going to make a full-tme salary up front without working 60 hour weeks.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are required to have diploma of US, Australian, Great Britain or Canadian univerity and have excellent English knowledge. Yes, that's all. 

FTFY below - BTW, I don't have a college degree. 

You are required to have A diploma from a  U.S., Australian, or British university, with excellent knowledge of English. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very interested in working for a company that has misspellings and grammatical errors in its FAQs. Plus, why are you requiring a university degree? That doesn't guarantee good work. I know plenty of freelance writers without degrees who do excellent work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a man who owns a smal motel. He says he hires illegals as maids and kitchen help because they work harder for the money. He pays them minimum wage, no benefits, and he gets twice as much work out of them than the Americans he's hired. He says he gets more complaints about American workers and also they are constantly complaining about low pay and are not appreciative of having a job in a town where unemployment hovers around 7%. He said they usually last about 3 months, then they quit and go back on welfare.  He has latino workers who have been there for years and are very much appreciative to have a job. 

Americans are spoiled. Mexico has no social welfare system. You work or you starve, so they are appreciative of any work they can get. Many lower class Americans have figured out how to play the system and make more on welfare than by working minimum wage. Honestly, I lived in a low-income neighborhood for a year during hard times, and I was told every day how to play the system, get onto disability, get free this and that. It's insane! They know every charity organization or goverment program by heart. One woman there had a 3/2 house free, was on disability so she had Medicaid for her and her kids, food stamps, got free clothes from charities and once a month, went to the food bank and got more free food. She got a free cell phone, free bus tickets, and all sorts of other free stuff. We sat down one day and figured out with all she was getting, she was making the equivalent of $40,000 a year when you added in their cash value + the FICA and income tax she would have to pay.

Now tell me why someone would want to work for minimum wage again? Minimum wage wouldn't pay her day care so she could work, and BTW, she was white as the driven snow, not a person of color, so please make no assumptions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could afford to live in Hawaii, that's where I'd be. Unfortunately, I can't. If you can afford it, go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.K., I was not aware of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously not, since he says he's been with his now husband for 40 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
