<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8479</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 12:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

https://soundcloud.com/wtf-united/different-times/s-64QMu (private link)

I made this as a part of an EP. Is it missing something? The track is still unmastered, since the EP is still to be completed. I am also considering sending demo tracks to labels. Do you honestly think my production quality is good enough?
Thanks for your feedback!

[Feedback 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/4td9wf/feedback_thread_july_18/d5gntp6)

[Feedback 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/edmproduction/comments/4td9wf/feedback_thread_july_18/d5gnx6i) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 12:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always recommend [Variens tutorial](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LRTrRa-cpyw). It even has a TLDW version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I thought the "International Christian Fellowship" was more popular. Seems to be more of a european thing though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 15:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys for your advice. There doesn't seem to be a Child Protection Agency near me, but I'm definitely going to report the case to the police tomorrow morning. Hopefully they will take it seriously and try and find that father to make sure those kids are alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friends family took me to church today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 10:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a friend of mine is in one of those free-evangelical, "International Christian Fellowship"-churches. His family is very nice and admirable. They knew I was an atheist and were "okay" with it, however they offered me to attend their service today and as I am very interested in other world views (I was raised catholic and I have heard of their church to be very "progressive") I agreed to go with them.

This visit made me aware of how religion is keeping people back from being reasonable people. It was so frustrating! There was a part during the worship where the pastor asked the attendants to share their encounters with god and jesus and there was this woman in her mid-30's who had a brother with a bipolar disorder. Apparently in his worst moments he tended to abuse his kids. So this woman told about that and how she was considering calling the cops on him, or at least warning his neighbors so that if they hear something they could step between. She said she was praying to the lord for help, so she would make the right desicion.

What eventually came about was: She realised that god is watching us all and he will watch her brother and his kids and he will lead them. Interfering in gods plan would mean she doesn't trust in god. So she did nothing. She did literally nothing and was totally happy about her brother hitting his kids "because god has his plans". In disbelieve I looked at my friend and his father (who I usually admired for his reasonable and rational views/behaviour) and they both were fucking cheering to the story along with everyone in the building. I can't believe that in a highly developed society (I'm from Switzerland btw) there are people who are okay with a father hitting his kids, just because of a "god knows what he does" label on it.

I wish I had done anything, but I honestly am not the type of guy who leans up against a full room of people and I don't think it would have changed a single bit, so I just went home to write this post to process my last experience with christianity. It definitely opened my eyes in some way. Even an intelligent and usually rational thinking person will do the dumbest things if they think it's "gods plan" and I will never trust them in anything like I was to.

**TLDR:** Woman does nothing about her mental instable brother abusing his kids because she thinks "god will fix it". Church attendants are okay with it. I realize that religion is danger, even in first world countries and I'm not to trust religious people anymore.


**edit:** words   formating

**edit II:** turns out the "International Christian Fellowship" is only a thing in europe, so [here's](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/International_Christian_Fellowship) the wikipedia to look it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 14:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Gang Beasts everyone thinks their experience is the funniest while actually it is just normal gameplay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 10:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the vs in this title in brackets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caught myself being weird today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caught myself being weird today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
