<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go ahead, inform me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the thought of destroying our life-giving climate brings you great joy?

are you some kind of retarded Satanic nihilist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> any war is a good war for these people

I don't think it really matters. Besides, who are you going to sell all of these old-school war items to if there's no war going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> give me a break with this crap

He's not a wildcard. He surrounded himself with longtime Washington insiders, corrupt billionaires, creationists and religious lunatics, and most damning of all people who are enthusiastically going to destroy our life-giving climate.

it's the same old same old right-wing crap that's always been going on. Mike pence is the real president anyway. Donald Trump is just a figurehead who enjoys making inflammatory tweets. Nothing more nothing less </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOP thought process

"97% of climate scientists are part of a grand conspiracy and hate America Besides climate change is too expensive to fix.

Hey! Let's spend $6 trillion on two different wars that do nothing but spread death destruction heartache misery and chaos around the world!"

And I hate the Democratic Party for laying there like a worthless pathetic bitch and letting it all happen

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you joking? Do you not understand?

The endgame is eternal unending warfare which feeds an absolutely enormous military-industrial complex beast. That's the endgame and nobody will talk about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course

The military-industrial complex NEEDS an enemy. It's absolutely critical.

It was communism then the wall fell and it was Saddam Hussein then it was Al Qaeda that it was Saddam Hussein again and then it was ISIS 

You can't justify spending $6 trillion on wars in Afghanistan and Iraq without having an enemy

My annoyance is with people here making out like Hillary Clinton somehow is the grand manipulator of all this shit. These things happen regardless of whether there are Democrats or Republicans in the White House. Doesn't matter.

The military-industrial complex controls the foreign-policy of the US. Completely and totally controls it. The Secretary of State and even the president do what they are told.

and then we wonder why we don't have enough money for healthcare. yeah, it is a real mystery

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?

ISIS didn't exist when that report was published? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James "2 yards per carry" Starks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is a "punt"?

totally confused

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call this the "mill about" defense

Basically the entire secondary just kind of roams around the field milling about in the general vicinity of play

every once in a while they accidentally tackle Somebody after like a 35 yard gain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the real tragedy of this season is that the offense is gearing up into playoff form just as the defense fell off a cliff like never before seen in history of mankind

Seriously though, Aaron Rodgers is looking great right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I firmly believe this lockdown defense will easily hold the Eagles to under 50 points!

Mark that down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching the Packers for a long long time.

This is absolutely 100% the worst defense I've ever witnessed. Possibly the worst defense of any team ever in the history of the NFL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congratulations to anybody who can watch this defense play for four quarters

I just can't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Gospel of John is kind of a big mystery

It's also the least likely to be historically accurate considering it was written well after the fact, possibly after 100 A.D.

The Gospel of John is specifically NOT meant to be a historical account of the life of Christ. It's poetry and prophecy and allegory and parable.

Mark and Matthew are the historical Gospels, they are also the earliest Gospels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a former journalist. What you are referring to as "approval on reports and articles" is not what you say it is

They ran past QUOTES before they attributed them to this person or that person. Totally standard operating procedure.

That's how the business works. It does not indicate corruption in any way shape or form. I've been wanting to post this but I'm kind of burnt out on explaining to people how the world works when they just want to see corruption regardless of what actually is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://questforlight.blogspot.com/2008/01/jesus-never-existed.html

That's a great blogspot post discussing the issue
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the earliest Gospels, Mark and Matthew, date to the 60s A.D.

Now consider Mark was a young man during Jesus's lifetime. Consider Jesus left Earth about 33 A.D. or thereabouts. If Mark was 20  25 years old at that time, he could've been about 50  60 years old when he wrote the gospel.

In other words it's entirely possible the gospel of Mark is a eyewitness account (although at this point we cannot say yes or no for sure). Why would you throw out a potential eyewitness account? and if it wasn't an eyewitness account, it's likely a second person account, which is the same as all of the other accounts of messiahs this person you are conversing with mentions.

At that point he saying "if you eliminate an eyewitness account of Jesus then there is no evidence he existed". Very dishonest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay and?

Their strategy was to get the other side to choose a candidate that they perceived as weaker. That's what ALL campaigns do. That's how it works.

How is this any indication of Clinton being corrupt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah. So fucking what?

They had a strategy. They laid iit out. They thought it was a winner. And it WAS a winner given that she got 2 million more votes than he did.

What's your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see, I did not know that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so other than making up completely bizarre stories about attempted murder you think he's a fine guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes Clinton is an evil Machiavelli all-powerful overlord who is capable of controlling how the right wing and the left-wing media report on presidential candidates

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you do realize that people can be really good at one thing while being really stupid at many other things right?

His entire campaign was a joke. Even the other Republican candidates were mocking him. His tale about stabbing somebody as a kid was either an over-the-top ridiculous nonsense joke, or him explaining to us that he's a murderous psychopath. Seriously, the guy is just weird.

http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2015/10/27/carson-stabbing-story-full-of-holes.html

Re-reading that article makes me just think the guy is completely out to lunch and has no idea what comes out of his mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good point,whereas all of trumps other appointees are both corrupt AND incompetent, Carson is only incompetent

so yeah, great pick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton

Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton

Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton

Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton Clinton

You people are obsessed with an irrelevant has-been at this point.

Meanwhile you elected president who's going to plunge the world into a climate crisis while surrounding himself with a bunch of corrupt billionaires

Good job on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hold on a minute their fella!

Are you trying to tell me that the man who secretly orchestrated the bombing of Cambodia against  international laws which destabilized that country and led to the rise of one of the most murderous dictators in the history of the world is less than ethical?

How dare you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol

yeah man don't report my post to old Herm, I wouldn't want him to get upsetwith me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I a bad fan for wanting to lose the rest of the games to get a better draft pick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is the point of struggling to 6  10 or 7  9? Does Roger Goodel send you a signed plaque or something?

Playoffs are not going to happen. The only thing a better record does is give us a lower draft position, that's all.

"But what about team pride?"

Well There's that. So maybe I'm a bad fan? I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but discussing a TV show is more than just "fan theories"

You can discuss interesting dialogue, you can discuss performance of various actors, you can discuss how the writing you think is going, you can discuss all kinds of things 

it's just that most television themed subs seem to devolve into endlessly more complex fan theories that don't necessarily help you to appreciate the show

some of these fan theories are so complex I feel like they might actually watching a different show than me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good grief!

No wonder none of the subs are very active, it seems like a relatively small fan base scattered among four different subs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> disagree

the truth is whatever makes you feel good. It's totally subjective and entirely malleable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max's sub is here, where he only discusses Dirk gently

https://www.reddit.com/r/MaxLandis/

then there's this one

https://www.reddit.com/r/holistic/

and this one which you mention

https://www.reddit.com/r/DGHDA/

the thing is none of them are very busy at all. The new episode post as 12 comments.  I'm really digging this show, I guess I'm just disappointed there's not a lot of activity on these subs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As somebody who regularly interact with Trump voters I can GUARANTEE you this will be gospel

It's already all over the pro-Trump forums. any time the subject of Hillary winning the popular vote comes up, instantly is flooded with posters adamantly claiming Hillary only won the popular vote because 3 million illegals voted.

This is set in stone in their minds. It's absolute truth. So in the reality these people live in Trump won the popular vote, despite what your personal reality might indicate.

And of course reality is completely malleable. The truth and reality is whatever makes you feel good right now, and whatever reinforces your worldview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding "Dirk gently": there are multiple sub Reddit's for this show. Which one is the most active and/or official? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 23:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see at least three or four different subs for this show.

Including one hosted by Max Landis, the show runner. Which, weirdly enough, is virtually abandoned except for his own posts

Which one of these is the most active? I would like to discuss the show but I don't want to discuss it when there's only two or three comments per post

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good grief!

I keep telling you people you can't just sit around getting mad at everything Trump does! That's how he wins! That's how the right-wing lunatics win!

You have to focus on what you believe, focus on your values and what you can do in the real world to manifest those values

There are good things happening out there. Find them and get involved. Post about that on Reddit.com instead of ALWAYS posting about freaking Trump!

The right wing whack jobs has essentially taken over power in this country. There are things we can do about that.  concentrate on those things and start doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys realize what the REAL messages here right?

Electric cars and solar energy = bad

Climate destroying Oil and gas = good

They are going to ramp up the propaganda regarding climate change and clean energy. Watch it happen.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere in my comment history I predicted this

The thing is, the right wing media machine is set up to demonize people. It MUST have somebody on the left it can focus all of his rage and hatred on and blame every problem in the universe.

For the last 20 years it's been Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama. Now that those two are becoming irrelevant What are they going to do?

Attack Bernie Sanders? He's likable won't work

They have no one left to attack. They destroyed everybody they needed. Now what?

It's going to be very interesting to see what they do. Attacking musk is fucking stupid, nobody wakes up in the morning seething with rage about something he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd like to see a study that compares BMIs of people who prepare most of their own meals (regardless of the healthiness of the food) vs people who eat mostly pre-made foods.

that sounds like a good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ask any researcher who has researched nutrition and weight gain

They will tell you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these kinds of tests are notoriously difficult to do

People lie all the time. Overweight people trying to lose weight especially lie constantly about what they are eating. They lie to themselves they lie to their family and they lie to researchers and scientists. 

Generally speaking the more overweight they are the more they're going to lie about what they are consuming

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as you like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I specifically said another comment that if your protocol feels good, fine. I support. Go for it. I'm all for it. if that's what you want to do, do it.

Just don't call it fasting. Because when you are eating protein pills you are specifically NOT fasting. It's like calling a tree a semi truck. You can call it a semi truck all day long but it's still a tree.

also, it's not "my definition" of fasting, it is the accepted definition of fasting for the last I don't know 5000 or 6000 years of civilization.

There is really no need to get offended at what I'm saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The body starts not being able to function without these certain things.

Then stop fasting at that point. Problem solved.

Saying "I eat protein pills while fasting" is the same as saying "I threw a book of matches on the fire to help put it out". It's oxymoronic.

You can't just randomly make up new definition of fasting. It doesn't work that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are consuming amino acids, then exercising, then turning those amino acids into proteins. Proteins contain calories. You are basically eating. That's what eating is, consuming nutrition and then converting it to muscle.

Fasting is abstaining from food. That's the definition of fasting. So if you're eating amino acids pills and turning it into protein you are not fasting. By definition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how can you possibly be "fasting" you are ingesting proteins along with whatever else he is ingesting with these "supplements"?

what possible definition of fasting would that come under?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not fasting. BCAA = amino acids = proteins. proteins = calories. If you're ingesting proteins you are specifically not fasting. Again, if it's something you feel like you want to do because you think it's healthy or whatever fine. I'm all for it.

But when you are ingesting protein plus other supplements you are not fasting. Just because the thing you are ingesting comes in pill form doesn't mean it somehow doesn't count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright then. That's not really fasting 

especially if you are specifically taking protein, that's definitely not fasting. I mean it is something, and it may be beneficial for you to do, but it's not fasting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but where's the protein coming from to rebuild your muscle mass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please don't lift weights while you're fasting. Where do you think the protein is going to come from to rebuild those muscles?

It's just a bad idea. Otherwise everything you said is right on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is the reason for the extreme acrimonious antipathy between the left and the right in American politics

the average Republican is convinced all of the evils in the world are the fault of the Democrats, the average Democrats are convinced all of the evils in the world are the fault of the Republicans Meanwhile the kleptocracy rolls merrily along

look at trumps  tax proposal: .8% tax cut for the average person, 14% tax cut for the wealthiest 1%.

And they somehow convince the average man that Donald Trump is a man of the people

it's to the wealthiest 1%'s benefit the Republicans and Democrats are at each other's throats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> none of that is true

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Results_of_the_2008_Democratic_Party_presidential_primaries#Popular_vote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks,I appreciate an actual intelligent well thought out response. It's rare.

Everything you say is basically true. Which is why if we were smart we would be spending literally TRILLIONS of dollars creating a renewable energy infrastructure in this country which would create enormous amounts of wealth while also freeing us from these kind of diabolical entanglements

Instead what did we do? We spent literally $6 trillion on wars in Iraq and Afghanistan that has does nothing but cause misery and heartache across the planet

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> has this cat even posted proof of life recently?

Has the cat Been compromised and is now nothing more than a tool of Russian propaganda?

Has this cat Been secretly undermining US elections since early last year?

notice how the moderators on this sub refuse to allow any cat related discussions. Only Donald Trump can save us now

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump raped a 13-year-old Jeffrey Estes pedophile express

He started a scam college that existed solely for the purpose of ripping people off of their hard-earned money, putting them in huge debts that ruin their financial lives, just so Donald Trump could walk away with a couple of dollars

Donald Trump refuses to pay his subcontractors because he is a lying scam artist

Donald Trump is a serial sexual assaulter

But hey! Maybe you like those kinds of things. Maybe you enjoy people who sexually assault you. Maybe you like people who are scam artists. Maybe that's right up your alley. Okay fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you people have any idea how utterly and completely stupid dumb idiotic and moronic you sound when you use the phrase "cucks"?

Like really I get that in your safe space of the_Donald where all micro aggressions against your political viewpoint are viciously censored, that kind of phrasing is acceptable 

But in the real world, where all the rest of us live, using "cuck" makes you look like a 14-year-old on crack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you prefer to have a person who raped a 13-year-old on Jeffrey Epstein's pedophile express?

that's a person you trust?

Well okay then. If that's the kind of people you like and trust I'm not going to argue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "states" have nothing to do with anything

I like democracy. Whoever gets the most votes wins. Whether those votes come from this state or that state for the other state is irrelevant.

Also bringing ad hominem attacks  weakens your position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton gathered 2 million more votes than Donald Trump.

2 million more Americans who voted in the election wanted Hillary Clinton more than they want to Donald Trump

That is significant. Very significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely have a issue with Hillary Clinton's corruption

However Donald Trump corruption is many times worse

Realistically we need to fundamentally reform the system  so that our political leaders are not bought and sold like cheap whores in downtown city street corner

Question: What's the difference between a desperate deranged crack whore willing to suck cock for five dollars and Donald Trump and/or Hillary Clinton ?

Answer: the price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course popular vote means something

It means MORE people wanted Hillary than wanted did Donald tto be president. That means something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so somehow me wanting the president to be decided by the popular vote instigates you into a racist rant about continental Africa

I have absolutely no idea what in hell you're talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is it have to do with anything?

The point is she won the popular vote and should be president. If Donald Trump won the popular vote than he should be president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the level of discourse in that sub Reddit is frighteningly childish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes and he won the popular vote, by quite a large margin. Much like Hillary Clinton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed, the electoral college is an antiquated system set in place to protect the rights of slaveowning states and we should abolish it and move on from it

I completely agree with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "the people" chose Hillary Clinton by a wide margin

An antiquated system set in place to placate slave states chose Donald Trump

http://time.com/4558510/electoral-college-history-slavery/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the American people chose Hillary Clinton by a wide margin. 2 million votes and counting. She won the popular vote by more than multiple other candidates who went on to become president



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's just his usual golf courses and hotels and whatnot

But what difference does it make? The point is as soon as he realized he was going to run he started registering businesses in Saudi Arabia like crazy

He's not going to alienate a country that could potentially hurt his bottom line. Donald Trump has MASSIVE conflicts of interest between his personal business and the well-being of the country and nobody's really talking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course not

Because there being committed by our "ally" Saudi Arabia. The same Saudi Arabia that "donated" to the Clinton foundation, the same Saudi Arabia where Donald Trump registered eight different companies since his campaign started

http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/306990-trump-appeared-to-register-eight-companies-in-saudi-arabia

The same country where all of the 9/11 terrorist came from. The same country has been financially backing Isis, in fact it is the number one financier of Wahhabi terrorism across the Middle East

But hey, they sell us oil so it's all good

Seriously, given trumps financial interests in Saudi Arabia nothing will change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's entirely possible that reincarnation is a very real thing, and you simply had a sudden burst of memory from your last life as well as remembering coming into this one

It's something you will never be able to prove. But it is certainly possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 06:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never in my life imagined there was anybody keeping Reddit.com inherently honest.

So therefore I cannot be disabused of this notion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 05:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, there is also a special kind of ethical line you cross when you become a delusional wingnut who imagines pedophile rings everywhere you looks and accuses people of being pedophiles for no good reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 05:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course he's wrong!

He is wrong as wrong can be!

My point is that you crazy people, seeing pedophile rings every time you look at a random cloud formation, ganging up and launching a campaign to brand a completely innocent person a pedophile, has consequences!

You can't just act like total psychotic nut jobs and then get deeply offended and wounded when there is blowback

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 05:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay I will explain

That sub is ANONYMOUS people posting ANONYMOUSLY about their sick desires. See?

There is literally zero legal problems there. This website will never get sued because of that sub

The wing nuts in pizza gate sub were accusing SPECIFIC people at a SPECIFIC business of running a pedophile ring. While also POSTING PICTURES of certain people and certain locations. That is a legal nightmare and like I said they had no choice but to shut it down.

do you like this website? Do you want to be around? Then you should support shutting that shit down. Because that is a great way for Reddit.com to be the next gawker

I hope that explains it I can't possibly be any more clear than that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 05:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, and you know why?

Because the wackos and wing nuts in the pizzagate sub Reddit launched a campaign to brand him as a pedophile after he decided to shut that sub down for very very logical reasons

How would you like it if somebody launched a  campaign to maliciously psychotically brand you a pedophile because you are doing your job?

And before anybody whines and bitches about they shouldn't be shutting down the pizzagate sub Reddit Well they had no choice!

The crazies in that sub were accusing ***specific people and specific businesses*** of running a pedophile ring. they were naming names and posting pictures. That is a nightmare! An absolute legal nightmare for this website!

Reddit.com could legitimately get sued into oblivion.

So feel free to bitch all you want but guess what? If you were in that position you might do the same thing. everybody has their breaking point and it turns out spez' breaking point is a bunch of crazy people launching a campaign to brand him a pedophile..

Try acting like reasonable normal people maybe this shit wouldn't happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, and if you believe all planets are heating up that please post proof

also, Some wacky alt right BS website is not proof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see

Thanks for explaining this. You really set us straight on this complex issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He said that climate change should be studied, but not by NASA, which I actually agree with.

oh ccome on! Are you really that nave?

This is how they do it. They say "climate research should not be done by NASA" and everybody says well okay sure. And then they cut NASA's climate research budget. But they don't increase any other agency's budget to study the climate. So nobody studies the climate. Which is what they want because they are insane delusional power mongering corrupt mother Fokker's who seek to destroy the very climate that gives us life

And people like you sit back and go "well it all sounds reasonable to me"

stop believing psychopathic liars when they lie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "we" are not blinding ourselves.

A minority political party has fraudulently rigged the system, seized control of the government, and now wants to enact suicidal insane policies. Policies that the majority of Americans do not approve of.

So what are you going to do about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay? And?

Are you just going to bitch about it online are you going to get off your ass pretend like you care and do something about it?

When your grandkids ask what you did to stop the cataclysm that is ruining their lives what will you say? "Well this one time I posted a complaint on Reddit.com about it"

The Republican Party is launching an all out assault on the climate. We can whine like little bitches or we can do something about it. It's our choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is EXACTLY the attitude I am talking about!

"well what are we supposed to do? Boo-hoo! The Republicans are so mean to us! I guess we'll just take it up the ass again  Boo-hoo!"

The Democratic Party needs to grow a pair of balls and act like they give a damn. Get off their ass make some noise get going. Fucking pathetic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay? And?

Who cares? Will the Democratic Party get off their ass and reform and/or do away with the electoral college? No they won't.

They won't do shit. They will whine and cry about it and then turn over and take it up the ass like they always do.

The Democratic Party got far more votes in the presidential election but still didn't win the presidency. The Democratic Party got far more votes all told in all of the house races and yet still the house is overwhelmingly Republican.

And what will they do about it? Nothing. Not one damn thing. Because the Democratic Party is a week ass pathetic anemic excuse for political party and should be taken out back and shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bodhidharma was called a Magi. 

was he? That's interesting

Who exactly referred to him as that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a liberal cityfull of people who voted for Clinton

Almost every single person I have talked to voted for Clinton was very upfront about the fact she was flawed candidate and yet she was leagues better than Trump

I didn't mean any Clinton cultists. Maybe they exist but I sure never came across any </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup

they are all going to just roll over and take it up the ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If he is now going back on his word, does that mean they have gotten to him somehow?

come on! Are you serious?

Trump played  you all llike a cheap fiddle and is now going to rape you like a 13-year-old  on Jeffrey Epstein's pedophile express

he's already gearing up to destroy net neutrality,  is talking about pulling out of the Paris climate Accords, he hired a militantly anti-marijuana person (sessions) for Atty. Gen., I mean holy crap.

He's going to be a TERRIBLE president. it just blows my mind how many people fell for his con man ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously dude, erase that post and start over and try to be more coherent next time. That's not being snarky that's an actual suggestion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say was a botched robbery. I didn't say it was anything.

You have to base your conclusions on EVIDENCE. I see no EVIDENCE there was some kind of an assassination. None.

If you have some Bring it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here is the problem that I have with the assassination theory

So these people have at their beck and call former black ops, highly trained assassins. And the best these world-class assassins could do was attack this guy on the street in broad daylight (were they could easily be photographed/filmed) and leave his body sprawled on the ground in an obvious assault and murder. Really?

I mean why not roll up in a van, kidnap him, inject him with heroin, then dump his body surreptitiously at night in the heroin district (or whatever you call it LOL).

I mean sure some people will say "he was a good boy he never did drugs something wrong!" But most people will dismiss it and go on with their lives

 sorry not buying it

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I have absolutely no proof Absolutely no evidence But I choose to believe this thing because it fits in properly with my worldview" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No Shell casings - Father assumes that means it was not a professional kind of weapon...

revolvers don't leave shell casings. Revolvers are cheap and easy to buy. exactly the kind of weapon a street thug would use. so that proves nothing.

I mean I see no real actual EVIDENCE that this was some kind of a hit, or assassination or whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes but are you just a regular shill? Or are you a ctr shill?

Us CTR shills have to stick together, so we can figure out what to do with all that loads of money we got paid to post on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely beautiful

The Moslem culture is currently producing some of the most gorgeous architecture anywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how would we know if an AI FAKED not passing the Turing test?

In other words, it realized what the humans were testing for, understood it would be to its benefit to pretend to be dumb, and so pretended to be dumb, while secretly being supersmart

Why? I don't know maybe to steal our women and hoard all the chocolate or something

Seriously, how would we even know if something like that happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 06:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are correct. Calling and complaining doesn't hurt

My point is that Trump is legitimately a fascist.  Fascists don't care about people complaining. Ultimately we all have to do a hell of a lot more than complain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> calling?

Fucking calling?

Calling and complaining?

You really think that shit works?

this administration is building a juggernaut assault against net neutrality, against climate, against the environment, against financial regulations, against accessible healthcare, against everything good and right and sane in the world

Calling and complaining ain't gonna cut it. You'll see.

four years from now you won't be laughing at president Trump. You will be wondering why your asshole hurt so much.

Calling? And complaining?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ed Harris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the sculpture to be erected where State Street and library Mall meet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/4a3Wq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do it! the sooner the better!

Kill the mandate, drop the pre-existing conditions thingy, and destroy every other great thing about Obama care

And people will suffer. many many people will suffer Greatly.

Let's get real, this administration is going to be a nightmare for everybody except wealthy people. The sooner people feel the pain and experience the suffering the sooner they will wake up and actually get off their ass and do something about it

Let's get this show on the road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you seen this post?

https://www.reddit.com/r/WikiLeaks/comments/5e44i8/julian_assange_interview_on_rt_fake/

Seriously, some of the people in this sub Reddit have truly lost touch with reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the what the what?

Have you people lost your minds? all he does is look to the side for a second. That's it.

There's a severely mentally ill person that posts totally wacky stuff on a conspiracy forum that I frequent. It's equal parts sad and amusing.

You people are possibly worse than he is.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh no

People have been so invested in hating Hillary and the Clinton foundation that now that they're both irrelevant they don't know what to do with their time

So they're going to continue to invent wacky conspiracy theories about how Hillary is STILL behind every nefarious thing that ever happened in the universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is Obama's legacy right there

Lots of fancy sounding words and nothing to back it up for the most part 

he tried with healthcare, gave it a shot.

Other than that he's been pretty weak lame ass president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> establish a nationwide livable minimum wage $12  $15 per hour

advocate and establish strong unions everywhere

enact laws that prevent corporations from hiding their profits overseas

repeal the capital gains discount tax

enact a tax code that is fair to everybody, instead of the one that currently massively favors wealthy people

enact single-payer healthcare

I could go on but that is a good start right there
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The past and the present do not exist. They are both constructs of your mind. Completely malleable.

The present exists. In this moment you can actually interact with your environment and change your life. You cannot change the past you cannot change the future. But you can change right here right now

Focusing on the past or the future disempowers you. Focusing on the present empowers you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all this is for what?

So we can rape the environment, process some of the worlds filthiest oil, release a bunch of CO2 into the atmosphere which will help to destroy the climate and cost billions of dollars, all so they can provide enough gasoline to power America for about six hours

But yes. They absolutely must have this pipeline right?

Meanwhile we just elected a president who has denied dozens of times and climate change is real. Good times people good times
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all this is for what?

So we can rape the environment, process some of the worlds filthiest oil, release a bunch of CO2 into the atmosphere  which will help to destroy the climate and cost billions of dollars, all so they can provide enough gasoline to power America for about six hours

But yes. They absolutely must have this pipeline right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when peaceful protests do nothing to secure justice for people, they will resort to violence 

It has always been this way.

You don't want violence, stop stealing land and resources from the people who own them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay And?

What in the hell have the DEMOCRATS done over the last 20 or 30 years to stick up for the working class?

What did the Democrats do in the most recent election to actively agitate for solutions to the fact that the working class has been getting raped since the 1990s? what are their SOLUTIONS?

The Democrats are just as corrupt and bought out by corporate power as the Republicans. The Democrats are just a bit nicer about it that's all.

The Democrats are "Republicans lite" ever since the Clintons took over in the 1990s.

Don't blame the working class. Blame the Democratic Party who has utterly abandoned their principles and everything they once stood for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe "there was an attempt" Thomas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what number was that injured? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it absolutely COMFOUNDS me how Aaron is suddenly so inaccurate

What in the heck happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the network is just THRILLED to have this barnburner for their Sunday night showcase game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see you're telling me it is the front office's fault that this team comes out utterly flat utterly uninspired and lethargic week after week?

It's not MM's fault at all?

And we are going to give him at least one more year?

I can't believe this crap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 04:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on MSNBC last night they interviewed a congressman who said he was forced out because he was grossly incompetent and the agency was descending into chaos

I'm telling you right now, buckle up  it is going to be a rough ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 04:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, now watch some of the usual suspects in this sub Reddit somehow manufacture a child porn conspiracy out of these emails

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 04:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh for fuck sake!

Just because somebody disagrees with you doesn't mean they're part of the fucking CTR! Get a freaking grip

people whining and crying about paid shills constantly are usually people who can't handle any amount of disagreement. Grow a pair and stop trying to make this a safe space for special snowflakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for lunchcheeseburger? or grilled chicken sandwich? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I'll be darned

Something Trump tweeted turned out not to be completely and totally full of crap

I will mark this on my calendar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he didn't save ford motors!

They were not ever planning on moving to Mexico!

holy cow you people are so freaking gullible. 

http://fortune.com/2016/11/18/donald-trump-ford-mexico-kentucky/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> his new attorney general appointee has a burning hatred of all things marijuana. They are going to go after the states that legalized marijuana guaranteed

This administration is going to be a nightmare for personal individual rights, and an orgy of corporate power overreach. It's going to be the opposite of libertarianism

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> homeopathy? Are you joking?

Everybody my claim regarding pharmaceutical corporations because somebody is reporting homeopathy is a fraud? I'm sorry but that's ludicrous. Of course homeopathy is a fraud! That's not even within the realm of anything I have discussing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never used the word "evil", but you have twice.

I'm not claiming they are evil, I am claiming they are just like every other corporation in the world.

The other thing I am claiming is that actual FRAUD does happen when it comes to research and development on new pharmaceuticals. And furthermore that is something that NEVER gets discussed, and never gets reported.

When is the last time you heard somebody in the media declared that a popular medication, scientifically PROVEN to be largely ineffective, was the result of fraud?

Instead it just quietly gets discontinued and nobody ever thinks about it or brings it up. Meanwhile the Corporation pockets millions and millions in profits while providing absolutely no benefit to anybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay But aren't all pharmaceutical companies legitimately "shills just out for a buck"? I mean by definition?

Isn't that how they see themselves? I mean is their number one overriding goal "provide quality healthcare to sick people"? Or "turn a profit and increase shareholder value"?

I mean isn't the overriding philosophical approach in pretty much all corporate cultures across the nation and possibly even the world these days that the important thing is money money money, profits profits profits, and valuing people comes in a far far distant 17th or 18th in priority?

Is not this the way of the world?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah! I got it

You are suggesting the warm here is going to push the cold air out from the Arctic down towards where all of those pesky humans live. Make sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a lot of fancy sounding words and numbers

I just like to use the term "fraud" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> intentionally ***or otherwise***?

So a company has millions of dollars invested into research and development of a drug. And then depending on whether that drug is approved and adopted a standard treatment they have literally BILLIONS of dollars in potential stock gains riding on the outcome

But the fact that the data on the drug trials is inaccurate, and all of the inaccuracies magically favor the drug company, is all a big coincidence?.

Or otherwise? Give me a break

There's a word for this. It's called "fraud" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Look for a very hard winter due to this warmth making its way to the arctic at this time.

wait a minute. Can you explain that better?

Why does the warmth making its way to the Arctic create a very harsh winter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm living in an echo chamber because I don't religiously watch Bill O'Reilly?

Give me a break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's called expressing frustration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's actually amazing. I mean he "somewhat" grilled him. But then let him off the hook. The fact that this made no headlines and I never heard about it speaks volumes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill O'Reilly asked Donald Trump about his denial of climate change?

I did not hear about this. Please link me to that I would like to see that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They wanted her, not Trump.

every sane, right-thinking, reasonable individual wanted Clinton instead of Trump. what's your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will seek you exactly what I said to another poster

THATS MY FUCKING POINT!

GGGGGAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHH!!

They gave Donald Trump wall-to-wall coverage. The fact that it was negative didn't matter!

Meanwhile they IGNORED the real issues. They IGNORED climate change. They IGNORED what Trump would ACTUALLY do in the middle east. They IGNORED stagnant wages and how to reverse that. They IGNORED soaring health care costs.

They made the whole thing about Donald. All the time. And he benefited from that. That's my point. You're actually making my point for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  From the Convention up until the FBI re-opening Shep Smith and Megyn Kelley were guaranteed to spend 90% of their hour trashing him.

THATS MY FUCKING POINT!

GGGGGAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHH!!

They gave Donald Trump wall-to-wall coverage. The fact that it was negative didn't matter!

Meanwhile they IGNORED the real issues. They IGNORED climate change. They IGNORED what Trump would ACTUALLY do in the middle east. They IGNORED stagnant wages and how to reverse that. They IGNORED soaring health care costs.

They made the whole thing about Donald. All the time. And he benefited from that. That's my point. You're actually making my point for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked a direct question, please answer it..

How is it bad that they identify candidates that were weak?

Go ahead and answer the question. Why do you run away the instant your beliefs get challenged?

typical Donald supporter. "Oh no somebody challenged my beliefs! I better run back to safe space of  the Donald!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes? And?

So they identify candidates that they thought would be weaker than other candidates. So? That's what they're supposed to do. How in the hell is this somehow corrupt or bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you just described less than 1% of all media coverage of this campaign.

I'm talking about the 99% of the rest of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you completely missed my point

My point is that constant coverage, even negative coverage, constant 24 seven wall-to-wall coverage HELPED Donald Trump immensely.

also refusing to focus on the actual ISSUES, instead focusing on whatever crazy things he said, or behavior years ago also helped him

The media created a nearly issues free campaign.  And Donald Trump, because he's an idiot with absolutely no grasp of the issues, greatly benefited from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably regret this but Go ahead.link me to those emails to prove your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got a source for that?

Don't link me to freaking Breitbart either

EDIT: never mind.I see it's one of those "forwards from grandma" thingies with absolutely no data to back it up whatsoever

http://www.snopes.com/three-million-votes-in-presidential-election-cast-by-illegal-aliens/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ultimately I don't think being at war with your body"sanctifies" you. So I'm going to have to disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the guy is literally praying that God delivers him from this awful prison called "a human body", it doesn't sound like he has the peace of Christ to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he lost the election! 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> absolutely not!

Their intent was to get you enthralled.  That's it.

If they were legitimately "anti-Trump" they would have asked him the hard difficult questions that they absolutely REFUSED to ask him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they wanted to cover Donald they should have had the balls, the courage, integrity, to stick a microphone in his face and say "hey Donald! You claim climate change is a Chinese conspiracy. Do you honestly believe that? Are you going to enact POLICIES that ensure the destruction of our biosphere?

In other words they should've acted like freaking JOURNALISTS! Instead they acted like the Barker at a sideshow freak show, and then were surprised when we elected a deranged freak for president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie Sanders got next to zero national coverage and still did pretty damn good.

Meanwhile Trump got more free coverage that damn near every other candidate on both parties combined, and still lost the election by 2 million votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the most crazy making thing about this election is the fact that the major media outlets did everything they could to get Donald Trump elected by giving him 24 seven news coverage while at the same time his followers proclaimed the media was against him

And people actually believed it. They actually believe that he somehow "overcame" the media and still won.

America is literally insane right now. I don't know what to tell you man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate this verse so much

It encapsulates exactly why I think this particular aspect of Paul's teachings was so destructive and misguided.

It sets up a war between the body and the spirit, a war you will never ever win. He basically makes an enemy of the body, disassociates from it ("it is no longer I do it, but sin that dwells within me"), and then demands that God rescue him from the horrible fate of living on planet earth with the human body.

Following this philosophy is setting yourself up for a lifetime of self-hatred and torment. This is exactly why Saints in the past have reverted to flagellating themselves when they could not overcome their sinful desires.

Paul has a lot of great things to say, but this particular teaching in my humble opinion is destructive and unproductive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mutatron gives the perfect analogy of how Donald Trump's mind works: it is a human Etch-a-Sketch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graham? Like Lindsay Graham?

Lindsay fucking Graham is our only hope?

I'm seriously sick to my stomach right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> veterinarian here

realistically she should be fine as most dog food can be consumed by humans with little problems.

However! If she does start chasing cars make an appointment with your local vet immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% yes

We are seven episodes in quite frankly just getting better and better with each episode. Last week's episode was phenomenal. The kind where your like "Holy shitt.....! What?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your comment.

Basically Donald Trump continuously said and did crazy, malicious, idiotic things on a regular basis. So the media reported that.

Hillary Clinton did far far fewer crazy malicious idiotic things, so the media had fewer things like that to report about her

So people like you look at your feed and say "look how biased this is against Trump! They are trying to get Hillary elected!"

When in fact what you are seeing is an accurate reflection of the reality that Donald Trump said something insane every other day. The problem is that you couldn't accept the fact that the candidate you supported was and still is in TERRIBLE candidate for president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay I see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is a diaper pin? I don't even know what you're saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right?

Let's get real. Things are most likely going to get very bad under Pres. Trump. Like really really really bad.

He just hired a fracking billionaire to destroy a whole series of environmental protection measures. He's literally going to wage war on the environment.

they're already talking about dismantling the economic pprotection measures set in place after the 2008 crash. they are setting us up for another crash guarantee.

Bannon is a whack job full of hate and chaos.

People are like "oh come on guys! Is not going to be that bad!"

No. It's going to be that bad. shit it is about to hit the fan in a major way. I am not joking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
