<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a picture of the actual device that is doing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm ducking buying this ducking game. 

Literally running in the store. Growing my money at the vendor, and running out with my copy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Blaine the cat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't China the sole contributor to the ivory market?

Why haven't they cracked down on it?

Killing a creature just for ivory seems pretty barbaric.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the amazing athletic genetics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously payday loans have always been disfavoured by banks and officials. 

As I've never used the service before, I've heard the interest rates can be well over 3 digits(as confirmed by the article)

How do these companies get past the predatory lending regulations? Obviously their service is provided to help borrowers in a short term bind, but their service also generates a substantial profit through incredibly high interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the same city as this guy. 

In Vancouver you get a lot of holiday campaigns where they promote gifting people "experiences" that don't result in waste and garbage. 

Like going to a play, skydiving, a movie, etc. It's more about spending time with the person than just buying them something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he use a suicide command at the end? Or just die of disgust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine this is how superman's day to day is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should come to the Canucks. 

He could extend that streak by another 60 games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *conversation while hiding*

"Why are we hiding?"

"He asked for sliced cheese and Oragel"

"What the fuck?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where a cat sees a cat door, a dog sees an opportunity to use perseverance to prove to his master that he can overcome anything. 

- dogs everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how he/she stated everyone lost heir shit and followed them out of the class in protest. 

When I attended lectures the only thing I cared about was going, getting the pertinent notes and info to do well on the exams and essays, then getting home. 

I can't imagine too many students prolonging a class over something as trivial as a professor being wrong on one or two things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but where do the courts draw the line in regards to when the line is crossed as far as "a few comments amongst a billion".

When would the courts need to explore further? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't played in two months.

Can anyone give me the ELI5 on what they did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless,

The industry of transportation needs a baseline for legal precedent. I guess they are going to start with Walmart first and move down the chain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much this. 

So are they your employees or not?

Or are they independent contractors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is excellent. 

Pay your fucking employees living wages you pricks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do vaginas have parasympathicus nerves as well?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey bro,

We just spent a fortune data mining your email information. We then used valuable resources that could be spent on better things like fighting terrorism or external cyber threats, but instead tracked down and confirmed your automobile/insurance information. 

Here's your $17 dollar ticket. 

Pay it by tonight, or we break every law protecting your existence as a Canadian citizen. 

Sunny Skies and with love,
Justin Trudeau (I really personally wrote this email to you) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Profit margins on books is one thing I've always wondered about. 

A lot of the books offered at UBC are at the same price point on Amazon. 

I would expect the books at UBC to be offered at cost. Not for profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you just have to laugh in the face of failure. 

Or you go crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all seriousness this guy has amazing colouring skills. His hand is so steady. 

Are you a surgeon OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to play this song while practicing my wrist shot and snap shot for hockey. 

Offspring have always been a hockey players music of choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like a Predator from the Arnold Schwarzenegger movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he's not a sexist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the Alien queens differ from the Alien soldiers facially? or is it just a size difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done this a few times.

I don't know whether to yell at myself, the TV, or my team mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://cdn.smosh.com/sites/default/files/legacy.images/smosh-pit/122010/batman-joker.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thousand yard stare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who doesn't watch e-sports, are women paid more for:

Streaming
Showing up to e-sport events (promotional etc)
The winning pots are more for women when competing in tournies

Etc. 

In real sports women make less largely because the viewer base is far less than men.

So in e-sports more people watch women? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I thought traffic was bad in Vancouver, Canada.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the escalators at the Skytrains in Vancouver they put these rubber bumps on the railings to prevent these shenanigans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The look on the guys face before he flopped over says he had a 33.3% chance of success.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 13:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like an Italian family relative of mine. After having too much and not enough vino for the night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could just see the janitor yelling on mafia chat. 

Kill your laundry. Kill him. You'll understand later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. 

Trippy man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should put some "The Rock" movie theme music on this video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't even hesitate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if we can actually fix issues like this.

These socioeconomic issues seem so entrenched in developing countries that you would need to a miracle to fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm catholic too. I don't necessarily "accept" all of my Church's beliefs on contraception, homosexuality, and abortion.

Any sane Catholic doesn't impose his feelings on abortion onto the public.

But as a citizen who shares the same sentiments as many other citizens, I don't believe in late term abortions. If you're getting an abortion in month 8 or 9, you sure as hell better have a good reason for it (life of mother is in jeopardy, etc). 

I'm a firm believer that once the fetus hits the 8th or 9th month, he or she should be protected under the charter of rights (Canadian) or Constitution (American). This belief isn't religiously based. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think SJW's have hit the pinnacle of craziness.

They then get even crazier.

I wonder how far they will go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the funniest scenes ever. 

"That took guts, we need guts." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was just a light jog out of the gate. Imagine being hit by these guys when they really throw their weight into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 million views per video. 

Entertaining young kids on YouTube is lucrative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did deathclaws evolve from kemodo dragons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Returning player on new account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played back in 2003 (I think, I played right when it was released in NA).

I quit a little after when the expansion with that place in the sky (it was circular, with the same architecture as that huge white building in la theime (holla) and had beautiful gardens and trees on the island in the sky. It also had 4 or 5 huge HNM's you could spawn. I forget the name.

I was in the Linkshell "Easy Company" from Midgardsormer, we eventually took over as the best NA Linkshell for endgame content after the main linkshell hopped ship to another game.

I remember competing with the JP players for HNM spawns, and literally watched them a couple of times reorient the spawn timer on a couple of HNM's by turtling them for 5-10 hours.

I eventually quit a bit before WoW came out, as I was a DRK and got bored of being a stun bot who was outshined by RNG and BLM for DPS. So I haven't played for a very long time.

Couldn't remember my credentials or anything about my old account so I'm starting over.

I'm planning to play a PLD, since I've always wanted to be a PLD back in the day, just didn't have time to reroll.

Is PLD/WAR still the basic job/subjob combo for end game content?

Also, I've read about all these new features (trusts obviously) etc:

In what order should I do these:

Get my subjob, WAR, up to 50.

Do ROV's up to the white ribbon (I think thats what its called)

Get my nation reputation up to Rank 5

Get my chocobo license

Records of eminence, I currently have 2500, but I have no idea how I got them. I remember killing some shit in that cave for the Squire II quest and seeing 1200/5000.

Are records of eminence and RoV tied in together?

Should I spend my Sparks on any swords yet? I'm currently lvl 36 on my war subjob.

Lastly, this is a big one thats really screwing me. Gil. I don't remember having a Gil issue back when I played. But right now I have no idea how to keep up with my Gil and levelling at the same time.

One more thing, I'm currently on Asura, any newbie friendly/chatting type linkshells I could get into. It's pretty lonely hanging out in new player areas, and seeing people chat on linkshell chat would alleviate that.

Thanks in advance for any input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KEIacvPgj0A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roberts has this way of writing where it sucks you in.

I've never been a fan of originalism, or the people who defend it as stoically as Scalia did.

The last line sums up Scalia perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that what they said is "bad", spiteful, and uncalled for.

But why do people need to lose their jobs with one stupid comment? We have free speech, yet if you say something really dumb and uncalled for, especially as a civil servant, you lose your job.

If you work in a private sector job, people will actually go out of their way to petition the company to fire you, or they will rally the other SJW's to boycott your company. Furthermore, the company itself will fire you as though it's something to commend.

Whatever happened to forgiving people and hoping they grow as a human being? We don't need to forget and turn a blind eye, we can ridicule them, but hoping/expecting these people to be fired is erroneous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah she hurt herself by backing Clinton. I get it.

But she's still a good human being, and a great politician.

The problem is that Hillary Clinton has been a stain on the Dems for years. Why the fuck would they usher her to a General election candidacy? Also why would they drag some good politicians down with her, like Sanders and Warren?

Both Sanders and Warren were excellent candidates, because they were 100% trustworthy. For fuck sakes, Clinton had a hard time finding any dirt on Sanders. They had to stick to policy in the primary, because even Sanders didn't want to get involved with the rhetoric of Hillary's emails.

The DNC created a huge mess. They fucked the Democrat party for years to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spread Eagle Bay sounds like a blast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did someone really run over a protestor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then Warren should have fucking ran.

She was 100x the fucking candidate that Clinton was.

I still don't understand why she didn't run? Inner DNC politics are not a good enough of a reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The end there when the horse starts dancing with him, and then he *struts* off camera.

Kind of entertaining.

He has no rhythm but kind of nails it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Star Trek: The Next Generation spandex costumes were smelly, too small, and ruined actors backs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like a lynx, lion, and tiger all at once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You only wish you could wear a graduation gown as good as she could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are notoriously bad guns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys have some really impressive collection of guns.

In contrast, what are some really poorly manufactured guns?

Guns that are notoriously unreliable?

Guns that need grossly invested time to maintain?

etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I got those gifts as well.

Did they say what was wrong with the service? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up. Working for me now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 13:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm stuck at 70% as well on the loading screen. 

Pretty sure I'm on COSA too. 

Have a link to Mobile Strikes customer service?

If enough of us complain hopefully they fix it ASAP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 13:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy is built like a tank. 

He actually makes that spandex Star Trek uniform look masculine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 09:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one of the left is gorgeous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here is not upgrading to a PS4 Pro in the near future? Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 02:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For either:

a) You don't have a 4K TV

b) You don't have a 4K TV with HDR

c) You wanted the PS4 Pro as a 4K Blu-ray player, and because it doesn't include that, you don't see any reason to upgrade from a PS4.

d) Not enough games take advantage of the PS4 Pro yet, and you want to wait to see how well it's adopted by current and future titles.

e) You're really satisfied with your PS4, and upgrading isn't necessary.

f) Can't afford it as moneys tight at the moment.

For me, its a combination of B and E.

Edit: Added f) Can't afford it as moneys tight at the moment.

Also why is this post down voted? It's a simple question inquiring about the PS4 Pro in my fellow PS4 community. Really strange someone would down vote this, especially when it's not trolling or inciting bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 02:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to some sources, it's actually Billionaire George Soros fuelling these violent uprisings.

I'm pretty sure its the peaceful protests that aren't about destroying property, but letting Trump know that if he channels the unhappiness of the current economy and job situation into hate for muslims, gays, and women after he takes office, it won't be tolerated by these people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Trump say he was going to release his tax records if he was elected president? If so, has he yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it legislated that if elected president, he must submit them for public record?

Or is it just convention? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.

Looks like a model from today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not available in Canada.

http://wallpapercave.com/wp/r3BPFdb.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like a lot of charismatic politicians were decent looking when they were younger.

I heard Stalin was charismatic when he was younger, and he looked like he had no problem with the ladies:

http://i.amz.mshcdn.com/ZxZsiWoz-odBpH35W4ZaJuAL8ts=/http%3A%2F%2Fa.amz.mshcdn.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2016%2F03%2Fstalin-14.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.

Is that really him?

He looks italian.

Anybody have anymore pictures of him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 00:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This right here.

His staff will schedule him with policy makers favourable to the agenda. These people will also be scheduled at the end of the chain.

Trump will serve a single term, then America will wake up and realize that their economy and job issues stem from years of Republican and neo liberals bullshit. (Reagan/Bush's, Bill Clinton). 

If you want to fix the issue, you also need to get rid of obstructionism in Congress. Meaning, get rid of the Republicans in both the senate and the house who have rather put party loyalty (and lobbyist interests) above the peoples needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right. From my understanding, game compatibility between PS4 and PS4 pro was the number one priority. 

After all there were close to 50 million PS4's sold, and Sony doesn't want to alienate that base.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sun bros. 

Praise the sun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 11:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful reaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too.

I get shot through smoke and gas nades by snipers a couple 100m away. I'm wondering if there is some shenanigans going on either:

a) that player has found a way to turn off these effects

or

b) these effects are not synchronized between every client. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more of an aerial cannonball than a hop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy shaking his head kind of looks like Mayor Giuliani after the guy falls on him, and he gets pissed off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This man is a danger to everyone around him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he didn't give up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They got Trumps orange skin colour down perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll live on in our hearts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean the old PS4 can have its wifi network instability fixed with a software patch?

My connection is 35 down and 5 up. 

Yet my PS4 shows 17-20 down and 2-4 up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 10:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe something went weird when I transferred my back up to my new iPhone a couple of months ago.

Thanks for checking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're actually building a wall right now.

It's to keep Lena Dunham from coming to Canada.

It's going to be 700 feet tall, but this may not be enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to Settings - General - Storage   iCloud Usage:

Under Storage hit - Manage Storage:

Mine says 1.77 GB.

If you click on the Pocket Trains App under his menu it says the App size is 95.8 MB, and Documents   Data as 1.68 GB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info!

I'll still with Mobile Strike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a better game in your opinion?

According to what you've said, Game of War is further along its development cycle, but does Mobile Strike have better potential?

In other words, which one do you play more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2007 New England Patriots know how Hillary feels. All that hard work was for nothing Hillary. Nothing at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look at the most successful people in this world, i.e. Billionaires.

One study showed that the degree most represented was Engineering, then followed by Business, then Arts.

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2016/06/03/what-degree-you-should-study-to-become-a-billionaire/

While STEM graduates like fostering their superiority, they only made up double as many Arts billionaires.

Ironically, the vast majority of Billionaires didn't study or have any degrees at all.

So I guess if you want to be a billionaire, skip school, be smart, be lucky, and pay engineer, business, and arts graduates to do your dirty work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newt Gingrich vs. Bill Clinton back in the 90s didn't end well for Newt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Game of War, identical to Mobile Strike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was thinking of trying Game of War too, but I've read that it's identical to Mobile Strike.

Is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is this game so big on iOS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's listed as 95.7 mb on the Appstore, but when installed it bloats to 1.77 gb.

Is it downloading something that i'm not aware of?

I know some games are bigger than their download listing, but no game I've come across goes from 95 mb to 1.77gb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys did well. Trump was the more honest candidate and people respect honesty and leadership more than a clay candidate. Hillary Clinton was the democrat version of Jeb Bush. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie was the first real politician in a long time who wore his heart on his sleeve.

You could tell he loved his country so much, that he knew he had to be honest about what he believed in, and which direction he would have steered the US had he been elected as president.

On the flip side, Hillary won the primary, and was a clay candidate who would shape herself, and say, anything she needed to win.

Leaders are honest about their own convictions, and they stand up for their own beliefs, even when it's against the grain.

Here's to Bernie 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read up about what forms and paper work needs to be submitted in the first couple weeks. 

Then once you're done with that. Figure out what your statute of limitations is. Here it is 2 years after the incident. 

Explore your options. These adjusters only care about their quotas. You need to look after what's best for yourself. 

Also don't feel guilty about taking them to the cleaners. Your well being is more important than their bottom line. 

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should go somewhere between the spawns before and the spawns now.

The spawns before made the game boring as not much happened.

The spawns now are overwhelming. I was out driving last night with my spotify in the background through my iPhone hooked up to my car stereo. I drove with Pokemon Go launched and every 2-5 seconds I could hear a pokemon spawning through my stereo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always think about the issues that could arise in the future.

You may feel as though it was "bump and bruises", but for all you know there is some lasting damage in your neck or back.

If you work a job where you're on the computer all day, a neck injury could be catastrophic as you'll have a sore neck from it being in a certain position all day.

If you work a labour job, a back injury won't be fun to deal with.

If I were you, and if you can afford to wait, I would wait to see what arises in a couple of months.

These adjusters rely on getting you to sign a release ASAP before any lasting injuries arise.

In a past family case, my family member waited the entire statute of limitations, and when the notice of claim was submitted the insurance company didn't bother fighting them anymore and just paid the entire amount asked. All the lasting injuries were laid out, backed up by the family doctor and medical records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically which vacuums?

The built in ones aren't that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact the ministry.

No employer in Ontario can circumvent minimum wage.

You also can't sign away this right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since iOS 10.0.2 none of my devices automatically update their apps. Is it the same for you guys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a iPhone 6S, and one of the newer iPads.

My moms iPhone 6S has the same issue.

All of my mobile devices (iPhone, iPad) used to automatically update their apps when the device was:

1) Above a certain battery percentage and on Wifi.

2) Plugged in, and on wifi.

They used to immediately update the moment I plugged in the devices to a power source.

But since 10.0.2, they have stopped updating automatically.

Now they do automatically update, but it's not immediately anymore, it seems to happen randomly 5-8 hours after being plugged in. 

I don't know if this is an intentional change? If so it seems a little silly as I preferred the apps being up to date ASAP as the device hit wifi.

Anyone else have this issue still? I thought they would fix it with 10.1, but now i'm assuming it's intentional.

Here are some other encountering the issue:

https://discussions.apple.com/thread/7685593?start=0 tstart=0

https://discussions.apple.com/thread/7668602?start=0 tstart=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it came up clean at purchase, and it comes up clean now.

How can the current car owner be on the hook for anything?

I understand common law enforces the idea of which what you do not have you cannot give, but the seller took out a title loan. Therefore why doesn't the title loan company sue the seller for damages?

The buyer did his diligence and should be clear through good faith and diligence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No we have it worse. 

Kamloops and Kelowna are 4-6 hour drives away from Vancouver. Places like that are not part of our bubble. It's not like Ontario where you have everything a bit more spread out. 
Areas like Vancouver Island and the Sunshine Coast seen a surge of $200k to $500k. 

Metro Vancouver has become unaffordable. 

This includes all of the surrounding municipalities. 

Go compare housing prices before they put in the 15% foreign investor tax. 

We had Vancouverites moving from Vancouver to Toronto because it was more affordable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vancouver passed a provincial law putting a 15% tax on foreigners purchasing homes. It's to prevent them from flipping homes. 

We had Chinese (primarily) hedge funds coming here buying homes en masse. Then flipping them a month later for $100k to $500k more. 

Since then, they are now going to Toronto to do the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I clicked on the Election Tracker. Noticed that in the Details tab, it shows r/asktrumpsupporters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't it show this sub as the official trump hub for Trump information?

It had r/hillaryclinton and r/asktrumpsupporters. 

In r/hillaryclinton there is zero criticism of her. 

In r/asktrumpsupporters they have criticism of Trump. 

It's as if reddit is part of this media bias against Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think Toronto is bad, just imagine Vancouver. 

The properties alone are worth $1 million to $1.6 million. Then factor in the cost of the actual house. 

Closing costs for houses over $1 million are over $300k. As it's required to have 30% down for houses over a million. Not to mention land transfer taxes, etc. 

The buyers deposit is around $50k.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are aware of the issue. 

I can't find the forum post where they confirm that they can reproduce the issue. But they did respond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His son is also having repeated unprotected sex with Catherine Zeta-Jones.

If my son brought home a prime Catherine Zeta-Jones, I know I succeeded as a father and mentor.

http://media1.santabanta.com/full1/Global%20Celebrities(F)/Catherine%20Zeta%20Jones/catherine-zeta-jones-31a.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the target demographic for this product hot women in their 30s?

I would have thought obese people would need a product like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys always have such a clear, comprehensive, and non-biased approach to reviews. 

I may upgrade to the PS4 Pro once more titles take advantage of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because banks already get tax breaks by being classified as a bank. 

Both democrats and republicans agree with these tax breaks. On the flip side to maintain bank status you need to follow certain protocols. 

Quid pro quo.

Banks typically back whoever they have in their back pocket. They are bi partisan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lobbying the judicial system and lobbying the executive/legislative system are completely different things. 

No judge or corporate law firm would risk being caught even entertaining the idea. The integrity of the law is the only first and foremost expectation on the judicial systems plate. 

Which means interpreting and implementing the law without "prejudice no favour". Not making it.

For the government, and its representatives they are expected to represent the public. Which means making laws and passing budgets. 
Unfortunately, businesses and corporations fall under entities. While lobbying is bullshit, politicians need both financial and public support, reelections are expensive, even for incumbents. 

The courts don't need financial support because they are appointed. So if they enter into this lobbying and backroom bribery, it's only for self enrichment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 01:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judges have no lost love for insurance companies either. 

While the layman may be overwhelmed by contract ambiguity, judges can see through the insurance providers games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 08:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duke has this sickly, maniacal, evil look to him.

Even when he smiles he looks maniacal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love medics who put healing and rezzing over killing the other team. 

I love even more when medics wage a one man war against multiple enemies just to rez their dead comrades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of women do this. 

Go Dutch if you suspect she's using you for a free meal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea why they are fighting legalization? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot Twist:

He's the pool cleaner.

Who prides himself in all things related to pool hygiene. Including but not limited to, keeping Alpacas out of the pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be the first seat taken on the airship?

I've never gotten it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a blanket response.

You also don't reside in the grey area.

When it comes to ethics and the behaviour of police officers, I'm pretty sure their code of conduct and due process isn't teetering on the "grey area".

As I responded to the other guy, I expect police officers to condone themselves in a way that upholds the integrity of the law, and the protection and respect for society while on duty. Whether the photo was supposed to be public is irrelevant.

And as I stated earlier, if this was a dead child who died in a car accident, would you be singing the same tune as though this shouldn't be viewed with empathy?

This idea that you're in the grey is just an excuse to stand back and let the chips fall where they may. I rather the chips don't fall where they may, and the police treat both dead and alive people with a modicum of respect and decency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So thinking straight means that it somehow is acceptable to take a picture smiling while thumbing up over a deceased body?

The point is that while it may not be "illegal"; or a touchy subject along the grey area of morally acceptable:

a) many people would not want a police officer standing over their loved one, taking a picture smiling while thumbing up. They would question as to why this is occurring. They would also file a complaint, in which that complaint would be investigated, or the police organization would face scrutiny.

b) secondly, for the people emotionally involved with the event, then yes, it needs to be addressed in a manner that is ethical. There are ethics boards with people who are more aligned in the matter for a non-biased decision that a couple of redditors.

Lastly, anonymity is great on the internet isn't it? I don't see anyone out there publicly stating that it's acceptable behaviour, advocating the right to behave anyway they want.

Personally for me, I expect peace officers and law enforcement to behave in a way that upholds the integrity of the law, and respect and protection of society. Whether this photo was not *meant* to be public is besides the point. When you're on duty, be respectful, that includes to dead bodies.

The question is, if this was the dead body of a child, who was ejected from a car during a car crash, would he be doing the same thing? And if he was caught, would there be more public uproar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be singing a different tune if pictures arose of a "professional" who is employed to discredit the severity of a corpse was thumbs upping over the body of your loved one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed a lot more teamwork in BF1. 

Last night my random squad worked together to capture and hold "C" on operations. It allowed the rest of the team to focus on A and B.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
