<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6752</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so if you get 0 crowns, you don't get a chest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you will be included in the chest if you join 1 day prior the clan chest starts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clan Screen being blank and people having issues with clan battle (starting it and etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No? I tested this and it doesn't.

The elixir of both of you is separate, however, any effect (spells) you place in the arena affect both of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different bug fix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 33GB of 256GB: http://imgur.com/a/Zf4Vx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://reddit.com/r/apple/comments/60llce/15_mbptb_now_being_sold_refurbished_from_apple/?ref=search_posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk Against Humanity by Launch LLC
https://appsto.re/us/ymD1gb.i </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple didn't cut them, just FYI. 

Read this: https://www.reddit.com/r/apple/comments/612ald/marco_arment_on_twitter_dont_blame_workflow_or/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, this sub is amazing. We brought you from -11 to 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, why is that the Redditor above should be a "normal" human being and not a Goth? Is there something wrong with being a Goth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP asked because of this: http://reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV/comments/60woce/tunables_update_in_gtaonline_duplicated_vehicles/dfa7ufw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who were curious like me: http://reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV/comments/60woce/tunables_update_in_gtaonline_duplicated_vehicles/dfa7ufw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. Don't. 

Get some help. PM me. Let me know what you need. I can't replace what you have lost, but I can help you out to get yourself back in your feet. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a different sub.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Base model, 13" TB version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can help. In fact, they do it without even asking you \\\_()\_/  (unless you tell them you aren't setting up the phone there)

And yes, the same card will work. They both take the sams SIM size (nano-SIM I believe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Workflow's price is now set to free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah. Good buy Apple. Hopefully we can see a deeper integration in the system with Worflow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although it says that, people still have issues even well past the date the update was written (same day of the article) Thus, the reason of my post. 

Article is from 2014, examples of people having issues: 

[1](https://www.reddit.com/r/applehelp/comments/37rveg/cannot_add_card_to_apple_pay/)

[2](https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/odd-apple-pay-card-not-added-registration-problem.1925969/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a smart buy, and you will definitely get updates as long as the 6S. No need to worry about 3D Touch stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most CCs will let you remove them, so call the three three credit bureaus and open a dispute. All you have to do is tell them the situation and that the primary cardholder is making late payments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. Get yourself an iPhone in **Jump on Demand** and upgrade whenever you want, 3 times a year. I was in the same boat as you and the program saved me. 

Call in on Friday, and tell them you want a phone in Jump on Demand (7+ Red), pay down payment if applicable, and receive it.

In September, when the stores get the iPhones, go in, tell them you want to upgrade on Demand to the 7S/8, and give them the 7+ and enjoy the new iPhone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure he doesn't know your ID? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What carrier do you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple's Secure Element has a flaw introduced since iOS 8 and it hasn't been fixed yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Sorry for shitty title. I didn't find another way to express this in a headline.)

Allow me to explain. 

For short, AP will be Apple Pay, SE will be Secure Element (not iPhone SE. iPhone SE will be referred to the phone). 

Remember when Tim Cook told you to not blink or you are going to miss it in 2014? He was referring to AP. Apple's take on mobile payments. It is cool and everything, but how exactly does it work?

Well, think of it like this. 

**1.**You phone sends encrypted data when you are adding a card to AP, to Apple. 

**2.**Apple decrypts that data to know which bank you have, and encrypts it again and sends the data to your bank. This data includes everything about your phone (model, phone #, IMEI, etc etc). 

**3.**Once your bank gets that data, they send it to Apple, encrypted, and Apple directly sends it to your device. This data has the Device Account Number and dynamic security codes. 

**4.** Now, once is in your device, this data is sent to the SE. The SE will save your card's info to allow you to use AP. **Note that the SE is separated from iOS or WOS.**

When you are going to pay in stores, the NFC will wake up the phone, to tell you to authenticate yourself. The Secure Enclave comes in to verify your fingerprint and will return a "True, this is me bro" message to the NFC. The NFC will then communicate with the SE to pull the card you authorized the payment on, and process the payment. 

Looks simple enough right?

Now, this is where the bug comes in. Did you notice the bold sentence above? That's where the bug comes in. 

When you restore your device, or your bank deletes your virtual card, the OS (iOS or WOS) tells the SE to forget the card's data. In some cases, you even receive a confirmation email from your bank saying that your card was removed. 

But the thing is that the SE fails to delete your card in some cases. When you are setting up the device again, and you are going to set up the same card the SE fails to delete, you will have a message similar to [this.](https://9to5mac.files.wordpress.com/2014/12/img_8932.jpg?quality=82 w=2500 h=0#038;strip=all w=1000). This message appears in between steps 3 and 4. 

Now basically your card is banned from Apple Pay in your device. If you grab another device, and use that same card and add it to Apple Pay, it works. But it won't do with the phone with the problem no matter how much you try. You can restore, setup as new, from backup, whatever, and the card won't be deleted from your SE.



The only solution is to replace your phone, effectively giving you a new SE that doesn't have an idea of your card's info. Unless Apple comes with an update to its restoring process. 


_____

In my personal experience, I had this issue with iOS 8 on an iPhone 6, iOS 9 on a 6S and now on 10 with an iPhone 7+. 

In iOS 8, my debit card couldn't be added to Apple Pay. My bank says everything is good. Apple says everything is good. I just dealt with it until before iOS 9 came out when that's where I had a theory what the problem was. Apple swapped it out and it worked. iOS 9 came, I got the 6S, and the issue happens with my Credit Card a few months in. Apple swaps it out and works as fine. Now I have an issue with a different card, on iOS 10, on my 7+. 

Apple's customer service is trying to give me the run-around as they don't know what the hell I am talking about (I don't blame them), and I am having difficulties reaching an engineer in Apple so that the issue is fixed. Hopefully sharing this in a public forum will help me contact an engineer who can look into this. 

Here is a link to a 2014 article: https://9to5mac.com/2014/12/31/apple-pay-glitch/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the iPhone is available to everyone, everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and made sure it deleted all my stuff

The alert reads: 

"What would you like to do with the data?"

"Delete, or Keep"

Are you sure you pressed Delete and not keep? It can be a common mistake if you mistap.

Another question, when you logged in to this account again, did you Merge the data, or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. The black one looks sexy. Maybe I will Jump to the S8 from the 7+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: When you receive a notification, check if the app's icon is rounded or square. If it is rounded, that means you can tap on that notification to go to said app. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is square, that means the app who sent you the notification doesn't have an Apple Watch app, or that it is uninstalled. 

Link to image (pay attention to the icon mask): http://imgur.com/a/nO0lD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  how do you know rbrenelli is in Brazil?

Posted in another thread: http://i.imgur.com/rGfGmdl.png  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The app is free, the $9.99 is an IAP to unlock the full game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is hilarious when it happens to people. 

I imagine them shaking copying and pasting,  and typing to be fast to be first and get karma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is out in the USA. You are in Brazil. So technically, it isn't a lie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *woosh*

Let me explain it. 

French Fries usually have salt. The image show you fries that doesn't have salt, and the Redditor told you to add your salt in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  bye bye internet!

They actually deleted their account...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple's Secure Element has a bug introduced since iOS 8 and it hasn't been fixed yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? Is it a social network of its own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this. I'm interested to see the source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None, use the stock QuickTime app. If you are new to the Mac, it is in the Launchpad, in the Other folder (only folder there) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, do you think Apple will make a product and not put it to the test themselves?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they did, but they still let us Like Posts, Share or Quick reply to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon Music for iOS updated with support for CarPlay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Face up. All notifications come on the Watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the $49.99 version have to pay for the subscription? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple releases iTunes 12.6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changelog:

"Rent once, watch anywhere. Now you can enjoy your iTunes movie rentals across your devices with iOS 10.3 and TVOS 10.2. This update also includes minor app and performance improvements" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the thing, you see me using all of those to protect the ebarbs, but the opponent can still counter them. 

I can use a Spirit, Log or Zap to cover against a Pekka? Right? No. I struggle with a Pekka.

Can I those cards to protect them against a Wiz + Ice Golem? Or Valk + Ice Golem? 

Point being, is that there are still counters to the ebarbs regardless of what the ebarb users carry. 

Edit: I don't mean it for you, but for people who struggle with them and get triggered when people use them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, now I see it. Sorry, your second sentence makes it look like the mugger should have a knife to mug the character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a mugger.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean that there isn't a restocking fee in the Apple Store. Stores like T-Mobile charge you like $50 or something.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who hurt you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a level 9... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think is the gold. OP got too much gold from the challenge  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody doesn't know how to counter them. Aw. 

Edit: And the downvotes why? 99.99% of the people criticizing the Ebarb and its users don't know how to counter them and that's why they complain. As an ebarb user, I can assure you that there is counters. Hard counters. Pekka for example. Wizard + Ice Golem is another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is this an artist stream count comparison and not a comparison between the two services? Okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you want to see the Red iPhone 7's box ahead of release, here is a pic of it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, personally, was expecting something extra like the Jet Black

http://i.imgur.com/sDyNf9u.jpg 

Credit: @mkbhd on Twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A build didn't come for iOS yesterday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I can tell, but it makes sense why should one think that. 

10 elixir against 20 is not fair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's yours? I also run an eBarb + Dart Goblin deck.

Here is mine:

http://i.imgur.com/5CykhUq.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Once I got my Mac, I barely use it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it won't take it because Apple places an [imaginary hold](http://imgur.com/a/mdltw) in your account to verify that you have money. If you don't, then you Apple can't verify that the card is valid and with money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically your only options is the phone you have (6S, 6S Plus, or the SE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the Messages Setting on the iPhone and turn on Text Message Forwarding to the iPad Air 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is not an Snapchat clone. Is a video recording app to share videos elsewhere.

I think the press release is pretty clear on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe so. The Gold came on the 5S and is here to stay. 

The Red iPods came out with the 5th Gen and they haven't stopped selling it and the 6th gen also got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, now I understand Will Little ^^^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we forgot about April Fools. We just thought April 1st was a nice day (new month, 1st day, and etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is right. Thing is that you don't know how to counter it and that's why you need a nerf. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is her exact actions/movements?

Does she just come up to you and spit? Does she say anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Apple ID and password


Seu ID e senha da Apple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hit 4k. My last opponent before I got there just didn't put any card at all. I won. 

Then I went to his/her clan to see what was up, as the game never told me they left the match and they told me they had this glitch. Felt sorry for them as they were trying to get to 4k too and they couldn't do shit to stop me from winning. 

Hope CR fixes this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First experience was with the first jailbreak ever made. 

My cousin jailbroke his iPhone and I got exposed to the jailbreak world and kept doing it to my devices since then. I've basically seen how jailbreak grew all these years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo.

The app even shows you this: http://i.imgur.com/TvpWZxC.png 

And telling Siri for 23h and 59m worked: http://i.imgur.com/qXbzVSV.png  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for taking the words right out of my mouth. OP is just BS'ing at this point and blogspamming his blog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source?

Edit: Other than this shitty article of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has it been confirmed it is Oreo or you are just guessing?

Edit: What even is this list? The OP1 didn't get Nougat (And Marshmallow too, can anyone confirm?) and will get Oreo? Tf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was the only one who put the app in the Finance folder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Just, no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that "JBME of 9.3" and the one that was cancelled doesn't install Cydia for you. You have to install it yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because those horns are loud and we are loud as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck was that? Anyone knows what happened afterwards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that makes sense. Thanks for the clarification  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the z at the end </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of logic is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I got it"

Unexpected and precious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will take anything you have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There has been nothing officially from Apple saying that it's 1 year

People working in Apple (Senior Advisor) are getting the emails from the higher ups. Senior Advisors in Reddit (in /r/apple) are confirming this. 

If this were to be a glitch, rest assure Apple will patch it in a second </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fake: http://i.imgur.com/NI8Hw0o.jpg 

Posted by him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enter your serial here: https://checkcoverage.apple.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://9to5mac.com/2017/03/17/apple-extends-applecare-purchase-window-to-1-year-for-iphone/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That changed yesterday. Everyone has a year now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is a feature  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  purchased in April 2016.


Buy Apple Care for $100 and use one accidental damage (so pay $100 to fix it). If something happens again, then pay $99 again.

If screen breaks it will be $29. Manufacturing defects will be covered until 2018

Do it over the phone tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like it was removed. Now it came back to life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you do the test? Did you do all steps required? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already posted 15 mins ago: http://reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/603tam/news_untetherer_for_ios_10x_it_will_be_package_in/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mario is at the 56th place of the Free category and no where to be found on the grossing list. USA store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, I forgot that was there . Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone is about to get a lot of hate...


A LOT of hate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay to play? That doesn't make any sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 27 now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As opposed to what's shown in the screenshot, my Watch Serial isn't qualified to add Apple Care+

I will call in to see what they say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, please Apple, do this for the Watch.

I missed the 60 days of the Watch by 2 days and I couldn't add Apple Care to my Watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. That's what I do since we can never get 50% of all players to vote kick the second random that comes in.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. What a comeback  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this pre-nerf? They should spawn horizontally, but with the furnace there, they might have glitched out and spawned vertically  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw 2 monsters and their dad with a 14 over their heads today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that happened to someone in this sub.

Report it to Supercell. Get his name tag, screenshot everything and send it to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. When you suck. By no means it isn't because you got a bad deck like 4 tanks and shit support that don't work with the tanks.

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grazzie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with these eyes:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So I'm just wondering if there was something I didn't do

You good. You vote- kicked as instructed.

The thing is that, if you are in a session with 17 people, including yourself, and a random comes in, that will be 18 right? 

Well, to kick that random, you will need 9 people to vote kick them. And the kick has a cooldown of 15 mins, so is hard to kick randoms who keep joining with that timer and the 50% vote kick stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ezy" when you get good decks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fucking stupid can people be? 

He could've gotten away with the bag easily. But no. He decided to have more charges against him.

He stole a city/state truck, killed someone, crashed into cars and shit (Can you get charged for this?) and still got arrested. 

I would take 1 charge rather than 3+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I got a little excited when Rondon pitched close to his face. I thought both benches would clear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah. That pitch was high and close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few, or a lot of things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reyes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you make them videos so fast?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dominicans, I got some pitchforks. You guys want some? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odor should punch Bautista again to see if it helps him hit balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally above where you wrote your comment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know the umpires for this game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you forgot to tell me that I forgot about HTC's "poor use of space" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that makes sense. I'm fairly new here and learning how the sub works. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I know. Is it something to do with not promoting the site here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what's the issue with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDW:

Price: $749

2-) Bigger than all phones (Pixel XL, G6, iPhone 7+, S7 Edge, Note 7), 8mm Thick.

3-) Camera's Hump is an example of bad use of space

4-) No headphone jack in a huge phone

5-) 3k mAH battery on a huge phone is "a little bit off"

6-) HTC could have put on-screen buttons, but instead they chose a small capacitive buttons. On a big phone.

7-) Not water resistant

8-) Lightbleed under the front facing camera

9-) Speaker isn't the loudest

10-) No wireless charging

3-10 are all examples of "bad use of space"


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDW:

Price: $749

2-) Bigger than all phones (Pixel XL, G6, iPhone 7+, S7 Edge, Note 7), 8mm Thick.

3-) Camera's Hump is an example of bad use of space

4-) No headphone jack in a huge phone

5-) 3k mAH battery on a huge phone is "a little bit off"

6-) HTC could have put on-screen buttons, but instead they chose a small capacitive buttons. On a big phone.

7-) Not water resistant

8-) Lightbleed under the front facing camera

9-) Speaker isn't the loudest

10-) No wireless charging

3-10 are all examples of "bad use of space"


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that was an actual tweet, McDonald's Twitter account "was compromised".

https://twitter.com/McDonaldsCorp/status/842380484260818945  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even when McDonald's is tired of BS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I keep waiting for it I will turn into a skeleton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EB user here, listen to this guy/gal, they know their shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ProCam](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/procam-4-manual-camera-raw/id730712409?mt=8) allows you to switch between the lenses manually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly because some people (like me) like to compare phone sizes to other people. We can also deduce that the update can bring small fixes (if it is 20mb for instance), or huge ones + features (100mb), or if it is a full update candidate (GM) (1GB) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of iOS 10.3 to Developers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah.

Kind of big too. 470.8mb, 7+ 

(If you are commenting update size, do so under my comment please to avoid comment spam for the same "topic") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tombstone + Musk: Postition matters. Act fast. Don't pay too much attention to negative trades. 

Golem + Musket: Good on 2x elixir. People use Golem on offense but forget to use him in defense. His HP and Death Damage help

Work on leveling up your cards as well. The Musket specially  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? Or you are saying this base on experience ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, basing it off your flair, you use a Golem deck.

What is your deck? Post their levels too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think bots are banned in this sub. Or it got banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, my phone isn't dirty, but just curious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here with an iPhone 7/+ rinse their phone when dirty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen people rinse their S7 and IP67 rated phones with no issue. I'm wondering if you guys do it once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an ebarb user (pre and post nerf), agreed with everything 

My EB barely touch the tower if the opponent plays well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
