<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 19:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting a Submissions 101 video - bold move indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 19:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say learn it at least a little so you can more easily defeat it. If you know what they're going for, it's extremely easy to reverse-engineer the RG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 19:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent question. Though I can't be sure without seeing you in action, here are some potential problems causing you trouble, along with solutions. 

Scenario: You have an underhook and a crossface, but your crossface lacks pressure because he's kicking away super hard. That's fine - instead of wedging your shoulder under his chin, use your forehead instead. **Essentially you're having distance management problems - you're trying to use a crossface when a better tool for that "range" might be the crown of your head.** If you still cant drive enough pressure through your head, use your outside forearm instead. You just need to create some kind of frame - use whatever frame is appropriate for the distance. When he gets tired of dealing with that pressure and/or gasses out his legs, if he lets go for even a second you'll slip right into a better crossface. Ryan Hall describes this super well in one of his DVDs... either Arm Triangles or Passing the Guard I think, or both. Also watch how Roger Gracie does HG pressure passing. 

The other principle here is that whenever someone is hanging on to you for dear life, they are tying themselves up too. When someone really extends their lockdown hard, it ties up their hips and makes it very easy for you to feel what they're trying to do and reverse-engineer it. For example, it becomes easier to just step your foot right out of the lockdown and do some of the silly stuff you can see from Erik Paulsen here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TpR6bG60cDM . Or sometimes I'll just gable-grip around their knees, sprawl and pass easily. I.e., if he insists on keeping you too low to get a crossface, I'll box his hips instead. 

Now the real answer to your question: **He really should not be able to defend the crossface, much less whip you up, if you have a good underhook and heavy hips. If that's happening to you, your hips are just not heavy enough.** You need to do a forceful pelvic thrust straight to the mat and at the same time curl your legs to the sky and pop your hips into extension. The underhook holds your upper body in place as you adjust your hips where you need them to be. You have such a mechanical advantage from here that no lift should be possible. 

For example, watch how Marcelo does a 100% standard pressure half guard pass against Epstein's lockdown here. He gets upper-body grips, drops hip pressure, walks Epstein's hips to the side, and finishes with a white-belt-standard half guard pressure pass. Nothing fancy at all: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2mc9-DXhCLA#t=124 . The only trick you might miss here is that Marcelo is jacking Epstein's near arm away from his body as he walks his left leg out, allowing Marcelo to settle his weight in the space between Epstein's Right knee and elbow. That's the difference between being in a dangerous half guard, vs. being essentially in side control with your leg incidentally trapped in a shitty half guard. No lockdown can save you from there.  **To your original question: Once your weight is safely settled to the side, even if your leg is still trapped in lockdown you can drop a monster crossface without worrying about the whip-up. If he whips you up, it should actually align more weight above your crossface.**

Last note just to be sure: If you're giving up the underhook a lot, #1: don't do that, and #2: work on your whizzer/darce and reverse-kesa-style half guard passes that involve switching the hips. These often allow you to just get the underhook back and thus resume the shoulder-of-justice attack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 15:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question! The key for the top guy is to relax and be patient. I mean literally relax your muscles and become dead weight. 

When he tries to "whip up" to unbalance but doesn't have an underhook, that should actually *increase* the weight in your crossfire arm because he's pulling you toward it. You're anchored to that point bc your shoulder is wedged under his chin. 

He'll quickly find that escape route actually made him more miserable and try to build frames with his arms instead,  but it's too late: if your top HG posture is good there will be no space for him to get his hands inside safely. Slowly but surely  if you relax, your leg will have been incrementally slipping out of the lockdown this whole time until it becomes ineffective. 

The concept of wedging under someone's neck/chin while passing turns up in lots of passing DVDs for top players, but it's hard to explain without showing tou.

To be fair, I do use the lockdown briefly sometimes to relieve pressure if I'm getting crossfaced, but I pull them South and away instead of North via whip up in that case. And I only use it long enough to make frames and get to a better posture where my hips are mobile and head free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 06:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree on all this. Also, helps me to think about getting to chill dog as quickly as possible. I feel that is safer than standard RG, for me at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 06:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yeah, you're not wrong: some people definitely use the term that way. I've heard wrestlers use the same term for both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 21:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which one are you wondering about? here's rob kahn choking someone unconscious with his crossface: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c_3OqoLfQnU

many people (especially new people) will tap to a proper stack or cradle as well, due to chest compression, lack of spinal/rib flexibility, or even just claustrophobia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> keep showing up. if you need motivation, watch some interviews with Caio Terra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good idea to use it as an open mat. pick technique videos from top people (mginaction suggested below) and drill the ever-loving shit out of them. find a like-minded partner. 

drill with resistance, drill without resistance, drill sequences where one flows into another, drill where the other guy has boxing gloves and can hit you. DRILL THE SHIT OUT OF a couple basic techniques.

and do a shit-ton of movement drills on your own: shrimp, sit out, backrolls, granby rolls, etc. get to the point where you're shrimping out of bed in the morning without realizing it. 

then, when you can train at a real gym, you'll have a huge leg up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 18:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> instructor got exactly what he asked for. one thing i love about grappling is you never know which guys might turn out to be badasses, much less how MUCH of a badass they might be. 

it's very empirical - you can test your skills constantly in a way that's just not as feasible with striking due to safety and other issues. therefore people get humbled - the ones who are okay with getting constantly humbled are the ones who keep showing up, and thus get better. 

hopefully this was a helpful learning experience for the instructor - maybe he'll start taking classes in judo/wrestling/bjj/catch to see how deep the rabbit hole goes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 16:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using certain 10p techniques for almost a decade and have mad respect for some of them (Geo). But I truly hate the koolaid attitude.

I cant deny the guilty pleasure of tapping someone with a crossface when they lockdown my leg, or with a stack/cradle when they rubber guard. 

The shit isn't magic, guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 00:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just like to say that I had a very similar path and agree with pretty much all of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 19:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best answer IMO. "Kill them with kindness" and keep rolling. No response needed.

If they really persist, I might follow it up with a "cool story, bro" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 17:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. New white belts do this all the time: he thought he was in a position where he "shouldn't" have to tap, so he tried to Hulk it out and grunted like a crazy person. People aren't laughing at his pain, they're laughing at stupidity. If you make crazy noises in a BJJ match they consider it a verbal tap and stop the fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 05:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My interpretation was that the guy on bottom spazzed and tried to hulk it out instead of tapping, hence the laughter. I could be wrong though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 04:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice verbal tap there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 04:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Roberts vs. Victor Silverio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 15:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody have a link to the full unedited match from the kumite? Obligatory "Lloyd sucks" caveat goes here.

Hoping to study this video because I, too, want a closed guard that makes my opponents rage quit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 04:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious answer: might be small cuts in your mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't defend chokes with your face"

Seriously though it's legal if it remotely looks like theyre going for a choke. Lots of various cranks have plausible deniability if they look somewhat like a choke. Incidental cranks while going for a choke are totally legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 03:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It highly depends on the gym. Ive trained at a few places where the blue promotion represents that they have trained consistently, and really didnt reflect technical mastery. 

My current gym is more like your first: the bar for blue is so high that iit takes ages to get, and by that time t's  very unlikely  one of our blues would not have run into leglock defenses at least a couple of times.

Ultimately though it's  entirely  up to your prof. Respect his decision and do your best to earn it in your own eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 03:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is absolutely a great match and Eddie undoubtedly has some great and technical jiujitsu. However, it's highly misleading to say Eddie's style represents more modern BJJ or is somehow more technical. 


This might be controversial but I think 10PJJ is quite old scool in the philosophy behind it, at least compared to what most people consider "modern" bjj. For example, both gracie jj and 10PJJ really emphasize designing techniques with striking in mind. Both involve really tying up your opponent as a result, and for good or ill, both end up not emphasizing mobility as much as modern jj players. I say this more as a fan of 10PJJ than gracie jj.


If you want to see the most technical and best representatives of modern BJJ, a more accurate example would be Rafael Mendes.


I like a lot of things about Eddie and 10p, but this idea that he represents an important sea change in bjj is just not accurate. His ideas are very innovative and some work great, but to be honest they have not been any more revolutionary than details we have gotten from lesser known folks like Gustavo machado.


As much as I love eddie, the biggest thing he has influenced in my experience is making new white belts exponentially more annoying every time his name hits the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Web scraping plus agglomerative clustering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 18:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all,

I'm absolutely brand new to Python, but would like to design a fairly basic applied challenge to guide myself as I learn. **CAVEAT**: This idea is well beyond my ability at this point. It's more of a motivator to look forward to in the future. So on to the idea...

Let's say I have a huge list of URLs I have collected over several years (spoiler: I do have this, and it is genuinely huge. On the order of thousands). They are completely unsorted.

Let's further say that, *as an end product* I'd like to have these automatically clustered into categories by topic. E.g., some of these links might point to machine learning articles, while others point to Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu techniques. 

A manual sort would involve re-opening each article, then taking a stab at categorizing them into topics (e.g., BJJ and Machine Learning).

To my untrained mind, the **automated** process would look something like this:

1) Plug all of the URLs into a program that automatically crawls each of them and scrapes all of (or a random sample of) the words. (Maybe the program that crawls them is different than the program that scrapes the data, maybe not.) 

2) That program spits out data on each link that can be plugged into yet another program - like an agglomerative clustering algorithm - that automatically clusters them into categories. E.g., the algorithm would be trained to recognize that articles talking about "double-leg takedowns" and "armbars" should be in the same cluster (jiu-jitsu) while articles talking about "neuroscience" and "bioinformatics" should be in another separate cluster. 

3) Finally, I'm sure there are lots of off-the-shelf programs that will show me the final visualization in various forms. 

Can anyone let me know if I'm on the right track here? If so, could you point me to resources? Again, I know it's beyond my ability at this point, but I'd like to have something concrete to look forward to. 

**TL;DR: Can I use Python to automatically crawl and cluster a list of URLs by topic?**

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 04:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few reasons:

1. he is currently signed to an mma promotion, unlike most other bjj guys (it's an open secret that many Brazilian pure bjj guys juice), and professional fighters get tested

2. he is known for having an extremely strong sense of justice, even to a fault. See his open letter after the TLI scandal for example. Like him or not, this is not the type of person who cheats.

3. Dude is skinny as hell. His thighs look like my forearms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the heads up. looks like you got downvoted, but what you say about the patch is true (or at least I've heard it many times before). 

it's not how i personally would run a gym, but if i'm in another person's house i respect their rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Gracie Barra gyms allow drop-ins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 15:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Googled and got mixed answers. 

Do they allow drop-ins?
Is it fine if i show with a plain white gi or will i have to use one of their branded ones? sounds like this varies.

BTW I plan to call or email ahead for drop-ins and you should too, regardless of the school, as a courtesy

EDIT: Thanks for answers all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 15:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The people I paid to help me with this shameless no-effort money grab are totally at fault here guys."

Fucking pathetic. Actually, the people who filmed and edited this were probably laughing at him too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 17:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> context: 
http://www.bloodyelbow.com/2013/3/5/4066506/team-lloyd-irvin-sex-abuse-cult-power-medal-chasers-exodus
http://assets.sbnation.com/assets/2272155/Jordon_Schultz_s_statement.pdf

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 17:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> google Marcelo Garcia's "baseball slide" sweep - it's similar to what you have in mind. 

Completely unsolicited advice: I think I know why you're getting downvoted. In the past I wasted a lot of time wondering "would this particular scenario work?" And there is some value in drilling stuff like this. But as I got better, I realized that spending more time thinking about principles actually helped more (e.g., am I using strong posture, frames and structure during my butterfly sweeps?) To me that type of visualization is more helpful because ideas like posture and frames translate to more positions than just the butterfly sweep. But do what works for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP: I would just like to add that you seem to be getting a lot of downvotes for this post, which I think is unfair. Fighting and rolling with strikes were critical to the evolution of BJJ as we know it today. 

To answer your question, it completely depends on the gym. Your BJJ will definitely suffer overall if you go to a gym with shit grappling instructors, of course. 

But assuming you like both styles equally, I advise you to go to whichever gym has better instructors. 

E.g., if you go from training BJJ with Cobrinha to training MMA with a random blue belt, you just won't get the same level of grappling instruction. But if the MMA instructor is legitimately a better grappler, then do that. Just find the best coach that works for you. 

EDIT: /u/MaedaMilitia does a better job explaining below </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 15:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> training pure striking, i'd say it's a stretch that would improve your ground game (at most it will improve your footwork for wrestling/judo from the feet.) 

on the other hand, **rolling with strikes** did help me. it taught me to remove small moments of hesitation, e.g., where you think about doing an escape with perfect technique but then lose the window of opportunity. those little pauses can become ingrained in your ground game, and that's not good (folks like Ryan Hall often say it's better to have perfect timing than hesitate by thinking about "perfect" technique)

in regular bjj you can often just wait for the opponent to make a mistake, and capitalize on that to escape. but that's just exploiting the ruleset, as Ryan often says. you don't have that luxury when getting hit. note that i did not say spazzing or thrashing around, rather it's about trying one thing after another without pauses. just keep moving. 

when strikes are involved and you're taking shots to the face, you will be amazed at the good technique your brain will come up with, even if they're very light shots. if you take that mindset of removing pauses back to regular bjj, i guarantee you'll see improvements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLI style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 18:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> adding to this: it's not the arm that ultimately cuts off blood flow, it's more the shoulder. So the shoulder can be pushed into the neck even if the arm isnt across, and the triangle will still work. "Arm across" is the advice they give new guys to help them understand and make it work, but it's not the only way. 

in this particular video, the legs are triangled more over the neck and humerus, so the far side carotid actually would be getting blocked by the arm - except these guys are extremely skinny so there was space. chokes are NOT all about the squeeze, they're more about eliminating space (it only takes a few lb/in^2 of pressure to close the arteries - if they aren't closed, its because there's space) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 18:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who would downvote this? an honest question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 19:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was **not** able to do a triangle choke

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 17:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SECONDED. Just watching her on YouTube has really sharpened up my open guard game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 16:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on your threshold for "under the radar," but i'd say murilo santana for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 16:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 21:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so much better dude. I'm sorry i said the original version made my brain bleed. in my defense I was drunk at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 00:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two great competitors. i have always loved eduardo's turtlemaster counter-fighting style - it is so fun to watch, almost like a sport jiu-jitsu version of drunken boxing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 22:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I remember correctly, the plaque said


the plaque said


plaque </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 19:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my other comment. If I remember correctly, the plaque said this was worn by the headsman who swung the axe. So more of an executioner than a torturer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 19:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the title is accurate. I was just at the Tower of London and saw this - it was an executioner's (headsman's) mask. Not the mask of a torturer. 

EDIT: Others below me have the right answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 05:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely great info in there but sadly I'm still capped at 1gb for some unknown reason. 

Im wondering if it's related to ENBoost or something like that? Or if I changed something back in the Sheson era? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Troubleshooting memory patches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 04:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preface: I have read the super epic guide in detail 

My question is, how do I troubleshoot memory allocation? My TESV used to allocate 2.5 gigs and above, but ever since the new release of SKSE it will only allocate 1 gig, after which it crashes. 

My SKSE ini is properly set up to use the memory patch, so I think there must be something else I have set up that is overriding the correct SKSE settings. 

Where in my data files should I look? E.g., Wrye Bash tweaks? Other dlls or loaders? 

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a limit to NPC aggro? (Tundra Defense issues) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 23:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running Tundra Defense, and for some reason with higher numbers of guards and raiders, they simply won't aggro each other at all, and nobody will appear hostile. 

At middling numbers, about half will aggro, the other half wont. At low numbers, all aggro. 

I've checked the factions and it seems fine. Am I missing something? I am wondering if this is related to limits in the game or script engine. Or possibly limited RAM on my rig. I've tested this for mod conflicts (vanilla game with Tundra Defense only) and still didn't work. 

Thanks

EDIT: Thanks guys, I tweaked the setting with Wrye Bash and my game is actually running BETTER than before. I suspect there was some kind of performance issue related to the engine loading and unloading the AI as I changed cells, killed enemies, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 08:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11/10 for low-effort imitation of nikbow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 07:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've walked back on your point so far that now you're just saying things that any rational person would have to agree with - but they add nothing to the discussion. 

Yes, obviously skill is domain-specific and obviously if you train zero striking you're going to get rocked if strikes are involved. What are you even trying to prove?

Marcelo lost his MMA match too. That doesn't mean BJJ is going to become Aikido. Your overall point makes no sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others are saying, it really depends on the context. 

Often, it is a passive aggressive way of whining that you beat them. In this case, ignore it. 

Sometimes coming from a white belt, they are interpreting something as strength when really it is your bodyweight or leverage. In these cases I'll explain it to them so they can see the concept behind what makes a move effective (e.g., using the end of a lever, or aligning your skeletal structure so you can direct your mass effectively). 

Sometimes it is a subtle hint that you might need to relax a bit to become more effective. But I would never use it this way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 16:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're setting up a false dichotomy. 

It takes SKILL to simultaneously go hard and be safe/technical. That skill absolutely translates to real world, self-defense situations. 

The absolute monsters at my academy are the guys I'm least concerned about injuring people, because BJJ is about control - controlling others and controlling your own body. 

These are the guys that are most combatively effective, not just because they are physical beasts, but because they have extremely precise control - they can use that precision not only to execute combatively effective moves, but also to protect their training partners from injury. 

Watch Buchecha up the intensity in 2014 Worlds and you'll see what I mean. He has great control, but you better believe a guy like that will be able to handle himself in a self-defense situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
