<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2433</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 05:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply. Life post college now seems like it more of something to look forward to now rather than something to dread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 05:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, now it seems more of something I can look forward to rather than something to fear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 05:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try. Would be much easier if I had someone to go with though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 04:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much to take the time to type that reply, it seems to straighten things out.

Not sure if my therapist will agree with my mother being bad, she says she is a great mother. However, my therapist does think she goes overboard on things and that I deserve more independence

It is very hard for me to say no or to stand up for myself, and your right i do do everything i can to avoid confrontation (including lying), and i apologize to people for all kinds of stupid little mistakes i make or even think i made, especially ones in social situations. But I'm not exactly sure what to do about it. These behaviors have really affected my social life with other people and I want to change them.

Also, how would I go about reprogramming that voice inside my head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is I ask for support so often that it becomes a burden on those people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what is life like post college then?

 I'll admit, I'm scared as fuck about life post college, I'm afraid of there being no time to do fun things and no time to spend with people, and having to act all grown up and professional all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
