<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9140</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sierra Nevada brewery issues 36-state recall of select beers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Updated Report from the Center for Reproductive Rights: Women in 33 States At-Risk of Losing Right to Abortion if Landmark Roe v. Wade Decision is Overturned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump labor pick in 2011 on his fast food workers: We hire 'the best of the worst' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which joke? Denis Leary's asshole song from 1994?

(If you mean my caption, then that's a coincidence. I definitely think Louis CK is funny but I'm unfamiliar with a bit where he references this) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denis Leary - Asshole AKA my new pick for the American National Anthem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends, was a female just elected president after being caught on mic saying, "Just grab 'em by the dick. That's what I do. They love it, they all love it."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phila. teachers plan Black Lives Matter week - not all are happy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 09:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philosophy. I work in investment management.

While the actual philosophy e.g. Aristotle, Kant, etc hasn't done much for me, 4 years of critical thinking and arguing my point have no doubt helped my career.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2015 The Economist was "not chasing" the millennial generation. In 2016, The Economist joined Snapchat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump book for sale at the Smithsonian museum is riddled with falsehoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people always try to pet my dogs when they are going to the bathroom? Would they want someone trying to scratch them behind the ear when they were on the toilet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liar's Poker.

http://www.investopedia.com/terms/l/liars-poker.asp
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol sorry.

Comfort animals are on par with able bodied people taking handicapped parking spaces (in my book). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far as I've seen no one mentioned the fact that the bitchy dog is:

1) Owned by a princess with a knock-off Louis Vuitton handbag 

2) Sitting in coach despite item 1 (the real version of that bag is worth a 1st class seat)

3). The dog is not in a carrier I.e. The woman paid for her dog to have a seat

4) (and I'm assuming) this is a "comfort animal" which is **bullshit.** You're saying your worry about (fill in the blank) is more important than people who are physically allergic to animals. Additionally, comfort animals are bullshit in general. I have a medical condition that would permit me to bring my 95 pound German shepherd on a plane, but I don't. You know why, because I'm not a selfish asshole. If I want to fly, then I need to live with what that entails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foreclosed mall once valued at $190M is auctioned for $100 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorability of Trump's Cabinet Picks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Troop leader's petition calls for Girl Scouts to ditch inaugural parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea nuke threat: Rogue nation plans to ruin Trumps inauguration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO...yes, of course. as the total value of the global money supply is about $60T; I kind of figured that out.

Hence the ridiculousness of my answer.

If OP had 1/6th of *all* money on Earth, then they wouldn't be concerned with US economy. They would literally be **their own** economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll explain this for real like you're 5:

If you have $10 trillion, then you start your own country as you are richer than pretty much all of them (by GDP).

Excluding the Death Star, you could actually build your own imperial army, AT-ATs and all!

Don't waste your money paying back the US. We'd just blow it on something stupid like we always do!

http://www.cinemablend.com/news/1551290/how-much-a-star-wars-at-at-would-cost-in-real-life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the baby elephants and tortoises you monster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed my ass off at this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Vermin-Infested American Cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first person to seemingly employ this tactic was Paris Hilton ("leaked" tape right before her TV show premiered), followed not long after, but much more successfully, by Kim Kardashian.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-SNL actor Rob Schneider lectures civil rights hero John Lewis about civil rights on Martin Luther King Jr. Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wannabe Celebrities using "leaked" sex tapes to become famous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Reddit...I'm surprised it made the list at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The map of sex offenders in Center City, Philadelphia. The area around south 19th with no pins...that's where the expensive real estate is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree and did not buy my books after 1st semester.

I also graduated with a 2.3 GPA.

Infer what you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than original comment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gary Oldman as Stansfield:  *EVERYONE!!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's repealed, then I will have *a lot* more money in my paycheck.

That said, 20 million Americans need that healthcare more than I need that money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Admits Windows 10 Has A Serious Problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump suggests he may do away with Russia sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Italians Americans frequently pronounce their own surnames wrong.

I don't care how your Nona said it; she was fucking wrong and *you're* fucking wrong

http://takelessons.com/blog/italian-pronunciation-rules-z09 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RyanAir: Be Grateful There Are Seats

Budweiser: Piss Never Tasted So Good

Coca-Cola: Extra Sugar to Offset The Missing Cocaine

Ford: You Can't Af**ford** Better

Starbucks: Only $6 to Prove You're a Tool

Eddie Bauer/LL Bean: Of Course I'm White; Look At What I'm Wearing

Comcast: Fuck You

All Health Insurance Companies: Fuck You, Pay Me

All Pharma Companies: We Won't Cure Your Disease,  but You May Shit Blood For a Week

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The English alphabet...backwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ringling Bros. closing Greatest Show on Earth after 146 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you crazy? This is America. I don't care if free/low cost birth control solves the national debt. 

If women really need cheap birth control, then let them learn to keep an aspirin between their knees!

-Old White Men of America

And now, the new American National Anthem:

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=fUspLVStPbk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to insult an entire country, then *at least* get their units of measurement right.

Germany uses the Kg not Lb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Judge Judy only works 52 days per year and makes $900,000 per day that she does. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Why I Rely on Reddit For News. It Took A Major News Outlet 5 Business Days To Siphon Off This Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 05:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regrettably,

Robert Mugabe

Kim Jong-Un

Omar al-Bashir

Bashar al-Assad

and Rodrigo Duterte

Could not be reached for comment. However, Donald Trump confirmed, "They love me. They all love me, everyone loves me."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every major news outlet steal their content from Reddit.  There's usually a 2-3 delay on anything that isn't basically about a foreign leader or government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An award for most quality puns (which feels like an oxymoron)

The award on your profile would be the cosmic cutie from Hitchhiker'a Guide to the Galaxy

The description on the awards info page would be: 

"You can tune a guitar, but you can't tuna fish. Unless of course, you play bass." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was widely believed that Julius Caesar suffered from epilepsy; however, doctors put forth a new theory in 2015 that he suffered from a number of "mini-strokes"

http://www.history.com/news/julius-caesar-suffered-from-strokes-not-epilepsy-new-study-says </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suit: Sleepy Uber driver gave rider wheel, awoke to high-speed chase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't work for Comcast (but know someone that does).

You also enjoy paying way less for cable and internet  compared to me (about $150 per month less)

If you have a Verizon wireless phone you get a 30% discount (I think, I know you get a discount)

And have WAAAY better health benefits than I do

While I take your larger point about a candy bar vs. $5B, it's disingenuous to say Comcast gives you nothing other than a candy bar.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.

The lack of an actual visualization is why I shared the item under r/news instead of r/dataisbeautiful

The data is interesting but presentation is underwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graphic: America Before and After Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No disrespect intended to any work you do, but honestly ask yourself, if you had to fly to Australia *wouldn't you do the same thing if you could?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't Chipotle currently own this crown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm isn't this literally the motto of the KGB:

*"We engage in collecting compromising material about you*"

(And yes I know the KGB changed names. New letters, same agency) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wicker Man

*NOT THE BEES! NOT THE BEES!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew a kid in high school that shoved a pizza crust up his ass on a dare.

His response, "What was I gonna do...not shove it up my ass?"

Me: "Yes...that's exactly correct. You refrain from shoving Italian food up your ass." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Two months ago I was eating a plate of osso buco with a nice side of buffalo *muzzarell*. Now they're feeding' me fuckin' strained peas and carrots. Jail was better than this. Next time I get whacked I better come back as the child of a Sardinian goat farmer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I appreciate you larger point, you are missing mine.

Since you've done these types of studies you're better equipped to tell me:
1) how often are women raping men (not children, grown men)
2) in those cases how does sentencing compare to men (I'm sure there are many more cases of men vs. women (or men), but there should be some
3) when compared to other crimes, how does rape sentencing typically play out E.g. Is it analogous to manslaughter, car theft or something else.

Again, you've done the studies so you're better equipped to know, but rape should definitely have a more severe punishment than 8 years in jail IMO (I cheated and grabbed a quick link for that number.)

Carjacking carries ten to fifteen years in prison in some cases (again, quick link)

If someone can honestly tell me that possibly being dragged out of your car and having it stolen, is worse than rape, then I'd be very surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what I get for trusting internet headlines! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snap at the waiter and then say "Hey Garon! Don't you see me fucking snapping here! I need a Stoli lemon drop!"

(I'm from NJ originally...such is life) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG I haven't thought of that bit in years! That's classic!

I too hate and called out Marketing (but no one is topping Hicks' bit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marketing.

There are ~10 people in marketing on Earth that are actually A) Creative B) Adding to their company's bottom line

The rest are glorified English majors that took 18th century French painting, Sociology and Communications as electives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you confront people with facts!

Maybe you have polio because you didn't swim in raw sewage with George Carlin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something tells me if women were the usual perpetrators of rape, then perhaps we'd see equitable treatment of rape as a crime i.e. it would have a much more severe sentence.

Was this father totally justified (in my opinion, yes)
BUT did he break the law, yes (and not an unfair law like Jim Crow laws)

He should serve time, but definitely not 40 years. The man isn't a danger to society.  He was a danger to one very specific person (and with cause) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gas attack is terrible but let's all agree that eating fried chicken with utensils is morally reprehensible.

I was gonna give Trump a chance...now I'm not so sure.

This may have done it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in investment management and you should definitely seek help from one (I can't tell you who to pick)

That said, you've explicitly stated:
-You have a fair amount of debt
-Both you and your wife are not financially responsible
-By posting this comment you are admitting you have no idea what to do with the money (that's a good thing because you realize it)

Investment managers, specifically those that act as a fiduciary for a trust (because they are legally required to act in your wife's best interest) are more adept at managing this situation than you are.

Those managers will most likely expect a % of assets they manage each year in fees; however, that should be deducted from returns i.e. Ideally your wife makes money every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move to the Caribbean and live out my days like a fucking pirate, drinking rum all day and tanning my skin like a piece of quality leather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E-BAY!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pulled over by Philly cops for a *valid* inspection sticker.  Apparently they didn't know the stickers expire at *month end.*

They then kept me for another 30 minutes running tags, etc (no doubt looking for a reason to justify the fact they pulled me over) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's times like this I'm reminded of the enlightened despot Emperor Joseph II of Austria who said, "Everything for the people, nothing by the people"

Or in English

"My people are too incapable/stupid/stubborn/easily misled to make their own decisions, so I will make all the decisions, but always in their best interest."

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Enlightened_despotism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a katana and a can of cheese in the background?

I feel like this is the start of a Writing Prompt by a man on PCP.

*Imagine your neighbor is a madman guitar teacher that verbally abuses his students and threatens them with ancient Japanese weaponry and foods of questionable origin* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My issue isn't the updates.

My issue is they've modified the lock screen to essentially trick users into updating.  Most people probably mindlessly enter their code on this screen.

While many updates contain necessary patches, it has always been explicitly at user discretion if they wanted to upgrade. This modified lock screen feels somewhat duplicitous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever Apple rolls out a new operating system there are invariably reports about something going wrong and a patched version coming out very soon after.

That something usually turns your phone into a $750 paperweight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice try, Apple! You almost tricked me into bricking my phone with the new O/S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naked woman in stolen police cruiser led cops on chase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking monstrous.

If you would kidnap a mentally handicapped person and videotape torturing them, then you are beyond reform.  I hope the courts impose the most draconian punishment possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science publishes new NOAA analysis: Data show no recent slowdown in global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG I laughed for a solid minute at this. Ubisoft really is giving people smallpox to download their untested software! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a bug in the matrix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean this in the best possible way...SHOW-OFF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mariahs team says NYE performance was sabotaged for ratings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN Host Don Lemon does shots, gets a piercing and has his mic turned off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can read the book and appreciate it without knowing the history, but it is heavily influenced by the Russian Communist revolution, Trotsky, Stalin and treatment of the proletariat.

However, to explain any of that to you in advance as it plays out in the book, would ruin the book.

So remember that stuff for later if you want to learn about the symbolism :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 06:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally watching Stranger Things.

As someone that grew up reading Stephen King, it's like a stroll down memory lane.  That and a sprinkling of Spielberg.

It's a good show in its own right, BUT very clearly influenced by King.

On a side note, never move to Philly...there is nothing to do here on New Year's Eve (or most other nights as celebrity tweets can tell you) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking this probably counts as reverse racism, but I went into a restaurant in Beijing and it was full.

When the owner saw me, he kicked two other patrons off of their table and made them leave! I still to this day have no idea if they even paid their check.

Perhaps it was smart on his part because I felt obligated to spend a good deal of money (after that.) I think I spent about $75 which was probably my second most expensive meal in the city over the course of a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever the fuck this guy is has my vote for president when he reaches the age of 35.

Made my night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Injured Dog Stranded on Train Tracks is Protected by Furry Friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 23:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this actually surprise anyone?  This is from the Center for Studies with Obvious Outcomes.

In 2014 the military published their own findings on the makeup of the military (see link below).  At that time more than half the US military was under 30 years of age.  This shouldn't surprise anyone because there are more rank and file soldiers than officers...like any company

As per food service, the millennials are the largest generation in our nation's history, overtaking baby boomers (link 2).  This may pain millennials to hear but they are still young and don't have that much to offer employers at the bottom end of the age group. When you're young you take shit jobs to get by (I worked at Borders Books for example...remember them?)

No millennial should read this study as anything more than:

The youngest people are in the two roles that historically have been filled by the youngest people in American society (excluding possibly during WW1, WW2 and Vietnam).

http://download.militaryonesource.mil/12038/MOS/Reports/2014-Demographics-Report.pdf

http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2016/04/25/millennials-overtake-baby-boomers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naked man sought after he chases after 2 girls on roadway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the tracks from this year and last year although I think 2013 was the worst.

Martin Garrix - Animals

Even at festivals where Martin Garrix was playing most DJs had this in their set. When I was at EDC that year it was unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JNCO jeans.

You could fit like 8 fucking people in those pants! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Death of Elisa Lam is probably the best example in my opinion. Google her name and you can easily find the video on YouTube. It's really creepy to say the least (knowing how the story tragically ends)

The story:
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Death_of_Elisa_Lam
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian operation hacked a Vermont utility, showing risk to U.S. electrical grid security, officials say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother in law is a Bears fan.

I laughed at this for a solid ten seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only that thinks it's a little fucked up the bull is dressed in Spanish style clothing?

You know, given the whole matador/killing bulls in a slow and painful manner for sport and entertainment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else reminded of the Beacon of Gondor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 03:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was considering taking the Deadmau5 master class for production that I saw on YouTube.

I think I'm good to go from here!

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Darth Vader and Luke Skywalker were not originally related, but Ep. V's original screenwriter died of cancer and George Lucas had to perform a rewrite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 03:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 02:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blame yellowcard lol!

Everyone remembers "ocean avenue" because it was goddamned everywhere and they performed at the MTV music awards.

A Perfect Circle's first song on TRL was Judith. 

Lyrics like "Fuck your God," doesn't play too well to the sponsors lmao! It doesn't matter that it's a very complex song about the singer's mother suffering a stroke, being paralyzed for life and yet still maintaining her Christian beliefs (and what is undoubtedly his take on it).  

As soon as you say "Fuck you God" in a song, you may as well shoot a puppy on live TV because the sponsors will avoid you like the plague.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Judith_(song) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do, you're missing a:

NeoGeo

TurboGrafix 16

Coleco Vision

Atari 

Atari Jaguar

Nintendo Virtual Boy

Sega CD

Sega Dreamcast

And it looks like every model of PlayStation 

Not to mention all the add ons and accessories like the NES Max, NES Advantage, NES Power Pad and NES Power Glove.

You have done well, but the student is not yet the teacher.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just like Jerome Bettis's restaurant in Pittsburgh.

Men stand at the urinals and sinks while staring at everyone at the bar through one way glass.

Just feels like a problem waiting to happen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In college my dorm room had bunkbeds.

There was a girl in my bed (I'm on top) and one of my friends was in my roommates bunk on bottom with a girl.

For some drunk reason, he decided it would be funny to interrupt us by lifting the top bunk with legs, which immediately comes off the posts.

The bunk falls on him and the girl below us, throwing me and the Girl on top to the floor.  I run through the quad's shared bathroom to the next room to grab my roommates for help.

I then *interrupt* one of them having sex with their girlfriend (not under the covers.). Me being drunk, and having just seen two unexpectedly naked bodies, stutter our friend is dead and we need help.

He gets dressed, we run to first room together to lift the bunk off our friend and the girl, somehow they're fine and just laughing..:no idea how to this day.

2 sexual experiences ruined

No dead bodies

On the whole...a successful night
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, someone should have told me before I bought KH2 first I had to buy 2 other systems and 3 other games because OH BY THE WAY by KH2 we really mean KH5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howard The Duck

That fucking duck costume was hilarious to me as a kid and the aliens at the end scared the hell out of me.

That, and the Ewok movies, because kids are stupid.

*Why the hell were movies made about Ewoks again* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ostrich thoughts: *In two years, I'm gonna eat that cat." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of simplicity, yes.

As stated before, if they harassed a camera person or lighting person, then it's probably easier to make the case because it's not on camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone else explain this clip to me? 

Reporter says: We said food stamp fraud was $70MM in 2016

Correction: From 2009 to 2011 it was actually $853MM for each of those 3 years. Nationally, food stamp trafficking is on decline. We're sorry about that

Ummm...$853MM is **WAY MORE** than just the $70MM originally cited, though I understand it's a different time period.

Irrespective of your thoughts on food stamp fraud, I would expect this data to have been presented as: 

"BREAKING NEWS: FOOD STAMP FRAUD WAY WORSE THAN ORIGINALLY REPORTED"

which is not how they've offered this correction.

Can someone tell me what the hell I'm missing? Are they just providing a different stat that is accurate, albeit old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Fox   Friends' issues correction on food stamp fraud report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the lawsuit you mentioned:

http://www.thewrap.com/att-directv-hit-with-10-billion-race-discrimination-lawsuit/

(Only one I could find that might be related but not really what you're describing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 16 dumbest celebrity quotes of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good points of differentiation. Also worth noting is that they looked a college aged couples. 

Thus I read the findings as "partner wealth" = "partner family income" because, let's be honest, very few college aged males are earning so much money that they statistically differentiate themselves from each other with any real dispersion.

However, the benefits of rich parents is highly correlated with rich children.  As a result, if a college aged girl is dating a college aged guy with rich parents, it is logically fair to assume that his parents' wealth is perceived as his wealth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just me but it doesn't feel that black   white.

If a performer, while performing said, X person is sexually harassing me, then I don't see how that doesn't constitute sexual harassment (even if the performer immediately says, "I was just improvising")

I read a news story in the NY Post a few months ago about a couple of female performers accusing a male performer of raping them on set while filming.  Now rape and sexual harassment are obviously different crimes but the existence of the more severe crime makes me believe the lesser crime certainly exists, and that laws have to exist to control for it BUT how do they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nintendo 64: All Star Baseball 2001

In season mode, on the hardest difficulty, I:

Played a perfect, undefeated season 

Closed out the World Series with a perfect game and over 100 runs scored

The tricks to doing so:

**Batting:** 

The batting reticle ( a 3D square within a square) appeared to encourage batters to get a bullseye to get better hits.  This was wrong and misled players.

You could crush home runs repeatedly by aligning the reticle so that the pitch crossed the plate at the very top of the outside square and then swinging.  I would expect this to result only pop-flys but instead it sent pitches over the wall with *a lot* of frequency.

**Pitching**

While batters had a box of "hot and cold" zones, the real trick was to keep it random.  If you threw 3 fastballs in a row at the cold zone the batter would catch on pretty much every time.

This was closer to the mindset of actually pitching and trying to outsmart a batter.  That said, pitchers with 6-12 curveballs, cutters or sliders could get up to two strikes with ease on almost every batter. From there it was painting the corners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO yes I understand harassment as well as the general rules and regs of HR law.  Additionally,  I have a pretty good handle of what is required to pass the litmus test I.e. At what point is something defined as sexual harassment.

That said, I'm presuming acting in adult films, much like acting in Hollywood films, has a certain amount of improvisation. I understand there is advanced planning (so to speak) but defining said improvisation as sexual harassment would be a challenge I would think (not that it doesn't happen, but how to make your case is more difficult than in your typical corporate setting)

Further, I would think most adult performers are not employees of the companies making movies but rather independent contractors, meaning they aren't exactly attending an employee orientation and given a handbook on "appropriate workplace interactions."

I'm sure There is also isn't a formal warning process when these contractors initially break those rules to correct the action.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Likelihood of Female Orgasm via Heterosexual Sexual Intercourse Directly Linked to Partner's Wealth, Confidence Level and Attractiveness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pa. man with hatchet flees from police through ventilation ducts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pantera started out as a glam metal band before they were the Pantera we all know today.

https://www.google.com/amp/uproxx.com/music/pantera-glam-metal-dimebag-darrell-phil-anselmo/amp/?client=safari </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paz Lenchantin played violin and piano as a member of A Perfect Circle (Front by Maynard from Tool.)

The first example that comes to mind of her playing  violin is  3 Libras on Mer De Noms.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there HR/Sexual Harassment laws in the Adult Film industry? How would that even work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you are definitely correct to some degree, don't forget that most media in this country is mostly controlled by only a handful of major conglomerates I.e. They claim to be the victim but in many cases are just as guilty of the crime by perpetuating it when selling their own content.

Check the list of media conglomerates here under notable examples:

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Media_conglomerate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because they are targeted to audiences you are not a part of does not mean it is racist/classist/anything else to make you pay for them as part of the content distributor bundling strategy.

Think of it this way, the goal of any company is to maximize revenue and profits.

Let's say you only want to pay for ESPN and it costs the content distributor $10 to produce that content but they (cable companies really as they pass through the cost) charge you $12.  They've made $2, or 20%, on their original investment.

BUT they know *everyone* wants ESPN and they also have the fishing network which they are producing content for and need to sell.  That content costs them $1.  The charge to you may be $2; however, that's a 100% markup on that content (albeit still way cheaper than ESPN to you)

The net effect is their return is increased by over 7% to 27.25% because they forced you to take content most people wouldn't pay for and your bill went up 16% as a result.

While this situation definitely sucks, what this example is meant to illustrate is that, irrespective of what motive you think there is for bundling:

The only motive ever is profit

The only color that matters is green  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Virgin Islands Will Pay You To Visit In 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Solo Cup inventor Robert Hulseman dies at age 84 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 06:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Closes School For Children of Western Diplomats In Retaliation For Us Sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of studying to be a CFA does entail reviewing financial statements but most CFAs that I know are some type of portfolio manager (and they aren't reviewing financial statements all day)

Large Investment firms have analysts that review, research public companies and sit on calls when earnings come out but I don't have a sense of how many investment analysts exist in that regard.  

You're right about product mgmt. but in a very high level sense.  If you wanted to be a product manager in technology usually that entails manages customer and executive expectations, working with tech developers and meeting with users to gather their input/requirements.  There are other types of product managers as well but I focused on tech since you originally mentioned it.

That said, none of those certifications I mentioned originally will necessarily get you a job as a product manager if you don't already have experience doing that job.  They would be a bonus, not a requirement to be hired (in most cases, at least) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HR Director Sues To Find Out Who Sent Her A "Bag of D*cks" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never heard of him before but I looked up his wiki and immediately laughed my ass off

My thoughts upon seeing his pic: Yep, British

My thoughts upon reading his nickname was "stuffy:" Yep, definitely British.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hugh_Dowding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hilarious! That's like when people ask me why I know the general layout of Washington D.C. so well.

"350 hours in the Capitol Wastes of Fallout 3 changes a man." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say I blame them...although that is a funny concept.

"Who's that? Just our royal family. Don't mind them though, we just keep them around for the sake of tradition" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
