<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4189</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More acceptable answer to me. I wish AJ fans could except that Shane did his part too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlotte's got some Chiclets on her too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if this gets traction I don't think they'll have a choice. You're right. But in a company that's been pretty outspoken about anti-bullying in the past this could be pretty rough to deal with down the line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"D'oh! I need to make Mun-E!"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a professional standpoint it looks better if he would release a statement. Hell he should probably go to the office and see where WWE stands on him with this and if they even what him to acknowledge it.

I'm not defending what he did or didn't do just saying everyone has a right to defend their reputation. Just because this sub has found him guilty doesn't mean he is. We don't know the full story with Mauro and the shit with Justin was 10 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because how can you defend yourself against pretty damning harrasment allegations when you're limited to 140 characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a better joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great story. Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After he got his concussion he was just dazed and confused backstage and wouldn't let anyone near him. There's footage of it on that documentary that Ventura narrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If his reputation is being threatened? No he shouldn't but he should find a better forum to defend himself than Twitter

Edit: So the guy just shouldn't respond to these claims? I'm not defending what he did or didn't do just saying everyone has a right to defend their reputation. Just because this sub has found him guilty doesn't mean he is. We don't know the full story with Mauro and the shit with Justin was 10 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember MetsFan (for anyone who still wants to believe his stories) talked about Justin being kind of a creep. Constantly asking for fan girls numbers at ringside and just being annoying in the back with constantly taking selfies with guests and any legend who came back.

Not much to hate on there though. Dude either got laid (good on him) or got some social media cred (which would annoy me but I don't have social media so more power to him too) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See Alexa is terrible to me on the mic. That promo she did before they announced her match for Mania was one of the worst things I'd ever heard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't carried. You've never wrestled and how could you watch that match and think that. God, I hate people like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And because of all that they kinda have to disclaimer the show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bryan Alvarez can leap off a bridge for as far as I'm concerned. I wish he was David Cross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is it's just their creepy way of saying 'she's hot af' which is fine, because it's the internet and no one should judge you for finding a woman who is partly on TV because of her looks attractive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brock being like a crazed rhinoceros when he got backstage after Wrestlemania 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that at all. These people who you are vouching also downvote any criticism you throw AJ's way. The fact that you think me calling that out is me being 'edgy and shit' is ridiculous and proves my point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is AJ sold as someone who can fuck up his oppenents badly? He's sold as a tremendous wrestler and that was the story going into the match. That he'd out-wrestle Shane. His lack of long term selling lead to some cool moments like The Angle Slam, The DDT counter from a Phenomenal Forearm, and clocking AJ with the trash can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt's got some nice veneers on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hotel Carter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your ball and go home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he didn't and the match was still awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His selling was fine. He sold AJ's offense in the Calf Crusher and the One Handed Styles Clash. Part of his selling is that Shane has always been booked as a resilient daredevil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His injury really limited a lot of what he can do. The fact that his whole program with Triple H started in the fall really stifled him because no one bought him beating Owens for the title because we knew he was facing Triple H down the line. He's also a terrible promo and sounds like a guy who's just trying to remember lines than someone who's in the moment. Seth Rollins summer 2015 was one of the best wrestlers (in ring) I've ever seen. I miss that dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Physically, hell yes. Her personality just sucks though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love The Rock and was bummed we didn't get to see him for his annual Wrestlemania appearance this year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braun and Brock will be awesome. Can't wait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at it this way. For as much as people he shouldn't have main evented Mania all those years ago and that it should've been Punk I say bullshit. He was so fucking despised and was so good at his job then. He was the perfect chicken shit heel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/mtvgk2ne--Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember someone pointed out a spot where he just carelessly shoved Corbin off the turnbuckle at a house show and Corbin spent the rest of the match at ringside being looked at and people were saying he did well on the fly making it up after Corbin got taken out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should've stayed with his face turn last year when he got injured. I don't know why they kept him heel when he came back. It's baffling to me

I don't want to say Bray Wyatt has run it's course but heel Bray Wyatt that never delivers certainly has. A lot of what's hurt him is hut typical bad guys lose booking 101. He's suffered from that the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A heel who can actually draw heat in today's day and age will always scream Main Event to me and I will totally value over someone like Kevin Owens who does annoyig shit in his matches to pander to the snarks who will buy his T-Shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "She's adorable"

Shut the fuck up. Go say that to any girl at a bar or something and watch her look at you as if you just licked her forehead. When it comes to people on here talking about any woman I cringe like I'm epileptic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're really going to slow build them winning a title due to the fact that they're very over and want to make the moment special. We all know how quickly they like to break up tag teams so Enzo fans should hope they take their time because God knows what happens to him after they go their separate ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryback invented overusing unfunny memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The strikes were stiff, but I liked that about the match. It was a grudge match. And I thought the selling was fine. What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miz is the only heel in that company who could get to the point where he's so hated people pay money to see him get beaten. AJ is a heel who's getting more cheered than booed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite being overrated in the ring, AJ Lee is easily the best woman on a microphone in the last 7 years and blows this current gen completely out of the water  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please ban any posts with the words 'bullying' or 'fired' in them for a month and a half </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the match was meh because the Hardy's coming back basically was what that entire 30 minutes was about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Owens is United States Champion level superstar to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because wrestling fans aren't funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AJ has done all he can on Smackdown. He's literally wrestled damn near everyone on that roster. What's so bad if he heads to RAW? He'll be fed to Roman? At this point I don't care because the matches will be awesome and they've shown that they value his talent enough that they aren't going to just leave him out in the rain. AJ will be fine. Lighten up


If anything you should be hoping he stays heel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Ththey've been lyin' to you, m-man* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shane deserves just as much credit as AJ for their match being great. I'm glad all of you AJ fans who bitched about it were left eating your words, but even then you still cling on to any excuse to give AJ all the credit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrestlemania 31 isn't that good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Ambrose feud was very good (definitely his best out of his heirs with all 3 Shield guys) and I was a fan of his brief feud with Ryback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luis and Jay on YKWD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edgy Ari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vince owes him one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, he was really lean back then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neville was the greatest NXT champion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to give you a few after that gem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Cena too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.tenor.co/images/ebd0d819e559547273b92ed7b03ec9fa/tenor.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don Rickles' scene in Dirty Work (1998) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't read the script. It has been reported that a lot of this this movie still stems from Fukanaga's original draft. Now that I've read it and seen the trailer it looks like it's true. A lot of scenes in it from the trailer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bill wakes up to his ceilling dripping and he then gets up to go get a bucket. While he's in the hallway he sees George's room is open with muddy footprints leading downstairs and into the cellar. After calling for his parents who don't answer he decides to go investigate. He slowly descends into the **slightly flooded** cellar not noticing the door shutting behind him by itself. He sees George who blames him for his death and invites him to "float too" (like the trailer). It is during this that you see Pennywise slink up from the water, revealing himself, and then you realize that his hand is behind George using him as a puppet. Really weird disturbing visual. Pennywise than chases Bill upstairs. Bill makes it to his room, locks the door and then lays in his bed terrified as his door jiggles, after awhile he goes to the door with his bat only to open it and fight out it's his father who heard him screaming. They investigate the basement but find out its no longer flooded and there is no trace of George or Pennywise.] (#spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed it. No problem if that draft would've been the final say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find the link. It had been leaked last summer and then had a resurgence last week due to the trailer but the site I went to said that New Line/Warner Bros. requested that they take it down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's *THE* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Fukanaga's script the other day and this scene is terrifying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While *Pleasant Vallet Sunday* plays over the speakers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Ya know what dude, I got plenty of culture. [Look I wear sunglasses on the red carpet, dude.] (http://diaboliquemagazine.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Rkelly1-620x348.jpg)"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where you're at on the main card. Ziggler? Probably not a good idea financially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Hey Justin, you have something on your pantslike a spotwhy don't you go take them offcome out an chill for a bit* - Triple H </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in my top 5 Mania matches of all time. The story is incredible. There is literally like 6 wrestling moves used the whole match but they told a tremendous story. And it has to be one of the best matches from a booking standpoint in a long time when you look at all who were involved (Roman, Brock, Seth) and where they went from that night.

I loved the build too. I remember Heyman said in an interview that they were going for an old school boxing feel to this whole match. I also loved the red lighting they used over the crowd
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time he gave a shit the reward was Brock getting to use his head as a drum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't even know that. Good on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tremendous score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braun vs Brock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my favorite examples of transitions in film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what's going on with The Creek   The Cave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rebecca said on FaceBook that until today it was closed for the last couple days and that performers are no longer allowed free food and drink. Awhile back she also mentioned having to sue someone also. Can anyone shed a little light on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lion King (1994) - This Land scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on her. I like hearing that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she talk about why she left WWE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing he told Braun to toss into the ropes so he could have more a controlled landing. AJ got the shit kicked out of him in this match. He was Braun's rag doll. The Shield spot. And JeriKO wailing on him several times
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AJ Styles with a crazy bump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For as briefly as the interacted, I always enjoyed the dialogue between Mufasa and Scar in The Lion King (1994) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like a salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twist of Fate through a steel chair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How good is it? Does it go through her time with the company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't bore me at all and I thought it was great from start to finish. Intense and fast-paced. I love that it woke the crowd up. That's the biggest criticism I have with Triple H/Seth. The crowd just didn't seem to care for a good chunk of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy this is going to kill me but I enjoyed Goldberg/Lesnar the most </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only he'd had his suit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Funches  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who gives a fuck what he thinks!!!! Just make me laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a grandpa. This is how they use twitter whilst also having a shitty sense of humor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vickie Guererro did a promo in Austin a few years back that had MASSIVE heat. It was this times 1000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're definitley right, but a good refreshening will only help it. The roster is small enough that a lot of guys were utilized well but a good chunk seem like they've done all they can do on that show (Becky and AJ are my examples). New people will be very welcome

A smaller roster means wrestlers will get more attention, but it also means that the show can't maintain original storylines for a year. This superstar shakeup is a great idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He talks like he's above it. That's his problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't talk like that, you idiot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, ya know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Found your alt] (https://www.reddit.com/r/StandUpComedy/comments/63d0fn/louis_ck_special_now_up_on_netflix/dftfyii/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not complaining. I just remember the people who were bitching after Survivor Series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negate was a poor choice of word. I guess what I mean is that it don't see Goldberg's win as a definitive he's better than Brock, more of he got lucky. I think we'll see the ultimate sleighing of Brock when someone (most likely Roman) has a 20 minutes match with him and pins him clean. That will be decisive and is still thenulitlmate rub here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Case in point] (http://m.imgur.com/YbyneJq?r) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can he not believe in heel managers when he's had Heyman under his thumb for the last 5 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking that he beat Goldberg clean 1-2-3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying to me, that I don't take it as a definitive clean win (even though it is). The storyline is that Brock didn't consider him a threat until it was too late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he'll come back every now and then. Maybe do something with Braun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"DRAGOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easter's in two weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brock's facial expression during this feud are what has sold it for me. When Goldberg shoved him at Survivor Series his 'Oh my God' look was incredible, and at The Rumble he looked like he was going to cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why eventually? Why wouldn't he do it last night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the last 5-10 minutes of Mania were a perfect way to do it. We don't need anything else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she get nude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I took the Rumble spot was that Goldberg was in Brock's head and had the mental edge over him. There's continuity there. At Survivor Series, Brock strong-armed Goldberg into the counter (his only offense) only to have Goldberg completely surprise him with a vicious shove, flooring him. 

At the Rumble, Brock just abandons all thought and mindlessly goes after Goldberg and gets speared and dumped out of the ring. 

I love shit like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who were up in arms saying that the streak was wasted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the first guy to completely beat Goldberg with no shenanigans basically negates Goldberg's win at Survivor Series, right? Now that the feud is over we can look back and all agree that kayfabe-wise Goldberg only won because Brock didn't take him seriously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/mtvgk2ne--Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is his mom ill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the story here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind where he ends up I just want him to stay heel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest thing that got people behind him was Survivor Series  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm skeptical that we'll see Angle wrestle at all. If every doctor in the world will clear Daniel Bryan except WWE's, how do you think they're going to handle Kurt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he say anymore vague JBL things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this dude. One of the best handled comebacks they've ever done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roman will face Strowman in a number one contender match next week and lose via shenanigans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much do Jim and Sam make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is DeepDiscount.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For tonight. Let's see where this goes in a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anthony is currently beating Keith/Garrett with a roll of quarters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of don't want to see it. That was awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like a thumb with a wig on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an entitled pretentious cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if he did the hypocrisy on here would be ridiculous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YKWD was really good this week. Soder was on fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HBK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome match. Loved that it wasn't what we thought it would be and that Goldberg lost due to a mistake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get more longevity out of the feud. And I felt better for Dean that if he's going to be relegated to the Pre-Show that he should get a win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how this match wasn't the squash we all thought it would be and that Goldberg lost due to a mistake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty neat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Goldberg/Lesnar encounter woke people up! Props to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was honestly my assumption. They were communicating pretty loudly at points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be said. As sad as I am for Taker, I feel horrible for Roman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like watching someone drown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brock's

It's always simple but has a big fight feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Proved me wrong and loved that it woke the crowd up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a weird thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least the crowd was respectful when Cena finally popped the question. As predictable as it was  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AJ won, Shane looked awesome, better match than I thought it would be. Great spots. We all can shut up now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - They take him serious because he's a very good wrestler who also is a bad guy. Look at how he won the title the first time. 

- You're saying he didn't take Taker to the limit by kicking out of Taker's offense and using weapon shots and low blows in a **Hell in a Cell** match?

- How is it disgusting? They're both part time authority figures/wrestlers who come back to put talent over? That's my comparison. Not their wrestling

- You're criticism of him the Survivor Series is also the same point I'm making in how he'll look strong

This is all my opinion. It's okay to have different opinions 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll just have to see tonight. Calm down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think think it's 9 months too late for Nakamura. He had a year long run and got his character established pretty well. Also nice that he spent the last 3 or so months putting Roode over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear that they're good friends with Mike Chioda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/jpMxpzfSRUA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://thumbs.ebaystatic.com/images/g/CMMAAOSw2gxYze6z/s-l225.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't look good with a head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaq wanted more money than they were going to give him. I was holding on to a crazy belief that they were going to have him come out for the Battle Royal again as a surprise until they announced it was on the Pre-Show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, sir. It looks pretty convincing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir, I don't think that's a real photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither. I'm just thinking long term. People still need to remember that aJ is a heel even if he is cheered and liked by the fans. His character is still a heel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's someone who took the Undertaker to his limits last year so much that they had Undertaker show him respect on Smackdown back in November. That shows a little investment by them in that they'd have Taker put him over. He's someone they can pull out every now and then to build a solid feud with someone. Very much like Triple H. They book him strongly because his character is basically this resilient risk taker that will kill himself if it accomplishes his goal. Not saying I agree but look at the past year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see him doing something crazy but I also see AJ winning by using a weapon behind the refs back (beating Shane at his own game) or with a small package or something (to emphasize that he's a better wrestler while also protecting Shane somewhat)

I feel that they're going to do something to keep heel heat on AJ going forward because I believe he'll feud with Randy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faggots (4:15) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These sit-down interviews are where Brock Lesnar really shines as far as mic work goes. This genuinely frightened me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man he looked a little chubby here. It's really nuts how since it's been confirmed he's on juice that you can go back and see how much his body has changed through different points in his career  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should assault you right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see what they see in her now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sheamus beat him at the next PPV. And Triple H isn't 100% retired </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lost his overall feud to KO. He lost his feud with Seth. He's lost to Wyatt, he's lost to Sheamus. He's lost to Finn. He's lost to Dean. He lost his title to Jericho 

I know that these aren't all clean wins, but they're heels. Heels rarely win clean in WWE. It's the way of the biz. And for the Seth excuse because he was suspended, well if there's one thing that proved is that Vince isn't going to always pick up after his messes and holds him accountable for his mistakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't fucking care about comics and their politics. If you can't separate that from any entertainer than have fun being miserable. Just make me laugh, cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be your alternative? From a long term story point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do. But go ahead and downvote me for being a genuine fan of Roman and liking him and Brock's match from Mania 31 that I want to see a rematch. Fuck me, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in neither alcohol or your idea. Get four of your friends and meet me in the ring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't. But there is a story that can be put in motion if he faces Brock next year. That would be the logical direction to go in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just picturing Joe looking like those God awful pictures of Virgil and screaming "REGAAAAAAAAAAALLLLLLLLLL" hopelessly for no reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By all accounts Taker is one of the most traditional people ever in professional wrestling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you put the younger talent over to set up the future. In this case, the guy who will be the face of the company </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my hope too that he can tough it out for one more year. But I think that that match was the plan for this year with Taker doing that Smackdown promo before Survivor Series saying that he was 'home'. I'm guessing at some point Taker realized that he just can't do it anymore and plans changed. They've never brought up the fact that he declared he'd stay on Smackdown. 

I'm guessing Vince weighed his options and was like two matches: Taker vs Cena and Taker vs Roman. And he went with the one that serves the future more. I can't argue with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as people will hate it, he should lose to Roman if he is indeed done. It's the right thing to do. No ifs, ands, or boos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish his speech could have been longer. Would have loved to have heard some stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a theory that it's because the crowd was so dead at the AlamoDome for Swann/Neville </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling that the image of Taker walking out after losing (to a big ass standing ovation) for the last time is what they think people will react to more. And if I'm right, I can't argue with that. It'll be an iconic albeit sad moment

Yeah Roman will get booed, but he'll leave and Taker will have his moment with the fans to close the show. There's my optimism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: You don't have a family  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what? That was uncalled for  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, I did! 

I'm truly very sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Powerful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God, this is the greatest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rock vs John Cena (Wrestlemania 28) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to see signature Brock's pyro erupt from that giant fucking ring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to see Brock's pyro erupt from that giant fucking ring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a miserable job. Ryback made a very good defense for them on his podcast by saying imagine if you were a painter and you spent God knows how long on your art. Day in day out you crafted what in your mind was a masterpiece and you went to you boss and he said "nah, I don't like that". So you went back and you made some adjustments and he still was unreceptive and wanted you to change it. Eventually after going back and forth so many times you would just start drawing stick figures and after awhile you would become complacent. Then add in the fact that you have to travel all the time, deal with wrestlers who can be difficult to work with, and then having to fly to Stanford to have meetings at 12 o'clock at night because Vince has to get a 4 hour workout in. And on top of everything be hated by 99% of wrestling fans and blamed for everything that's bad with the current product and never praised when something hits. Who wouldn't hate that? I don't know how people do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a hot dog eating contest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they stopped having him use the blue contacts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well one of them is 84 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had to do what he had to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the ring apron blue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy you stopped using Colin's character, but it bums me out that you're just ripping off Ms. Swan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
