<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3387</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it as having somebody do something for you. 

 - give me a call 
 - say something for me 

As a question:

 - would you teach me? 

Etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and  are related in the way you are thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally tend to think of  as "since" and  as "because". 

 is basically + ( being the simple form of ). 

Same with . This is +. To my ears the  makes the expression a lot more colloquial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine the shit storm if the gender was reverse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. 

Your first sentence is ok too, but it does seem a bit long winded and unnatural having the double "nakatta" in there. Maybe this is better? Somebody else may add something better here. 

"I had to study, so I was busy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before we lose all clarity here - basically if you see  or something similar, (as mentioned already) its just a phrase tacked onto the end of the main sentence, and is almost seeking approval from the listener. 

- that's good hey?!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In restaurants you say (for "take out" or "to go". And simply  can be used for "here". 

The waiter will then ask would you like a or () which is "smoking seat" or "non-smoking seat" respectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the  part of the expression. This is where the  form happens. So It would become  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  would be like making the statement as a question though right? (like I literally just did.) 

Wouldn't it be something like "I think Taro is innocent, right?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  is single handedly the one Japanese word which has given me more issues with pronunciation than any other. To this day, I still can't pronounce is properly. This is after years of living in Japan and speaking business level Japanese.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently (about two months in) been manning the helm of my own start up and also think the Back to Work Enterprise Allowance is fantastic. Just for anybody interested, there is also a lot of financial support out there. The Local Enterprise Offices and Enterprise Ireland have been nothing but fantastic for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're aware. The surprising thing is her name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 19:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we claim her anyway? Kind of like the English do with our athletes/actors/anybody who is doing well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well I wasn't expecting a Siobhn Bernadette Haughey to be swimming for Hong Kong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is correct. "When" is an accurate translation.  E.g. . What do you think when I say "Tokyo". 

It can also mean "with". For example.
? (You went to Tokyo?). ","(Yep, with John). This is kind of a contraction of "Jon" (yep, together with Jon) I'm guessing.

Finally  can be translated as "and" in English. (tomato and negi).

You can also make  which carries a different meaning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 glasses, not pints.  But actually this is a bit of a myth. Essentially you just need to replace as much as you lose to maintain a baseline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can vouch for Zara. I got my last suit in there. Great quality and fit. It needed very little tailoring. 

Topman and River Island generally seem to sell only slim fit outfits I find. You have to squeeze into them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or if you want to get really japanese, straight up 

! 
! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 16:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure is this a joke or not? Me and my girlfriend have lived in different countries for the entirety of our relationship. 40 mins is nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 16:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 16:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non American here. What's a "handle" and a "fifth" exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 14:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I agree. The goal would certainly be to turn 15 minutes into 15 hours.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 14:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this.  This is absolutely great.  I like the "how do you recommend we stay in touch" question.  It's cheeky without being cocky, and bold without being audacious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was considering pitching my business and asking "would you invest and if not, why not". But I feel they've probably heard that a million times. If I'm going down that route, I'd rather focus on specifics of my business. However, getting into details would eat into time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if you didn't mean to come off this way, but no need to be smart. I'm asking in general terms. Should I be asking open ended questions.

E.g. what's difference somebody who becomes a market leader? 

Or should I ask them about their background and how they excelled.

Or should I focus on my business (might waste time. It's only 15 minutes).

Or should I ask them about the marketplace.

Etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
