<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7891</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 20:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the hell do you care what other people buy? It's not a fight - buy what you want with your money and I'll buy what I want with mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 09:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all of this seems like an impossibly deep hole to climb out of, remember that you don't have to do it alone. Involving your wife might help your relationship. If that's not appropriate, get your friends or even coworkers involved. Just having someone encourage you or occasionally ask how you're doing can make all the difference in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 03:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mettle" is an archaic spelling of "metal", not a separate word. "To test one's mettle" - referring to one's character - is a poetic image relating to testing the integrity of armour or blade during smithing anyway.

http://www.etymonline.com/index.php?term=mettle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 03:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 22:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you all for your very helpful, insightful and kind comments. After much deliberation and background reading, I started taking the SSRIs today and have booked myself into a course of counselling. I know the drugs will have had no effect yet, but just to be proactively doing something to address the situation has improved my outlook immensely.

Thank you again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 22:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The laser painter is zoomed and it's slow to turn so it can be quite difficult to track fast-moving objects, especially if your pilot is throwing you around avoiding terrain and incoming fire. Sometimes it's very useful to be able to switch back to "cockpit view", especially if you're on comms with the pilot and spotting for him. Never underestimate the usefulness of the Mk I Human Eyeball.

I'm an atrocious pilot, but an excellent copilot and gunner... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 19:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in exactly the same place. You're doing better than me on one front; I am completely unable to meditate at the moment because of spiralling negative thoughts. I'll do anything to avoid them, ranging from calling my mother in tears late at night until I exhaust myself into sleep, or taking well-meaning friends up on their offers to get me drunk (which is ironic as I very rarely drink and the end of my relationship was largely due to my partner's drinking).

I have been beating myself up about it - I know this is not a productive path - but you know what? This is the way my mind is dealing with the hurt and grief. I'm not going to sleep for a while. I'm still going to see her out of the corner of my eye for a while. I'm still going to be imagining what she's doing and who she's with for a while. I can't stop these thoughts and the more I try, the worse they get. All I can do is be aware of them and understand that they pass away. This helps with the despair, but I just have to endure it all now. For a while.

It's called depression. It's not something you can just snap yourself out of by main force.

Also, it's ridiculously trite, but this actually (surprisingly) helps me: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j-cVn_8MY0g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 17:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear your comparison of Schindler's List and Iron Sky. They've both got Nazis in them, right?

I hope you agree that vigilantism in a fantastical context, like in the Batman movies, is very different from what this film endorses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 18:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes for everyone!

May I also add that Kaneda and Searle both mirror Pinbacker (a Dark Star reference in the name?) in that they all experience the overwhelming "sun-bathing" but interpret in 3 different ways - Kaneda appears thoughtful and rationally, intellectually analytical; Searle is overwhelmed by the emotional and psychotropic aspects and their effect on his identity; Pinbacker addresses it in religious terms. These are the three basic human responses to the unknown and correspond to left-brain, right-brain and pineal gland experiencing (cf: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neurotheology). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 18:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it as an exploration of "spiritual atheism" and no, that's not an oxymoron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 02:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all. On paper I'm everything you loathe - a spiritual atheist and Western pseudo-Buddhist who comes to the practice via Nichiren Buddhism. Worse, I freely pick and choose what suits me and I don't get hung up on what I don't yet understand. I'm pretty sure I don't buy into many of the aspects of karma and reincarnation that I see discussed on Buddhit and at my local SGI group, and I certainly don't believe in any gods or deities ... right now. That may change, of course.

I'm a former committed Christian with a degree in Biblical Studies (and another in Literature) who turned his back on that faith for very rational reasons and I emphatically didn't come here looking for a new religion, but rather a framework and kit bag of mindfulness techniques to help me manage my cyclical depression without medication. 

I'm used to being called a tourist and a dilettante by purists and it doesn't bother me very much any more. My practice *works*. I am a better human being now than I was before. My life is more enjoyable to me and I cause less suffering to those around me. What else matters? I'm about 18 months into this leg of my spiritual journey, and the paths I am currently treading are Buddhist in nature, that's all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 13:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have either 30 or 45 days to reverse the transaction, depending on where you are. Keep all your emails to the seller so that you can show PP Customer Support that you tried to resolve the issue. I'm almost certain they will refund you straight away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 13:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 16:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it always a left-hand rotation in Buddhism and a right-hand rotation in Naziism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 22:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 03:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you're not, and it's a valid observation .... But all of the other kids are unpleasant caricatures, not just Chardonay - Jered calls Crispin's picture a "love letter to banality" which is not natural language for a little kid; one kid has a literal booger-head etc. They're not really like that, but that's how Clarissa's mind works now and we're seeing them through her eyes.

You're right that it doesn't sit well, but I think the writer is trying to show how different and separated from the other kids Clarissa feels. She's not a child anymore. She can't relate. She has nothing in common with them. So she sees them as stereotypes and caricatures. 

I don't think it's very obvious this early in the sequence and so it's easy to think that it's the writer trying to use racism for comedy effect.

I don't think there's any comedy intended here at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 17:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And oddly enough, he didn't write "Alien" either - Dan O'Bannon and Ronald Shusett did. And neither PKD nor Scott wrote "Blade Runner". That would be Hampton Fancher and David Webb Peoples. And we all know that Scott didn't write "Prometheus" - the credit/blame for that is shared between Jon Spaihts and Damon Lindelof.

Seriously, if we're going to look for a common thread here, let's at least compare apples with apples. Scott's a director, not a screenwriter. And the question of who "owns" a film is not an easy one anyway. Is "The Shining" a Kubrick film, a Stephen King film, a Jan Harlan film, or even a Jack Nicholson film?

FWIW, my dissertation was on looking for an auteur common to all three Alien films (as they were at the time) in order to justify the position that they formed a complex (as opposed to compound) narrative. Closest I could get was David Giler and Walter Hill who produced all 3 (plus Resurrection and Prometheus later). Unfortunately, they had nothing to do with Blade Runner. Or Firefly, Soldier, Angel etc.

I thinking many cases it boils down to film-makers wanting to doff their caps to properties they like. Hell if I was making a scifi movie, I'd find some way to get a W-Y or a Tyrell logo in somewhere just because I think they're cool. When Scott reuses a couple of graphics, it's probably just for convenience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 17:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Deckard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 22:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S-maw-g. But when I first read it as a kid, Smay-ugg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 13:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this.

Did you know that many armed forces around the world select colourblind people - specifically red/green - for sniper-recon roles as we are more visually sensitive to movement? Not that I can find a reference online.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 12:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your points are all completely valid. I guess my complaint is that - for me - the entire world was set up purely to bring about circumstances where he would have to choose between his own life and the greater good, and the elements of the setup were a little bizarre and arbitrary. Yes, I understand why Loopers would sign up for the program, but WHY would the powers that be put it in place? There is no advantage in it over getting someone else to do it, and that would be much lower risk. And it seemed - to me, again - that the TK McGuffin exists in an otherwise purely technological milieu JUST to provide a threat to society at large. It just didn't fit naturally.

But it seems I'm the only one who feels like this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 13:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I think I saw a different film from the one you saw. The one I saw was trying to be a high-brow sci-fi character study which closed its own loop (see what I did there?) and therefore I would be very surprised to see a [good/worthwhile] sequel. Of course there is probably going to be a crap cash-in sequel, that being the way of the world at the moment.

My complaint is that the rest of the film seemed intentionally plausible - a near-future extrapolation of how OUR society would function with time-travel. Ad then they pasted TK in on top. For me it jarred horribly.

The other big issue is I see no reason why a boss would send an end-of-career Looper back to himself for disposal. Surely sending him to another Looper would make much more sense. But then they wouldn't be called Loopers and we wouldn't have a story.

It just all seemed so contrived to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 18:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean telekinesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 13:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think of it as levels of reality, think of it as metaphor. Everything happens in the real world, but Baby Doll - mentally traumatised beyond coherence - "imagines" herself in different worlds in order to gain some power and control. In the club-world she is a rare "dancing" talent; in the fight-world a kick-ass ninja commando; but in the real world she is a powerless victim of some of the most horrific cruelty I've ever seen on film.

You can read the film as if Baby Doll teaches the other girls to do the same, or that it's just her and, since we see everything from her perspective, that's what's presented on the screen as reality. There's probably some deep insight about looking for "reality" in a flickering series of photographs on a screen, but there you go.

One could argue that this device provides a mechanism for the film-makers to explore the psychology of a victim of horrific abuse without actually showing the abuse and therefore without distracting the audience with cruelty-porn. I would suggest that it's not very successful at that on account of the violence-porn and the skimpy outfits... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 13:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah? Would have been nice if they hadn't felt the need to use the biggest McGuffin of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 12:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is a niggle. But you have to remember that guns have to look good in film. That's how I can put up with guns like the M41A Pulse Rifle in "Aliens" - it's beautifully designed, looks the business, but has the illuminated round counter on the wrong side, facing the camera not the user. The reasoning is obvious and it also pales into insignificance when you notice that the shoulder-mounted lamps serve only to illuminate the actors' faces not what they're looking at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 18:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd add Godspeed You Black Emperor to the list of post-rock, and I'd also suggest that film soundtracks can sometimes be a worthwhile addition to your ambient/downtempo collection, particularly:

Sunshine OST (Jon Murphy and Underworld)
Moon OST (Clint Mansell)
Monsters OST (Jon Hopkins) (for me, the nicest to listen to of all of these)
Book of Eli OST (Atticus Ross)

If you want something with a structure and beat to it without completely losing touch with the Brian Eno end of free form ambient, have a look at:

HECQ
Aes Dana
Minilogue
The Boats
The Field
Peace Orchestra

And if you like those, you might like Trentemoller, particularly "The Last Resort" (but it's too structured to meditate to). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-25 14:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that on Willis' first day on set, Gilliam took him over to a pin board with photos of him doing the three or four "Willis expressions" - pretty much his entire range at that point - across a whole bunch of his movies. They spent five minutes playing Name That Movie together and then Gilliam turns to Willis and says "I don't want to see you using ANY of these expressions in my movie."

And that's why it's Bruce Willis' best performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 11:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a deleted scene from Alien wherein Ripley finds Dallas in a half-turned-into-egg stage. First "k-k-kill meeeee" of the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 11:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought the "father" worked in the deleted scene. More, "You're supposed to be my father but look how fucked-up your relationship is with me," than the theatrical "...and you're my father! Dun dun DUUUUUN!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 04:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the Owner's Club, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
