<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7881</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glimmer of hope for 10,000 refugees left stranded by Australia's inaction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grassley and Feinstein request briefing on Flynn resignation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hope that others may follow suit.

As symbols go, I'll take a symbolic stand against apartheid over deference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also a *really* good point.

The answer is we started with a legal framework that was geared to handle permanent resettlement only and then proceeded to turn it into an adversarial shit fight.

Proper refugee hosting provisions in Australian law are 30 years overdue but we need to defuse the hostile environment the last 20 years of politicking have created before it would function properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that the next sentence is simultaneously necessary and fantasy.

Australia must do what is necessary to assist Indonesia and the UNHCR to ensure that the necessary protection is provided in Indonesia while refugee claims are processed. 

We've abandoned the Bali Process as far as humanitarian engagement is concerned and we're still working through the damage done to our relationship with Indonesia and the tensions we created on this issue with our encroachments.

Without those protections in place turn backs are both a breach of asylum seeker's human rights and absolutely asinine if your objective is to improve safety.  Mixed migration pathways operate on the path of least resistance as it is.  Block one last mile and, as we've already seen had anyone bothered to look north, you open up another, more dangerous option.

If we intend to engage with the region we absolutely should.  We should have been doing so since the early 1990s.

At this point however, *we* need to be getting out ahead of the political problems and putting in place contact points in collaboration with the UNHCR and our neighbours.  We could start today in PNG and work from there and there's clearly no issue funding it given the billions we've spent without a peep from the electorate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Shorten pressured to commit Labor to diplomatic recognition of Palestine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not 3am in DC yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would also guarantee either a de jure or de facto apartheid state in Israel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flynn departure erupts into a full-blown crisis for the Trump White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The officials said the intercepted communications were not limited to Trump campaign officials, and included other associates of Mr. Trump.

With how closely his children have been tied to this whole effort, the family may well be directly involved in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosneft?

I'm inclined to think the motivation is less carrot and more stick however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In which Matt Lauer of all people manages to take Conway apart.

She looks like she's about to burst into tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kellyanne Conway: Michael Flynn knew hed become a lightning rod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morrison pushed NDIS 'hypothecation' announcement despite caution about timing from Turnbull's office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Launched by the Federal Government today in collaboration with Evocca College... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also related and worth a revisit given its handover to the Prime Minister this morning, [The Redfern Statement](http://nationalcongress.com.au/redfern-statement/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm out and about on a mobile phone at the moment.  If I get a chance this evening I'll put together something better sourced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst a start, UBERAssist aren't ramp/lift accessible vehicles.

https://newsroom.uber.com/australia/uberaccess-expanding-transportation-options-2-2/

They're fine for people with folding chairs and walkers etc. that need a little more space and someone with half a clue about how to assist people into and out of a car.

They're *not* a replacement for wheelchair accessible taxis for people who use mobility scooters (other than the little collapsable ones), use fixed manual chairs or motorised chairs and particularly those who are wheelchair bound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partially correct.

I'm concerned how services like disability access etc. will persist in the long run and suspect they're going to need significant propping up.

We've relied on taxis as part of our public transport infrastructure, or at least as a safety net for it, without ever properly bringing them into the PT sphere.  With the advent of unregulated taxi services like Uber and the move to deregulate as a counter to them that fall back is likely to evaporate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  If.

If this next budget is substantially hobbled the leadership team will be gone, assuming the government doesn't come apart at the seams entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But of course he does.  He's a cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen sweet FA as far as proper reporting on this, particularly in an Australian context.

Uber thumbing their nose at legislation should be pretty self explanatory from actions both here and abroad and you can find a fair bit on their treatment of workers globally if you Google. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The WA Liberals probably cost the WA Liberals the election anyway but the implied threat here is far more interesting than the expressed one.

In a battle of spongey invertebrates, I'd wager Joyce has more cartilaginous mass than Turnbull.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used them a bit in the early days because, to be blunt, we couldn't get taxis to pick up black people from our offices.  But having seen how they operate and now the predatory lending bullshit we've seen them pushing I bought a shitbox Falcon wagon and parked it out back.

The theory of the service is sound, it's the total lack of ethics by the business behind it that's the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research shows how petrol retailers pushed prices up in Perth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure they're hilariously abusive to their workers, ignore mandated service requirements and flout the law in a manner which would cause explosive outrage were it in another sector.

But this is reddit and I got something slightly cheaper at the expense of others I don't care about so its all good, right?

I have major issues with the taxi industry, and this protest is spectacularly tone deaf, but I have far, far more concerns with businesses like Uber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Intel Committee looking at legality of Flynn Russia contact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth a read.

https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT203027

It becomes pretty clear, pretty quickly why those wishing to on sell data despise the thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but it took them years to get caught out on it.  Nixon's actions have only been confirmed with statutory declassification.

This one is happening right here, right now and may well end up with enough rope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, a jetski.  That's about what I was expecting.

I refer you again to my comment above.  Inform yourself, or don't.  Good night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can desire something without distress for the lack of it.

Congratulations on the realisation that gender is a social construct independent from sex btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're interested in the reality here, you should read the DSM again.  Or at least the APA commentary on gender dysphoria.

Gender dysphoria is a condition causing a person significant distress or impairment of their functioning.  Gender nonconformity in itself is *not* a mental illness.

If you're not interested in the reality of it, then to be blunt I'm pretty glad you keep your opinion to yourself in public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 20 odd years worth of demonisation and dehumanisation of these people, does that surprise you in the slightest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likely.

That said, this will probably be an argument played out at the gates rather than in a courtroom.  The legal specifics can quickly give way to political optics, and that goes for the PNG and Nauruan governments as much as our own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We shall see.

Article 4 provides for visitation to "any place under its jurisdiction and control where persons are or may be deprived of their liberty, either by virtue of an order given by a public authority or at its instigation or with its consent or acquiescence".

The government will argue against on jurisdiction but it's not entirely clear cut, particularly when the purpose of offshore detention in the first place was to exclude it from local judicial oversight.  Manus probably has a better chance of avoiding scrutiny than Nauru as well because of the partially merged legal structures.

As for the government willingly extending coverage to those camps?  Not a chance in hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TSA screening program risks racial profiling amid shaky science  study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abusive publishers with effective local monopolies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 10:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you needed a demonstration of why our government failed to find its tongue on Trump's Muslim ban.

Utterly disgusting and I've no faith that Labor will do anything other than capitulate, again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Christensen says he will cross floor to back banking inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 10:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who needs insight and reasoned action when you've fear and knee-jerk reaction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As would the prosecution of human rights abuses before our courts.

I wish I could say I was surprised by this from Labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an overreach, not sure I'd describe it as petty however in light of the British Parliament deeming the man unfit to address the Hall.

McKim would have been better served seeking an analogue of the process we've just seen play out in the UK as I don't believe the Parliament here has any similar right of refusal comparable to the key holders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...a lifetime travel pass for a start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with that in mind, when the AP reports that national security aides in the administration have sought information about Polish incursions in Belarus, despite the fact that theres no reason to believe there have been Polish incursions in Belarus, it gives one pause.

Straight from the talking points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She literally backed local branches of Ustase even after getting caught out and called out for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are none

Fierravanti-Wells kind of torpedoes that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake news and alternative facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  About time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vetting requirements are basically incompatible with dealing with refugees in an ethical manner.

They require information to be provided from their country of origin which is unlikely to be forthcoming and can be actively dangerous to ask for in some cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have been a poorly chosen battle but the hint of a spine in Turnbull's a bit of a turn up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether Trump was smart enough to realise it on the call or not, and I'd lean strongly toward the latter, the deal remains utterly toothless in the face of the new vetting decrees in the US.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make Cory Great Again would be more accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With t_d calling for boycotts and Reddit on the list, one can only hope they make good on the threat.

Disappointing to see Musk fumble an opportunity to take stand yet again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grattan Institute report finds 40 per cent of school students disengaged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't but wonder whether Uhlmann has his eyes on preselection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps if Turnbull had sufficient capital to do it.  I very much doubt he has.

Whilst Bernardi could draw a few names, Turnbull's still got to deal with the Abetzs and Morrisons and Fierravanti-Wells of this world.  Not to mention The Nationals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty obvious attempt to emulate elements of it from Bernardi. 

Only he's traded Russian funding for Rinehart funding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rats like Cory Bernardi will merely help to sink the Liberal ship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the year 2525, if man is still alive...

This rather explains why I've vanished off the 3 year plan, again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big money is Gina Rinehart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over a century in fact.

[    ](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/And_you_are_lynching_Negroes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP Fact Check: Conway cites 'massacre' that didn't happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rod reckon's he's going to be Peter's chief of staff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What went wrong? Inside Sunday's raid in Yemen by Navy SEALs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minerals Council's Sid Marris to join PMO in climate role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump can "honour" it without taking a single person.

The vetting procedures now required, namely the need to have information supplied by their country of origin, are incompatible with lawfully or even realistically handling refugees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was an action considered by the Obama administration and ruled out as lacking sufficient intelligence detail and carrying too much risk.

I can't help but wonder, horrified, whether Obama's reluctance contributed to Trump pulling the trigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only Schwarzenegger's reply were possible.

https://twitter.com/Schwarzenegger/status/827169996866347008

I mean, he couldn't be worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schwarzenegger in reply...

https://twitter.com/Schwarzenegger/status/827169996866347008 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump through a loudspeaker, darkly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the lie comes out in the wash.

No request from Australia for transfer of the patient was received by Nauru before our previous statement. Nauru has no control over decisions by Australia on who to transfer. Within the last 30 minutes we have received confirmation from Australia that the patient will be airlifted and this is expected to happen tomorrow.
 

http://www.nauru-news.com/single-post/2017/02/02/Statement-from-Nauru-Health-Department </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://support.twitter.com/articles/18311?lang=en

* **Violent threats (direct or indirect):** You may not make threats of violence or promote violence, including threatening or promoting terrorism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 10:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On who's orders? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a hard "no" then.  Thanks for your contribution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wild theory:

He knew about the deal.  He was told he was "taking refugees from Australia".  He assumed it was white people from Sydney fleeing the dropbear hordes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fucking christ this site's really bought that conspiracy bullshit lock, stock and barrel haven't they?

Do you have any idea what the organisation actually does? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *tropical island shit hole.

Torturing refugees in desert shit holes was more Howard's style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably thinks they voted for Hillary as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP ANZUS

1951-2017 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's already seen as weak and ineffectual.  He just added misleading the public to the list.

On top of that, barring a miracle or the bloodiest of blood money, he's also painted his entire party into a corner on the Nauru and Manus Is deal.  Most, if not all, of those refugees are going to fail the US's new vetting protocol as it requires input from the country of origin which is unlikely to be forthcoming and illegal to seek under our and the UN's protection requirements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something's got to give.

The administration carrying on as it is won't last the year, let alone four. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eternal question for the delcons, do they hate brown people more than they love orange people?

If Bishop was ever going to have the right soapbox, this would be it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's anyone in the Liberal Party with the stones to take a stand on this insult, Turnbull could be on *very* thin ice.

That's a bit of an "if" though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at least time to put a very clear distance between Australia and the current US administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an Australian:  Stay safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nuance you're possibly missing is bipartisan support from our two major parties.

We're about a generation deep at this point into our conservative party (confusingly called The Liberals) making a political point out of asylum seekers to quite some success when it comes to extracting votes from a significant, xenophobic portion of the electorate.

In recent years our centrist party (Labor) have hopped on board on supporting the policies as well.

If you really want to dig into it, following the ramp down in the late 80s and very early 90s of a regional processing framework for asylum seekers flowing out of Vietnam we, as a region, unfortunately did not have the foresight to modernise it instead of shutting it down entirely.

The result is we're one of very, very few in SE Asia with any legal framework around offering protections to asylum seekers.  Offshore processing was established as away of removing these people from the protection of these laws, the oversight of our courts and, as the system has gone from bad to worse, the scrutiny of the press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's subject to the vetting process, it's dead.

The order includes an ability to permanently ban entrants whose identification isn't confirmed by their country of origin.

Not only is cooperation in the event of such a request unlikely from governments accused of persecuting these people, it can not be sought in many cases because of the risk of endangering others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to Mexico: Take care of 'bad hombres' or US might </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electricity prices could double with new coal-fired stations, energy experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the ACLU could use a skilled and experienced attorney at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN producer detained in Atlanta files lawsuit against immigration ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you do say may be used against you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder whether Loughnane and Credlin knew it was coming.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is rather.  Curious if we'll see a repeat in Germany with AfD's links.

Perhaps not with how happy they were to have them in the open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Front National / Russian connection wheels have rather oddly fallen off in recent weeks.

Le Pen had her Russian financing suddenly dry up after a bit of US intelligence interest.

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/21/marine-le-pens-russian-links-us-scrutiny/

https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2016-12-22/le-pen-struggling-to-fund-french-race-after-russian-backer-fails </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia has not been given a preferential 'exemption' from Donald Trump's US visa ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why you read the articles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did Galaxy's poll tell us about freedom of speech and 18C? Not what the IPA said it did </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parakeelia, also Calandrinia

used commonly as feed for cattle and sheep grazed extensively in arid and semi-arid areas of Australia, these plants have a high oxalate content and are suspected of causing deaths in wethers due to obstructive urolithiasis.

Apt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The missing millions: Political donations likened to money laundering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swallow the money: Malcolm Turnbull's donation disclosure delay is foolish and unconscionable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other details are now up with Turnbull's notably absent.

Frankly, raises even more questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia bankrolls Papua New Guinea APEC summit costs, stymies China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration Department pays $1 million compensation to Save the Children workers fired from Nauru </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have told Matthew Guy they were sideways mobile high rises whilst we had the chance.  Just would have needed a Chinese bloke in a suit to front it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's welcome to attend, he's not welcome to claim he's a senator.

It's impersonating an official and, if anyone actually took the man seriously, would have the potential to get you into serious legal strife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is that this hasn't actually occurred as yet and Im seeing others confirming my information.

Hopefully I'm wrong and she's in the air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I maintain it's a huge pity we didn't have a high speed rail project on the boil to pick up some of the slack.

Skills and even facilities on the end of both the perfect, easily installed preliminary track and the southern maintenance base for a east coast network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toyota announces timetable for closure of Altona plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully history repeats a little quicker than 10 months this time around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's puppets all the way down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New acting Attorney General orders DOJ to defend immigration executive order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading between the lines, Ragsdale may have bucked at a deportation policy coming down pipeline.

Time will out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Manservant - Alan Moir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been ridiculous for some time.  It's getting dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Monday Night Massacre continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you're just being willfully offensive

Oh you weren't?

We're done here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Unadulterated realism.

The average Australian has no fucking idea about the intricacies of the legal processes of this country.

Feel free to stick with your alternative facts if you'd prefer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ALP should arrange to have all of Bill Shorten's speaking appointments be conducted outdoors, to a receptive crowd, via a megaphone.

I'm only half joking when I say this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As have Canada, the UK and NZ.  All have spoken out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WA Liberals' Mandurah candidate steps down after negative tweets about PM, women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call your Senator as well, tell them you consider approving Sessions to be tantamount to support for the Muslim ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a frighteningly accurate depiction of the current state of IHMS's standard of "care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you prefer a strict interpretation of our ICCPR requirements with no judicial discretion or do you prefer we just ignore our human rights obligations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You expect detailed understanding of our legal system from an electorate fed soundbites at best.

It's utter garbage but it's also unsurprising.  Now if we had leaders prepared to and capable of leading from the front... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want a prison sentence?  Because that's how you get a prison sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Hottest places in hell' reserved for those remaining neutral: Former US Ambassador unleashes on Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughable that we're all clearing this up after the fact.

Both for the so called "special relationship" between Australia (and Canada and the UK) and this US administration and for the breathtaking incompetence and stupidity of the Muslim ban in the first place.

And still Malcolm can't find his tongue to condemn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could say I was surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These days? To Russian backing oddly enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's correct on a technicality.

The executive order doesn't remove them.  It simply enables them to be removed at whim at any point in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likely, but these and similar statements from other Republicans, are cracks worth working.

If they feel comfortable or feel it necessary to make these comments then you've a reason to identify and work to be done appealing to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collins: Trump's Refugee Ban 'Likely Unconstitutional,' Bannon Appointment 'Entirely Inappropriate' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tracking Congress In The Age Of Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ.  If they cancel a Young Libs meeting every time the Klan turns up they'll never get anything done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way that Bernardi would play second fiddle to Hanson.

And even less chance of him taking orders from Ashby.  For the obvious reason.

Bernardi's a bigoted loon but he's a bigoted loon of a decidedly different flavour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an environment where the electorate is increasingly dissatisfied with the major parties I can not think of a more tone deaf move than a push for a unicameral parliament.

Who better to raise it then than Tone himself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turnbull news conference an exercise in avoidance and obfuscation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay Conversion Therapy Has Been Driven Underground, But Its Still Widespread In Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian Houston, the son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we'll appease Trump.  Why not appease ISIS as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mistreatment of asylum seekers and refugees.

Houston was a major mentor of Morrison (it shows I might add) so the split was pretty significant and reached the point that the church was directly involved in protests at his office while he was immigration minister.

I've not heard much of it in recent years though and I'm left wondering whether the allure of influence has closed the gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess there's a symmetry in turning a blind eye to religious persecution in order to yet again shirk our protection obligations.

The sad thing is that "agreement" seems to be simply that.  An agreement with no further substance, detail or commitment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he's still sidelined from Hillsong.

He'd gone too far even for them at one point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, pity it's in a race to the bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May to warn devolved nations: you have no veto on Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Spider Jerusalem.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four federal judges issue orders blocking parts of Trumps executive order on immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Not even close.

You were already dealing with mass internment at the hands of the nazis well before 1939 along with longstanding hostility across Europe. Jews absolutely had a well founded fear of persecution and the failure to recognise that need for protection cascaded around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now we know the consequences of those actions and have an established international framework borne of a global undertaking not to repeat the mistakes of WW2.

Unfortunately we also have multitudes who fail to learn from history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then that's debatable.  Today it's irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pity his mother isn't around to instill some parental guidance because it's pretty clear, both from past statement and present act, that Mal doesn't give it much thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's incredible how quickly we've forgotten the lessons of the holocaust.

We're doing a fine job of ensuring we'll all get a refresher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the western world can waste away behind ever so leaky walls.

You are centuries too late to put a stop to a multicultural world.  Decades too late to even slow it down much with halts on the movement of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The order also said the Director of National Intelligence and the Chairman of Joint Chiefs of Staff would no longer be automatic principals on the committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the "deal" being nebulous to the point of formlessness, this doesn't entirely surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there's the beginnings of the terminal rift should pressure continue to be applied to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pauline Hanson rejects claim she is chief of staff's James Ashby's puppet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the more reason why it's vital that the people raise their own armies and have them march.

Though I'd still suggest placards and song be the standard issue for the time being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.  Though it's more disgust than amuse for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you've protections in place at least.

Having seen [shit like this](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CwXwe6AXUAQsiCp.jpg) barfed up in the UK, I can still see it getting pretty ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull as well by what I'm reading.

https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2017/jan/29/donald-trump-malcolm-turnbull-phone-call-immigration-ban-muslim

http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-10-30/manus-nauru-refugees-asylum-seekers-to-be-banned-turnbull-says/7978228

Then we knew his hypocrisy already.

This has all been stayed by the Eastern District Federal Court just a few minutes ago.  It's going to be interesting to see how aggressively this White House will go after the courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good first step.

There's going to be a hell of a fight from here.  And dare I say, a hell of a fight coming to protect your judiciary from your executive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FSH88aE_ggQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naturally. He's a coward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twelve Nobel laureates, thousands of academics sign protest of Trump immigration order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Recalls Staff to U.S. After Trump Immigration Order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 11:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ms Dhu's family's fight for prosecutions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually Russia are doing to France what Russia likely did to you.

Front National has long standing Russian financing.

http://www.politico.eu/article/le-pen-russia-crimea-putin-money-bank-national-front-seeks-russian-cash-for-election-fight/

http://time.com/3605080/russia-france-national-front/

Funding that's supposedly dried up in recent weeks, after this.

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/21/marine-le-pens-russian-links-us-scrutiny/

https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2016-12-22/le-pen-struggling-to-fund-french-race-after-russian-backer-fails </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd guess this is more about payloads for SpaceX than subsidies for Tesla.

Doubly so given what a cozy relationship with Trump will look like to much of Tesla's present and potential customer base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labor 'n Vain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well that's the campaign slogan sorted...](https://i.imgur.com/maZ4SYw.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking more along the lines of O'Brien's interview of Shier.

If something of that measure is already beyond reach there's bigger problems than Guthrie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to get Guthrie on for her 7.30 interview me thinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairfax generally has had its fangs out for the Greens for a while and notably ramping up following Massola's ridiculously poorly targeted declarations hit piece.

You can't write off all the reporting, and this has a sizeable nugget of truth below the hyperbole, but check their sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABC's chief operating officer David Pendleton resigns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A structured and communicating shadow executive and departmental interface is starting to look like something worth building.

This is beginning to turn from destructive to dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is getting payments from foreign governments. We have no idea what they are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump parrots Fox News again with attack on Chelsea Manning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious whether this sees a reaction from the executive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Washington Post is the most-read news source among government leadership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is some spectacular irony in a Russian backed and funded "nationalist" international.

Of course it makes much more sense as a coordinated attempt at destabilisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refreshing is super hit and miss.  I'll get a desktop view, than navigate back to mobile though I think it is eventually unsticking it and staying desktop after several attempts.  Is this just a caching thing you think?

There's no double tap / long tap refresh in iOS AFAIK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and as I've said that reclamation was driven from within those communities, not dictated from outside of it.  Baazaa's example above is the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't work I'm afraid.  I'm on 10.2.1 as of yesterday if that's possibly made a difference.

From the in reddit menu I'll get it for a page load or so but navigation around the site rapidly returns me to the mobile view.

iOS's in built Request Desktop Site dialogue isn't respected at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You expect me to tip toe around other's bigotry because it makes them uncomfortable?

The real world isn't your safe space.

If you want change you need to fight for it.  If you want to hold it back, don't be surprised when you're fought against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Safari on iPad served mobile site. Safari on iOS generally can not request the desktop site. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tablets should be served the desktop site.  Between reduced functionality and an incredibly wasteful layout on a screen that size, the mobile site isn't even close to appropriate currently.

Further more, **please** honour a browser's request for the desktop site. Simply refreshing back to the mobile view is awful UX and absolutely infuriating if you need to access something specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I was under the impression they were combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think the comments are bad, you should see my inbox.

It's about the response I expected unfortunately.  This subreddit never fails to disappoint on issues like this nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really!? iPad now served mobile view in Safari, does not honour request for desktop site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil Rights Group Rebukes Trump Justice Dept. Over Case Delays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump actions affirm fears for environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's that Trump projection again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And once reclaimed there'd be no issue with the media using it.  You're not going to be able to dictate reclamation of a term on behalf of even a large minority, let alone a relatively small one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A prejudiced society's ability to turn an innocuous word into a slur neither prevents nor prohibits individuals and organisations from choosing not to partake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Convince the Republicans they can disenfranchise some minority voters and they'll sit up and beg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's likely more than that.

This is very easy to feed into wholesale, federally orchestrated voter suppression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comment: Trans people are not the punchline to a joke. The media must do better on gender identity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A similar facility is provided by The Guardian at: https://securedrop.theguardian.com

And by the ICIJ at: https://www.icij.org/securedrop

Numerous other media organisations, globally, offer equivalent facilities.

If you do have information worth leaking in the current environment, please *do not* entrust it to a single source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
