<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal leader Philippe Couillard dodges language bullet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 15:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 16:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing happened with the US in Iraq and Afghanistan... I'm disgusted that we couldn't do better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 14:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, but failing to approach it at all is just asking for trouble.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 14:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, we're already geoengineering our planet, we might as well go about it scientifically and with a clear perspective on the consequences.

People had the same misgivings about genetic engineering... And, while those misgivings are merited and need to be considered, it's not hubris to suggest that there should be no focus of science that is fully taboo.  

The science and technology of geoengineering will be needed in the future, regardless of whether they're used to combat climate change on earth.  But if they are used on earth, having some capacity to control the weather could mean major economic advantages.  We need only look to the [common practice of cloud seeding](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cloud_seeding) to observe such advantages.  Furthermore, I think we can all agree to its necessary potential in terraforming beyond earth.

Continuing to have little to no control of weather and climate is folly and will only make us victims to the inevitable circumstances that will follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 14:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, we're already geoengineering our planet, we might as well go about it scientifically and with a clear perspective on the consequences.

People had the same misgivings about genetic engineering... And, while those misgivings are merited and need to be considered, it's not hubris to suggest that there should be no focus of science that is fully taboo.  

The science and technology of geoengineering will be needed in the future, regardless of whether they're used to combat climate change on earth.  But if they are used on earth, having some capacity to control the weather could mean major economic advantages.  We need only look to the [common practice of cloud seeding](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cloud_seeding) to observe such advantages. 

 Continuing to have little to no control of weather and climate is folly and will only make us victims to the inevitable circumstances we're certain to face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give geoengineering a chance to fix climate change: David Keith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 14:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give geoengineering a chance to fix climate change: David Keith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 14:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 15:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't know or understand what these researchers have published, but here's my heavily prejudiced, nonsensical ramblings on the subject..."

More or less... 

If NP wanted to write up a critical editorial of the model, McFarland could, I don't know, interview dissenting researchers in the area. But no, it's wild associations to Elizabeth May and David Suzuki.

Minus Coyne and a couple others, the NP editorial group are turning into a soapbox void of any serious journalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelly McParland: NASA-backed study indicates its Elizabeth May, or mass extinction. Your choice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 15:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 18:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see these criticisms submitted as a letter to the editors of the NP.

Blatchford's cheese has slid right off her cracker for this op/ed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanford opening new lab to study bad science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 18:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 23:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite entry is actually the last one.  Troubleman is such an awesome Marvin Gaye song:

http://youtu.be/Usl-h5f-8W0

The movie it was for looks hilarious too.

http://youtu.be/_K5IEqmrUio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 04:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally, I feel like Batman was actually the worst thing that happened to him... Well, Batman Returns anyway.

Him in Beetlejuice, or hell even Much Ado About Nothing. He's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 00:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. I hope she writes more op-eds in the Sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 14:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I wouldn't force anyone to vote, just put a mildly irritating tax on not voting. 

Also, if I were American I'd make election day a holiday, I don't believe this would work in Canada, since the day can change too easily, but I think people would be more accepting of the responsibility of voting if several of their other responsibilities were discharged for the rest of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 22:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disenfranchise all voters and then award voting citizenship on the basis of intellectual merit and civic service.

(I'm joking of course, Starship Troopers is a funny book/movie) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 22:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think he's qualified to consult on the subject area that's a major focus of his academic research? Really?

The guy who writes books on the topic. The guy Harvard Law has invited on more than one occasion to do fellowships. Who teaches this stuff professionally... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 20:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I would propose the writing of a BilingualismBot that replies to comments written exclusively in English with a Google translation in French. 

However, that's not really the point here. We're looking to express inclusion of francophones in our community dialogue.

I support this suggestion completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 19:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fair; I don't expect any party to be more or less corrupt than any other. Or any other human institution for that matter.

Awareness and opportunity of corruption though will be proportional to current level of relative power and influence.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lakota Indian Promotes New Digital Currency, Mazacoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 23:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 23:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was in Chong's riding I'd vote conservative without reservation.  I love that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 14:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went looking for an article [blaiming rail-bitumen for why wheat isn't moving](http://theglobeandmail.com/report-on-business/economy/railcar-shortage-leaves-farmers-in-lurch/article15370310/), but apparently that's not the real culprit. Found this [blog post](http://albertadiary.ca/tag/canadian-wheat-board) giving some interesting info. Skim till about the 10th paragraph.

The real problem, as farmer Bill Gehl, chairperson of the Canadian Wheat Board Alliance, a group representing farmers who tried to save the board, said last November is that without the farmer-controlled single-desk Wheat Board, nobody is coordinating grain sales, transportation logistics, and the efficient use of port terminal facilities.

That, in turn means port terminals are now competing with each other to use rail transport capacity just to generate grain handling revenue.

The result is they do not always have the right grade and type of grain in place so ships either cannot get a full load at one terminal, as they could when our Wheat Board arranged deliveries, or ships have to wait for more of the correct grade and type of grain to arrive, Mr. Gehl said. The result is too many ships waiting much too long and that means farmers get less money.

Added together, Mr. Larsen says, this is truly a train wreck of immense proportions. If we assume last years western crop was worth about $7 billion, it means more than $2.8 billion has been taken out of the wests economy! Include the effect of the drop in the U.S. dollar, since most grain is sold in that currency, the actual decline has been more than 50 per cent.

Another thing Canadian farmers will soon be free of is the excellent reputation Canadian wheat and barley had with buyers abroad  Japanese and Chinese end users are already complaining the new privatized Canadian system isnt delivering the quality theyve expected for generations from the Wheat Board.

Edit: Basically, it just seems that the market hasn't shifted to account for logistical aspects of the grain trade yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 22:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real problem as I understand it is trending 'demand'.  Power consumption and location in the grid are challenging with current infrastructure.  Adding storage capacity  is often brought up along with the concept of a 'smart grid' where they actively measure and trend demand.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 18:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My limited understanding is that a great deal of electrical energy is lost in the [transmission and distribution](http://www.nema.org/Products/Documents/TDEnergyEff.pdf) (pdf link) from the power plant, and also trying to match production against the system load. 

A good example would be countries trying to use renewables, like Denmark, where they sell off a lot of their excess power on the cheap, and then have to [purchase it back](http://www.scientificamerican.com/article/gathering-the-wind/) when the load increases.  [Ontario has a similar problem to this](http://www.thestar.com/business/2011/08/29/ontario_pays_others_to_take_its_surplus_power.html).

If we had the capacity to store the surplus power that we generate in the grid, not only would be have an easier time avoiding blackouts, but we could run our power-generating facilities a lot more efficiently, only generating power to top up the system and saving our surplus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other thread is getting more responses to this, but personally I would invest in the loading and storage capacity of the Ontario power grid.  

As a for instance, in California Tesla is starting to sell their advanced batteries separate from their cars and people are putting them in their homes to minimize their power-draw from the grid during peak loads.

There are other larger simpler options that can be implemented at the neighbourhood-scale.

Currently, we waste ~~most~~ a lot of the electricity we generate. (Edit: hyperbole) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 16:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infrastructure for distributed loading and storage on the power grid would go a long way.

Tesla is starting to sell their advanced batteries separate from the cars and people are putting them in their homes to minimize their power-draw from the grid during peak loads. A strategy in this vein for the Ontario grid would help solve the actual problem, rather than just temporarily alleviating the symptoms of the cost of electrical power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 16:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, I don't mean it like that. If the govt uses resources to collect that much capital, they should do something higher impact.

I'm a big basic income supporter, but I hate half-measures like this where the problem doesn't go away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 14:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why they wouldn't spend $440M on smarter infrastructure instead, and bring down costs that way. The gov't goes to all the trouble of taking your money, only to give a meager bit back... Ridiculous.

Edit: We should be [modernizing our power grid infrastructure](http://science.howstuffworks.com/environmental/green-tech/sustainable/grid-energy-storage.htm) to allow for distributed storage and loading to reduce the costs for everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 16:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right... As terrifying a prospect as that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 15:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I kept saying Sudetenland in my head, but wasn't sure if I was remembering correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 14:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Chong. I love his reform ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 07:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, this really has little to do with the Crimean people, and everything to do with Russia securing strategic resources it previously held in the region with a friendly gov't.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 07:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Historically relevant; recompensing Ukraine for the land becomes more defensible.  

I'm not saying this isn't a terrible situation, with an equally atrocious set of events that have lead us to this point.  However, moving forward means a realistic diplomatic resolution, despite how outrageous Russia's conduct is in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 06:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are currently annexing it, whether or not it's validated won't change the fact that it is so.  

One option: isolate Russia, 'send a message', economic sanctions, halt trade, depress European markets further, damage to the world economy and markets, if Russia isn't economically destabilized leading to uprisings relations normalize and Russia keeps Crimea.

2nd option: negotiate some kind of  realistic diplomatic resolution where Russia gets Crimea (which they already have, and they're keeping), and the new Ukrainian state isn't crippled economically.  At least with some kind of 'purchase' they get something out of this.  As things currently stand, they'll be digging themselves out of an economic hole for a decade or more without an armed conflict occurring.

Call it appeasement, there are certainly some parallels with ~~the Anschluss~~ the Sudetenland, but Crimea isn't Czechoslovakia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 06:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So it's okay to violate national sovereignty so long as ethnicities match up?

The morality of the maneuver is moot.  They've sacked Crimea, without firing a shot, and they won't lose face and give it up, regardless of any economic sanctions.  The largely Russian inhabitants of Crimea also make 'taking it back' morally grey. 

 you can make it clear that any attempt to expand by military force will be made to fail, one way or the other, so as to discourage further attempts.

I am honestly curious what you would suggest for this.  Economic sanctions would probably work, seeing as the Russian economy is already faltering.  However, the damage to the world economy to cut off Russia isn't going to be insignificant.  There's also the possibility that destabilizing Russia economically could cause political uprising there, which might sound good on paper, but would mean instability over a very large region and several global markets.

Some kind of realistic diplomatic resolution must occur, we're all connected now.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 05:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You definitely can't out-macho Russia.  Jingoism or military escalation isn't the answer.  

Frankly, given that Crimea is ethnically more or less Russian, its being annexed isn't completely unjust.  

However, the stresses that are being leveled on the new Ukrainian state, and the amount of funds that have been [robbed out of the country](http://www.theguardian.com/world/2014/feb/27/ukraine-search-missing-billions-yanukovych-russia) are the part what concern me the most.  Furthermore, the [Russian economy is tumbling](http://www.forbes.com/sites/maggiemcgrath/2014/03/03/russian-rate-hike-ukrainian-unrest-send-stocks-for-a-tumble/) and everyone is shorting the ruble, so they're not actually in great condition following this; to say nothing of the ["G7" pulling out of the next G8 meeting](http://www.cbc.ca/news/world/ukraine-crisis-g7-jointly-condemns-russia-halts-g8-prep-1.2557174) which was supposed to be in Sochi.  

I would like to see a negotiated settlement where Russia buys Crimea from Ukraine.  Sort of like the [Louisiana Purchase.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louisiana_Purchase) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 20:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These lists are pretty common in the US, there should be plenty of data on whether they are at all effective for deterring repeat offences. However, I suspect theyre not effective and the program will simply cost money and succeed in winning votes... It's also probably not constitutional and will eventually get struck down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 23:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like they're probably great for targeting a relatively elderly demographic... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 02:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably right, but if there's a peer reviewed study published by UMiami I'll be more interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redefining skills for an age when machines outsmart humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 20:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 06:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came across some interesting data after our conversation at the convention about this.  Interestingly enough, the manufacturing capacity and production from the US (and probably Canada too) has continued to rise unabated regardless of economic downturns over the past few decades.  Manufacturing jobs, however, have stagnated and are going down.  

Automation...

Canada needs to be more concerned about making new innovative products and less about faltering brands and unskilled labour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 03:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'School' changes a lot after you get out of the typical bachelors.  I'm in the 3rd year at the graduate level (engineering), and my 'classes' are just getting together with researchers from other backgrounds and talking about interesting topics.  

Everything becomes self directed. You really just try to investigate stuff you're interested in.  I don't do any memorization.

The only real downside is that you get to be poor. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 17:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, something like the convention should be easier to organize around since we're all there anyway. It was good meeting you btw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 15:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part of the convention was actually Stphane Dion. That guy is so badass in real life. He hangs out quietly at the edge of a room, and then just appears suddenly and without warning at a mic to yell about a topic.

My other favorite part was meeting Marc Garneau when I got up up during a policy session to defend the role of the National Science Advisor, and the resolution that the position should be reinstated.

Beyond that just meeting and hanging out with so many people from this sub was really awesome.

Another amusing thing that happened is I have slightly longer hair right now so I kept getting mistaken for Justin Trudeau as long as my back was turned. One woman kept demanding to know if I was his secret half-brother throughout the convention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 23:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This policy should be based on more than just science because now it involves weighing short-term vs long-term public benefits

Agreed, a certain amount of hedged risk is appropriate in strategic policy decisions. Hopefully the initiative pays off as opposed to setting the industry back longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 22:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see this being the new norm though. Direct attacks on Justin aren't sticking, so they'll go after anyone near him to cut his legs out from under him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In his speech on Thursday where he noted the Canadian debt-to-GDP ratio with respect to the UK   USA, and then said we had 'room to invest'; it sounded like a clear indication that he intends to do deficit-spending.  Especially if he's not intending to raise taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 07:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purely speculation: I'm curious whether the weight of the pond/temperature-shifts can cause the clay to fracture and allow seepage over time...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 15:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever been unable to buy bread, or have clean water, and there aren't even any cops around to prevent protests, because there are no protests.  It's just a warzone with buildings exploding and predatory militias rounding up and putting a gun in your hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Predictably *less* violent and by definition not chaotic, since it's predictable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 21:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morality, like money, is fungible... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stability is stability, I mean come on.  Bloody civil war is worse than a corrupt dictatorship any day of the week, especially since there's no telling who will come out on top.  

Saying that the ends don't justify the means would be a better argument. 

Honestly, I'd like to see an outcome more like what's occurring in Myanmar right now for many of these states.  You're right that simply propping up these governments isn't the answer.  However, /u/truejaywasright is right (hah) in pointing out that any solutions in this region needs to be brokered along with China, Russia, and any other power that will add to that final stability.

Unfortunately, that will probably have to wait until oil is no longer worth recovering. Or, like in the case of N. Korea, there's no longer a need for a buffer state between China and Japan.

The status quo is better than any other achievable outcome under current circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 14:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't deny the existence of repression, nor that propping up corrupt states is morally reprehensible. However, there is an argument for supporting stability in that region, as allowing the overturning of other corrupt governments in the region hasn't lead to better or less repressive outcomes for citizens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 03:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think you mean disenfranchised.

Wouldn't this mean we'd taken away their vote?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retired soldiers, Mounties hit by Conservative budget changes - Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 00:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 23:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also thought it was kind of an arbitrary Canadian literarature plug... she plugged a lot of stuff on that AMA. I'm not sure she's not a robot at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 20:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was making a funny. I didn't feel her book preferences were especially consequential.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 14:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true, she really lost my vote when she said her favorite book was The Stone Angel by Margaret Laurence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 05:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She claimed in an edit she'd come back and answer questions over time, but who knows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 00:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why anyone would give you a hard time for your comments, JP.  That AMA was an condescending affront to the reddit community at large.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 19:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She definitely wasn't adequately prepared for 'what this is'...  It's sad too, because this would have been a great way to build her image and brand.  Even just a modicum of frankness and honesty would have gone a long way on that AMA.  Wasted opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was not pretty...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 161 LPC policy resolutions to be debated this month in Montreal posted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 14:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 16:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Further to ending subsidies, I'd like see them actually make a very high upper limit to donations, and then just institute an increasing tax rate on donations above $1200.  Then people can donate large amounts if they really want to and it will act as an extra revenue stream for the government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 23:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is senate approval required for a constitutional amendment?  

I'm just curious if Trudeau could be elected, face a largely conservative-member senate, and then somehow run the gauntlet of constitutional reform to abolish that senate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelly McParland: Introducing, the new and improved Liberal party. Now get out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 18:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand it this outcome is unlikely, because the various minimum income strategies are not funded by 'printing money', but through tax policy, and as such there is no net change in the total money supply.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 04:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised that the Elections Act isn't part of the constitution.  It seems too much a conflict of interest if whichever party holds sway in the commons can just change something so fundamental to the electoral process.  Especially if they're currently under several investigations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 00:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my perspective I see this as an excellent way to spur innovation and entrepreneurship. When you're worried about financial security you don't take risks. Give Canadians a real financial safety net instead of a welfare trap and they will start more small businesses and startups, which will provide more jobs.

Widespread automation is going to disappear conventional labour. Canada needs new economic sectors or it will cease to be globally competitive.

**Edit:** I want to [draw attention to this short video](http://youtu.be/u6XAPnuFjJc) [10:48] that details a counter-intuitive disconnect between a person's personal motivation and financial rewards, which is really good to think about when considering the merits of any minimum income strategy.  Please take a moment to watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 18:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without reservation? I would have thought it would be limited to other parties/parliamentarians etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 13:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if there's anything buried in the terms of service agreements for accessing these WiFi points that effectively legalize this surveillance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 13:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my assumption as well. I wonder if a dedicated security guard is necessary or if having a police officer check in throughout the day, even just by radio, would be sufficient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 15:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised the impact on major sports franchises isn't being brought up more in the media as an easier way to communicate the issue to readers and the electorate at large.

Reminding Canadians why the Quebec Nordiques and the Winnipeg Jets had to move to the US, because they couldn't remain profitable in Canada, could make the recent changes to the value of the dollar a lot more unpopular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lower Canadian dollar could have huge impact on NHL teams, affect CFL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 15:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lower Canadian dollar could have huge impact on NHL teams, affect CFL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 15:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme weather cost Canada record $3.2B, insurers say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 20:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamilton loses over 20 top environmental scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 20:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 02:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coal is pretty typical, fracking chemicals can be fairly exotic though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean the price to individual users, rather total price of digitization. Also, when does it become available again, presuming they're currently warehousing materials that are going to be digitized. These materials could be unavailable to individual users for years in the mean time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Findlay says that it is not clear that all of the records will remain accessible, or that the department has the resources to digitize its entire collection. We dont know what has been discarded, what criteria was used or how the digitization will happen, he says. The rationale was cost-cutting, so where is the money for digitization going to come from?

Digitizing isn't free, I think it's fair to consider the timeline and price associated with making these records available again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 19:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this obviously hasn't taken place in Canada, I felt it was topical to consider this outcome with respect to the numerous closures of environmental and water research stations that have been in the news recently.

It's not out of the realm of possibility for spills like this to occur in Canada with similarly unknown results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans Become Unwilling Test Subjects in West Virginia Chemical Spill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 19:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olivia Chow 'seriously considering' run for Toronto mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 18:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olivia Chow 'seriously considering' run for Toronto mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 18:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olivia Chow 'seriously considering' run for Toronto mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 18:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's likely that they would pass this bill.  If they're suspicious of some staffers it makes more sense to investigate them privately, and then invent a reason to excuse them.  

If they passed this bill, and then it was official knowledge that this person or that person had previously or currently subscribed to a political affiliation other than the party in power, then it would open the government to too many potential discrimination lawsuits.  

It's really just a lose lose bill for any governing party to pass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 07:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are probably good bets: 

http://theagenda.tvo.org/blog/agenda-blog/greatest-political-speeches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 07:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> delightful. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 22:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why they defunded the MRI and NMR stuff. The environmental and wastewater stuff made for a pretty obvious trend, but those other ones stood out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby boomers not to blame for youth unemployment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 19:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby boomers not to blame for youth unemployment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 19:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 19:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These seemed like very interesting talking points coming from Prentice.  I know some users on this sub think he might try and come back to win the leadership of the CPC someday.

This quote in particular struck in line with him moving in that direction:

 "In a world focused on environmental issues generally, and climate change specifically, energy leadership and environmental leadership have become two sides of the same coin. Today, if you are in the energy business, you are in the environment business," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 19:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The unfortunate reality is that you have to get to a sales point, regardless of what it is you end up transporting.  

If they did all the refining in Canada, it wouldn't change the fact that all of the industries that depend on purchasing petroleum products have existing infrastructure to buy it from say the gulf coast, or Texas.  

Canada is actually a pretty good example of this reality.  We have all these oil and gas reserves, and yet we continue to buy it from the existing sales point in the States rather than invest in the infrastructure ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 01:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One major area of health policy that needs to be revisited is the manufacturing of the influenza vaccines.  

The current process involving chicken eggs really isn't flexible enough, in terms of production, compared to available alternatives.  If a pandemic starts, or if the flu-variant that gains supremacy doesn't match with expectation put forward by [the WHO](http://www.phac-aspc.gc.ca/publicat/ccdr-rmtc/13vol39/acs-dcc-4/index-eng.php#siv), or if in the case of this article, the demand for vaccination is just higher than expected, it's not possible for industry to increase supply to meet that sudden demand.

[Several alternatives are emerging](http://www.reuters.com/article/2013/01/19/us-flu-vaccines-idUSBRE90I0AI20130119) in the US, capable of far more rapid deployment, that should be more closely examined at the policy-level here in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flu vaccine supply boosted by half-million doses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 01:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Rhubarb' Battery Could Store Energy of Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 02:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 04:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy to say the Liberals never call me.  They're pretty good about just sending emails every once in a while with messages from different party members.  Easy to read or delete depending on my level of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aussie invention eliminates piston rings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 18:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this is a further sign of a loosening of power from the PMO.  A few years ago, it would be pretty unlikely for this admission to be made by a backbencher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 18:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised the conservatives instead of pretending the problem doesn't exist haven't considered just acknowledging climate change and funding research in geoengineering as their approach to combating the problem.  Then at least they would have a talking point other than denial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 04:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~I think you mean 'unfavourably'?~~

No, but the Bank of Canada is an independent body, and as per the article, it's very unconventional for the finance minister to make any statements regarding interest rates, which are the sole purview of the Governor of the BoC.

 More to the point, how is this any of his business? The minister of Finance doesnt set interest rates in this country: the Bank of Canada does.

i.e. these answers Flaherty has given are not just out of character for him, but out of character for any finance minister ever.

Mr. Flaherty doing so to screen for Poloz would seem to tip their hand that the Tories are seeing themselves as feeling vulnerable about their federal appointments lately.  Possibly due to senate scandals of the past year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 02:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The raising of interest rates is typically viewed as a fairly unpopular move by businesses.  I feel as though Flaherty is actually carrying water for Stephen Poloz in this case - taking the negative focus on to himself to test the waters on raising rates, so when they are increased in 2014 the new governor won't receive as much flack from business for the move. 

The [selection of Stephen Poloz to succeed Marc Carney](http://www.cbc.ca/news/business/stephen-poloz-named-next-bank-of-canada-governor-1.1302494) this past year as the Governor of the BoC seems to fit with a similar pattern to the appointment of Justice Nadon to the Supreme Court in that both were [unexpected selections](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/national/what-justice-nadons-appointment-says-about-the-supreme-courts-future/article16192045/?page=all) by the Tories.  

I think it's fair that the gov't doesn't want those appointments to be viewed unpopularly, which means taking measures to keep them from looking bad in the media.  In this case, Flaherty could be getting out in front of the rate-hike, blaming it on 'international pressure' from the OECD and IMF, taking the focus off Poloz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gecko feet will let robot minions fix space stations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 19:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 23:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In scientific research, a conclusion follows directly from a hypothesis (made by a researcher), which provokes the initial experiment in the first place.  Therefore to divorce the conclusions from the researcher is impossible in the scientific method.

It's the communication of those conclusions which is inherently political.  So the question is, should the communication of research conducted by government scientists be restricted by the state.  

Various countries have different policies in this regard; however Canada under the tories have erred on the side of being [more restrictive](http://news.nationalpost.com/2013/04/01/information-commissioner-to-investigate-harper-governments-muzzling-of-federal-scientists/).  This hasn't been just with regard to science, but with regard to communication in general.  

It's not a war on science, it's just controlling the message.

That said, the Canadian public finances this research and unless it's something dangerous for public consumption, access to that research should be available.  Further, just because one is employed by the government shouldn't restrict their ability to communicate as a free citizen provided they announce that they are speaking from their expertise and not from their office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercury levels rising in expanse around Alberta oilsands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 19:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 01:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true, Favreau was given a lot more flexibility and the expectations were much lower with the first movie.  The fact that he was able to hire Downey in the first place is a testament to that.  Plus the film was made by Marvel before it was purchased by Disney 2009.

I think we've probably seen the end of any risky or edgey superhero films from any character with an established fan-base at this point.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 03:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first two acts were pretty good but the third act and the way they set up the Cerberus scenario fell flat for me, although the apocalyptic scenario they devised was pretty clever. They shouldn't have let the president's son escape. He should have been in permanent danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 02:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be curious to learn in further research if there's any link between this effect and oncogenesis.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 22:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see Kenney take over, but I feel like whoever grabs the leadership might end up stepping down soon after when they can't maintain the previous success the party received in 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 17:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The Conservative party passed a motion at the convention to go after John's and not prostitutes

Interesting, were they any suggested provisions/mechanisms for this?  For instance will brothels be legal, but somehow patronizing them will be illegal?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 00:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, how many waterloo people are on this sub anyway? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 14:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the idea behind such a program, and I think overall it would be a major boon to the economy, but one bias in the previous studies that has always concerned me is that the participants always know the financial-support is temporary. Would the results still be as good if the policy was tested long term? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 14:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why did Kenney break ranks I wonder? Assuming he didn't make his Ford comments on impulse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very much like this idea. :)

I'm looking forward to running into the thorium proposal guys from Alberta.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 19:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my first party membership after a friend I met on this subreddit who lives in the same town as me invited me out to a party function that required membership (until then it hadn't clicked in my head that just because you vote for a party doesn't make you a 'card-carrying member'). 

Since then I've been out to a few events and am attending the next policy convention, which I'm pretty excited for. The people in my riding are all pretty nice and fun to have discussions with. 

So, all-in-all very positive experience thus far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 00:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But, the preview suggests it's something to boost astronaut morale.

Hot showers maybe?  He might have devised a solar-heating concept as opposed to solar power.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 00:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really is a good public health investment, HPV keeps getting linked to more and more varieties of cancer.  I hope eventually they have a therapeutic vaccine instead of just the current preventative ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 22:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've come to the comments section for something other than speculation, I hope you find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 21:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but feel like the timing of this is to re-frame perspectives on the recent G20 story to an "everybody spies narrative".

Not that I think this narrative is inaccurate, since I think every nation and several private organizations are indeed always seeking to gather intelligence, and I think most Canadians expect this of our government. However, I wonder if it would be more valuable to turn this known spy or give them false information rather than out him for more favorable media coverage.

If this is to deflate the recent G20 story from the CBC and Snowden, then it's basically spending national security capital for partisan benefit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RCMP arrest Ontario man for attempt to sell naval secrets to China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 21:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 02:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was probably referring to this subsidiary:

http://www.qnx.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 01:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the first forms of these could come a lot earlier, especially with the high proportion of elderly citizenry in Japan right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesse Brown - The CBC's secret deal with the Harper government [Video 4:01] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 15:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Geist - The Trans Pacific Partnership IP Chapter Leaks: Canada Pushing Back Against Draconian U.S. Demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 20:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Election Quilt  Runoff Voting Explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 16:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but it certainly wasn't the attack ads that were the cause of Dion's failure.

By this do you mean the debates?

I would say Dion had a lot in common with Richard Nixon in the sense that he's a very intelligent policy maker and is apparently very good in one-on-one interactions, but on television he lacked charisma and just didn't look and sound right.

Regarding the comparison to Nixon, I'm referring to when Nixon and JFK had the [first televised presidential debate in US history](http://content.time.com/time/nation/article/0,8599,2021078,00.html).  Those listening on the radio thought Nixon won, while those watching on TV were taken in by JFK's looks and charm, catapulting him in the polls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trudeau gets online backlash after his surprise pick for most admired country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foolish for Canada to be too clear on foreign investment rules, Harper says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 19:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 14:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT:  Unopened toothbrushes and contact lens solution + case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 22:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty of laissez-faire subs for political discussion where anything goes. I would rather this sub remain something unique from what's readily available elsewhere. 

  I understand the need to have rules that sometimes are broad and overreaching, it makes moderating life much simpler and easier. 

I don't think it's fair for you to suggest that the mods have set up the rules to be broad or overreaching, thus making them easier to enforce.  First, the rules are very specific and minimal in order to maintain this as an open forum where actual content and perspectives can be posted and discussed as objectively as possible without being suffocated by lazy downvotes.  Second, the mods contribute and curate in most threads, and are hardly taking an 'easy' time of it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 02:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was hilarious to read, though I would swear some of those phrases must have been said today. 

For instance:
 Hysterical (1943)
 Deliberate distortion (1968)
 Deliberate falsehood (1961)
 Deliberately trying to pervert (1960)
 Deliberately deceived (1960)
 Deliberately distorted (1972)
 ...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 21:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that many people will sign up?  I would think the average person/student might not be able to pick up and go to Montreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 20:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just filled out the intent form.  Please let me know for the delegate meetings, this could be pretty interesting I think.

Do you know how many delegates/riding get sent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 17:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm going to try and get out for the LPC one too, I've never been to a political convention before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 18:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting the way that the major indicator of poverty used in this case was analysis of aerial photos to find houses with thatch instead of tin roofs.  

If a similar program was conducted in Canada, it's been suggested that distributing funds would be linked to tax returns, but I've always been curious how many Canadians living in poverty actually file tax returns.  I tried looking up a stat for it just now but couldn't find one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 02:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strong R D tax incentives are already in place, the government is practically throwing money at companies to do research through universities (not that it's effective at all).  

The pulling new markets out of the ground aspect interests me more, I admit.  I wonder how many federal dollars go towards things like accelerator centres and young entrepreneurship (not that money is necessarily the answer).  It's definitely hard at the federal level to make small impacts without making a mess of things, though I think a lot of small impacts is the answer here.

Everyone I know who has started a company has inevitably moved south because the environment was just better for start-ups.  Investment, mentorship, etc.

Your earlier comment about draft-picks for sports teams reminded me of an idea I had a little while ago about how it might be interesting to develop a conference/festival sort of like SXSW around the idea of setting up a competitive draft-style system for helping companies/investors to make relationships with new inventors/creators.  

Set up a government-sponsored bursary program to fly inventors/creators out to the location with matching dollars from industry partners as part of the sponsorship-packages.  Offer start-up workspace in Canada at accelerator centres to help keep business foundations in Canada.

The conference would be a competition with lots of online voting and free PR for inventors that want to get their products noticed that could match funding from small individual donors like kickstarter with a matching investment from whichever industry-partner that wins the pick for that group in the draft, and another matching investment from the gov't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 02:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably should have written it explicitly that a low dollar is not a realistic policy strategy.

That said, I did have difficulty considering what *would* succeed.  Reducing the corporate tax rate alone might not be sufficient to really grow new markets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 18:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything I'd like to see corporate income taxes reduced and look into alternative revenue models.

I'd like to see more creative policy development to help encourage corporate investment and new business to drive the economy and bring jobs back.  Raising corporate income taxes will simply further diminish the appeal of Canada as a place to do business.

Back when Canada had a low dollar we were seen as a good place to invest because it was cheaper to do manufacturing up here.  That wouldn't work today because it will inevitably be cheaper at this point to start new manufacturing overseas.  However, the lesson remains if it's cheaper doing business here, especially with the proximity to the US market, it's advantageous for businesses to move here.

Edit for clarity:  I also do not recommend Canada return to having a low dollar.  Rather that the analogy shows the benefits of establishing a circumstance where it's more competitive for businesses to invest and establish themselves here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 20:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine for you, but what if he supervises/trains any new workers... Does your company not have any kind of "near miss" reporting system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
