<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying that you believe that child is better off never having been born? That's a crappy, judgemental way to think  

If you had seen the things I have, I'm sure you would agree with me.   I was a paramedic when I responded to a sick baby call.

Turns out, the waste of a human life mother bottle fed her baby drano and clorox bleach because she thought the baby was dirty and possessed by evil spirits.  The baby died.   The pathologist who performed the autopsy later described it as the single most horrific autopsy of his 25 year career. 

She also had another two kids chained up in the basement, whom she regularly beat with carpet track strips.

So yes. I think *sometimes*, in some situations the children would have been much better off not being born. 

Although, I'm not saying that about my niece.  She's only 7, but she has told me sometimes she wishes she'd never been born.  I'm more involved than sitting back judging my sister in law.

But to think abortion is murder while seeing examples like these, I have a hard time thinking a fair and just God would punish someone for aborting a fetus before any conscious life even exists.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sounds like a horrible person  

Well she's a guy, so...

Oh wait.  That's Jake, from state farm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This only strengthened my views on abortion... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have I been living in a Pepsi free cave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would have to prove that he went there with the intent to kill them. If the DA brings those charges and the prosecution can't prove that beyond a reasonable doubt, he walks. In this case they figured that first degree assault was the highest charge they could prove in court. 

Even if the brought charges of 5 counts of attempted murder, and they can't prove it,  the dude wouldn't necessarily walk.   The assaults, even if not filled, are considered "lesser included offenses."  He could be found guilty of those charges even if they weren't specifically filed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because most felony convictions, including multiple felony convictions for multiple crimes, result in sentences being run concurrently and not consecutively.

Even if he was charged with 5 separate assaults fir the five victims, or one felony assault charge for each round fired, the sentence would be the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . Sure, the legal theory is the police officer is doing a quick pat down, for the officer's safety, to make sure you don't have a weapon. Everyone with any knowledge of what's happening, knows they are looking for drugs. 

Except the pat down its only for weapons and only areas where weapons are readily accessible.  Also, officers are not legally allowed to reach into or remove items from from pockets or closed containers without a warrant, probable cause, or consent. 

So even if a police officer feels what they believe might be drugs in someone's pocket, they cannot legally retrieve it without the aforementioned legal authority. 

Also, I don't know what judges, lawyers, etc, you're yakking to.   All the ones I know do not use the term stop and frisk.   They all use the legal term Terry stop or terry search. 

I've only heard the teem term on tv.  It might be a regional/geographical thing. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but my problem is when I was working out, I wasn't losing or gaining much weight and then my pants weren't fitting anymore.

That's because as you burn fat, you're building muscle.   Muscle is denser than fat, and weighs more while taking up less space.   That's why your pants don't fit while at the same time you're not losing weight. 

If you're trying to lose weight, stop bulking and doing heavy weights.  Do lighter weights, more reps, and a shit ton of cardio.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep yep, in many areas it is. Which is my point. You stop and frisk in areas where it is high for blacks and not whites..... well that's my point. 

That's not true.  "Stop and frisk" was a term coined in areas high in gang and drug crimes.  It's a clever name, nothing more.   It's not made legal by any city council or police department policy. 

It's based on a US Supreme Court decision: Terry vs Ohio.  Terry stops, Terry searches are what the media call frisks.  It's legal everywhere, provided the law officers can well articulate what led to reasonable suspicion, abs ultimately probable cause.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know drug use isn't higher for African Americans.

Actually, in many areas it is.   Most disadvantaged people of color (blacks predominantly) grow up in "the hood," where criminal violence and sexual assault are rampant.  Growing up witnessing and experiencing these things causes a great deal of PTSD, which often goes undiagnosed and/or untreated.

The most common coping method then becomes self medication with alcohol and drugs.

People on college campuses, as you mentioned, have far less collateral damage caused by their drug use, which is often at a lower rate to start with.   The college kids aren't out shooting up street corners on a regular basis.  They're also not out burglarizing homes or cars to support their habit.  

Thus the target of most drug enforcement becomes controlling the symptoms (shootings, burgs, etc) by targeting the drug users themselves while trying to work up the chain to the dealers.  Sometimes this works, but most organized drug traffic organizations do a fantastic job of protecting the top level people, just like corporations.  The worker bees get screwed.

There's a new book out, and the author just did an AMA yesterday.   The book is titled Narconomics.  And does a phenomenal job explaining that, due to the corporate like structure of Nevin drug cartels (and organized crime), the war on drugs will never really succeed. 

The war on drugs is more like cancer treatment than a cure.   Some areas (people) may have great results and live with cancer/drug problems in remission fir years.   Others may never see any results at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How is that a scumbag move?

Because I work in a job where shifts have to be filled 24/7.  Anyone calling in sick get someone else forced into overtime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sick leave is a benefit, they said. Use your benefits, they said... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To be fair, she said it was "real fruit." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] When I hear about any event scheduled in Berkeley, California these days... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the old "Planetary Traveler" video that was made to show how awesome Bryce3D was at the time it came out.  This is some impressive shit right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard for anyone to do anything like that without making some sort of ruckus...  And when people start fidgeting that much, I generally warn them ahead of time any manipulation of handcuffs would be interpreted as an escape attempt or preassaultive indicator...

I also visually check people through closed doors/clear windows before opening the back door of the patrol car.  If I can see they're no longer handcuffed, or have moved their cuffs to the front, I let the jail staff know, and they send out a team of people to help prevent escape or attacks on officers.

I haven't added any charges to my arrestees who did that enroute to the jail.  I have added it to people who did something to/with their handcuffs while sitting in houses, sidewalks, etc before transports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've worked in our county jail for 7 years, and spent 4+ years on patrol.  I've seen more than a few people slip cuffs off, or move their arms to the front of their body.

I even have a video I recorded of an inmate showing me how to pick handcuff locks open with a plastic comb.  Handcuffs are only temporary restraint devices that can easily be escaped from.  That's part of the reason a search incident to arrest is not only legal, but a life saving precaution.

EDIT:  To answer the OP's question... Just moving handcuffs to the front, or removing them partially/completely... Is it a violation of the law/can it be considered an escape?  Just like anything else, we can arrest someone for it, and articulate why we believe it's a violation of the law... But still up to the prosecutor's office to determine if they want to file charges in court, and up to a judge and/or jury to determine if it is, in fact, a violation of the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She said she couldn't reach the brake pedal... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jury_nullification_in_the_United_States

I completely understand the idea of jury nullification.  That's a defense in court.  Not a right to ignore the laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda like TV evangelists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to post, "Why doesn't this have more upvotes."  Then I realized all 34 people here upvoted already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most liberals would disagree with you.  I agree with you though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the common theme here is any law that primarily serves to protect people from themselves is "tyrannical."  While I would agree that many of the laws that do nothing but protect people from themselves are absurd, they are far from tyrannical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you name/cite one tyrannical law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
