<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2561</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used Mogl before and it works great, especially in addition to one of the airline dining programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Referrals right now are at 40K. If you have an upcoming need, then go for it, otherwise as others have said, wait for a higher offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomahawks have been the bread and butter the Navy's missile system and are installed in many of the warships that are stationed in the middle east. Here's a paragraph from a WaPo article about them:

 One of the largest advantages to using the Tomahawk is that it does not require a pilot to be anywhere near a potential target. They can be launched from Navy destroyers up to 1,000 miles away, a tactical consideration when facing enemy air defenses.

source: https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/checkpoint/wp/2017/04/06/why-the-navys-tomahawk-missiles-are-the-most-likely-option-for-a-strike-in-syria-against-assad/?utm_term=.6717ef416a51 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a key point, the Everyday can maintain the MR points you earn on all of Amex's charge cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, let's change Piedmont Park to Piedmont Parking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reuters is quoting a Pentagon source here, though I agree that in these early hours it is hard to know what's what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, probably a smart idea to let other countries know so you don't accidentally start another conflict </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [gonna try as best as he can!](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/5f/0d/5f/5f0d5f1821372335651791d6f5c7e005.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steelix coming in for a bear hug! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The U.S. military gave Russian forces advanced notice of its strikes on a Syrian airbase and did not hit sections of the base where the Russians were believed to be present, Pentagon spokesman Captain Jeff Davis said on Thursday.

 Davis, briefing reporters on the operation, said the U.S. military had "multiple" conversations with Russian forces on Thursday before the strike, using a line of communication that had previously been established to prevent an accidental clash in Syria during the fight against Islamic State.

http://live.reuters.com/Event/Syria_conflict/823809983 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump calls on 'civilized nations' to join U.S. in 'seeking to end the slaughter and bloodshed in Syria' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey no worries! Happy to help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can go to your comment and edit it with the new link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be no problem from Plastiq's end, as long as your lender is okay with multiple checks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Yep, it pulls straight from the Reddit thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah most lenders don't accept credit card, it's usually through a service like Western Union. 

Plastiq is great, 2.5% fee and they have excellent customer service if you reach out to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just need one more Gold and then I can evolve it into a Plat!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to be more optimistic than this, but I agree this is a dangerous precedent they've just set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! My plan is to do an updated analysis if/when we achieve 200 data points on three-way ties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, that's the point I was trying to make, that it's more likely to be intentional rather an accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect June 1 would be alright, and worse case if they deny you would have 30 days which would put you comfortably in the clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be strange to have that mistake though, considering they already had three-evolution logic in place for Eevees back in Gen 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! That sounds great, especially for ATL because the only PP lounge currently was in the international terminal (which you can get to from domestic but it is a bit out of the way). Do you have a link to more info on these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the cheapest charge card would be the Green card with a $95 fee. If you're looking for a no fee option to store/accumulate MR points, I'd recommend the Amex Everyday credit card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, unfortunately they removed the free Delta card some time ago. There is one unadvertised tier that's lower than the Gold, but it still has a $55 AF and provides no benefits (like checked bag, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this link, which provides higher offers for some of the other Amex cards: https://americanexpress.com/mgmfall2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An absolutely good point, and we're also limited to the readers of this subreddit. Still, let's make the most of what we have!

Additionally, I will update this post if we get enough new data points to suggest that this initial analysis was biased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend reading this section of the wiki, which details all the rules for Amex, Chase, and others: https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/wiki/index#wiki_bank_specific_questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate votes to invoke the nuclear option to remove the 60-vote filibuster rule for nominees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screenshot of vote from C-SPAN: http://imgur.com/a/2u8eS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, you should be good to go with the charge card with regard to 2/90. They may deny you for other reasons. On the bright side, there is no hard pull if you're denied (it's on approval) so no harm in trying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and only credit cards, not Amex charge cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly this is from 2015, but when a friend used my Delta link it took ~3 days for the referral points to post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Analysis] If all three base stats are tied, Tyrogue has a 50% chance of evolving into Hitmontop and 25% each for the other two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday, I had posted a [survey](http://www.strawpoll.me/12684380/r) requesting inputs from people who had a Tyrogue with two or more stats tied. Thank you all for your response, we collected 375 data points.

For the cases where two stats are tied, it appears that there is a 50/50 chance as to which evolution will occur, as expected.

However, the data suggest a non-random pattern when all three stats are tied. Here's the analysis.

We collected 93 data points for when all three stats are tied, with the following results: 45 Top, 23 Chan, 25 Lee. I conducted a Pearson's Chi-squared test with 2 degrees of freedom to see if these results are statistically significant from the null hypothesis that the data come from a random distribution. I obtained a one-tailed critical value of 9.54, which  yields a p value  0.01. Thus, I will conclude that when all three stats are tied, we can reject the null hypothesis that it is random which evolution occurs.

Based on the distribution, we have approximately a 2:1:1 ratio of Top:Chan:Lee, indicating that **if all three stats are tied, there is a 50% chance of evolving into a Hitmontop**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also for $1k less min spend, which could make up for the 2.5K points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nunes to step aside from Russia probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got some interesting results from the survey as to what happens when all three stats are equals. It doesn't appear to be completely random but rather a 2:1:1 ratio for Top:Chan:Lee. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/TheSilphRoad/comments/63ody9/tyrogue_tied_stats_evolution_survey/dfvphlp/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, all credit cards count for 2/90. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear ya. I've been running with mine for dozens of kilometers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't happen for all cards (and I don't know if we've figured out when it does or doesn't) but it will give you the option on the approval screen. After that though, you can't request it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With those stats, you might say he's a hitmonbottom :D

Cheers on getting the Top! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep they'll give you everything so you can start making purchases with it online. I believe the CVV will be different on the actual card though, once you receive it and activate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newbie question. I noticed I had a referral on Plastiq but it said "not eligible" - does that mean it's something wrong on my end or the person who used my referral is not eligible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left on the IP duplication check by default. If it's not too much trouble and you want another vote, maybe try a VPN or using your mobile off of wifi? Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely take into consideration extended warranty and/or purchase protection as a factor into which card you select to use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! Just be sure to also bring a Visa card with you since Amex isn't always accepted (though it often is in big cities) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the professional grade Macs can definitely hit that price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I created a survey, let's collect more data and see what they suggest. 

http://www.strawpoll.me/12684380 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To collect data on what happens to Tyrogue if it has tied best stats (a tie-rogue, if you will) and you evolve it. Is it truly random or does one or other evolution win out? Lets find out. 

**Edit**: Thank you all for contributing! Based on the 350 data points we have as of 9:50am EDT on 4/6/17, we can start to see an interesting trend.

For the cases where two stats are tied, it appears as expected that there is a 50/50 split between the evolution.

However, in the case where all three stats are tied, it appears that we have a 2:1:1 ratio, favoring Hitmontop. Of the 86 data points of all tied, 42 of them turned into Top, with 20 and 24 for Chan and Lee. I will wait to see more data points reported before making any statistical conclusions, but this is quite interesting!

**TL;DR: It appears that if all three stats are equal, there is a 50% chance of evolving into Himontop, and 25% each for Hitmonchan and Hitmonlee** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tyrogue Tied Stats Evolution Survey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens then? Is it random between those stats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His op-ed could have been found in The Onion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You absolutely have a legitimate business. I would recommend recon (though it might be too late) and be ready to show them documentation for your LLC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll take a few business days. When I got a Delta referral from a friend, it took 3 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, they do hard pulls on approval if you're an existing cardholder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks for the clarification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I think the best thing for now would be to report duplicates to the mods. Also pinging u/zackiv31 about this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give an example of a particular thread (not pointing out any particular users)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat idea! Buying a new home can be cheaper than paying exorbitant internet costs! /s, but only kinda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so he's 4 days late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there is a particular megathread / discussion for this unfortunately. In general, all of your MR points are tied to the same account and as long as you keep one MR card open, you maintain points.

There are 2 MR cards which have no annual fee:
--the Everyday card, which has benefits such as transferring to other partners
--the Blue for Business card, which does not have transfer benefits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A key counterargument to Pai's logic is made by Ars, comparing the wireless market to home ISPs:

 Total market share is a relevant statistic in mobile because customers really do have a choice, from four major nationwide carriers and various resellers and regional carriers. In home Internet service, a similar nationwide market share stat would on the surface show even more diversity of broadband companies, as even the nation's largest home ISP (Comcast) doesn't reach 35 percent.

 But for home Internet customers, the relevant point is whether they can choose from multiple providers at their home or apartment. And they frequently can't, since ISPs often avoid each other's territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman Ajit Pai says broadband market too competitive for strict privacy rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! Did you say anything in particular to get them to give you the offer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it does! I get a few on there that are decent (like the HSN one from last week). Because it is not an MR-earning card, though, it does miss out on offers that are targeted towards those cards only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on your timeline / when you plan to cancel the Plat, currently the top offer on the Everyday is 15K MR after $1k spend via referral. If you want to hold out, the incognito offers for 25K after $2k may or may not come back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, just make sure you keep an UR- earning card open at all times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah missed churning connections... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $150 plus the 10% back at restaurants is currently the best, via referral. Looks like incognito offers haven't been working since the beginning of the month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others have mentioned, this is not possible. Here's a useful chart for seeing what points can transfer where: https://www.uscreditcardguide.com/wings-points-points-miles-transfer-chart-amex-chase-citi-spg-marriott/

Hope you get some good travel from your skymiles! On the bright side they won't expire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are unsure of future plans, I would recommend opening the Everyday card, which would let you maintain your MR points long term with no annual fee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we are all getting 302 - Moved Temporarily errors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the debut of u/soupbrah's churning search engine, what are your thoughts on coming up with some sort of standardized syntax for data points, so that they can be easily searched? Maybe something like [DP][SPG] for a data point on SPG cards. Hoping to hear your thoughts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of one of my favorite books, "Waiting for GADOT"

But in all seriousness, props to them for the ambitious timeline and I wish them success! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have some luck getting an incognito offer for 25K MR/$2k spend , but if not, there are 15K / $1k offers via referral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's definitely a mistake, call them and ask for another one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a banner ad on Delta.com i believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signature is a tier you can get on some Visa cards when you open them with a $5000 credit limit or higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can opt-in at the following site, which is the one used by most of the big banks (and is approved by the FTC): https://www.optoutprescreen.com/?rf=t </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, do the two elevators merge at some point?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highest offer to date! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it parses through the threads every 6 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will post to your account within a couple days of your statement closing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you to whomever used my Discover student referral :) I appreciate you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay I had that issue as well. Try regenerating the offer from this link, then clearing your browser cookies / cache before opening the email.

https://www262.americanexpress.com/business-card-application/raf/201045-OPEN
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately it looks like incognito offers haven't been working for the last few days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of the referrals have expired and have not been regenerated, but I do see a few of the 50K ones working on rankt.com for both the personal and business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All comment scores are hidden for 4 hours. If you scroll down to some of the older comments in this thread, you'll see the scores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letting unauthorized immigrants get driver's licenses led to a 7-10% drop in hit-and-run accidents in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope the upgrade shouldn't affect your approval status or 2/90 status </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Occasional deals, like today's Amex offer for $5 off $5 on Android Pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would wait for a higher offer. The [Delta Dominic](http://www.homedepot.com/p/Delta-Dominic-Single-Handle-Pull-Down-Sprayer-Kitchen-Faucet-with-Touch2O-Technology-Soap-Dispenser-in-SpotShield-Stainless-19940T-SPSD-DST/205502818) is first class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be sure to do it within 30 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. Federal Communications Commission has voted to reverse a requirement imposed under the Obama administration that Charter Communications Inc extend broadband service to 1 million households already served by a competitor, the commission said on Monday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC reverses Charter Communications 'overbuild' requirement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since American, Southwest, and Alaska all seem to have these type of offers for their cardholders, here's hoping that Delta and United follow soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be morbid, but someone should start a service for handling this sort of thing. ChurnFromTheUrn, or something like that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes for an excellent glass clinker when giving a toast at a wedding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hope so as well. I would hope they would be providing incentives drivers to take more UberPOOL riders so as to reduce congestion as much as possible; traffic's been a hot mess with the spillover from the highway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, and best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't churning related per se, but if you live in the Atlanta metro area and user Uber, they are cutting prices this week to help commuters affected by the bridge collapse. I say good on them!

https://www.reddit.com/r/Atlanta/comments/6369h2/cheaper_rates_for_atlanta_uber_riders_due_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all the flights are going to be on the same airline, you could look into getting that airline's card to get benefits like a free-checked bag. Usually those don't require super high credit scores (I got a Delta card while I was in college). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that is correct. If you want to confirm, check to see what the Membership Rewards account number is for both of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See if your local grocery store accepts Android Pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't had a chance to test it out yet, but I imagine anywhere that Android Pay is accepted (Uber, Whole Foods, Kroger, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, you would have no issues booking other people with your Delta Plat card, and it would trigger the credit. The only thing they wouldn't get if you're not traveling with them is the free checked bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get a refund within 30 days of the fee posting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! I was sadly only able to get it on the one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $200 more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll post to your account within a couple business days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The change in the trust documents occurred on February 10th (after Trump was inaugurated as President) and stipulates:

 The Trustees shall distribute net income or principal to Donald J. Trump **at his request**, as the Trustees deem necessary for his maintenance, support, or uninsured medical expenses, or as the Trustees otherwise deem appropriate.

So basically at any time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amex offer for $5 off $5 using Android Pay, up to 3x. Got it on my Delta Plat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a county tax, your county's tax commissioner (or equivalent) would be the best. If it's state, there is probably a revenue department that handles it, or the agency that handles business registration (I.e. the Georgia Sec of State for us) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I beg your pardon - https://www.tacobell.com/food/specialties/mexican-pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
