<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7127</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like that you sent a rover on Pizza to take pictures and explore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I guess the traditional versions are made with Indian Paneer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 19:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marinated in mozzarella? Such a useless waste of an expensive ingredient such as mozzarella which is very mild flavorwise and wont  help at all in a marinade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 16:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! there is meat and also walnut meal. There is a recipe link on imgur picture . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pomegranate blood orange glazed walnut meatballs[OC][4607x3072] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 13:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 00:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! go to a romantic restaurant with the date and come back home to play with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 00:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thickness is optimal unlike that casserole-like dish called "Chicago style pizza". This one can still be considered as pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 15:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See a sausage, find it fascinating that it looks like a penis, let Reddit know about your discovery!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 16:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am actually a research scientist. That's why I think the reactions here are absurd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 15:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! finally a constructive comment. I was gonna make my move towards the end of the trip. I was also deeply struggling with the 'what if' feeling and also the underwear debacle changed the course of events. The thing is unlike the image that comments give here, I am highly educated with a good job in NewYork city and am not from Florida. I surely am much more intelligent than people who are calling me retard and idiot right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 13:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bro! not all are bright enough to use technology in a genius way like this. Apparently it is cool and hygienic to suck a guys penis or lick a girls arse and very unsafe and dangerous to dry out a clean washed underwear in microwave.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When putting wet clothing in microwave the water gets really hot and you immediately see water vapor. Even if organisms survive the waves, they wont survive the heat and vapor motion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 19:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably should have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 19:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but in my defense, those waves kill all the germs; Not a living organism can survive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by leaving my underwear in my crush's microwave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved out of Florida around 6 months ago. During my final couple of weeks down there, I used to meet my female co-worker over coffee breaks having fun and casual hangouts. Nothing serious happened of course because of the moving out thing. Nothing until last week when I had to travel back for a work/winter break trip. 
A couple of days before my trip, she saw my FB update announcing my grand winter break plan. she texted me shortly after inviting me to stay over at her house in case I needed a place. There was a day gap between the hotels reserved by my company (for work) and the one by me(for fun) so the idea of  staying at her place would actually work perfectly(wait till the end). I immediately replied and said that I would love and need to stay for a day. 


   
Long story short I stayed the night over at her house. The next morning, she left to work and as my hotel check in was at noon, I decided to stick around for a couple of hours. As the trip was long, I realized that my clean underwear supply was being depleted. Given this, I decided to wash the dirty ones in the bathroom sink and dry them in her microwave. This is btw is a great LPT for drying out cotton clothing in Florida(I might post it to LPT sub at some point).
I did a couple of cycles of heating and waiting. During the last one, she called me to make sure I am doing fine and don't need anything in particular. That phone call completely distracted me and as the result I completely forgot about the underwear stack in the microwave and so left her house to hotel with bunch of my underwear in her microwave.  I checked in and when I opened my luggage I suddenly realized: fuck...fuck ...fuck..
This was a completely awkward situation and I truly had no idea how to handle it. I decided to text her and tell her the truth. I did and she laughed(or pretended to).  Her behavior however is completely changed since then and we also did not meet down there anymore.
TL;dr dried out my underwear in crush's microwave. Got ignored by the crush and fucked by Reddit!

Edit1: Jesus! Calm the f.. down people! it was not your microwave for f.. sake! 

Edit2=LPT: you can dry out your cotton(100% only) clothing in a microwave! 

Edit3: Calm the f.. down people(2nd request!). If you ever have had sex, eaten out, been in public pool, or consumed canned food, you have been through worst than a clean washed, but still a little damp, underwear in your microwave! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 06:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all! I guess the bun is consisted of two individual grilled cheese sandwiches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 16:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaly has issues! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 14:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a bastard with a possible Italian or middle eastern or Spanish or Mexican father!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 18:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next generation muffin top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 07:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works perfectly. Also Cabbage family match particularly well with seafood(Anchovies, fish sauce and tuna). Believe me! I tried this recipe with ground beef as well but the result was not even nearly as good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe here:

Ingredients:


2 cups Jasmine rice

1/2 TSP turmeric

salt and water as needed to par-boil the rice

2 cans tuna in oil(300 gr)

1 Poblano chili, finely chopped

3 cloves of garlic, crushed

2 whole dry Kashmiri red chilies, torn into small pieces

3 slices of preserved lemon, finely chopped  

75 gr parsley, finely chopped

200 gr broccoli(fresh or frozen), finely chopped

1/4 cup caramelized onions

Method:

http://www.shamshiricafe.com/2016/01/persian-tuna-and-broccoli-biryani.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persian tuna and broccoli Biryani[OC][4607x3072] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 22:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Persia here! No way this is Persian. No Persian serves curry with the holy kebab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 22:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over cooked?. But you did what you could to make her happy and that is admirable. For love of god, do your practices before cooking for guests or occasions like this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the Sardines Moroccan or is the recipe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me more about Bals-BBq Sauce.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a typical airport string cheese syndrome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where's the penis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 02:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selling them to the gluten-free folks who have no idea what gluten is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cookbook top picks these days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard as a rock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An elder gentleman was standing next to me while I was taking this photo. He smiled and at said:
"I have a few years left. But my generation grew up eating everything;that's how we would develop immunity and tolerance!. I see so many gluten free cookbooks for people who have no idea what gluten is!" .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top picks in cookbooks today; against gluten, sugar, salt, grains and basically against everything... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 17:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/foodporn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 17:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Originally spotted in /r/mildypenis and hence was qualified as foodporn material.
https://www.reddit.com/r/mildlypenis/comments/40r96e/thomas_kellers_salmon_tartare/   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 16:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Pudding! fucking black pudding! is where the problem is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 16:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to roast them once but they still tasted like shit. The best way to cook them is shredding them followed by a quick satuee in bacon fat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 03:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bbc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 22:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad then! New York city's tasting menus rang within 200-300$ zone!. All I need is 3 friends now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 21:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am planning to as it is close enough to NYC area. How is the price range? and also do i have to include the ridiculously high downtown Philly parking prices too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link for you:

http://www.shamshiricafe.com/2014/03/3-modern-tah-chin-recipes.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 20:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the Persian rice he recommends to serve it with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 19:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A more exposed one for you:

http://imgur.com/uZvepwG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 15:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe is by Michael Solomonov in Zahav cookbook. I found a link to present:


http://andrewzimmern.com/2015/10/20/zahav-lamb-shoulder/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Zahav Lamb Shoulder, absolutely stunning.[OC][3072x4608] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 15:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 03:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some fresh green element is missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 03:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping it classy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the meat lover large or is the Poutine large? Or possibly both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 02:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing! just poached my chicken with garlic, onion, dried chilies and bay leaves as I am against using canned cream of X soups or premixed seasoning packages. So much weird stuff in them ...    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 02:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did the roux as I said, (2TBSP butter+2TBSP flour)

then added the cold low fat milk(1 cup) and then added the cream cheese(half a block=125 gramish). 

Next added, all the broth from my poached chicken and made a nice shiny sauce.

 added the sauce and juice of Persian lime(that much fat needs some acid to balance the flavor) to the fully cooked chicken pieces and simmered for a few minutes till got a nice consistency. 

Forgot to mention that I poached the chicken(2lb~1kg) with onion, garlic, pepper corns and Dried Kashmiri chillies and bay leaves.  

Hope it does it for you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 02:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not easy but worth trying!. It takes several trials to perfect the rice texture. Ask me any question you might have either here, or on my blog's comment section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big yogurty rice cake to be exact!

http://www.shamshiricafe.com/2014/03/3-modern-tah-chin-recipes.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and milk and also chicken stock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by this:
http://crockingirls.com/recipes/creamy-ranch-chicken/


cream of chicken soup removed, off course! did my own roux and ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ranch chicken stew[OC][3072x4608] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 19:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those seeking a recipe: from what I see, this is not a curry dish!. This is most likely grilled spiced chicken topped with some sort of mustard sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who hunts chicken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is easy and you won't need a sandwich maker.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ISzjeN6FxPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue cheese is awesome! If I get to pick my last supper, It would have some sort of blue cheese in it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 21:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuban bread, dill pickles, mustard and being pressed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sausage, blue cheese Cuban[OC][4608x3072] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 17:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I discovered this amazing three world combination somewhere on Reddit! Most have been yours if unique. Thank you for the wisdom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 02:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General Tso's penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maple cumin Yam qualifies for submission to:

https://www.reddit.com/r/mildlypenis/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: Granny is not British.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mushroom are supposed to like phallic in general, but this one ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 16:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from thumbnail: https://www.reddit.com/r/mildlypenis/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 16:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is wrong with a golden Brioche bun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 16:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that rice enough for 84 dishes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 21:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the hen is Korean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 04:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the left one is also r/mildlyvagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 03:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin's girlfriend's aunt's Mary is also not bad: 
https://www.reddit.com/r/mildlypenis/comments/3h7430/this_virgin_mary_sculpture_in_my_cousins/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 15:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for clarification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 15:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fill up a condom and be fascinated that it looks like a penis! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 16:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/floridaman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 15:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those greens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 15:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Brazzer's headquarters in Slovakia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 15:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check before eating it! there might be some actual penises behind the chocolate cover! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 17:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a dickhead that knight was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Virgin Mary sculpture in my cousin's girlfriend's aunt's house! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 15:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
