<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2800</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he truly believed he'd inherited a mess, he'd be working. But we all know he just needs his ego stroked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In many ways, it makes no sense to distinguish between Trump and the Republican Party any longer. Trump is popular among Republicans, and Republican officials are satisfied with the White Houses policy output. 

This. Criticize not just Trump, but the Republicans. They own this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it's bad when he's considering someone with a mustache. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when to we get our ~~monorail~~ Great America? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By mess does he mean a functioning government? Growing economy? Strong alliances? Improved access to health insurance? Yeah, he's working on "fixing" all of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadians too. I'm not sure how significant the #'s will be but it is definitely something people are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have any European friends, ask them about this. Take a look at some foreign papers to get a picture of the way the rest of the world currently views the US. It's sad to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Trump Did in His 4th Week That Actually Matters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he did double the fees to join Mar-a-Lago. He's profiting bigly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why he needs to demonize the press. He needs to convince his supporters that they can't trust the media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ???? Weird interpretation of "hoping Congress will do the right thing". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Kentucky congressman gets his way, guns would be allowed on school property </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The President is increasingly bewildering or worrying friends and foes alike. Longstanding allies now publicly chide America. On Thursday, the French Foreign Minister, Jean-Marc Ayrault, called the Trump Administrations policy on the volatile Middle East very confusing and worrying. German Chancellor Angela Merkelwho has become the de-facto spokesperson for the Wests liberal democracies since Trump took officerebuked his America First policy this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Flailing Foreign Policy Bewilders the World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can tell, they feel no shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually we want her to go away, and not destroy the public school system. Making her life hell is a means to accomplish that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be fun watching her spar with Maher. But since she's reached the point where she does nothing but lie, I just can't watch her at all. CNN did the right thing by announcing they weren't having her on, and if the rest of the real media follows suit maybe she'll vanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on her history, she is not a true believer. In a sense that makes her behavior worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything by Kligour Trout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have said publicly that they would prefer a delay, and failing that they would need to vote against. McConnell made it easy for them, and they still showed typical Democratic backbone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitch McConnell, however, said he would not allow a delay. Asked by a reporter to explain, he answered succinctly: Because I choose not to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some bombshells might drop on Scott Pruitt next week. The Senate confirmed him anyway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, I bet some of the people on the senate intelligence committee already know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was an odd case. Essentially it came out after he'd been approved when a friend of his was going thru the process and was honest about who he'd smoked with - and it included someone who hadn't been honest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My feelings too. As much as I dislike him   what's happening, I think having electors overturning the election would have been worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they are hoping Congress will do the right thing. It would be ugly for the intel community to need to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrote this above, but I know someone who lied about smoking weed on his application, got found out,   still got Q clearance. So it isn;t an automatic disqualifier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know someone who had Q clearance at a national lab, despite them finding out that he lied about ever having used illegal drugs - since someone else had admitted to using with him. Since then I've always figured there was leeway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The email was really just an excuse, and we all knew it. But it convinced enough people to stay home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least since McCarthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but only if he was opposed to slavery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It obviously should be delayed, in the interest of properly vetting the candidate. So clearly it won't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Betsy DeVos isnt backing down from her grizzly bear gaffe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you up until ...after the election. At that point unfortunately he had won based on the US' flawed electoral system 

But yes, they own him   his turmoil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been banned from there since well before the election. I suggested that Hillary might not be the antichrist and was banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Concedes Defeat on Travel BanFor Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Whatever you have to tell yourself" would have been better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is still campaigning against Hillary because it's easier than leading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he were a humble and thoughtful human being this would be possible. I don't think he's either, so this won't happen, but it would be the type of strategy a real leader could use. FWIW, Clinton had to do something like this bringing in David Gergen when his administration had early turmoil, and it was nothing close to what we're seeing now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for Trump to Hit the Reset Button </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he enjoys directing government money into is personal accounts too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the saying goes, he was born on third base and believes he hit a triple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey really is a fucking giant.

Oh, and yes, of course Sessions should recuse himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen the movie as well? Curious how the compare - I've had the movie on my Netflix queue for a while, but wondering if I should read the book first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the financial meltdown, I really enjoyed "The Quants" as well. It doesn't have the amazing writing style of Michael Lewis, but is an engrossing read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listened to him, read him, and saw his shows live a couple of times. He was a national treasure and will be missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading Cat's Cradle at age 18 was really eye opening. I had the good luck to see him speaking a while later, and after that I pretty much devoured all of his books. I also didn't always enjoy the ones considered his best as much as some of the others, for example I really loved Galapagos and also thought Player Piano was really under-rated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you can handle the rain, it's nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I agreed, but I actually don't believe the Republicans are going to allow the information to come out. Hope I'm wrong, but I think they'll pull their old BS of invoking patriotism and calling out leakers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does nothing of the sort. It points out that there was clearly lying done, and if it was done to the FBI then he's in a whole pile of crap - and that the alternative is that he lied to a bunch of colleagues, came clean to the FBI, and then Trump ignored it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps he couldn't bring himself to vote McCain/Palin? It'd be hard to blame him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it would seem just if they showed up on Wikileaks now, wouldn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to have forgotten how many investigations there were into Clinton. But you're right on one thing, we need to know the truth. So I'm sure you fully support a full investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell them that since it has come to light that POTUS' campaign had contacts with Russia during the campaign you think it's increasingly important for at least Congress know the full extent of his financial dealings. The only way to get this is to see his tax returns, and there's precedent for doing this when POTUS won't release them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is ok, the angrier the real press gets, the better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I only made it up yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are missing the point that all that happens due to statements like this is Trump can criticize Hillary, call sore loser, and deflect attention from the big issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Elections matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the article. Feel free to report back and disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Need a Special Counsel to Investigate the Trump Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, conviction would happen in the Senate. But there is much evidence needed first. With evidence, the house would impeach. It isn't like he gets convicted and then impeached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attorney General. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need an investigation to get solid evidence. Chicken, egg, all that. Hopefully the Repubs will allow an investigation to move ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey is the best chance to get Trump investigated right now. He fucked up, but perhaps he'll repent by taking down Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody reasonable? Zero AFAIK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exactly do you know there is no solid evidence? There has been no public investigation / report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is #Flynngazi. The Republicans have shown they only investigate scandals ending in azi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but they need to move on from the campaign into the present. I feel their pain, but allowing Trump to discuss Hillary will always be to his advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The appeal was that he was the only one who could plausibly get thru confirmation. Plus since Repubs were on record as specifically saying they'd consider him, the hypocrisy of not doing so should have been an effective weapon for the Dems - they were just too incompetent to wield it properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is correct, I think the Hillary campaign needs to STFU. She is not going to become POTUS. The important thing right now is keeping Trump in check or removing him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been joking that Merrick Garland would make a great independent prosecutor, but in reality there are people they could find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also for those who didn't read it, the law in question is rarely used, but has been used, including in 1974 to see Nixon's returns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All we need is the pee stained sheets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. But even if you buy their logic, there is an approach to get this investigated. I'd trust an independent prosecutor more than the house Republicans, although the Dems could ask the right questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These 23 Republicans Passed on a Chance to Get Trump's Tax Returns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's actually some logic here, but this is what Special Prosecutors are for. They should investigate Flynngazi. In parallel, a special prosecutor should be looking into Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know, but it's kinda fun to rub the Trump-bots noses in how ridiculous their inconsistency is at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consistency was never his strongpoint, or required by his supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they are setting it up to protect him. You won't get your wish, I fear. They are either keeping him out of the loop or giving him plausible deniability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard a story on CBC news this morning about school trips from Canada to the US being cancelled. It made me really sad as an American to hear the country discussed like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine are ok... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be. 18-D Yahtzee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selection of the special prosecutor would be critical. Merrick Garland would have a certain beauty to it, but they could find someone unbiased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he did. And rather than leaks, we should hear facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that we deserve to know what happened. The article points out how implausible some of what the Republicans are claiming is. For the good of the country, we need to know the truth.

While it is not clear what he said in his F.B.I. interview, Mr. Flynn maintained publicly for more than a week that his conversations with the ambassador were innocuous and did not involve Russian sanctions, something now known to be false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Trump could be VEEP, yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best POTUS TV ratings EVER!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what a Special Prosecutor is for. It's not like they'd pick Hillary as Special Prosecutor. Merrick Garland might be interested though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't write the title, reddit requires me not to change it though. If you actually look at my comments, you will see all I want is an open investigation - you should want the same, FWIW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not my concern. If they have a full investigation and he's cleared and people refuse to accept it then you can whine. But let's do the investigate part first, K? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? What part of *we have absolutely no idea right now on the details* did you miss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course that matters. When the POTUS' party has a majority on Congress they shouldn't have oversight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was nothing wrong with the anti-Clinton people asking for an investigation. There was a problem with them chanting "Lock Her Up" after the results of the investigation were known, and Trump led this. There is nothing wrong with people asking for a full investigation into the Trump Administration contacts with Russia right now. If they are cleared, then we can talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is what they did and whether they were honest with the FBI, and we have absolutely no idea right now on the details. So claiming they are the same is ridiculous. Nice attempt at deflection though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try. He can't deflect by invoking Hillary anymore though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hasn't been 4 weeks yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Reagan defense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. It isn't exactly what Clinton did. But even if it was, didn't Trump say that she should be locked up? Didn't he say there should be a special prosecutor? Didn't the Republicans demand investigations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think Pence may be out of the loop. Pence will give us the shitty policies without the crazy. Bannon would be gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is where a special prosecutor comes in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he intentionally discussed policy with a foreign government. As long as they put as much effort into investigating Flynngazi as they did into Email and Benghazi it'll become clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accusations are Logan Act. But a full and open investigation will make it clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the public deserves this - if it's truly not a crime then Trump should actually want the investigation. We need full public disclosure on Flynngazi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even 4 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if Hillary had done this. I say that so often now that it's making my head spin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About fucking time. There should be a complete media ban on Kellyanne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I despise what Pence stands for, policy wise. But what's happening right now is insanity, and both dangerous   embarrassing for the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see Pence and Ryan not being tarnished, apart from their support for the tainted POTUS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, I agree with this. But this is why we need a full and open investigation. What did Flynn discuss? Who told him to? When did POTUS know he was lying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cincinnati Republican says it's time to impeach President Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was waiting for this question to get asked yesterday. It's implausible that it didn't come from Trump, which is why the house will resist investigating. There would be no choice except to impeach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm not sure this qualifies as politics, but it made me smile. Not much on here these days makes me smile, so it gets an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a full and open investigation of Trump and his campaign's Russia ties. It's implausible that Flynn discussed sanctions without Trump's knowledge. It's clear that Trump knew for weeks that his administration was lying, and chose to go along. Time to get it all out in the open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The strong implication is that Flynn lied to the FBI. To believe otherwise, you must assume Flynn discussed U.S. sanctions with Kislyak, then lied about it publicly and to colleagues, then told the truth about it to the FBI, then lied about it some more. Not likely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lock. Flynn. Up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two key differences: Clinton was under oath. Clinton was a Democrat. Both of those would have to be satisfied for the House to impeach.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He only investigates scandals ending in azi. Hereafter, this shall be called Flynngazi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes one would. And the question needs to be asked of all parties involved, Flynn, Counsel, Pence, Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Trump is gonna be pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought in my wildest dreams that Lindsey Fucking Graham would say anything I could support. This is clearly the darkest timeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My all time favorite was Cats Cradle. It includes one of my alltime favorite quotes:

*Beware of the man who works hard to learn something, learns it, and finds himself no wiser than before. He is full of murderous resentment of people who are ignorant without having come by their ignorance the hard way.*

 Bokonon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly though, even now he looks like a cretin that they put into a suit, even more so when he's speaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first book I read by Vonnegut, I wish I'd read it a bit later - it is probably his most confusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Naked Lunch as well. I wouldn't go quite as far to say no idea, but I finished it and was glad I did. If you understand the state he was in when writing it may help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It's been clear for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they did. Ignore the crime, but try to find out who prevented them from keeping it hidden. We're getting close to pitchforks and torches time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grade 7. I picked "Heart of Darkness" for a book report because it was short. Big mistake... I recognized the words. And sentences kind of made sense. But by the time I reached paragraphs, and god forbid chapters I was way over my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read this yet (it's on my list), but I just wanted to chime in the Wolf in White Van was one of the best books I read in 2014. Hope there haven't been too many comments like this, afraid to look due to spoiler concerns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But his hair is slicked back, proving he's a businessman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impossible to believe that Trump wasn't involved in Flynn's calls   the messaging. We need a transparent investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the public part. But behind the scenes we have no idea what is going on, what loans are being forgiven, how much money he's funneling directly into his accounts, or what preferential terms he'll get for building permits. I fully believe that he's profiting at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all we want right now is a full and transparent investigation. Flynn isn't the one I want to see take the fall, but I fully believe a real investigation would show that he wasn't going rogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In any normal time, this would have launched the scandal of the century; Congress would have half a dozen investigations already underway. The public still has no idea what Trumps global business ventures around the world really are, to whom he owes money or who owes money to him. Although the Trump sons have pledged not to do any new deals in foreign countries, that doesnt mean much since nobody knows what the existing deals are. There is no official and public record indicating that the president paperwork is no longer operating as the CEO of the Trump Organization, and hes spending weekends at his private golf course in Florida, hobnobbing with people who have personally paid him six figures for the privilege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beneath the deepening chaos of the Trump administration, the Trump business is doing just fine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use the words: Special Prosecutor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Putin tell them not to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The WaPo story on the timeline said that she told the WH counsel, not POTUS. At this point the only clear thing is we need a full investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Trump lying when he said on Feb 10 that he had no knowledge of the Flynn/Russia discussion, or did White House Counsel fail to inform him? That question needs to be answered.

Did Flynn have the discussion on his own with now input from PEOTUS or VPEOTUS? That seems implausible.

There are questions that need to be answered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for exactly this article. It's tough to keep track of this, and seems important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, another possibility is more likely: The ship is in serious trouble. The first reason is that the system cannot function with an absent commander in chief. Since World War II, the United States has evolved a system for making foreign policy that depends on an effective White House operation in the form of the National Security Council staff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rudderless Ship of State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didnt Trump do to Flynn what he has done to so many reality TV contestants in his only real preparation for his current job? Why didnt he just fire him instead of allowing him to quit? After all, that is exactly what he did to the woman who warned him that Flynn was compromised.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Trump call him a puppet too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, the people representing Trump have no credibility. Perhaps Trump himself should take some questions from real reporters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These stories are just nasty at this point, they only serve to keep her name around for the Republicans to point to. Of course she isn't running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think he's holding meetings in public? He wants to boost membership - and he's getting tons of free publicity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What scares me most isn't actually where we are right now, but that enough Americans support this government   our system is so broken that people may continue to vote this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, I agree with you on the cost - but then it is undeniable that it cost more than estimated. But once the money was spent and it was set up, this becomes irrelevant to the decision to scrap it.

Citing a source like Canadian Shooting Sports with individual interviews is a bogus argument. This source has a clear agenda, and is cherry picking there interviews - which is the reason we need actual media sources with real reporters - CBC/Globe   Mail/The Star, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The acting attorney general informed the Trump White House late last month that she believed Michael Flynn had misled senior administration officials about the nature of his communications with the Russian ambassador to the United States, and warned that the national security adviser was potentially vulnerable to Russian blackmail, current and former U.S. officials said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NH claims are specific enough that the WH should be able to provide proof. Well, at least that's what would happen if the Republicans even gave a crap about reality anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, what are the chances that Flynn would have done this on his own? What did the President know, and when did he know it?

An investigation is in order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House was warned on Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven't even shown that. They have shown nothing, all they do is make allegations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice link, "Canadian Shooting Sports" is certainly among the more reputable sources for Canadian news coverage.

How about CBC's article on the RCMP report?

http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/long-gun-registry-efficient-rcmp-report-1.886843
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree with you, but I fear that isn't what's going to happen. Given a choice between a pardon or him being sent to jail, I'd take the pardon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if it's worse to imagine that they believe it, or that they're making it up to advance their agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police disagree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was supposed to be the one with government experience. Reality is that he's a party hack. He seems to me like the one they may toss overboard, with Pence picking a replacement who actually understands how the government works. Priebus' experience is in how to KEEP the government from working, turns out that's not the job requirement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it does. In what universe would this even be debatable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's obviously a reason they keep talking about this, and it isn't good. We're clearly going to see federal voting standards with claims to be related to fraud but really intended to suppress the minority vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His objective of being there is siphoning money into his account, and he doesn't give a shit about anything else including the country.

That's the real defense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pardon Obama should have given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, the GOP are Lucy holding the football. And the press plays the part of Charlie Brown, charging in believing more than two will vote against. We know how it ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he won't. That would require admitting a mistake. Not happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More money into Trump's pocket. Really, that's all he cares about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're fair. That's why he will not take questions from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for the super soaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really true. Canada's media is devoting a lot of time to the crap going on in the US, and Canadians talk more about Trump than they do about Justin at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't count as a press conference. I think it's going to be quite a while before we see another press conference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't the BuzzFeed headline be "The New Online Right had it's First Mass Shooting... and you Won't Believe how America Reacted!"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, there's one thing you might have noticed I don't complain about: politicians. Everybody complains about politicians. Everybody says they suck. Well, where do people think these politicians come from? They don't fall out of the sky. They don't pass through a membrane from another reality. They come from American parents and American families, American homes, American schools, American churches, American businesses and American universities, and they are elected by American citizens. This is the best we can do folks. This is what we have to offer. It's what our system produces: Garbage in, garbage out. If you have selfish, ignorant citizens, you're going to get selfish, ignorant leaders. Term limits ain't going to do any good; you're just going to end up with a brand new bunch of selfish, ignorant Americans. So, maybe, maybe, maybe, it's not the politicians who suck. Maybe something else sucks around here... like, the public. Yeah, the public sucks. There's a nice campaign slogan for somebody: 'The Public Sucks. F*ck Hope.

--George Carlin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can siphon taxpayer money straight into his company this way, why not? I wonder how much he pockets each time he does this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lock Him Up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, you don't think she worker her way up from the ground floor and launched her clothing line based on her amazingly original designs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Billy Carter sold beer. But there weren't any employees of the government advertising for it   he wasn't on the federal payroll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet the people who believed Hillary's handling of classified info was sloppy are fine with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bully. That girl shouldn't pick on someone as intellectually challenged as Chaffetz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While they're at it they can look for the people who were bussed into NH to vote for Hillary. 

Problem with this is that we assume they care about proving their facts, but their supporters don't demand this; accusations are sufficient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was insanity, that the Conservatives shut it down and ordered the records destroyed, after much $$$ had been spent setting it up. At least after enough years of Harper enough Canadians wised up and voted in their own interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What spending has been cut?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
