<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related *Intercept* article, [What Did @realDonaldTrump Know About Russia and When Did Donald Trump Know It?](https://theintercept.com/2017/02/14/trump-know-flynns-talks-russia-know/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related *Intercept* article, [What Did @realDonaldTrump Know About Russia and When Did Donald Trump Know It?](https://theintercept.com/2017/02/14/trump-know-flynns-talks-russia-know/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Leakers Who Exposed Gen. Flynns Lie Committed Serious  and Wholly Justified  Felonies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Leakers Who Exposed Gen. Flynns Lie Committed Serious  and Wholly Justified  Felonies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. Apologies. There were like five of these in one day, and some got a proper link and others I replied to via mobile and c/p is a hassle. :)

No one sees these after they're removed, though (although folks that posted can backtrace). So you're the only one affected, but for that, I'm sorry. :D

PS: I like the Atlantic and if yours made it sooner, I'd have loved to have it be "the" post. We like diversity! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah. This is a PDF from a government *really* over-the-top w/ citizen surveillance. We're not fond of PDF  can you repost with a non-proprietary version?

And perhaps save some grief from readers by making more clear these are the gov't arguments. Your tag is good but even better [gov.uk - UK Gov't Arguments Favoring Mass Surveillance] or something along those lines. (This  is advisory, just to save you potential hostile responses :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already covered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost of https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5to34n/a_usborn_nasa_scientist_was_detained_at_the/, so removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost of https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5to34n/a_usborn_nasa_scientist_was_detained_at_the/, so removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, /u/Synisterly.

We tracked the article down to this page: http://puppet.zone/securing-online-personas/

However, it is only in ebook format. A proprietary one, known to sometimes be a security risk, PDF.

Do you have a link to a non-PDF source? We like the material but aren't crazy about the format. Can you message us back w/ a better source, or reply to this?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, already covered. But /u/JuliettPapaRomeo kindly provides a better link to the Ars article https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/02/justice-naps-man-jailed-16-months-for-refusing-to-reveal-passwords/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll include your Ars link in my removal message. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're not going to approve this since it violates Rule #4. But thanks for considering us. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi.

This seems more support-related, which we don't really do. But have you tried /r/Google? They'd be better since they know what Google policies are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get quite a few posts per day and when someone reports a post as Spam (which they did in this case), we're not going to spend a great deal of time researching the provenance of a site. We (volunteers) just don't have the time for it. Original source (ACLU) or authentic media (of which there are many [stories that cover this](https://duckduckgo.com/?q=aclu+tsa+lawsuit t=hd ia=web) move to the front of the queue. Both of these already exist **and** the topic has already been covered (another strike).

Especially for a rehash of an article that doesn't add any value.

There are exceptions: if a blog writes an original, interesting, sourced article that doesn't hype their commercial ventures, we've approved those. But the bar is higher since shilling for commercial ventures is always a concern here.

Hope you understand. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Already covered, Rule #8. Plus update, Google is appealing order and order is suspended (for now?)

Thanks, though, /u/trendekidervis! And thanks for whoever reported this: we really rely on you folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the post was original source - the ACLU article - it'd be valid. Instead it's a rehash of the ACLU one, thus low quality.

I'm going on the name of the site, securitySALES, which indicates it's commercial, versus ACLU being objective and non-profit. Thus trying to drive traffic to a personal or commercial site, thus being a Rule #4 violation.

Does that help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a blog, right? A commercial one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This got a few reports, but while  arguably lacking objective evidence or supporting the argument well, it doesn't violate sidebar rules. So, it stays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, even Mods here might use it, since for them and their threat profile, DDG is fine.

Hypothetically.

OK, I admit it - I love !Bangs too much to switch. TOO MUCH!

Everyone is different, in other words. Scope things out and make the educated choice that works best for you, guilt-free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi.

We need some kind of third-party sourcing for this. We simply lack the time/expertise to review code posted to Pastebin. If you provide a link from someone impartial and reputable in the security space, we'd be happy to approve that article.

Thanks for considering us, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, if there's not a book, maybe we can extrapolate amongst ourselves what a Pinoy, say, might be concerned for with regards surveillance. That is, much focus is on Northern countries, Five Eye nations, or Russian or Chinese citizens. 

Assume you're a citizen of a Southern country. How much of a threat do you face and what kinds of things can you do to mitigate them?

1) You don't have to fear a Five Eye nation spying on you. But only because you know they already do. But the GCHQ probably won't be informing your leader (Duerte in this case) that you're interested in pro-Democracy efforts. I'd think if you follow the same techniques we're familiar with, you're pretty safe.

2) While you have to worry about your government's surveillance, they don't have the budgets or expertise to be the same kind of threat as the NSA. They *might* outsource to some of the commercial entities, but this isn't mass surveillance and if you use secure digital OpSec, you're too expensive for them to try breaking into your activities and comms, assuming they can.

So, along these sorts of lines, what are the advantages/disadvantages of being a citizen of a Southern (Lesser-Developed) nation that's not a Five Eyes nation?

Assuming your nation isn't strategically important to a Five Eyes (or Chinese or Russian) nation, such as Saudi Arabia or Turkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, Rule #4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, Rule #4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've done everything right and we commend you for this. Especially being transparent and answering all questions with follow-up.

But next time, give us a head's up? We prefer it in case folks who are worse representatives of their companies don't behave have good as you have. :)

Posting is fine, as you have. But please send a follow-up message to Mods saying, FYI, I work with Wire and I'm answering some questions about Wire here with a link.

Thanks again. You did everything right, except the head's up (which again, is for people who aren't as great as you've been) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed since it's low-value and from a commercial site hyping its business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were a Mod, I'd make your comment stickied and distinguished.

We're loathe to delete things here, but I've added a flair pointing it it's an anon Washington source claiming this. With no evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Banned for a week.

Racism has no place here. Next time, permanent ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, it's a bit old. But it's still a pretty cool post. Chockful of SCIENCE!

It's another scientists' proof that the Collect-It-All approach that the Five Eyes agencies use is useless. Bruce Schneier included this as a followup to another post he wrote with a similar conclusion, [Data Mining for Terrorists](https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2006/03/data_mining_for.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrorists, Data Mining, and the Base Rate Fallacy (Bruce Schneier proves thru SCIENCE (and Bayes Theorem) why NSA-style wholesale surveillance data-mining systems are useless for finding terrorists) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory for general tips, check out:

* our FAQ on the right sidebar. 

* Also /r/privacytoolsio's.

* The [EFF Surveillance Self-Defense Kit](https://ssd.eff.org)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, all 

So I was writing to /u/oh hell the HELL no way I'm typing that out, but let's say, OP on his original post. I didn't approve it since it seemed confusing. I'll post what I wrote him explaining why, so everyone has an idea of what he's looking for, for this post which we approved.

What are some great privacy/anonymity related books that aren't written from a US perspective? Maybe more Euro-centric? British? Even better, from a Developing Nation one? It's a global fight, so let's hear from non-US perspectives! Thanks!

So, if you're looking for anonymity related books, but from a Euro/non-US perspective, include that in the title.

Something like,

Any suggestions on good privacy/anonymity related books, only written from non-US perspective. Europe? UK? Developing nations? Thanks!

Advisory only. My only qualm is if you dislike those two books, don't put them in the title. Why give them free hype? But mentioning as a comment you aren't looking for those two, and why, would be great. Make sense?

Probably TMI, but we'd probably cut slack if it was a universally liked book. "I like *No Place to Hide* and am looking for other great books. Suggestions?" would probably be okay.

Yeah, I admit it's fuzzy like Hell. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if you're looking for anonymity related books, but from a Euro/non-US perspective, include that in the title.

Something like, 

Any suggestions on good privacy/anonymity related books, only written from non-US perspective. Europe? UK? Developing nations? Thanks!

Advisory only. My only qualm is if you dislike those two books, don't put them in the title. Why give them free hype? But mentioning as a comment you *aren't* looking for those two, and why, would be great. Make sense?

Probably TMI, but we'd probably cut slack if it was a universally liked book. "I like *No Place to Hide* and am looking for other great books. Suggestions?" would probably be okay.

Yeah, I admit it's fuzzy like Hell. :)

PS: I'll post this in your post that I just approved. It may get better responses to the questions you have. And, you might want to add a comment, too. Be sure to check back! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mock-up be the size of a Newton, strapped onto a burly wrist.

And people would still be amazed.

Without even bringing up On More Thing. "We've been playing around with a little thing we've named WiFi that lets it talk to something 40 times more powerful than your Mac Quadra that is in your pocket, that connects with a global network of a billion other things that all communicate with each other."

"Oh. One more thing after One More Thing *CATS!"*

It's incredible the rate of change we're living through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind reposting this as an open-ended question asking for great books on (topics), especially ones written by non-Americans our for those living outside the US?

The titles could be seen as backdoor promos for the books. I'm normally pretty lax for getting anyone to read :) but we have to apply the same rules as we do for software, which this post wouldn't be allowed as written.

Also: check out the FAQs both here and in /r/privacytoolsio and possibly /r/europrivacy (and consider posting the modified question there. We list some in these places. :)

Of course, once posted, you can mention all the titles you'd like. It's just the titles we're persnickety about. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Spies: how we got to age of mass surveillance without even trying. Law Prof explains (phenomenally well) how the road to bad law is paved with good intentions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Spies: how we got to age of mass surveillance without even trying. Law Prof explains (phenomenally well) how the road to bad law is paved with good intentions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed, Rule #2

PS: thanks for the reports, folks. They really help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. There's a lot of assumptions in your thinking. You presume much. 

Much like your original comment, come to think of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because? 

Look, OP made a hypothesis, then delivered with *seventeen* cites backing it up. Summarizing the points made in the articles, even. That's Best-Of material. 

Even if you think that a post about China focuses too much on, well, China.

Let's see you put in 10% the energy and care in your future posts. It'll make for a more interesting Reddit. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, then, you probably shouldn't have written you're not familiar with Sri Lanka, then. You can't blame Reddit after you do. 

Since you are familiar with Sri Lanka and presumably SE Asian international relations vis a vis bilateral US/Sino relations in the region, what is your take on the *eighteen* articles from a *variety* or mostly well-regarded media that the OP suggests that China is benefiting from the first 21 days of the Trump regime?

OMG: it's only been *three weeks?!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the posted comment the OP cites *entire purpose* is listing the numerous other stories written by other news sources. *Seventeen* of them.  

And the topic of the post is *China*, so it's a bit absurd to criticize a story on China for focusing on China.

facepalm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am not familiar with Sri Lanka specifically

The fact that you're ignorant about Sri Lanka, and too lazy to visit Wikipedia (etc.) to find out more, disqualifies much of what you said about independently verifying a news story. You realize that, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even worse, regardless of your political affiliation, Trump made the United States look weak. Blustering. Ill-prepared. Stupid. A nation that folds easily once confronted.

All of these make escalation to crisis more likely. All of these weaken our national security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, this makes no sense since you're asking Some Guys On The Internet via a social post to download then send files to you. Defeating the purpose of anonymity. Among other problems.

You might want to make the jump to setting up Tor. And maybe a VPN. It's time. :)

So, no approval, but check out our FAQ -- and/or /r/privacytoolsio for more info :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/u/jlg9721 for the head's up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI cites ongoing investigation and national security exemptions for file on deceased WikiLeaks director. Bureau cites six different exemptions, hints at a Confidential Informant in WikiLeaks case. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, fast-tracking them. 

Along with a "Golden Key" backdoor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sez Who? 

What's your background? Your expertise in patent law? Have you viewed the actual patent application?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it's an Internet of Things device, by a company whose core area of competence isn't software (let alone security software for streaming WiFi devices), theres **no** way this could end up badly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you know you're being recorded, by a company, for consideration (your job) and that someone somewhere is responsible, (hopefully) capable and liable if they're reckless. 

See any differences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also troubling that there's no hardware-based, non-defeatable means to signal those being filmed that they're being filmed. As odious as those glass frame video cameras are, at least manufacturers can hardware a red LED light to warn subjects.

Indeed, no visual signs at all. At least Google Glass or SnapChat glasses are distinctive.

Especially since these things are inevitably paired with insta-face-matching, either by Sony or 3rd parties, geo- and time-tagging, the works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the first batch is more explodey that a freight car of Nexus 7s, so this abomination never catches on.

Or at least, it'll be easier to see who's trying to record me. In case I miss the screeching and agonized screaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if The New World had as many vampire hitchhikers as you have, so would we! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For aspiring scientists out there, the term for this phenomenon is Red Shift. Astronomers are debating what term to use if your car uses automatic transmission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: as your vehicle approaches the speed of light, high beam use is acceptable.

High beams produce angrier photons, thus they are more reactive. Light waves, on the other hand, maintain their mellowness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Unverified, clickbait claims and most likely shilling for a private, unverified service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another digital security guide, but this one is especially nice since it refers to other great guides like EFF's in addition to their own. It's also nice because it's for laypeople and includes why certain privacy tactics are better in which cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freedom of the Press Protect Yourself Guide  Updated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freedom of the Press Protect Yourself Guide  Updated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another digital security guide, but this one is especially nice since it refers to other great guides like EFF's in addition to their own. It's also nice because it's for laypeople and includes why certain privacy tactics are better in which cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freedom of the Press Protect Yourself Guide  Updated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're not dealing with fairy dust and pixies. There are real hardware and software required, with an already dizzying queue of genuinely interesting subjects ahead of some random customs arrival.

I mean, geezus, the FBI blew a cool million dollars to tap into that obsolete iPhone the employer of the San Bernardino shooter had, and it took months.

A KeePass default key length is what these days? How many tries involved in that, just for one person? Let alone millions a year. Then reviewing all that data.

[Encryption Works](https://freedom.press/training/), as many people have famously asserted. That's why authorities are trying so hard to circumvent it through empty threats and social engineering tricks like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's value  a lot of value  to making the costs of surveillance too expensive to do on a mass basis. Even assuming the NSA is going to look fondly at the prospect of scanning 256- or 5120-bit encrypted keys for millions of phone and laptop archives per quarter. Or can, which is highly unlikely.

So, chin up, buttercup! Turn that frowny-face upside down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet.

Let's assume those 18m Canadian day-trippers spend $40 per trip. That's a conservative amount. That's **$720 million** per year these geniuses will be throwing out per year.

And again, anyone that's a real threat will easily counter this measure.

Double idiocy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If any Mods from other Subs ever give you grief over this, tell them to PM us Mods here. No guarantees it'll carry any weight, but we'll vouch that this is a common and legitimate thing to do. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it comes down to how you want to define uncertainty. Someone certainly said it. Whether they'll do it, in what form, to who, if it'll morph after counter-actions, if it'll pass review, etc., is fluid. That it's from an aspiring Authoritarian narcissist suffering low-energy and mild illiteracy (or more charitably, ADD), raises concern   skepticism. 

So, "FUD" is a reasonable criticism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unsure about that notion, especially among the great unwashed hoards who don't Tweet or know what Reddit is, let alone those who don't subscribe to /r/t_d.  

Keep in mind there are a lot of people who would stare blankly if you said, "Gamergate" and that misogynist thigh-dribble is something the little ponce has been railing about the longest.

And of those that do, leaving out t_d, bots and 4Chan, his gig is a pretty repulsive one. Outside of the Neo-Nazi and Red Pill crowd, do you think his schtick carries?

But, besides talking about trolls who are no longer on Twitter, did you read the editorials? What did you think of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. And "bitch" isn't off-the-charts. But if we let you start, then others :)

FWIW, it *is* FUD. Savvy folks will say they have no accounts or point to a dummy one.

What is left unsaid for now is that they *say* it's for the Muslim Ban countries (who for the record are responsible for a cumulative total of 0 US Terror deaths) but it's certain to be expanded to other countries, then all countries, then US citizens returning home. 

CF: Mission Creep. And Authoritarianism.

That's why it's good to try stomping this down before it takes flight. Useless *and* dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Jesus, though. With soft brown hair, blue eyes and rock-hard, chiseled abs.

Not that Arab/Semitic Middle Eastern Jesus. *That* poor bast%rd wouldn't stand a chance of being allowed to enter the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proper credit to u/jlg9721 for finding this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cellphone Surveillance Gear Floods US Cities. Major cities throughout the US have spent millions on mobile surveillance toolsbut there are still few rules about what happens to the information they capture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/jlg1921 for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cellphone Surveillance Gear Floods US Cities. Major cities throughout the U.S. have spent millions on mobile surveillance toolsbut there are still few rules about what happens to the information they capture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't allow crowd-funded project posts, but thanks for thinking of us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. We won't be approving this since the topic has already been covered to death. 

You might want to check out our Peerless /r/Privacy FAQ 

Doing a search on the keywords will find interesting posts.

Or, /r/PrivacyToolsIO or their site also cover this category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends who I watch frantically gesticulating 20% of the time we're out together (and I am one charming mother-freaking conversationalist), hyperventilating and red-faced. All Facebook drama, confined to Facebook drama, meaningless and mundane outside of Facebook drama. All trivial and wouldn't exist without Facebook.

Another thing that's weird: when FB addicts ask what I do on my down time when I'm on the Metro or waiting in line or whatever. "I observe. I recollect. I think."

It's like I said something in a different language.

I'm thinking of getting a box full of copies of *Walden Pond*. Hand out in times like these, silently and without comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you're reading the map upside down, it isn't! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't an OMG YOU KILLED OUR COWS warning, but more a Tsk, tsk, you can do better and your arguments are stronger w/o grade school insults warning.

So, uh, you can do better and your arguments will be more compelling.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note this is a Sept 2016 article, but I thought it was interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These apps were made to share your secrets, and thats why they couldnt last. In the two years since the heyday of Yik Yak, Whisper and Secret, virtually every anonymous messaging app has slowed down, pivoted, or closed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are all of us doing this? No, quite the contrary. So please stop suggesting either side is equally responsible for what a small minority do.

Now, the hate speech, the racism, the shifting government policies and laws to target specific classes of people, all of them do that. Plus the whimsical fascist mob violence abetted by their President. So, yeah, on that, we'll call them on it. Because it's unAmerican and un-Constitutional. And, y'know, evil as Hell.

Are you suggesting we roll over? Invite them for tea   crumpets?

**Hell** no. We're the party of FDR   JFK, too. They want a knife fight, we can do that too. But it's idiotic to go all Corporate Democrat, wailing "Can't We Get Along, *Please!?*" while they're jabbing our bellies.

 #Indivisible. https://www.indivisibleguide.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Donald Trump ordering the beating of people 

Wait. Didn't Trump, in fact, encourage his mobs attending his rallies to assault people? Didn't he promise he'd pay all legal expenses if they did? In a mob situation, which 

I seem to recall that. Don't you? Before older men, women and other pacifist people were cold-cocked (and the Trump supporters jeering wildly when they didn't join in)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parte uno:

 You *do* realize that "Alt" and "Neo"   "Right" and in this context "Nazi" are literally re-workings of each other? That these geniuses are on record boasting about this? Their (and your?) own words.

So, "Neo-Nazi" = "Alt-Right," minus *cutsie-*ness. And almost *everyone* hates cutsie-ness. So don't use it.

Parte dos: 

No one outside your fevered mind thinks that all conservatives, or even Conservatives, are Alt-Right (or see above, Neo-Nazis). Only you.

Your doing so makes what they call un hombre de paja. You don't mean to create hombres de paja, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. 

It's almost as though most Cal students  and thus most Daily Cal writers  think poorly of carpet-bagging, fame-whoring, Neo-Nazi provocateurs who planned on giving a lecture on how to Narc their fellow UC Berkeley students to the Federal police.

What *monsters*.

Ahem Go Blue! Go Daily Cal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Californian Op/Eds favoring removing troll lecturer that caused MiloAtCal protests: Violence As Self-Defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/jlg9721 for the head's up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA rejections hint at lingering secrets surrounding Cold War codebreakers. Agency insists encrypted VENONA transmissions - some of which could be over 70 years old - are classified TOP SECRET. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one remembers anyone's phone number or email addresses any more, they input it once and forget it. So why bother with putting in your real name?

As a compromise, you could always use a partial. E.G. "Trai_Campus", although in my case, it's so unusual I wouldn't use "Trai". So I'd use "Timmy_Campus" and wait for the Provost to expel me when they find out :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems it's more hypothetical at this point, on its way to experimental. Far from common but certainly an emerging threat to worry about.

Some of the Linux community [are exploring ways to counter this](http://phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item px=Anti-Keystroke-FP-Wayland-Kern)

I suppose using old-school things like hunt-and-peck when in another identity, or even not using, say your ring fingers, would throw off the algorithms. Does anyone know of any other counters, either in meatspace or software? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One might argue charity built upon a lifetime of controversial actions isn't the same as running a company from the start from enlightened self-interested principles.

For instance, both Carnagie and Rockefeller ran *monstrous* business conglomerates, but then took some of their vast, arguably ill-gotten profits and gave some of them to charity. Microsoft did, and does, some pretty sleazy things. So does Facebook.

It's better than nothing, sure. But even better is doing the right thing, from the start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook is evil, literally founded on the notion, "They trusted me. The stupid fucks."

A lot different than Apple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Enlightened Self Interest". It's a Thing. A perfectly valid, ethical and awesome thing. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool. Thanks!

Well, the idea of threat modeling (of which your threat profile is a part) is that being secure costs. Time, money, focus, learning And to be super-secure all the time against the best adversaries is exhausting. Which results in mistakes. So instead, figure out what you're doing, when, and who might want to know about it behind your back. What's the cost if you lose? What's the effort? Where's the sensible balance?

Ex: your horrible kid sister breaking into your diary w/ a hairpin is different than your boss finding out you attended the Woman's March protest last month, which is different than your reporting on fraud, waste   abuse at the NSA in one of their billion-dollar programs that they'd just as soon not have everyone know about. Or your girl (boy) friend's hostile parent/cop might be interested in knowing you buy weed but have an expired Rx.

All sorts of harmless  even heroic  things that face different threats, with different outcomes. If you're worried about your kid sister but you're countering it as though she were the NSA, that's wasted effort that will make it likely you'll screw up or decide, Screw It. Then get busted by your boy (girl) friend's crappy parent abusing his power to break you guys up.

So, you want to balance out the threats and outcomes from the work involved, and compartmentalize. Do social things you don't care about without much worries, pay your credit card bill with more concern, attend a legal protest (sigh: yes [it's come to this, at least in the US](http://mashable.com/2017/02/06/dc-police-subpoena-facebook-inauguration-protests/)) with more care, and communicate with someone (who knows someone who knows someone) who's a whistleblower with even more.

(Shout-out in reference to the above *It's Come To This* link: Don't Use Facebook To Organize *Anything*. Even better, don't use Facebook)

* The [Electronic Frontier Foundation](https://eff.org) has more in their [Surveillance Self Defense](https://ssd.eff.org/ssd) kit. They also cover what to do for your mobile, when protesting, if reporting and other situations. They're pretty cool.

* *The Intercept* is a great site and have an [If You See Something, Leak Something](https://theintercept.com/leak/) campaign with further tips, especially journalism-related.

* I'd be remiss if I didn't mention Reddit resources like /r/Privacy and /r/PrivacyToolsIO.
______

So. Back to the question.

Before, there was you, there was the threat. And there was Apple on your side. Then the US government tried through a sneaky, sleazy and almost secret process to **force** Apple to create a version of their iOS that would betray its users. This custom GovtOS  would make it trivial to break any iPhone. Apple said, "You *crazy!*" the FBI said, "Screw you, DO IT," and [The Apple vs FBI](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FBIApple_encryption_dispute) case happened. People  a **lot** of people  freaked out, Apple stood tall fighting for us, the FBI caved (after lying about 20 times (yay, FBI!) in their formal legal statements). Apple wasn't forced to create GovtOS and we were all saved. For now.

But the *idea* that governments would **force** Apple to betray their users made Cook and Apple decide, "Geez, we always assumed we'd be free to protect our users' privacy. But what happens if/when governments pull this crap again?"

Thus going forward (and already for many, many things), Apple's privacy protocols ensure that Apple is *also* a zero-knowledge party. iMessage? End-to-End encrypted that (so long as you don't back up to iCloud) not even Apple can read. Your newer iPhone and all Macs? Encrypted, usually by default, that Apple can't read. [Etc.](https://www.apple.com/privacy/) 

iCloud is the big remaining item, and some folks would like to see some more transparency with Messages, so that might be tweaked.

These last steps are what happens when Apple includes itself as part of the threat model. That is, in addition to your kid sister, your significant other's crazy, abusive dad, your boss or E. European hackers, Apple includes *itself* as a party that might (hypothetically!) be forced to betray you.

TL;DR: the fact that a company like Apple has to worry about (hypothetically!) being forced to betray its users, after decades of fighting for us, has to piss Tim Cook (and Apple) off. It'd be great to get his reaction to that.

Does that help? Enjoy the lecture  I'm envious!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk's SpaceX and Tesla join filing against Trump's travel ban, now join 97 other tech firms in supporting Washington state lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the last decade, despite only having a core group of around 15 people working on its research full time, Citizen Lab has uncovered evidence of government espionage within the Dalai Lama's network; lifted the lid on Western companies that quietly sell spyware used by police and intelligence agencies to target dissidents and human rights activists in Morocco, Bahrain, Ethiopia and many other countries; and revealed the existence of a new powerful Chinese censorship system. These are just some of the lab's most famous reports.

When I asked renowned security expert Bruce Schneier what Citizen Lab research impressed him the most, he paused for a moment and then said: "God, it's all good. Right?"

Click thru for more. A great series and a great article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the last decade, despite only having a core group of around 15 people working on its research full time, Citizen Lab has uncovered evidence of government espionage within the Dalai Lama's network; lifted the lid on Western companies that quietly sell spyware used by police and intelligence agencies to target dissidents and human rights activists in Morocco, Bahrain, Ethiopia and many other countries; and revealed the existence of a new powerful Chinese censorship system. These are just some of the lab's most famous reports.

When I asked renowned security expert Bruce Schneier what Citizen Lab research impressed him the most, he paused for a moment and then said: "God, it's all good. Right?"

Click thru for more. A great series and a great article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Deiberts CitizenLab Is the 'Robin Hood' of Cyber Security. (Humans of the Year series) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Deiberts CitizenLab Is the 'Robin Hood' of Cyber Security. (Humans of the Year series) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone Modded Wolfenstein 3D to Ask If Violence Against Nazis Is Okay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, it's not only Vizio:

The allegations are only the latest to raise troubling privacy concerns about Internet-connected TVs and other so-called Internet-of-things devices. In late 2015, security researchers found that Vizio TVs failed to properly validate the HTTPS certificates of servers they connected to when transmitting viewing-habit data. That made it trivial for anyone who had the ability to monitor and control the Internet traffic passing between the TV and the Vizio servers to impersonate the servers and view or tamper with the transmitted data. Smart TVs manufactured by LG have also been caught collecting potentially sensitive data, including a list of shows being watched, the names of files contained on connected USB drives, and the names of files shared on home or office networks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vizio smart TVs tracked viewers around the clock without consent, will pay $2.2 million and delete data to settle privacy-invasion charges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about paying a living wage for their drivers, with benefits, while obeying state   local labor and safety laws? *Disrupt* that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if there's one entity I want in control of mass market, consumer flying vehicles, it's the one who snuck autonomous driving cars onto CA roads without notifying police or the DMV. Then told them to screw themselves when they asked Uber to register their early beta-test on public roads like every other freaken' Bot-driven car company.

Oh. Bonus points: running red lights and not "seeing" bicyclists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a world of surprising political changes, what role does technology have to preserve our ability to read, think and communicate without fear of governments and others looking over our shoulder?

Ten years ago, did you ever think governments would force you to include Apple as part of a MacOS   iOS threat profile? From a moral/ethical standpoint, how do you feel about being forced into this situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During Trumps chaotic first weeks in office, the Golden State has embraced its reputation for progressive politics and civil rights activism and has cemented its role as the state that will lead the movement to defy the White House.

Despite concerns of possible retaliation from Trump, Californias leaders have pledged to aggressively resist him  on immigration, health, the environment, voting rights and more  while grassroots activists have strategized ways to stand up for the most vulnerable communities and launch mass actions... 

Click thru for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google to appeal against order to hand over user emails stored outside US. Judge rules Gmail-provider must comply with FBI warrants despite privacy implications, contrary to previous ruling in similar Microsoft case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse than Falluja, really.

In fact, it's amazing I'm typing this since my head was lopped on then posted to YouTube ages ago. The bits that weren't already blown up, that is.

I mean, the act, not my physical head, posted to YouTube. I'd imagine that'd make my touchscreen sticky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What special class of idiots go through the bother of splitting into two states, then as a follow-up, both keep the same name but lazily slaps North and South on them?

The last imaginative thing the Dakotas did was host dinosaurs briefly. Until they realized they lived in North Dakota and all joined in on a mass suicide event. And they had *bird-brains!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to remove this, since [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5s99eh/fbi_demands_emails_from_foreign_google_servers/) beat it by a few hours and covers the same topic. More comments, too.

Thanks SO much for the effort though, /u/powercow. Plz think of us again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By accommodation, do they mean allow her to transfer to a different school? Transfer the alleged student rapists? Transfer/expel the student hosting the parties? Sanction his parents?

And what happens if the victim doesn't want to identify the victim (thus blocking at least 1/3 of the options)? And of course, due process (for the alleged rapist or the party host (and his father)).

Don't get me wrong  100% sympathies for the victim here. Crappy dad. But what remedies, against whom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm usually one to err on the side of plaintiffs in cases like these, but it seems unreasonable to hold a district responsible for a parent of a student going to an alternative school. Teachers weren't involved. It was held off school property and the school had no role promoting the parties. 

The article seemed confusing on this point: were these school events, or were these events that students of the school attended? 

Even for what could be viewed as someone trying too hard to be a Cool Dad, neither he, or his kid, were aware of these rapes (not 100% sure since the article is confusing on this), were notified of them or participated in them.

Suing the father I could see. You hold several parties where bad things happen (damage, underage drinking, etc, let alone sexual assaults), you have some culpability. But a district, of an alt-school, of one student, with a sloppy parent?

Keep in mind, monies the district pays out in attorneys, settlements and judgements is money that's not spent on schools, learning, teachers and kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please review points AD again. You point isn't related to any of them.

It's like saying, "If a publisher posts a story on their Facebook feed, none of the pernicious aspects of Facebook are a concern." This would be patently untrue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I especially like how there's a glossary for this. Honestly, some of the terms mystify me, and I'm a supposed knowledgeable person on these things!

Kudos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Please** don't use Google links. 

a) we have no way of [evaluating the source](http://www.sfchronicle.com/crime/article/Wild-parties-an-alleged-rape-and-a-high-10906945.php) to see if it's worth the bother of the click-thru (SF Chron in this case).

b) It provides clicks  and thus revenue  for a 3rd party that did no work (or spent costs) to write the story. Reporters gotta eat and without the original source getting paid, fake news will rise triumphant.

c) It provides analytic data for a 3rd party that does a *lot* of work (really brilliant work) to track down anyone on the net, tying together the various things we all do on the web, ties it up in a pretty bow then sells it to other parties. Really, Google, Facebook and the like already do this well enough on their own. Do we *really* need to help them more?

d) I suspect it's a Google AMP link, so it's mobile-optimized. Everyone's not on mobile, folks.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duplicate of https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5ry36i/hacker_dumps_older_ios_cracking_tools_allegedly/.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dup of [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5ry36i/hacker_dumps_older_ios_cracking_tools_allegedly/), but thanks!

Also, we're running an experiment this weekend to flag non-HTTPS links, which your MacRumors post flagged. We want to see if we can get more secure links to sites as our default.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminder that just this November,  the Director of the FBI, against Dep't of Justice statutes, issued a letter accusing Clinton of bogus charges which many credit flipping the Electoral College election in Trump's favor. That he was forced to retract, but not before it served its purpose.

Regardless how you feel about either candidate, reflect how poorly you'd think of an East European federal internal security chief issuing false but inflammatory charges that changed the results of that election. Now consider, shouldn't America be better than Soviet-era East Germany? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no criminal and I've got nothing to hide!

Yeah. About that:

In January, EPIC obtained two years of monthly statistics for the NGI system under the Freedom of Information Act. The summary sheets show that the databases expansion has been fueled by submissions of non-criminal identifiers, such as the prints submitted for background checks. Fact sheets from January 2015 through August 2016 show the database growing at a much higher rate from its collection of data from civil settings than from criminal justice purposes. During that period, **civil submission rates constituted nearly 70 percent of new submissions. Through the Rap Back program the FBI is collecting biographical and biometric data on potentially millions of civilians for purposes not associated with criminal justice,** Scott said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beware of unintended consequences, though.

Imagine the resulting carnage to your sex toy collection, for starters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose at some point, there'd be consumer band-sweepers that look for unknown WiFi streams pumping out data that you're not expecting then flash an LED light. Possibly with a gauge that helps with proximity?

The only problem would be a lot of false positives, especially considering how far, say, your neighbors' or roommate's IoT devices broadcast.

What other approaches would work conceptually? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a link](http://craigconnects.org/2016/10/poll-shows-social-media-usage-is-growing-but-so-are-concerns-on-personal-privacy.html) to the CraigConnects blog with the original survey + raw data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans Don't Trust Facebook, Twitter to Protect Privacy, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'You would never know it was there': Peeping Toms go high-tech with covert cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hacker responsible has publicly released a cache of files allegedly stolen from Cellebrite relating to Android and BlackBerry devices, and older iPhones, some of which may have been copied from publicly available phone cracking tools.

"The debate around backdoors is not going to go away, rather, its is almost certainly going to get more intense as we lurch toward a more authoritarian society," the hacker told Motherboard in an online chat.

"It's important to demonstrate that when you create these tools, they will make it out. History should make that clear," they continued.

Considering the government can't even secure super-sensitive OPM files, and neither the RNC or the DNC bother spending the (relatively) modest capital to secure their systems, I'd say this gentleman has a very good point.

Click thru for more  it's a great article by Joseph Cox! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hacker responsible has publicly released a cache of files allegedly stolen from Cellebrite relating to Android and BlackBerry devices, and older iPhones, some of which may have been copied from publicly available phone cracking tools.

"The debate around backdoors is not going to go away, rather, its is almost certainly going to get more intense as we lurch toward a more authoritarian society," the hacker told Motherboard in an online chat.

"It's important to demonstrate that when you create these tools, they will make it out. History should make that clear," they continued.

Considering the government can't even secure super-sensitive OPM files, and neither the RNC or the DNC bother spending the (relatively) modest capital to secure their systems, I'd say this gentleman has a very good point.

Click thru for more  it's a great article by Joseph Cox! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacker Dumps [Older] iOS Cracking Tools Allegedly Stolen from Celebrate. Hacker says, This demonstrates that when organizations make hacking tools, those techniques will eventually find their way to the public. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacker Dumps [Older] iOS Cracking Tools Allegedly Stolen from Celebrate. Hacker says, This demonstrates that when organizations make hacking tools, those techniques will eventually find their way to the public. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off-topic and promoting a site with murky goals. Removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple will sell students $630 of professional software for just $200. Package includes Final Cut Pro, Logic Pro X, Motion, Compressor, and MainStage 3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny  I'm a critical reader, even if it is from one of the "legitimate" sources since Stuff Happens. I may drop my guard a bit more if it's a more reliable source, but I still check the quality of it  sourcing, multiple parties involved, etc.

In this case, I was pleasantly surprised. And Buzzfeed (News probably as you point out) has broken some good stories. I put them in the same category as Business Insider  normally schlock but every so often, a good story.

Yeah  it's pretty frightening, actually. And it's useful to see how the propaganda sausages are made, and how easy it can be if there's an organized echo chamber to amplify these efforts.

Maybe next time, folks will be more skeptical. That was the main reason I felt it was useful as a Press Freedom story here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not know that. I guess that's why I found my experiences hit-and-miss.

It's funny how much people are freaking out over their animosity towards the site (even funnier since as you point out, they misunderstand it, as I did) yet few are actually discussing the content of the article, or whether the practice of using *Agent Provocateurs* to manipulate the media for propagandist purposes is a good or bad thing.

*Sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also agree this is way too opaque to have any lift to make a difference with the US electorate. It's a curiosity for me  the OP's post draws far more strands together, better.

Besides, we're not even past our second week  are we at war with Australia yet? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. It's laughably insane that a Presidential candidate wouldn't do as all prior candidates did, and release his tax forms. Why wouldn't he? Because however bad *not* releasing them would be, whatever is there is unimaginably worse, corruption-wise.

Same thing with all those ethics forms that his nominees refuse to complete. They don't get it: it *protects* them, too  from claims like Trump is drowning under now, simply because he didn't do the right thing when he should of. Thus eliminating these doubts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but /u/Aethien took the effort to pull the figures out, with context, succinctly. That's why I wanted to give him the credit.

The major take-away is that there are significant amounts of money unaccounted for that the Glencore/Qutar explanation can't explain. It's *not* a routine, if overly-lawyered, corporate finance deal.

That's all I'm saying. If it was on its own, I'd agree, Tin-Foil. Sure. But as the OP's post shows, there are *way* too many of these "coincidences", further compounded by Trump's actions before and after the election.

These situations are tough: it's not as though Russian oligarchs or other corrupt Authoritarians are stupid enough to walk into each others' offices carrying big gunny sacks with "$" printed on them.

Do you think they'd go through the effort then *not* have a plausible story lined up? Their problem is the figures don't add up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I'm* not claiming to be a financial expert. Where do you see that?

That's why folks use links to, say, Reuters articles. Those journalists are, or know those who are. Aren't reputable journalists *great?* ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're normally hit-and-miss. Particularly when they go full-on clickbait with the titles. But in this case, if you bother reading the article, you'll see they did original research, with public evidence, including from the subject of the article, Posobiec.

I agree they're not a go-to source, normally. We live in interesting times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credible, actually. As close as we can get, given the opaque nature of so shifty of a transaction.

Especially for such a large transaction of a company that operates globally, and thus needs *some* pretense of transparency of ownership to avoid most other nations and companies being hesitant to invest or trade with them Unless, of course, there were illegal but compelling reasons to forge ahead, anyway.

I'll bring /u/Aethien's [excellent summary here](https://np.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/5roev7/donald_trump_lifts_sanctions_on_russia_that_were/dd96pel/) since it's perfect and reputably sourced (Reuters).

[Glencore contributed only 300 million euros of equity to the deal, less than 3 percent of the purchase price, which it said in a statement on Dec. 10 had bought it an "indirect equity interest" limited to just 0.54 percent of Rosneft.](http://mobile.reuters.com/article/amp/idUSKBN1582OH)

Qatar paid for 2.5 billion, QHG (unknown owners through various shell companies including one at the Cayman Isles) paid 5.2 billion which it borrowed from an Italian bank which leaves a 2.2 billion dollar gap.

This quote from the article is also interesting: 

"But public records in Singapore show that Russia's second-largest bank, state-controlled VTB, loaned the Singapore vehicle QHG Shares the full 10.2 billion euros that it paid to the Russian state last month to buy the stake." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The photo of a Rape Melania sign that went viral was not the work of an anti-Trump protester at all. Instead, according to sources, it was the brainchild of a group of Trump supporters led by Jack Posobiec, one of the organizers of the controversial DeploraBall inauguration party and a prominent figure in the pro-Trump internet.

Furthermore, as shown by a series of Posobiecs text messages obtained by BuzzFeed News and confirmed by a source who collaborated with Posobiec, the sign was the culmination of a disinformation campaign by Posobiec and others intended to paint the anti-Trump rallies as violent and out of control.

Click thru for more, including an interesting case of a secure means of communication, Signal, being used to verify a 3rd-party source's claim was valid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The photo of a Rape Melania sign that went viral was not the work of an anti-Trump protester at all. Instead, according to sources, it was the brainchild of a group of Trump supporters led by Jack Posobiec, one of the organizers of the controversial DeploraBall inauguration party and a prominent figure in the pro-Trump internet.

Furthermore, as shown by a series of Posobiecs text messages obtained by BuzzFeed News and confirmed by a source who collaborated with Posobiec, the sign was the culmination of a disinformation campaign by Posobiec and others intended to paint the anti-Trump rallies as violent and out of control.

Click thru for more, including an interesting case of a secure means of communication, Signal, being used to verify a 3rd-party source's claim was valid.

Since manipulation of media, including social media, and manufactured "fake news" is a propaganda tool affecting a functioning press, I'm tagging this as Press Freedom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside The Alt-Rights Campaign To Smear Trump Protesters As Anarchists. Viral photos of a sign urging violence against Melania Trump at an anti-Trump protest  and worse  were planned by one of the organizers of the DeploraBall, Jack Posobiec </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside The Alt-Rights Campaign To Smear Trump Protesters As Anarchists. Viral photos of a sign urging violence against Melania Trump at an anti-Trump protest  and worse  were planned by one of the organizers of the DeploraBall, Jack Posobiec </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially during Taste Test Week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friendly reminder, car-addicted folks:

* Lights off, especially at dusk and dawn. Black lights at night

* Objects moving twice as fast are four times harder to hit

* Windshield wipers only smear water around  say NO to hydro-flow tyranny!

* Pedestrians are surprisingly spry. Most will heal without further attention. 

* Since talking on your cellphone while driving in the rain is too distracting, try to minimize risk by texting instead. 

* Does the idea of your extended commute make you drowsy? Wouldn't watching the entire *Lord of the Rings* trilogy  Extended Version, 'natch  be grand? Who deserves it? *You* deserve it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To which, [Rep. Barbara Lee replied](https://twitter.com/RepBarbaraLee/status/827187557838491652),

Pres. Trump doesnt have a license to blackmail universities. Hes the president, not a dictator, and his empty threats are an abuse of power.

**Congresswoman Lee's Statement on Berkeley Protests**

Milo Yiannopoulos has made a career of inflaming racist, sexist and nativist sentiments. Berkeley has a proud history of dissent and students were fully within their rights to protest peacefully. However, I am disappointed by the unacceptable acts of violence last night which were counterproductive and dangerous.

President Trump cannot bully our university into silence. Simply put, President Trump's empty threat to cut funding from UC Berkeley is an abuse of power. As a senior member of the education funding subcommittee, I will continue to stand up to President Trump's overreach and defend the rights of our students and faculty.

You go, girl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To which, [Rep. Barbara Lee replied](https://twitter.com/RepBarbaraLee/status/827187557838491652),

Pres. Trump doesnt have a license to blackmail universities. Hes the president, not a dictator, and his empty threats are an abuse of power.

**Congresswoman Lee's Statement on Berkeley Protests**

Milo Yiannopoulos has made a career of inflaming racist, sexist and nativist sentiments. Berkeley has a proud history of dissent and students were fully within their rights to protest peacefully. However, I am disappointed by the unacceptable acts of violence last night which were counterproductive and dangerous.

President Trump cannot bully our university into silence. Simply put, President Trump's empty threat to cut funding from UC Berkeley is an abuse of power. As a senior member of the education funding subcommittee, I will continue to stand up to President Trump's overreach and defend the rights of our students and faculty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To which, [Rep. Barbara Lee replied](https://twitter.com/RepBarbaraLee/status/827187557838491652),

Pres. Trump doesnt have a license to blackmail universities. Hes the president, not a dictator, and his empty threats are an abuse of power.

**Congresswoman Lee's Statement on Berkeley Protests**

Milo Yiannopoulos has made a career of inflaming racist, sexist and nativist sentiments. Berkeley has a proud history of dissent and students were fully within their rights to protest peacefully. However, I am disappointed by the unacceptable acts of violence last night which were counterproductive and dangerous.

President Trump cannot bully our university into silence. Simply put, President Trump's empty threat to cut funding from UC Berkeley is an abuse of power. As a senior member of the education funding subcommittee, I will continue to stand up to President Trump's overreach and defend the rights of our students and faculty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Threatens UC Berkeley's Federal Funding After Milo Yiannopoulos Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Threatens UC Berkeley's Federal Funding After Milo Yiannopoulos Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Threatens UC Berkeley's Federal Funding After Milo Yiannopoulos Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy convicted - whoops, sorry forced to settle b/c overwhelming evidence - of fraud has no business at all of informing real academic institutions on what they do.

Besides the fact that is wasn't the Cal Administration that caused a bit of property damage.

How many *lives* have Republicans destroyed since Jan 20th? How many will they in the next four years?

Let's work on stopping that, instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It may only take 3.5% of the population to topple a dictator with civil resistance. The US has a rich history with effective uses of nonviolent resistance. Its time to become familiar with it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see many people confused on this, so it's worth noting again.

It doesnt matter, by the way, whether the Muslims in question are citizens or noncitizens, green card holders, visa holders or refugees. The Equal Protection Clause explicitly prohibits deny[ing] to any person within its jurisdiction the equal protection of the laws This means that all foreign travelers on U.S. soilthose waiting at U.S. airports, for exampleare protected.

The Constitution and Bill of Rights places limits on *government* powers, versus protecting citizens directly. Likewise, any powers not specifically, limitedly granted in these documents, the government does not have.

That's why, for instance, we can have a Constitutional right to privacy, even though there isn't a specific amendment for it.

But, no free lunch: they gave us our republic, now it's our job to keep it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uber has confirmed it has had to install an automated process to handle account deletions. First noted by Mike Isaac of the New York Times, previously an Uber employee had to put through each account deletion manually.

*Ouch!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Google business model isn't predicated on ignoring local   Federal laws, while destroying living-wage jobs, many with benefits, to below-wage jobs, with none.

So, there's that.

And, it's not as though Lyft is the only option  mass transit, taxies and swapping rides with actual friends are still available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why we shouldn't allow extremes in wealth. At Junta-tastic levels, you get to the point where there's always *some* oligarch that owns a piece of both sides of the transaction.

Besides using local mass transit and taxis, which *are* more ethical alternatives, what's your suggestion? No boycotting Uber and do nothing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since local police departments are compromised with White Supremacist groups, the FBI doesn't investigate Right Wing terrorism. And since the GOP largely lionizes them when they do, they're even less inclined to pursue them, even without these local police resources.

And now we have a President many see as either extremely close to an Authoritarian eager to trample the US Constitution (and media, and dissent) or an outright Fascist, it's hard to argue we live in singularly perilous times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Has Quietly Investigated White Supremacist Infiltration of Law Enforcement; Bureau policies have been crafted to take into account the active presence of domestic extremists in U.S. police departments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Based on a Vague Tip, the Feds Can Surveil Anyone; Low-level assessments allow the FBI to follow people with planes, examine travel records, and run subjects names through the CIA and NSA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Gives Itself Lots of Rope to Pull in Informants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Trump has inherited a vast domestic intelligence agency with extraordinary secret powers. A cache of documents offers a rare window into the FBIs quiet expansion since 9/11.

This is an amazing set of documents, liberated by numerous FOIA demands then annotated (follow the link to see them). Additionally, a series of articles have also been written based on this trove that we'll be featuring here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Donald Trump has been in power less than two weeks and has already done incredible damage. Hes signing executive orders like they are autographed pictures  but this isnt a reality show. 

This week on Intercepted we talk to former senior FBI agent Ali Soufan about the commander in chiefs radical edicts, the Muslim ban, and Trumps campaign to make torture great again. Constitutional rights lawyers Faiza Patel and Vince Warren dissect the (il)legality of Trumps immigration ban and Rep. Barbara Lee breaks down Trumps terrifying approach to government. Former covert agent Mike German and Intercept Editor-in-Chief Betsy Reed explain what secret FBI documents published this week by The Intercept tell us about how Trump could resurrect J. Edgar Hoovers legacy. Hip-hop artist Brother Ali performs. Plus, Peter Sarsgaard stars in the bizarre true story of an NSA operative with exciting vacation tips for fellow operatives on their way to interrogate prisoners at Guantnamo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intercepted Podcast: Trump Week Two, The Rise of Chief Yookeroo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congresswoman Barbara Lee Discusses Trump's First Week As President. 'This is the beginning of something.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Sanctuary State' Bill Moves Forward in California Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Sanctuary State' Bill Moves Forward in California Senate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time To #DeleteUber In Oakland. The companys attempted sabotage of taxi drivers supporting immigrants should doom its move to Uptown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever wonder how Federal agents go about recruiting informants? Now you know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confidential Human Source Assessing Aid - Leaked FBI Guide by The Intercept </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it is Trump-free. There are 8 stories concerning hacking   surveillance. Many of them cover non-Five-Eye nations, so most Americans and British may have not read them (and if they had, so what?). And they were written in 2016 by Privacy International, an internationally recognized digital and civil rights non-profit.

OP's user name /u/PrivacyIntl even checks out!

*Geez,* people. Let's bring convo back to the topics that matter, not diverting meta-conversations about things that don't. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stout works really well. I have friends that swear by it.

I lack the self-discipline  I end up drinking all mine before I am supposed to pour it in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly goose. If you sprinkle crushed Doritos over it, how will you ever find the grated Oxycontin pieces? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, /u/Graintop, you are AWESOME! The best part about chili is that everyone makes their own, and each pot of chili is it's own wondrous, delicious reward. Even better than pizza!

But frankly, after the past 10 days, I get tired of typing out Trump-related responses so instead I went for a whimsical Chili War post.

I'd have *thought* the 20-paces-at-dawn-Chili-Dual  and FIVE emoji!  would have been a tip-off, but allow me to add:

/s. Or ;)

Better? 

Much love (and loved your initial post, too)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be one of *those* people who lament your not using black beans you've soaked in brine water for two days instead of canned beans, but I'm not one of those people. (I'm happy with *silently* judging, thanks!)

And where are your limes?

But upon your not including fresh chilis  and **lots** of them, several varieties  I must make my Chili Stand.

Habaneros. Or *maybe* those pale green ones that only kick in a minute after eating them. At dawn.

20 paces. 

Whoever can eat five of them ( for the chili-impaired) the quickest wins.

Err, "wins".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, the poster, Privacy International (PI), is a UK-based registered charity that defends and promotes the right to privacy across the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if she goes against an un-Constitutional religion-based Muslim ban, I guess I dont need to bother asking her legal guidance on my accepting 19% of the Resneft oil fields via 20 Cayman shell accounts in exchange for removing Russian sanctions for hacking the DNC and invading Crimea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy?!!

You're doing corruption wrong if the government official/US President you've turned against his country needs to *buy* anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also might want to check out [this thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/5nps4d/will_using_a_bluetooth_earpiece_affect_the/). Another journalist was asking similar questions.

But both The Intercept, the Press Freedom Foundation and of course, EFF are great resources, as others have noted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting Op/Ed thought piece. 

The administration is testing the extent to which the DHS (and other executive agencies) can act and ignore orders from the other branches of government. This is as serious as it can possibly get: all of the arguments about whether order X or Y is unconstitutional mean nothing if elements of the government are executing them and the courts are being ignored.

Yesterday was the trial balloon for a coup dtat against the United States. It gave them useful information.

It builds on what the author, Yonatan Zunger, wrote the day before, [What Things Going Wrong Can Look Like](https://medium.com/@yonatanzunger/what-things-going-wrong-can-look-like-400f84a0cc3a#.hydz0nzbq) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trial Balloon for a Coup? Analyzing the news of the past 24 hours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa.

This is as unprecedented as a President earning a disapproval rating of more than half of America in under ten days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama breaks silence on Trump presidency to condemn migration ban. Exercising right to assemble and be heard is exactly what we expect to see when American values are at stake, former president says through spokesman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, they've renamed that seat the Vladimir Putin Chair, so some confusion is to be expected. They don't allow cell phones in NSC meetings, so it was the best Russia could do.

It's also noteworthy that the WH Press Secretary, Sean Spicer, amplified this blatant lie as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Grugqs Twitter Activist Security Guide  Guidelines for Safer Resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspect in Quebec Mosque Attack Quickly Depicted by Fox News   the White House as a Moroccan Muslim. Hes actually a White Nationalist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U.S. military officials initially denied any civilian deaths, and (therefore) the CNN report on the raid said nothing about any civilians being killed.

Spoiler: there were. Many.

But reports from Yemen quickly surfaced that 30 people were killed, including 10 women and children. Among the dead: the 8-year-old granddaughter of Nasser al-Awlaki, Nawar, who was also the daughter of Anwar Awlaki.

The girl was was shot in the neck and killed, bleeding to death over the course of two hours. Why kill children?, the grandfather asked. This is the new (U.S.) administration  its very sad, a big crime.

I'm not completely sure this is an area in which US Presidents should be competing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we said, We will make history!

We never said it would be the *good* kind of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much. Removed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have provided each of the account holders with copies of the relevant NSLs (certain information redacted to protect privacy) as well as the account data we were compelled to produce. While the actual NSLs request a large amount of data, Twitter provides a very limited set of data in response to NSLs consistent with federal law and interpretive guidance from the U.S. Department of Justice.

So, don't panic. If Twitter hasn't contacted you yet, you're not the target. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have provided each of the account holders with copies of the relevant NSLs (certain information redacted to protect privacy) as well as the account data we were compelled to produce. While the actual NSLs request a large amount of data, Twitter provides a very limited set of data in response to NSLs consistent with federal law and interpretive guidance from the U.S. Department of Justice.

So, don't panic. If Twitter hasn't contacted you yet, you're not the target. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #Transparency update: Twitter discloses national security letters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #Transparency update: Twitter discloses National Security Letters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And only to fight the worst of the worst. Worser than the worst, even. They *swear!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To show all you budding (real-world) privacy activists what's possible, and why focusing on local municipalities first works better than trying to take on the entire Federal government (at first), the CA cities of San Francisco, Oakland and Richmond all pushed back. 

A fusion center was significantly cut back, contracts cancelled, scopes limited, data retention windows accepted, etc. And Richmond and Oakland have active, feisty Privacy Boards overseeing what happens in their cities. 

All police aren't bad, the same as all police aren't all good. A balance needs to be struck, which only happens with citizen involvement.

Here are a couple of stories by another great reporter, Darwin BondGraham, of the excellent *East Bay Express,* on this:

* [Privacy Commissioners Question Oakland Police About Capabilities of Cell Phone Surveillance Device](http://www.eastbayexpress.com/SevenDays/archives/2016/10/07/privacy-commissioners-question-oakland-police-about-capabilities-of-cell-phone-surveillance-device)

* [Oakland Privacy Commission Approves Surveillance Transparency and Oversight Law](http://www.eastbayexpress.com/SevenDays/archives/2017/01/06/oakland-privacy-commission-approves-surveillance-transparency-and-oversight-law)

! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know what kind of privacy protections exist for NY   NJ city/state fusion centers? Were local governments forced to adapt better policies? 

A lot of residents are pushing back on these so-called domain awareness/fusion centers. Is this happening there, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm approving it but please be aware we don't allow IDing people here, so any "reveals" should be done via PM or outside Reddit.

Also, Mods haven't verified OP is a reporter (odds are s/he might be, but we don't want folks to think we've taken this step). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The proposed system would be massive, the [memo reads](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/3428597-RFI.html) (document cloud):

The Authority is interested in implementing a Facial Detection System, in a free-flow highway environment, where vehicle movement is unimpeded at highway speeds as well as bumper-to-bumper traffic, and license plate images are taken and matched to occupants of the vehicles (via license plate number) with Facial Detection and Recognition methods from a gantry-based or road-side monitoring location.

Click thru for more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we have any idea of how much money is involved? To which companies? Are they politically well-connected?

And what are the start-up costs versus maintenance ones? Is DHS or other Federal money involved?

Deep Throat's dictum, Follow The Money, is handy with stories like these.

We defeated one of these efforts a couple years ago. The Feds wanted to create a "Fusion Center" tying together all the public surveillance cameras with private companies' license plate readers and data-mining. Supposedly, as always, because TERROR!

Leaked internal memos revealed planners never mentioned terrorism, or even crime. Just "protesters" and "labor strikers". Dystopian, much? 

We beat it down and they retreated.

A funny thing is, the Fed grants were hyped as making it "free" to our city. However the labor of city police and the like, as well as annual subscriptions and related costs were more than one million dollars per year. So, they're very sneaky about supplying the syringe, the spoon, lighter and tourniquet. And that *delicious* one free taste.

Then once a municipality is hooked is when the lobbyists move in and start gorging at our trough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We **love** it when authors and journalists participate here, FWIW.

Let us know if anyone is trollish, but we're a good crowd. I don't expect it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The state of New York has privately asked surveillance companies to pitch a vast camera system that would scan and identify people who drive in and out of New York City, according to a December memo obtained by Vocative 

This is a highly advanced system theyre asking for, said Clare Garvie, an associate at Georgetown Universitys Center for Privacy and Technology, and who specializes in police use of face recognition technologies. This is going to be terabytes  if not petabytes  of data, and multiple cameras running 24 hours a day. In order to be face recognition compliant they probably have to be pretty high definition.

Click thru for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
