<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5460</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People spitting anywhere or people leaving faucets dripping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For 1. I started doing this for the past few weeks but instead of describing the whole thing, I just speak one sentence and that's it. Maybe I could start adding more sentences and do it more frequently.  
  
For 2, I really enjoy listening to podcast so I think this is easy. I also set my browser's page at work to bbc news so I wont forget listening to it eveytime I work.  
  
Being an introvert and shy, its really hard for me to socialize. When I was little, If I feel like a person doesn't like me or doesn't want to be friends with me, I will stay away from that person immediately. This is my defense mechanism as a child and still using it as an adult. I think this contributed a lot to my lack of social skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined my other coworkers during lunch this past few weeks and try myself to engage in their conversations. Its hard but im getting used to it. 
 
I like your suggestions on keeping a journal. Maybe I could try to write a diary or anything. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a girl so nope..:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yun lang! Pero alam mo ba na nagpadagdag ng puwet si John Estrada? Kaya flaunt it girl! JK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but I am getting anxious when talking to someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a language exchange partner right now. But i feel Iike I always bored him out because Im bad at conversations and can't fully express myself. And also, I am getting anxious everytime I talk to someone, either its online or irl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i enjoy listening to podcast :'(  
  
I guess I have no other options then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think listening to podcast everyday will help me to become spontaneous in english? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is me specially during races or if there's a photographer nearby (need to show my best running form) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] How to become spontaneous in English </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My language exchange partner advised me to work on building my vocabulary and to become spontaneous in english. I was wondering if listening to podcast everyday will help me to achieve this? To be honest Im not a good conversationalist and I am having difficulty in expressing myself even in my native language. I know it is more like a social skill problem rather than language but I still would like to hear your comments on this. TIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napansin ko nung nagstart akong tumakbo at nag-lose ng weight medyo lumiit ang puwet ko. Kapag nagsusuot ako ng pantalon, dati fit pa sya sa bandang puwet ngayon maluwag na :'(. 
Ang masasabi ko lang eh maganda sa girls ang may matambok na puwet kaya dapat ipagmalaki mo yan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of James Reid songs was composed by him. Check out james' latest album Reid Alert.

Edit: Pakinggan mo yung kantang Labing isang numero by thyro, ang ganda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naku ako rin. Minsan inaabot pa ako ng isang oras para lang makapag-isip ng maayos na reply hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nahihirapan ako both writing and speaking. May ginagawa ka to improve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not a job related but Im sure it will affect my work someday.  
I have a language exchange partner who can speak a little tagalog. Im really having difficulties in expressing myself even in my native tongue, maybe because I rarely talk to people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have a speech problem. Sabi nung nakausap ko parang robot daw akong kausap kasi pahinto-hinto yung sinasabi ko. Sabi rin niya kailangan ko i-improve ang vocabulary at maging spontaneous. Minsan nahihirapan din ako magsalita at nagiging hoarse yung boses ko kapag nakikipag-usap. Nahihirapan din ako minsan mag-formulate ng thoughts. Kailangan ko na ba magpatingin sa doctor?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A day where I can sleep all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paggising palang pagod na agad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi beginner here, zero knowledge palang sa japanese. Any tips on learning? Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was it?  
  
I want to be like Elliot someday pero parang malabo hahaha. So ano, may nahack ka na ba? JK. 
Speaking of Elliot, di ko pa napapanood yung season 2 :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright Im sold! I will definitely install this. The reason why I want to try Linux (aside from not needing to install anti-virus) is to force myself to learn something technical hehehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will check out those and see what's good to use. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, Im planning to study the japanese language and would like to try to listen to podcasts as my way of learning. Do you have any recommended podcast that has transcripts in romanji, japanese and english?(if there's something like that exists) TIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yung pang normal na gamitan lang like internet browsing, torrent downloading, movie watching etc. Pero balak ko rin sya gaimitin for software developement balang araw. For now, my goal is to familiarize myself of its usage and functions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im planning to reformat my pc and use Linux as OS. What are the pros and cons? Suggestions on how to make it more user-friendly? Any spefic type/variant of linux should I use? TIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing this! Downloading it right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dapat magkaroon ng The Ultimate Anxiety Challenge tapos isali tayo. Ano kaya magiging itsura natin hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Rush hour. So many armpits, so little deodorants" -Tall Story by Candy Gourlay
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Responsibilities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, I love the smell of kerosene. The smell is addicting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha..anyways I actually want this to be a book but a tv show will do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah..and I was thinking the requirements of the body he needed like the body should be a 13 year old boy (i cant still find a reason why it should be 13). The maturity of the body is 30 years old so he should switch to a different body before it matures. Then the ritual to perform this body-switching should be creepy as hell.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
