<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject405</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed reading your paper and therefore I wanted to share it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bodhidharma the Chan Master of China: Why Bodhidharma was instrumental to large-scale acceptance of Mahayana Buddhism in the Middle Kingdom and the development of a new form of Buddhism. | Chant Cowen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 13:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rousseaus State of Pure Nature | Louis Althusser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 09:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 00:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Epicurus however preceded Socrates and Plato

According to the Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy, [Plato died in 347 B.C.E.](http://plato.stanford.edu/entries/plato/), [Socrates died in 399 B.C.E.](http://plato.stanford.edu/entries/socrates/) and [Epicurus was born in 341 B.C.E.](http://plato.stanford.edu/entries/epicurus/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 17:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An old joke certainly is an indifferent. A newer and less obvious joke, however, would be a preferred indifferent indeed. I personally prefer preferred indifferents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 11:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At the same time, that's taking autonomy away from the person she is right now.

It's not about autonomy, which, by the way, is not taken away from someone at all just because assistance is not offered too easily. Assistance involves other people and therefore it cannot be only about the autonomy of the person being assisted.

That being said, the fact that someone wants to die does not make assistence automatically right. The question in which cases assistence is right is a tremendously difficult one raising many ethical and legal problems. I think, the questions being raised by /u/Liempt are important ones indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 10:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I somehow misread that part, it was a failure on my side. Apart from the imagined inexactness, I found your comment valuable and upvoted it when I read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 09:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although Cato is something like a Stoic role model, he was a politician and military commander, but no philosopher.

Cicero was an ecclectic and highly influenced by Stoicism, but he was no Stoic philosopher. One of his teachers was Philo of Larissa, the head of Platon's Academy, and basically that's the philosophy Cicero subscribed to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dangers of Happiness | Carl Cederstrm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 00:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Franois Morellet, French Abstract Artist, Dies at 90 | Hannah Olivennes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philip Pullman: Why I love comics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Other Peoples Anger  Resources and Reflections from Epictetus | Gregory B. Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 16:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I guess I just expected more *substance*.

I think that discussions within a group just about being against something are less interesting than such within groups about being for something. That's a sufficient reason why I do not participate in any of the atheism subreddits. And although there are good books about atheism and its arguments like *The Miracle of Theism* by John Leslie Mackie, most books being discussed in such subreddits are not what I'd call good literature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stoics argued that Virtue was defined by God.

The Stoic version of god is no theistic one as your description suggests. It is pantheistic and somehow similar (but not equal) to Spinoza's god. The Stoics were materialists and identified god with *logos* being one of the two first principles of the cosmos. For the Stoics *logos* was something like *universal reason* being immanent in nature and we humans share an especially big part of *logos*. Thus, being rational animals is our nature and that's why we shall cultivate wisdom. The other virtues are being derived in a similar manner.

It should be mentioned further, that the word *virtue* is the usual translation of the Greek word *arete*. However, *excellence of character* is a much better translation in the context of Stoicism. We know that technical terms like that are usually explained, but mostly left untranslated in academic literature, because there rarely exists a translation covering the whole semantic range of the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Stoicism we are rational and social animals and therefore friendship is valued rather high, although not so much the superficial one. Read, for example, Seneca's letters to Lucilius:

[III. On True and False Friendship](https://en.wikisource.org/wiki/Moral_letters_to_Lucilius/Letter_3)

[IX. On Philosophy and Friendship](https://en.wikisource.org/wiki/Moral_letters_to_Lucilius/Letter_9)

[XXXV. On the Friendship of Kindred Minds](https://en.wikisource.org/wiki/Moral_letters_to_Lucilius/Letter_35) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 22:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm asserting that people are motivated to seek pleasure and avoid pain and that the happiness promised by Stoicism is simply a higher form of pleasure (negative hedonism).

Stoic methods can be highly efficient for dealing with difficulties and challenges for non-Stoics, too. By applying teachings of Stoicism to one's life with the motivation to seek pleasure, however, one actually leaves Stoicism. That's hedonism and not even far away from Epicureanism indeed, but it certainly isn't what Stoicism is about.

 What motivates people to seek virtue if it is not a form of pleasure?

It's about *eudaimonia*, which is mostly translated as *human flourishing* or *happiness*. This is not a form of *hedone*, pleasure. These are distinct words with distinct meanings and neither of them is a form of the other.

Also don't forget, that these technical terms are mostly left untranslated in academic literature, because there is very rarely a translation covering the whole semantic range of the original. A sloppy usage of words leads to confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My question is whether Stoicism subscribes to the negative hedonism

This is quite trivial: Stoicism does not subscribe to any form of hedonism. According to Stoics, pleasure is a preferred indifferent and as such far from being *the* goal. Being a preferred indifferent, pleasure is allowed as long as it does not interfer with virtue, though, but, as I said, it cannot be the goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Happiness is not a form of pleasure in Stoicism, even though eudaimonia might be defined that way by Epicureans. 

Happiness isn't a form of pleasure in Epicureanism either. Basically, Epicurus uses *hedone* and *ataraxia* virtually synonymously and neither of them is equal to *eudaimonia*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ancient Stoics most probably didn't practice insight meditation as we know it from Buddhism. There were contacts between ancient Greece and India during Alexander the Great's military campaign, but I don't believe the ancient Stoics even knew Buddhist insight meditation nevertheless. We cannot know what they would have thought about it, if they knew it.

That being said, we are no ancient Stoics. There has been so much new philosophic and scientific insight since then, it's like living in a different world (although I don't think that human nature has changed much). What would Epictetus say, if he lived today? Unfortunately, we cannot know for sure. It is our task to bring Stoicism to life again while staying true to Stoic tradition.

According to my opinion, if insight meditation helps you with being virtuous, you may be well adviced to practice it. You may have to find the right balance, though. It certainly should not be a withdrawal from real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Botticelli: Love, Wisdom, Terror | Andrew Butterfield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studying the history of Humanism goes against the founding principles of the Rationalist Association? Really? If this were the case (and I doubt that they are *that* irrational), this would certainly prove their principles wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 10:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this can be quite irritating, but this changes as soon as one knows that the Stoic's god is a pantheistic one. It is similar (although not equal) to Spinoza's god. Stoics believed in providence and this is what Marcus Aurelius refers to in your quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [original passage](https://en.wikisource.org/wiki/The_Thoughts_of_the_Emperor_Marcus_Aurelius_Antoninus/Book_V) including its context is:

 Thou sayest, Men cannot admire the sharpness of thy wits.Be it so: but there are many other things of which thou canst not say, I am not formed from them by nature. Show those qualities then which are altogether in thy power, sincerity, gravity, endurance of labor, aversion to pleasure, contentment with thy portion and with few things, benevolence, frankness, no love of superfluity, **freedom from trifling, magnanimity**. Dost thou not see how many qualities thou art immediately able to exhibit, in which there is no excuse of natural incapacity and unfitness, and yet thou still remainest voluntarily below the mark? or art thou compelled through being defectively furnished by nature to murmur, and to be stingy, and to flatter, and to find fault with thy poor body, and to try to please men, and to make great display, and to be so restless in thy mind? No, by the gods; but thou mightest have been delivered from these things long ago. Only if in truth thou canst be charged with being rather slow and dull of comprehension, thou must exert thyself about this also, not neglecting it nor yet taking pleasure in thy dullness.

There is just a comma missing in your quote and this missing comma changes the meaning of that part tremendously.

Does this answer your question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 22:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I personally disagree on the opinion, that without god there is no meaning and morality.

We know that opinion from theists and I am not convinced by that, either, at least not as long as 'god' is to be understood as usual.

The concept of god of the ancient Stoics, however, is not exactly that of a theistic god. The Stoics were materialists and identified god with *logos* which was one of the two first principles of the cosmos to them. For the Stoics *logos* was something like *universal reason* being immanent in nature and we humans share an especially big part of *logos*.

 I think humens can set their own rules of living a good life.

That's fine, but we are in a forum about Stoicism and therefore we usually discuss and favor the Stoic understanding of a good life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Things a Stoic Must Learn | Chris Fisher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 08:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The German philosopher Bernulf Kanitscheider, who takes a stand for hedonism, critizises Stoicism that it is used to make soldiers being happy to die for their country in wars. There are several articles by representatives of the military writing about the use of Stoicism in military and this article, which is based on a talk, is an example of that. It's also an example of what you wrote and linked to [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4ita7q/why_is_stoicism_so_popular_in_the_us_army/) yourself. I certainly regret that I did not comment on the article and do not share Michael Evan's extreme conservative views, but I think he did not exactly write what you understood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Am I being uncharitable with this reading?

You may not agree with his critique, but Stoicism certainly isn't fully compatible with promiscuity and postmodern arbitrariness indeed. I am going to remain politely silent concerning the rest of your polemics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifty Shades of Grey readers show higher levels of sexism, study finds | Alison Flood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superfluous Torment - It is likely that some troubles will befall us, but it is not a present fact. | Seneca the Younger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 17:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ancient Stoics considered Socrates, Odysseus and Heracles as role models, although the latter two were no real people. I think there is a reason for considering these as role models and therefore studying them certainly makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 07:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tattoos can be quite risky, [as we have seen lately](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4ids3m/i_just_got_a_tattoo_of_what_i_thought_was/).

*Eudaimonia* is the goal in many ancient Greek philosophies, but they differ in how to achieve it. The Stoics thought that virtue (*arete*) was necessary and sufficient for *eudaimonia* and that all externals like health and wealth were indifferents. Aristotle did not agree that virtue was sufficient and considered what the Stoics called preferred indifferents as important for *eudaimonia*. 

It is very often translated as *happiness*, which comes close in a way, but also misses something of the original semantic range. It's difficult and maybe impossible to translate *eudaimonia* preserving its whole semantic range. In Academic literature it is therefore explained, but mostly left untranslated.

I think, [this Wikipedia article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eudaimonia) is quite good and is also linked to in our FAQ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pilgrim Journey | George Jisho Robertson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic Philosophy and the Profession of Arms | Michael Evans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life lessons from ancient Greece: stoicisms revival | Rowland Manthorpe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 17:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree with you, I just want to add that, for example, St. John's Wort ([*Hypericum perforatum*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypericum_perforatum)) was already used by the ancient Greeks for depression or melancholy. The knowledge that one's moods and one's mind can be influenced by taking meds is even older than about 100 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 14:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened again: [I just got a tattoo of what I thought was Epictetus and I discovered was Epicurus](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4ids3m/i_just_got_a_tattoo_of_what_i_thought_was/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Natural justice is a practical agreement not to harm one another nor to be harmed (Principal Doctrines 31) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 11:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 11:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Heracles/Hercules as described in the article (the situation in which he had to decide between virtue and vice) was a famous role model of ancient Stoicism in general and is referred to by most of the ancient Stoics indeed. But it does not stop there. Stoicism had quite a huge impact on philosophy, literature, politics from the Renaissance on and Heracles is being referred to even then a lot, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 10:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoicism is certainly compatible with Humanism and had a huge impact on Humanism in the Renaissance. Studying the history of Stoicism and its influence until today is quite interesting in that regard. When you read the Ancient Stoics' writings, you should know, however, that the Stoics' god is a pantheistic god, since they refer to god quite often. Their god is very similar to Spinoza's god and therefore not really incompatible even with Secular Humanism.

You may also be interested in the article ["Ancient Stoicism And Rational Psychology. Humanistic Ways To Mental Health"](http://americanhumanist.org/humanism/Ancient_Stoicism_and_Rational_Psychology) by Fred Edwords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Zen Buddhist priest who runs a planetarium - Ryo Kasuga teaches the dharma with help from the cosmos | Marie Scarles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 23:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Was David Hume? | Anthony Gottlieb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 22:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Choice of Hercules in Stoicism | Donald Robertson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Renaissance did for us. The meaning of the word humanism has been argued over for years. Lets take inspiration from its rich and varied traditions. | Martin Spence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Love Letter to the Midwest: John McCarthys Ghost County | Heather Cox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Episodes in the Life of Einsteins Mother | Adam Ehrlich Sachs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are doing so many jumps that it feels like nailing a pudding on the wall. I am afraid we have to agree to disagree for now, if possible.

 What are your views on this subject? Epicurean, Buddhist, or Stoic?

After studying these three world views (and Christianity, since I am living where this is the most common religion), I have finally arrived at Stoicism lately. I value Epicurus highly and agree to many of his teachings, but I disagree that pleasure is the highest good. I don't share the rather bad opinion of some Stoics about pleasure, which is a preferred indifferent anyway and as such *per definitionem* not bad (as some seem to think). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I never said money leads to happiness.

[really](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4ht86d/what_is_your_opinion_on_epicureanism/d2tjlmj)?

 I know it's a great paradox, but think about it for a second. Even if you're not actively pursuing happiness, you're still subconsciously doing so. Let's say you work at a tech company. You want to work harder to be promoted? Why? To be promoted. Why? Because..um...more money? **Money will lead to happiness.** Not the kind Epicurus described, but a kind nonetheless.

(The highlighting is mine.)

 The first part is of differing psychological viewpoints, not philosophy.

It isn't about different viewpoints. If someone says something and it turns out badly, just saying *"but we are doing it subconsciously"* is not sufficient for a rational response, especially if the original claim was about doing something actively. Even if the 'subconsciously' part were true indeed, that would still have to be shown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the Greeks actually believed in rebirth though

In this general wording, this is not true. The ancient Greeks called the concept of rebirth/reincarnation *metempsychosis*, which was part of the Orphic religion and Pythagoreanism, for example. Some say that Plato believed in *metempsychosis*, which is disputed, but certainly the cause for overestimating the belief of the ancient Greeks in *metempsychosis*. There may be more religious movements sharing the belief in *metempsychosis*, but it wasn't that wide spread as some people claim.

According to the specialized literature about ancient Greece I have consulted for this reply to be on the safe side, the ancient Greeks of the archaic period basically believed in what we know as Hades (as far as it is possible to say something about their concept of afterlife at all). In later times there were several mystery religions (like the mentioned Orphic religion), but these had no single concept of afterlife in common. And there were Epicureans, Stoics and Skeptics who did not believe in any afterlife at all and certainly not in *metempsychosis*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not living in the USA and don't know enough about the education system of the USA to comment on it. But I want to try to draft some of my thoughts nevertheless, since Massimo writes that many European states follow the trends of the USA and I think he is right about that.

A lot of the responsible people do not only fail to *recognize a basic difference in ability between people* and therefore fail to offer children a sufficient range of educational environments and support according to their needs and abilities. They also seem to confuse the equality of people concerning their worth as human beings (this kind of equality is true) with the individual equality of their abilities (this kind of equality is certainly false). At the end, the individual abilities of children are levelled down to the lowest common denominator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Epicureanism and Buddhism are not mutually exclusive, first of all.

Basically they are. Buddhism and any kind of hedonism are mutually exclusive. But there is no need to follow either 100% of a teaching or 0% indeed like some seem to think here. Even very commited Christians do not follow 100%, although they usually claim (and even think) that they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On education, Stoic and otherwise | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you're still subconsciously doing so.

This is certainly not the case and by the way a really bad argumentation. Claiming that one's assertion which has turned out badly is true nevertheless because it is true subconsciously is an example of bad psychology.

I don't agree that money necessarily leads to happiness, either. Have you ever heard of the so-called hedonic treadmill? Typically, these people are never satisfied, since it is always possible to have even more money. Well, that should be clear to an Epicurean anyway, since Epicurus writes about that quite clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not the place to discuss Buddhism in detail, but I highly recommend articles like ["10 Misconceptions about Buddhism"](http://tricycle.org/magazine/10-misconceptions-about-buddhism/) by two of the most renowned scholars of Buddhism (unfortunately, this highly interesting article is not free any more - there is even one longer article for each of the ten points).

For example:

 Buddhism is nontheistic, it sees God as irrelevant.

Buddhism has been full of gods from the very beginning. Buddha himself is no god, not because god is too high, but because god is too low. Buddha is above all gods and *devatideva*, which is one of Buddha's many titles, literally means 'god above the gods'. Praying to Buddha is an essential part of Buddhist practice in virtually all traditions. The Christian scriptures are not clear about Jesus being god and therefore this was discussed for some centuries, but in Buddha's case this is part of the earliest Buddhist scriptures. Fortunately, this article is still free: [God or Human?](http://tricycle.org/trikedaily/god-or-human/)

There are some similarities compared with the Western imagination of Buddhism, which is quite young (basically, it was invented by Eugne Burnouf in the 19th century). Unfortunately, this has nothing to do with Buddism as it has been practiced by Asian Buddhists for nearly 2500 years and taught by Buddhist scholars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 09:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever investigated Buddhism? (That's only a rhetorical question.)

Buddhism and Epicureanism are nearly opposites of each other. In Buddhism the goal is becoming free from *samsara* and ending the circle of rebirths, in Epicureanism the goal is pleasure within *samsara*. In Buddhism that's not only not the goal, according to Buddhism everything is *dukkha* (suffering, anxiety, stress) and seeking pleasure strictly opposes its goal.

There also aren't just *some metaphysical discrepancies*, these discrepancies are tremendously huge. Buddhist cosmology with all it's realms from hell to the sphere of gods is completely different to Epicureanism. I cannot mention even one similarity and I have studied both world views quite a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 09:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Happiness is the only thing we pursue for its own sake.

This is not only wrong, but pursuing happiness for its own sake is nearly a guarantee not to gain it. That's a well-known and well-researched paradoxon regarding happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 09:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddhism, Epicurism and Stoicism value a tranquil mind highly. That's the biggest similarity between Buddhism and Epicureanism. Apart from that and some similarities which are common among most world views Buddhism and Epicureanism are completely different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 08:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My biggest Problem with Epicurus is his definition of Justice. According to him we are just only because we do not want to get punished.

Epicurus' actual definition of justice is quite different to your's and similar to some common modern definitions: *"Natural justice is a covenant for mutual benefit, to not harm one another or be harmed."* ([Principal Doctrines #31](http://www.monadnock.net/epicurus/principal-doctrines.html)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like Sculpting Smoke - Arundhati Roy on Fame, Writing and India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 00:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bertrand Russell on Epicurus | Stuart Pickering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divine Comedy: Lucian Versus The Gods | Nicholas Jeeves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it pays to work less. Your boss may disagree, but working fewer hours could be better for you and your company. | Callum Williams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lord Byrons Darkest Summer. After an Indonesian volcano erupts, a group of writers meet in Switzerland to turn darkness into art. | Nina Martyris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 18:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The premise that pleasure is a good produces unacceptable philosophical consequences.

What exactly are the unacceptable philosophical consequences and how do you define 'pleasure'?

According to Epicurus, the highest pleasure is the absence of pain/distress and this is impossible without virtue. Epicureanism is about as far away from the common understanding of hedonism as Stoicism. I don't regard pleasure as the highest good, though.

 Gandhi: I like your Epicurus very much. Your Epicureans, not so much.

Epicurus is misunderstood quite often, especially his understanding of *hedone*. I am not even sure that people calling themselves Epicureans typically agree with Epicurus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, for example, [here](http://expandedconsciousness.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/feature_image_template67-620x400.jpg) and [here](http://www.zen-mama.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/ZTipsLaoTzuLet-of-what-I-am2.jpg): these links show images of Buddha with quotes attributed to Lao Tzu neither of them ever said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you are right indeed! How could I miss that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even think it is an exact Epictetus quote, at least it seems to be tremendously simplified. Well, I was not sure what you really meant, but you are right that the picture shows Epicurus. These images are not being created by people being familiar with philosophy. I suppose these people just take a template and put a wise sounding saying on it. Ignoring this kind of pictures is the best thing to do.

By the way, even Gregory Sadler uses the wrong picture in [this article](http://gbsadler.blogspot.co.at/2011/02/epictetus-on-anger-part-1-of-2.html).

As far as I know, there does not even exist a statue of Epictetus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting to read about different kinds of riding and their cultural context for someone like me who does not know much about riding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Triumph of Piero | Willibald Sauerlnder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 20:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bosch Mania | Morgan Meis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 20:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's completely out of my control that people mix up Epicurus and Epictetus, thus I am totally indifferent about your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens quite often that people mix up Epictetes and Epicurus. Unfortunately, you are one of them. This is a quotation of Epictetes who was a Stoic. It may not be a precise quotation, but the [Dichotomy of Control](http://www.traditionalstoicism.com/2016/04/19/dichotomy-of-control/) is one of the most famous Stoic principles of Epictetes, who was one of the most famous Stoics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For instance, I see someone else who sees the goal of Stoicism as attaining tranquility.

According to my understanding, *tranquility* is a common translation of *ataraxia* and highly valuable. It's more a consequence of pursuing virtue than an end to be pursued, though.

 But isn't the goal, as in the thought that the Stoic strives to pursue, actually eudaemonia?

Basically, no translation of *eudaimonia* satisfies the whole range of its meanings and therefore *eudaimonia* is often left untranslated, but it is also an emotional state. You are certainly right that *eudaimonia* is the goal.

 To me seeking out an internal emotional state is a kind of hedonism.

I think that equating seeking out an emotional state with hedonism is wrong. While seeking out specific emotional states may be part of hedonism indeed, it is essential which emotional states are to be seeked out and seeking out emotional states is far from sufficient for hedonism anyway.

 But the same page also sees kindness and equality as subvirtues of justice, which doesn't make sense to me.

Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Search for the Soul of the Mainland - The Big Red Book of Modern Chinese Literature | Yunte Huang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 07:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zeki Basan: I am 16 and live alone in the wilderness. I have an open fire and spend my evenings tanning animal and fish skins, and carving wood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Different Guernica | John Richardson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Degas Invents a New World | Anka Muhlstein </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gifford Lecture Book: 'Emotion and Peace of Mind' by Richard Sorabji </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 00:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may mean the following [passage of Seneca's *On the Shortness of Life*](http://www.forumromanum.org/literature/seneca_younger/brev_e.html#9):

 Can anything be sillier than the point of view of certain peopleI mean those who boast of their foresight? They keep themselves very busily engaged in order that they may be able to live better; they spend life in making ready to live! They form their purposes with a view to the distant future; yet postponement is the greatest waste of life; it deprives them of each day as it comes, it snatches from them the present by promising something hereafter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confessions of a Former Fundamentalist: Confirmation Bias | Eric Simpson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 07:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tales of the Unexpected: saying yes to today's composers | Stephen Newbould </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 23:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A person who does something in secret against what has been mutually agreed upon as to not harming or being harmed cannot be sure of escaping notice, even after escaping notice for the present ten thousand times; until death it will be unclear whether escape is possible (Principal Doctrines 35) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 16:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you reread what I've written before claiming that I have not understood Epictetes. And I won't answer any monologues which completely ignore all arguments anyway. That's wasted time which can be spent better.

Hint: *having an influence on something* is not the same as *having something under full control* and saying that the *preparation is under one's control* is not the same as saying *the results of an exam are under one's control*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Musonius Rufus Diet | Kevin Vost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 16:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The outcome of an exam is an external and is not under our control.

It is *not completely* under our control, because there are things influencing the result which we certainly cannot control. But how good we prepare ourselves for exams is under our control. A better preparation usually leads to better results (although not necessarily).

 the result of the exam is based on chance [...]

That's a typical lame excuse of lazy students. There is no doubt that also chance influences the result of an exam, but that does not mean that it is exclusively based on chance. The dichotomy of control is not meant as excuse for being lazy.

 [...] whether we got good sleep the night before, whether we chose to study the things which end up being on the exam, whether our brains are able to recall the correct information correctly, etc.

Although there is some chance involved, it's not completely so. We can go to bed early enough and drink less coffee or do some sports the day before the exam, we can inform ourselves about the kind of things which have been asked in the past, recalling the learned information can be trained...

By the way, the best possible preparation and indifference towards the results of exams together can have very positive effects on all points you attribute to chance and usually contribute to better results, too.

 Those things which are up to us are fully under our control (our thoughts, choices, etc.) Everything else is not up to us, not within our control, and subject to hindrance from outside forces.

Things not being fully under our control aren't necessarily completely outside our control. There is not just black and white, there are also many shades of grey. Things being fully under our control is the exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 00:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting combination: a skeleton and a cheerful advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 00:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both Hellenistic philosophies and share a lot indeed. I enjoy reading both, too, and have been doing that for a while now. However, my interests have been leaning towards literature about Stoicism and works by ancient Stoics more and more lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exams differ from rainy days. The latter are not under our control, while we can influence the outcome of an exam by preparing ourselves for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the Stoic and the Epicurean Cohabit? | George P. Simmonds (X-post /r/Stoicism) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the Stoic and the Epicurean Cohabit? | George P. Simmonds (X-post /r/Epicureanism) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off the Beat and Into a Museum: Art Helps Police Officers Learn to Look | Sarah Lyall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 23:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original article:

[**What Predicts Childrens Fixed and Growth Intelligence Mind-Sets? Not Their Parents Views of Intelligence but Their Parents Views of Failure**](http://pss.sagepub.com/content/early/2016/04/23/0956797616639727)

by Kyla Haimovitz and Carol S. Dweck, Department of Psychology, Stanford University

 **Abstract**

 Childrens *intelligence mind-sets* (i.e., their beliefs about whether intelligence is fixed or malleable) robustly influence their motivation and learning. Yet, surprisingly, research has not linked parents intelligence mind-sets to their childrens. We tested the hypothesis that a different belief of parentstheir *failure mind-sets*may be more visible to children and therefore more prominent in shaping their beliefs. In Study 1, we found that parents can view failure as debilitating or enhancing, and that these failure mind-sets predict parenting practices and, in turn, childrens intelligence mind-sets. Study 2 probed more deeply into how parents display failure mind-sets. In Study 3a, we found that children can indeed accurately perceive their parents failure mind-sets but not their parents intelligence mind-sets. Study 3b showed that childrens perceptions of their parents failure mind-sets also predicted their own intelligence mind-sets. Finally, Study 4 showed a causal effect of parents failure mind-sets on their responses to their childrens hypothetical failure. Overall, parents who see failure as debilitating focus on their childrens performance and ability rather than on their childrens learning, and their children, in turn, tend to believe that intelligence is fixed rather than malleable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents' responses to failure and not their beliefs about intelligence guide how their children think about their own intelligence, according to new research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 23:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly one of the main reasons why I don't watch this video and earlier ones of the same user. The video may even be fine (although I personally prefer other types of videos), but the way it is promoted is way too similar to spamming. If the thread opener is serious, he may be well-advised to rethink his strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic theology | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fu Hou, a revered Buddhist monk in China, has been mummified and covered in gold leaf, a practice reserved for holy men in some areas with strong Buddhist traditions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But part of Stoicism is not worrying, fearing, avoiding the difficult.

I agree to your comment, but want to mention that Stoics do have feelings like fear or worry, Stoics are no statues after all, but we differ in how we deal with them. For example, we transform *fear* into *caution* and *pleasure* into *joy* to name two examples.

 While you worry about being too young, I'm sure there are 30,40,50,60,70,80, 90, 100 year olds worrying about being too old.

Some days ago I cited Marcus Aurelius at /r/Epicureanism, so let me cite Epicurus here (from the [Letter to Menoeceus](http://www.epicurus.net/en/menoeceus.html)):

 Let no one be slow to seek wisdom when he is young nor weary in the search of it when he has grown old. For no age is too early or too late for the health of the soul. And to say that the season for studying philosophy has not yet come, or that it is past and gone, is like saying that the season for happiness is not yet or that it is now no more. Therefore, both old and young alike ought to seek wisdom, the former in order that, as age comes over him, he may be young in good things because of the grace of what has been, and the latter in order that, while he is young, he may at the same time be old, because he has no fear of the things which are to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Health is an example of what Stoics call a preferred indifferent and Stoics certainly prefer being treated by a physician, if necessary, as long as there is no strong reason against it. Also don't forget that Marcus Aurelius' personal physician was the most famous physician of ancient Rome, Galen, whom Marcus Aurelius sent out at the outbreak of the so-called [Antonine Plague](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antonine_Plague). I am quite sure that Marcus Aurelius doesn't want to say that diseases should not be treated, although the text is not unambiguous in this respect.

I think that Marcus Aurelius basically wants to say that we should not allow sickness to prevent us from doing what we are supposed to do. In other words, sickness should not hinder us from staying true to our philosophy. The higher goods of Stoicism and Epicureism differ from each other, but Stoicism and Epicureism agree about the importance of living philosophically even under difficult circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 12:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be great, if this excellent advice were part of our FAQ or wiki? I think this should be made aware of more widely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 07:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very good point indeed and I agree that this understanding of duty certainly isn't healthy for younger people, but I don't think it's healthy for older people either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Some of the messages from Stoicism would have been bad for me overall.

What specifically do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophers at the Festival of Life | Chris Fisher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some years ago the author offered the PDF at his home page for free. You may still find it with Google. It is also available at Scribd ([A Guide to Stoic Living - Keith Seddon](https://www.scribd.com/doc/77465459/A-Guide-to-Stoic-Living-Keith-Seddon)), but you have to be (or become) a member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Necessity is bad, but there is no necessity to live with necessity (Vatican Sayings 9) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 14:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 February 1908: On his first visit to London, The Observer reviews Claude Debussy conducting his works at the Queens Hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 09:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 08:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Epictetus was still a slave, [his master broke his leg](http://www.iep.utm.edu/epictetu/):

 There is a story told by the author Celsus (probably a younger contemporary of Epictetus)  quoted by the early Christian Origen (c.185254) at Contra Celsum 7.53  that when still a slave, Epictetus was tortured by his master who twisted his leg. Enduring the pain with complete composure, Epictetus warned Epaphroditus that his leg would break, and when it did break, he said, 'There, did I not tell you that it would break?' And from that time Epictetus was lame.

And I agree with /u/EsquilaxHortensis that this comic is unfair. The Discourses, the lecture notes written by one of his student, give a completely different picture of his lectures. I'd enjoy attending Epictetus' lectures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 08:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right: it's #35. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are we so bored? We live in a world of constant entertainment  but is too much stimulation boring? | Sandi Mann </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 15:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This immediately makes sense and should be made aware of more widely indeed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 10:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He was a philosopher, which apparently gave him license to be the master of any subject.

I appreciate and agree to your excellent comment, but I think that calling Steiner a philosopher gives him way too much respect. He wrote a dissertation about Fichte's concept of the ego, for which he received a doctorate in philosophy at the University of Rostock, but did not contribute anything significant to philosophy otherwise. His dissertation, of which I read about a third, is something like a philosophical basis for his esoteric construct, the anthroposophy, and I doubt that it is ineresting in any other respect than for a better understanding of anthroposophy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 00:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [**Abstract**](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0153857)

 Despite international advancements in gender equality across a variety of societal domains, the underrepresentation of girls and women in Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (STEM) related fields persists. In this study, we explored the possibility that the sex difference in mathematics anxiety contributes to this disparity. More specifically, we tested a number of predictions from the prominent gender stratification model, which is the leading psychological theory of cross-national patterns of sex differences in mathematics anxiety and performance. To this end, we analyzed data from 761,655 15-year old students across 68 nations who participated in the Programme for International Student Assessment (PISA). Most importantly and contra predictions, we showed that economically developed and more gender equal countries have a lower overall level of mathematics anxiety, and yet a larger national sex difference in mathematics anxiety relative to less developed countries. Further, although relatively more mothers work in STEM fields in more developed countries, these parents valued, on average, mathematical competence more in their sons than their daughters. The proportion of mothers working in STEM was unrelated to sex differences in mathematics anxiety or performance. We propose that the gender stratification model fails to account for these national patterns and that an alternative model is needed. In the discussion, we suggest how an interaction between socio-cultural values and sex-specific psychological traits can better explain these patterns. We also discuss implications for policies aiming to increase girls STEM participation.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries with Higher Levels of Gender Equality Show Larger National Sex Differences in Mathematics Anxiety and Relatively Lower Parental Mathematics Valuation for Girls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 00:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I just fear that not providing any response will get OP more seriously injured at some point.

Stoics are no punchballs and certainly act against being confused with one as far as it is within their control. Fighting back in the same way, however, is not the Stoic type of response. Don't misunderstand that as not providing any response at all. The response just should be one of a rational being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 11:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The working link of this submission is [this one](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Humanism_and_Its_Aspirations).

However, you may have better linked to the [Humanist Manifesto III](http://americanhumanist.org/Humanism/Humanist_Manifesto_III) directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negative visualization is not about making you feel bad, but about preparing yourself for future troubles and about being more appreciative of the present situation. So don't simply visualize something negative, but also how to deal with it when it happens and how valuable your present moment is considering the impermanence of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 23:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great, many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the best (and cheapest) way to take a trip to space? | Richard Hollingham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 00:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Chernobyl exclusion zone is arguably a nature reserve | Colin Barras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 00:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original article (unfortunately behind a paywall):

[**The relationship between transformational leadership and follower sickness absence: the role of presenteeism**](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/02678373.2016.1170736)

by Karina Nielsen, Kevin Daniels

 **Abstract**

 The impact of transformational leaders on employee health and well-being has received much attention. Less research has focused on the relationships between transformational leaders and followers sickness absenteeism. Transformational leaders promote a group climate that may lead to absenteeism, especially among vulnerable employees (those with high levels of presenteeism). In the present study we examined the relationships between presenteeism, group-level transformational leadership and sickness absence rates in a three-year longitudinal study of postal workers and their leaders in Denmark (N=155). Group-level transformational leadership in year 1 predicted sickness absenteeism in year 2, but not in year 3. In examining conditions under which transformational leadership may be linked to higher levels of sickness absenteeism, we found that presenteeism in year 1 moderated the link between transformational leadership in year 1 and sickness absenteeism in year 3, such that followers working in groups with a transformational leader and who were high in presenteeism reported higher levels of sickness absenteeism. Our results suggest a complex picture of the relationship between transformational leadership and sickness absenteeism; transformational leaders may promote self-sacrifice of vulnerable followers by leading them to go to work while ill, leading to increased risks of sickness absence in the long term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The relationship between transformational leadership and follower sickness absence: the role of presenteeism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Hume, the Skeptical Stoic | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no need to like something a book is about in order to read it with interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This blog post may be of interest: [Why calling Seneca a hypocrite isnt very helpful](https://lizgloyn.wordpress.com/2015/03/16/why-calling-seneca-a-hypocrite-isnt-very-helpful/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original study:

[**Wrong place to get help: A field experiment on luxury stores and helping behavior**](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/15534510.2016.1160839)

by Lubomir Lamy, Nicolas Guguen, Jacques Fischer-Lokou   Jrme Guegan

 **Abstract**

 Three experiments were conducted in field settings. It was hypothesized that luxury stores may act as environmental reminders of materialism and that helpfulness would vary according to the presence or absence of such cues. Study 1 (N = 80) indicated that consumers coming out of famous brand stores displayed less helpfulness, as compared to mere passersby. Study 2 (N = 112) showed passersby were less helpful near a luxury brand store than in an ordinary street with no shops. In Study 3 (N = 360), passersby were less helpful when walking down a street lined with highly exclusive stores, as compared to streets with ordinary stores or no stores. Results, limitations, and directions for future research are discussed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are less likely to come to your aid near a luxury store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camera Geekery: Custom Cameras by Dora Goodman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peace and Safety For Your Twentieth of April  On Ever-Changing Desires | Cassius Amicus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The It Worked for Me Gambit | Steven Novella </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 22:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's by far my most favorite radio channel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were certain agreements, but Stoics and Epicureans still saw themselves as opposing schools and certainly not without good reasons. At least the later Stoics Seneca, Epictetus and Marcus Aurelius discussed Epicureanism quite soberly, though. Marcus Aurelius even [established four Chairs of Philosophy in Athens, one for each of the principal philosophical traditions (Platonic, Aristotelian, Stoic, and Epicurean)](http://www.iep.utm.edu/marcus/). That is, one of the best known and certainly mightiest Stoics helped the Epicureans.

I want to finish my comment with a quote from Marcus Aurelius ([Meditations, Book IX](http://classics.mit.edu/Antoninus/meditations.9.nine.html)):

 Epicurus says, In my sickness my conversation was not about my bodily sufferings, nor, says he, did I talk on such subjects to those who visited me; but I continued to discourse on the nature of things as before, keeping to this main point, how the mind, while participating in such movements as go on in the poor flesh, shall be free from perturbations and maintain its proper good. Nor did I, he says, give the physicians an opportunity of putting on solemn looks, as if they were doing something great, but my life went on well and happily. Do, then, the same that he did both in sickness, if thou art sick, and in any other circumstances; for never to desert philosophy in any events that may befall us, nor to hold trifling talk either with an ignorant man or with one unacquainted with nature, is a principle of all schools of philosophy; but to be intent only on that which thou art now doing and on the instrument by which thou doest it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 18:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is born and lives in a country where a huge part of classical music is from, I may have experienced that to a much lesser degree than people somewhere else. But this might not even be the case, if I were born about twenty years later. Today many people living in the country where Mozart is from don't know more composers than Mozart, Beethoven and Johann Strau, according to a recent poll.

That being said, as a listener to classical music I have always belonged to a very small minority and I have also been looked at funny for hearing classical music *exclusively*. Today I prefer to say that I *primarily* listen to classical music (which is not completely false anyway). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemony Snicket: the trouble with being interested in classical music is that people look at you funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 07:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dichotomy of Control | Chris Fisher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 07:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Taught Myself to Procrastinate | Adam Grant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pragmatic mind-body dualism | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 13:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Michael Hurley: how the north made The Loney a gothic horror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 12:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preferred Indifferents and Stoic Ethical Theory | Georg Schauer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anarchy and the Sacrifice of Polyxena (Euripides Hecuba, 604-608) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 20:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done. Many thanks for your note! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Invisible Shakespeare | Matthew Ritger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 20:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 16:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the article has been deleted, I could read it some hours ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is Ancient Philosophy Still Relevant? | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 12:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 13:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antoninus Pius does not belong to the classics paragons of Stoicism indeed, but it is also said that he naturally matched the ideal which Marcus Aurelius was aiming for according to his Meditations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 13:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We're not going to be Socrates.

We're not going to be Socrates indeed, but taking Socrates as role model helps nevertheless when we reflect on our thoughts and actions during the passing day or on our duties during the coming day. One needs a normative ideal for measuring our progress and for Stoics that's the Stoic sage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick Guide: Applying Stoic Ethics in Modern Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maria Callas sings "Si, mi chiamano Mim" from Giacomo Puccini's opera La Bohme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 23:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 20:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siddhartha is no philosophy book. Siddhartha is a novel. Sometimes a novel is just a novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be interested in this paper:

[B. Alan Wallace - A Buddhist View of Free Will. Beyond Determinism and Indeterminism](http://www.alanwallace.org/buddhistviewoffreewill.pdf)

 **Abstract:** While the question of free will does not figure as prominently in Buddhist writings as it does in western theology, philosophy, and psychology, it is a topic that was addressed in the earliest Buddhist writings. According to these accounts, for pragmatic and ethical reasons, the Buddha rejected both determinism and indeterminism as understood at that time. Rather than asking the metaphysical question of whether already humans have free will, Buddhist tradition takes a more pragmatic approach, exploring ways in which we can acquire greater freedom to make wise choices that are truly conducive to our own and others genuine well-being. One key to achieving such freedom is the cultivation of attentional skills so that one can deliberately focus ones attention with continuity and clarity on ones chosen object. A second theme is the cultivation of insight into the manner in which our own attitudes shape experience, allowing for the possibility of altering not only the way we experience events in the present, but also how we are influenced by our memories of the past. Finally, the Great Perfection school of Tibetan Buddhism emphasizes the realization of the deepest dimension of consciousness  pristine awareness  which transcends the nexus of causality. This is regarded as the ultimate source of freedom and the ultimate nature of human identity.

The [**Journal of Buddhist Ethics**](http://blogs.dickinson.edu/buddhistethics/) has published a four-article series about Buddhism and free will:

1. [Riccardo Repetti - Earlier Buddhist Theories of Free Will: Compatibilism](http://blogs.dickinson.edu/buddhistethics/files/2010/12/Repetti-Earlier-Buddhist-Theories1.pdf)

2. [Riccardo Repetti - Buddhist Reductionism and Free Will: Paleo-compatibilism](http://blogs.dickinson.edu/buddhistethics/files/2012/04/Repetti-Buddhist-Reductionism-and-Free-Will-final1.pdf)

3. [Riccardo Repetti - Buddhist Hard Determinism: No Self, No Free Will, No Responsibility](http://blogs.dickinson.edu/buddhistethics/files/2012/04/Repetti-hard-determinism-for-publication1.pdf)

4. [Riccardo Repetti - Recent Buddhist Theories of Free Will: Compatibilism, Incompatibilism, and Beyond](http://blogs.dickinson.edu/buddhistethics/files/2014/01/Repetti-Recent-Final2.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 00:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard F. Gombrich  - Theravada Buddhism: A Social History from Ancient Benares to Modern Colombo

Richard F. Gombrich  - What the Buddha Thought

Walpola Rahula - What the Buddha Taught </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 11:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> twice =/= a lot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epictetus Prescription for Psychological Resilience | Chris Fisher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 21:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with Nicolas Bommarito on buddhist ethics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 21:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 23:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed reading the article. It's funny to say that 'zombies' is what I am used to call people who are running around with their smart phones in their hands without noticing much of their surroundings. These people seem to be everywhere, which I think is rather queer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All friendship is a good thing in itself, but it has its origin in utility (Vatican Sayings 23) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 13:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophies of the East and Philosophies of the West: Chinese philosophy as a genuine philosophical system of thought | Chant Cowen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 08:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucretius, face to face | Llewelyn Morgan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 00:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ven. Bhikkhu Bodhi: All Lives Do Matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 16:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tibetan Buddhist Nuns in the Himalayas (photographed by Olivier Adam) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 08:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Shakespeare Lives Now | Stephen Greenblatt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 23:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The story of Pseudo-Seneca | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Message of the Epicureans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](http://www.philosophyoflife.org/jpl201505.pdf)

 Humans strive for some kind of happiness in a world that is not conducive to it. As each human life is a collection of random thoughts, choices, experiences, memories, and their interpretations, a permanent state of vague happiness does not exist, since everything is temporary. The pursuit of happiness, or the pursuit of anything in life, does not lead to a permanent state or thing. One can only experience moments of contentment in life. Some measure of temporary sense of perceived happiness is achieved not by pursuing it but by recognizing meaningful moments that could be missed during the pursuit itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life and the Pursuit of Happiness | Ben G. Yacobi [PDF, 9 pages] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maria Callas sings "Vissi d'arte" from Puccini's Tosca (New York 25/11/1956) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 20:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine too.

Renata Tebaldi was the second most famous soprano of that time and it's interesting to hear [her version](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1woH96ROG-c) for comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maria Callas sings "Un bel d vedremo" from Puccini's opera Madama Butterfly (1954) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 19:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We must not spoil things we have by wanting things we do not have, but realize that among things we wished for are things we have now (Vatican Sayings 35) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 13:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 13:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to leave, so I have to make it short: there is even a whole book about anger by Seneca (*On Anger*). Basically, anger belongs to the unhealthy feelings. Stoics are no statues after all and also have unhealthy feelings, but Stoics try to transorm them into something positive (for example, anxiety can be transformed into caution). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 13:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks for your comment which I appreciate very much, especially your concluding sentence:

 I've never seen anything good come of anger unless it's channeled into art or a creative endeavor.

I completely agree to that.

(edit: typo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic Philosophy and Anger | Gregory B. Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 11:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jonardon Ganeri, Why philosophy must go global </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 21:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have a look at the earlier thread: [Is the New Stoa website still active?](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4bi960/is_the_new_stoa_website_still_active/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](https://digilib.phil.muni.cz/bitstream/handle/11222.digilib/115762/1_GraecoLatinaBrunensia_16-2011-1_3.pdf)

 Article compares some aspects of current interdisciplinary discourse critical of religion with Lucretius poem De rerum natura. In the first part, I try to show how a brief review of modern scientific literature can assist to resolve one of the much discussed problems in Lucretian scholarship, namely the attitude of Lucretius towards traditional Graeco-Roman religion and the question of (in)coherence of his thought. In the second part, I change the perspective in order to show that, in some key aspects, Lucretius can be viewed as the precursor of contemporary critique of religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucretius and the Modern Interdisciplinary Critique of Religion | Juraj Franek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoicism and the Art of Archery | John Sellars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lenny Interview: Isabel Allende. Collier Meyerson talks with the author of "The Japanese Lover" about love and death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mentor Yehudi Menuhin: 'I can still hear his beautiful sound' | Daniel Hope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophy Core Concepts: Socrates as a Stoic Sage | Gregory B. Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 00:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a good book about that: [Warren, James, *Epicurus and Democritean Ethics: An Archaeology of Ataraxia*](https://ndpr.nd.edu/news/23406-epicurus-and-democritean-ethics-an-archaeology-of-ataraxia/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hedonism and Pleasure | Philosophy Tube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](https://www.academia.edu/22420515/The_Affective_Multitude_Towards_a_Transcultural_Meaning_of_Enlightenment)

 This essay proposes to explore a transcultural meaning of Enlightenment through an encounter between Madhyamaka Buddhism and contemporary critiques of Kantianism inspired by Object-Oriented Ontology. The concept of translation-as-Enlightenment in relation to the affective multitude of existence is explained in relation to ideas about causality, compassion, translation, aesthetics, epistemology and politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Affective Multitude: Towards a Transcultural Meaning of Enlightenment | Jon Solomon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Deal with Tragedy - Stoicism | Philosophy Tube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should not approve of those who are quick to enter into friendship, nor of those who are reluctant; but one does need to venture favour for the favour of friendship (Vatican Sayings 28) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The body asks not to be hungry, not to be thirsty, not to be cold; and someone who has these things and expects to have them could compete even with Zeus for happiness (Vatican Sayings 33) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Light, time, legacy: Francis Townes watercolors of Rome (British Museum) | Jenny Uglow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 22:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 22:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Stoic position is quite complicated and much discussed, since they also believe in free will. This is quite surprising, since Stoic cosmology is not only deterministic, but also cyclic and each cycle is completely identical to all other cycles:

 The world-process is circular. God changes the fiery substance of himself first into air, then water, then earth. So the world arises. But it will be ended by a conflagration in which all things will return into the primal fire. Thereafter, at a pre-ordained time, God will again transmute himself into a world. It follows from the law of necessity that the course taken by this second, and every subsequent, world, will be identical in every way with the course taken by the first world. The process goes on for ever, and nothing new ever happens. The history of each successive world is the same as that of all the others down to the minutest details. ([IEP](http://www.iep.utm.edu/stoicism/#H3))

How can free will be compatible with a cosmology like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frederick the Great: A Stoic on the Throne? | Kevin Kennedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tibet: With Scenery And Colors Like These, No Wonder Photographer Jan Reurink Keeps Coming Back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Borges Memorial Library: A Brief Survey of Imaginary Books | Seth Gannon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Limits of Absurdity | Robert Zaretsky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Often Engaged, but Never a Bride: Kassandra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 14:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hate, of course. But do they know that or do they really belive in what they are saying about hating the sin, but loving the sinner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 08:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stoicism and the Art of Happiness

I've read this lately and liked it a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhist rebirth in different planes of existence | British Library </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 23:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicureanism after Epicurus  The influence of Epicurus on Western thought | Robert Hanrott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 22:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historical predictions that technology would bring calamity have largely failed. Joel Mokyr, Chris Vickers and Nicolas Ziebarth place todays angst about technological change in a historical context. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 14:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think I was looking more for an online forum to discuss and learn about Stoicism with other people

I think that /r/Stoicism is a quite fine place. There are also some Facebook groups, which are quite good (or at least were good before I left Facebook), like Donald Robertson's Stoicism group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 07:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This part is certainly a weak part of the article indeed. Izhaarbir Singh has written a [short comment about Epictetus](http://izhaarbir.com/phil/university-of-houston-undergraduate-%E2%80%93-senior/epictetus-reaction/), which he refers to in the article. Stoicism is being misunderstood quite often, in particular the Stoic's understanding of emotions, which on the other hand is quite a complex subject. I also think that Epictetus' handbook is easier to understand after reading Epictetus' lectures. If you don't know the broader context, [texts like the one being quoted by Izhaarbir Singh](http://izhaarbir.com/phil/university-of-houston-undergraduate-%E2%80%93-senior/epictetus-reaction/) may be misunderstood easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicureanism vs. Stoicism | Izhaarbir Singh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 00:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
