<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorgeous. Glad the weather held. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. We've seen them in Cape Breton, and on Flowerpot Island (I'm pretty sure). I mean, it isn't an official "checklist", but you can use it as one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Get Lucky was probably the only "pop" song on that album. A lot of complaints I heaed from the unwashed masses was that it sounded too "disco". Give Life Back to Music, Fragments of Time and Giorgio by Moroder could easily fall in to that classification. Motherboard, Contact, and Doin'it Right are more along their "we're totally freaky future robots" theme.

I agree that they changed on that album quite a bit, and I feel it was because most tracks were half a tribute to their influences. I don't see the pivot.

Strongly disagree with them ever not being world famous. If a 13-year-old kid from Canadian suburbia is playing their album in '97, they've got to be everywhere, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 21:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bruce is gorgeous. Where did you stay? And whereabouts is this picture from? We've done some backcountry up there and it is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 21:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the individual parks have stamp books for kids, and spots throughout to collect the stamps (at least Cape Breton Highlands did). 

The [Share the Chair](http://www.pc.gc.ca/eng/voyage-travel/serapprocher-connect-twitter.aspx) promotion might be something you would be interested in. Not a stamp book, but it is location specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy knows where the drugs are kept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, sure. And it suffers from a lot 90s problems, like fashion stuck with the worst of the 80s/90s combined. And almost as much as DS9, the characters of the future always seem to reference the 20th century to make their point. Kinda broke the fourth wall for me.

That being said, the overall story, the characters, and the universe made me a J. Michael Straczynski fan for life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 06:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had me hoping for a minute there. I stopped halfway through season 2. Terrible villains, cutesy references, every moment Bruce is on screen. It's a horrible show. Why can't it just be Bullock and Gordon getting in over their heads? Why'd they have to start Bruce as a tween? The Batman mythos, especially if you aren't terribly concerned about continuity, has plotlines (good ones!) for a decade's worth of shows. But they seem to want to cram everything in as quickly as possible. They should have gone the X-Files approach: Monster-of-the-week, plus season long plot that actually GOES somewhere. Useless!

/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Algonquin is a ~3 hour drive from Toronto. I always recommend at least one overnight, if you're making the trip up. 

Here's a list of trail [maps](https://www.ontarioparks.com/pdf/maps/algonquin/interpretive_trail_maps.pdf) for you. The provincial park website should have even more info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking into it, and the best legitimate (without stealth camping) way to finish the Bruce seems to be the 'end-to-end' hikes offered through the various chapters of the Conservancy.

I was extra disappointed when calling a campground on their list which told me I wouldn't be allowed to camp there. Turns a 20k hike into 50k and counts me out for that section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked it up and put it down several times, eventually starting from the beginning. Well worth the fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 01:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mill St. used to be one of the only accessible options for craft beer in Toronto. Not so anymore. The Vanilla Porter is great. That and the Tankhouse is basically all I drink from them (mostly when it's on special at a bar). So, so, so many better craft breweries here now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Hell (graphic novel, emphasis on novel) is a chore. Much more in depth than the movie, obviously. I sat down with it last year. Moore paints an excellent picture of the doctor's insanity, and his obsession with the occult but it does drag on.

I don't want to say the movie is dumbed-down. It is certainly more concise. And accessible. And enjoyable. (sorry Alan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 05:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, a lot of people hate directly on Samberg. I think it's one of the best ensemble comedies on right now. The way the characters interact, while fairly predictable, makes for some hilarious moments.  The whole cast just kind of clicks. I can see future seasons getting tedious if they run out of plot ideas, but hopefully they'll go gracefully into syndication.

 Also, to echo sentiments brought up every time this show is discussed, Andre Bragher is the best straight man since Nick Offererman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 05:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect Holt response. "This show is a show that is on television."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Just always seem to pop up.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 08:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We took an architectural river tour in June. Our guide told us he was legally obligated to call it Willis Tower once per tour, but warned us doing so outside the boat would cause us to be shunned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 08:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Churchill last fall (for the polar bears), and found it to be a welcoming community. The train trip up was long, but most people we met, tourist and local alike, were friendly and accommodating. We now try to convince others they should make the trek, although the cost and time investment causes most people to balk at the idea.  All this exposition is to make my questions seem a little less harsh.

It's unfortunate to hear what is happening with the port and the rail line, but I honestly wouldn't know how to go about convincing the general Canadian public that this is a major issue. Until actual threats, not just perceived, threaten our "territorial Northern waters", how can Ottawa justify spending money on what will probably be a money-losing proposition? I am all for helping communities in need, but at this point, how can you revitalize the industry/economy there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 07:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plus my parking tickets, plus 407 fees, and that pesky little emissions asterisk I missed...I don't feel like I've won today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno, station at 407 looks kinda cool so far, and York U, but between Vaughan and Finch stations, they just kinda look like holes in the ground. Still in progress I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just do yourself a big solid and sit down with the entirety of Frisky Dingo. You'll see...his ass is everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They damn well oughta be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classy chirping is so much better. Do the staff at the game still warn/toss people for swearing? I always liked that. Need to get creative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure the labour costs money too, champ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 04:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add a little gravy and baby, you've got a poutine going...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I mean, come on!

Like the guy in the five thousand dollar suit has time to care about what's best for everyone. Come on!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 00:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has it been five months already?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 18:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes from an Aussie, it's usually backhanded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 05:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget "for free". How many times do I need to tell the ttc guys "that isn't in our contract"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Eh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bring my own sandwich!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know for next summer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. I guess so! We've got a puffin/whale boat thing going on, and some hiking up the mountain. Then just going to try and find the best value-for-money restos in and around Bar Harbor. Looking forward to the whole thing, touristy or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 04:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't argue, but we started planning for Bar Harbor this weekend in March/April, and Airbnb was getting slim/expensive (for our range). Camping ftw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to stick with Steinbeck, maybe one of his shorter works to ease into *Eden*. Perhaps *The Pearl* or *Cannery Row*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Howey's series was much more original than anything in that genre in a while. The worldbuilding and characters were excellent. I enjoyed Wool quite a bit, Shift a little less. Haven't gotten around to Dust yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But what about blank???" is my constant refrain when watching the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still, STILL, reading **The Wind Up Bird Chronicle - Haruki Murakami**. Enjoying it, but can't seem to finish. And I am still not sure where everything is headed.

Also floating around: **Down and Out in The Magic Kingdom - Cory Doctorow** in the bathroom, and **Armada - Ernest Cline** in the car (when parked). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the act.

I saw Roger Waters at the SkyDome here in Toronto a few years ago, and that show *demanded* a huge venue. Well worth the price, and the kilometre from me to the stage. Same goes for AC/DC when I saw them in the same venue. Do I get excited when a primarily acoustic act, or one without a naturally epic stage show comes into an arena? No. You wind up watching the singer and other band members on a giant screen. Boring, useless. 

For example, I have tickets to a Tragically Hip show in Toronto at the Air Canada Centre, which I think is way outsized for them (this being their potential "last go 'round", my principles take a back seat).

Everyone wants to sell more tickets, but I wish some bands/promoters would understand that there is an ideal setting for their shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks. Posted this yesterday in last week's thread, hopefully visibility is higher.

Has anyone hiked up Cadillac Mountain in Acadia National Park? Girlfriend and I aim to hike up from Blackwoods campground this weekend via the South Ridge Trail. Doesn't seem too intense from my googling, just curious if anyone had any tips, or anything to say about the trail.

Also headed up to Cape Breton in Nova Scotia afterwards. Staying in the national park there, one night near Ingonish and a couple nights near Cheticamp. If anyone has any "must-see" trails, short or long along the Cabot Trail, suggestions are appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut your pirate hooker mouth about Pacific Rim.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a serious note: Is Oscar Isaac in everything now? I mean, he was starting to be everywhere before Episode VII, and now he is everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I like the Oregon Files books even more than I used to like the Dirk Pitt books. The ensemble cast keeps it a little fresher, but they get stale too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are the same. I tend to bring one 'mindless' book (no offense, Mr. Cussler) and one slightly more intense book when travelling. Most recently, I've been pairing a Discworld book (light) with dusty literature classics on my shelf. The Cussler books usually wind up in a second hand store donation bin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whirlwind tour of a small part of Maine this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone. Been looking forward to our brief stay for a while now. Have a few questions, if that's okay. Some state/province/city subs are more receptive than others.

Was just hoping for a little input from those who know best. We would desperately like to avoid tourist trap if possible. We just want to eat seafood and stare at the ocean from the best places possible.

We're driving in from Toronto via Montreal to Bangor to stay overnight. Then off to Acadia National Park for two nights to see puffins, whales, and to climb the local (Cadillac) mountain. On our way out, we're probably heading up highway 1 (do you call it that?) on our way to PEI.

Any suggestions for food, drink, can't-miss scenic places and all of that along our slightly-adjustable path will be welcome and appreciated!

Thanks! Can't wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Mumford on Which that year, iirc. Still a big crowd. Was right when they were blowing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 00:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone. S/O and I are headed to Acadia National Park in Maine next weekend, planning to hike from Blackwoods campground up Cadillac Mountain via the South Ridge Trail. Has anyone done this route before? Will the Park office have maps? I mean, I assume they would, but any experience from you guys would be welcome in the way of hiking time (roundtrip) and what to expect.

Thanks a bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 21:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly who came to mind when I saw this. Bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 20:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly who came to mind when I saw this. Bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 20:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda get it. Especially on big, busy patios (Amersterdam Brewhouse comes to mind). There were a couple dogs on the outside of the patio fence at Eulalie's yesterday, and they were chill and may have been okay in the mix. But for every well-trained dog on a patio, there is the opposite number. Same kind of people who free-range their children at restaurants would ruin dogs on patios immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're just doing a wall or two, don't bother. But if it's something like a whole house, say for a reno, it might work. The real trick is learning how to move the gun so you don't get unwanted buildup. I suppose that falls under "needed skill". I'd also recommend keep a roller handy, and back rolling your work, for a better finish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your doing it right, the paint should soak into the roller fully. The real trick is not over rolling. Use a 13-20mm sleeve for most walls, roll top to bottom and never more than two roller widths. Put it on heavy and backroll for smoothness.

There, now you have all the secrets of twelve years in the industry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not wrong. Get recycled paint from the dump, you're going to have a bad time. On the other hand, $100 a gallon at Benjamin Moore is a waste of your money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 12:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say "Move out of Toronto, you fool. Come to the 'burbs." But the rent I would save will be more than made up for in gas, commute time (re: sanity) and the eventual burial-at-sea for my automobile. Just chipping away at my crushing debt and paying for the privilege of working. I'll start saving for retirement at 40. Maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 18:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only seen the first three episodes, but I think it is pretty great. There are a bunch of jokes that fall flat, but when they connect, it's gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 18:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky you. As a fan since season two, the lengthy wait between seasons is brutal. 

Edit: Just counted. 6 seasons for a total  of 66 episodes since 2004. Filthy Game of Thrones casuals only have to wait 9 months for the next season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what I think I know about the genre, and /u/kilertapir's summary of it, I would say [Kraken](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/6931246-kraken?from_search=true), by China Mieville might interest you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Ontario, we have "the 401", "the 115", "the DVP", etc. Seems totally normal to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you feeling at this exact moment? Oh, sorry, the Germans already have a word for that, snowflake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 23:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'll come right off when we throw it in the lake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 06:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's Barbara. There's no sich name as Brabra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I wouldn't say cut off, exactly. Definitely need to know your points of access outside the Loop. I spent Saturday riding a bike up and down the lakefront trail (Navy Pier - Museum of Science and Industry). The have a lot more greenspace than us along the waterfront. It was nice to see that much shoreline undeveloped. We were joking about all the good spots for condos Chicago was leaving as parkland. IIRC, a later boat tour told us there was only one residential building east of the highway, but that might just be downtown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time at Wrigley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 07:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, coming out tomorrow night for my first Cubs game (in town from Jays territory). Was wondering if there was stuff I shouldn't miss at the field or around. Any mandatory ballparks snacks? Any anything?! Might not be back for a while. Thanks! See you all tonight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 22:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying that people who never buy tickets aren't used to the disappointment. The assume they will be able to get tickets they want for whatever show.

Is the system broken/corrupt/unfair? Certainly. But it has been forever. I welcome any changes that fresh protest brings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even. Many people I know 25-35 are shocked (shocked!) that getting tickets, decent or not, to a popular concert is difficult. I made peace with nosebleeds years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had high hopes. A few laughs here and there, but honestly more eyerolls and sighs. I don't want to see the joke coming a mile off, and then have you beat it like a rented mule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 05:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. You took it for granted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember wanting to go see the Eagles a while back on their fifth or sixth farewell tour. Tickets started at $100+ and went up from there. The band gave some line about how other jobs give you a raise after so many years, why not theirs? My friends and I, in our mid-20's at the time, assumed it was because their fan base (no offense, baby boomers) had more disposable income to toss about. Sucked for us kids looking for cheap seats.

...looking back on this comment, I am not sure where I was going with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 19:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I meant for Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 15:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know this was a thing! I love his shorts. Between this and finding out that Silicon Valley started without me knowing, my dance card is full. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping for some smaller festival type gigs. Easier that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 04:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, I ruined a huge pot of mac n' cheese with [The Hottest F@#%n' Sauce](http://www.hotsauce.com/The-Hottest-Fuckin-Hot-Sauce-p/1172hf.htm). We thought it was just a clever label, but my god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 04:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy the Budweiser Tailgate^tm and Have A Catch^tm with your friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 18:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or remove parking on major streets altogether. Maybe we could make all the new condos going up set aside a certain amount of space for public parking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 18:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all the street parking for cars that slow you down around streetcars. If that lane was constantly empty, problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 15:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First game of the year for me, and this is basically what I'm telling the haters saying Kershaw's gonna murder us. I'll be throwing elbows for today's walk-off HR in left field, see y'all there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the embarrassing angle, living here, travelling to other cities I find more efficient. But I've had many friends come in from areas where busses are as mass transit as it gets, and they're blown away. Matter of perspective, to a point, maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but that's not important right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 03:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least people are paying attention this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 10:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they did compress a lot of cool shit that happened in ancient Rome in a decade into one season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 18:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cristal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 11:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, Algonquin has always seemed daunting to me. Digging into it in more detail now. Holy crap the amount of "backcountry canoe" sites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks interesting! Meets all criteria, too. Could be a good long weekend. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a "beginner" canoe/portage camping trip (South/Central Ontario, southern Michigan or upstate NY) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The s/o and I started backpacking last year. We've got our gear and food prep to a point where we're comfortable for 1-2 nights with what we have on our backs. 

We want to up our game with short canoe trips and/or portaging to our sites, but neither of us have much experience in this area. So maybe shorter trips? Not requiring an expert navigator? I've looked around at some parks, but can't really gauge the "difficulty".

Any suggestions in the aforementioned areas (decent drive from Toronto, basically) would be appreciated! Places where we can rent watercraft, even better!

Super-specific, I know, but we're taking baby steps.

Thanks folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A chokeout *and* a spanking? Where do I sign up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I think a regional transit authority (I have my issues with Metrolinx, but...) is necessary. Eliminate the petty power struggles at the municipal level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad they're doing it this way. Keeps it in the headlines. Doesn't let people forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmm, that's a fresh reference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 18:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this near Cheticamp? We're planning a camping trip around NS this summer and this is basically the exact spot we're hoping for. Would love to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 15:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds cool. Puts me in mind of Bill Bryson's A Short History of Everything, which followed the scientists as well as their ideas. I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 04:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, definitely prefer nonfiction. Any subject really, as long at it doesn't sound like they're just reading a wikipedia article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for new, long-form podcasts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got into the whole podcast game recently, getting a feel for what I like, and what I don't.

Really enjoyed Serial, and also Hardcore history. Both seem to run over multiple episodes. In the case of HH, for hours at a time. I like this format better than shorter standalone episodes, and was wondering if anyone could direct me at something similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's exactly because we're guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 01:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said it. It can be interpreted by some as offensive.

I'm fine with the comment, and the non-apology. However, if he had just said something along the lines of "some people got offended, apologies to them," in addition to what he said today, this would never come up again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 01:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Life's

Don't worry, Reddit isn't the grammar nazi it used to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word you want is "tone-deaf". Rogers sees an active social media outlet. Rogers says "We can social media. But our way is better. Let's change your way to our way." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 11:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have to imagine, if it isn't a joke (in fairly bad taste), probably a promise of freebies? I think the key word in my quoted post is "vote".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 05:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's a whole team of arms

Great, now I have *that* image stuck in my head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant the arm up the puppet's butt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone who missed it:

 I'm going to get in shit for posting, this isn't a joke unfortunately. Shit hit the fan due to a recent news post about a statue. We got slayed. I didn't vote for the fucking babysitter. I'll post my take on the whole events in the next few days, taking a break from the drama.

/u/CanaDan in the [locked thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/Torontobluejays/comments/4cnep9/why_is_rogercares_a_mod/d1jszvf)

I'll be interested to hear who the babysitter is, eventually. One post from one user and now all posts are subject to censorship? Frustrating, to say the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 03:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that you, Polish grandmother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 02:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jays coverage through the years:


2013: Baseball is boring, but tickets are cheap

2014: Holy crap, look at those low attendance levels.


2015: Another year of medioc-**TULOWITZKI**... We may never lose again!


2016: Why is Shapiro doing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 02:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you said that other guy told you exactly what you wanted to know? Which one is it, M. Flip-Flop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 02:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a weird feeling at the SkyDome when it's a beautiful day but a chance of rain, so they keep the roof closed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 02:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think we won't! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing there was a Toronto star poll years back where it was voted as best choice to replace O Canada. I think it's a toss up between that and Lightfoot's [Canadian Railroad Trilogy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yzo6Otpgj-E) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
