<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7495</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appears to be big telecom pushing this.

http://www.rawstory.com/2017/03/republicans-are-about-to-let-telecoms-sell-your-internet-browsing-history-for-your-protection/

And here's a list of co sponsors of the bill

https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/blog/2017/03/24-senators-introduced-bill-let-telecoms-sell-private-internet-history/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A list of Senators sponsoring the bill.

https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/blog/2017/03/24-senators-introduced-bill-let-telecoms-sell-private-internet-history/

The telecom industry apparently has a hand in this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Republicans Are Preparing to Kill Internet Privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Republicans Are Planning To Kill Internet Privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill sponsored by Republican Senator Jeff Flake AZ

https://www.opensecrets.org/politicians/contrib.php?cycle=2016 cid=n00009573 type=I newmem=N </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> further or worth 'investigating'. 

So no smoking gun slam dunk evidence yet. Innuendo, inference and subliminal messaging using nefarious sounding open ended phrasing.

I have never seen 'professional' politicians so careful or choosy about their words on all sides. Maybe that's a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet conversations and/or obtained data don't mention Russia. So why is non national security related data being handled by a congressional intelligence committee. 

Keep in mind the New York Times 'wire tapped' story came out January 19, 2017. One week earlier Obama signed off on making NSA more available. So by coincidence the NYT is leaked information regarding information/transcripts from surveillance that the NSA would not have shared 10 days earlier. Just by coincidence.

Jan 19 New York Times says investigation into Trump administration and foreign ties citing 'wiretapped' conversations.

http://www.newsmax.com/Newsfront/Paul-Manafort-intel-investigation-wiretapped/2017/01/19/id/769517/

One week earlier raw NSA data is easier to 'share' with more people per the Obama Administration

https://www.scmagazine.com/nsa-to-share-raw-intercepted-data-with-other-intel-agencies/article/631334/

Just by coincidence that this intelligence committee had access to NSA data that might have included leaked data in which the NYT cites in article released right around Inauguration Day. No timing issues or coincidence here, right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowd Strike, no physical examination or direct extraction of system condition, activity, viruses etc. 

Is Comeny being propped for one specific outcome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was 'the' deal?

 The article says that amount of work performed by Manafort is unclear. Being an unregistered agent or disclosing and/or conflict of interests are big issues. But what was 'the' deal, policy, arrangement etc that affected US policy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes Mr Holder, that man who represents big banking for a living.

http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-holder-mortgage-idUSTRE80J0PH20120120

Covington and Burling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LIBOR, exactly. Banks have been globalized for centuries. They're not going to give up that status too easy and will do just about anything to keep it going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Deep State still wants power and job security silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napolitano is/was a commentator who presented his theory-he is not a reporter. Trump rather than take responsibility for acting on a theory shifted blame making Napolitano the fall guy.

His theory actually has more possibilities than people think since it's known the UK has it's own NSA type program called Karma and was caught spying on world leaders in the past at a G20 Summit. 

https://theintercept.com/2015/09/25/gchq-radio-porn-spies-track-web-users-online-identities/

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/16/gchq-intercepted-communications-g20-summits

Keep in mind many in the EU and anti Brexit in the UK wanted and still want to see Trump fail especially with a contrary stance on immigration   globalization. It's a theory with possibility but needed a little more qualification. 

All that being said when Trump said they were quoting a Fox news analyst that was chicken poop on Trump's part. He threw Napolitano under the bus.

 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

If the community isn't strong enough or large enough to proceed with the event perhaps the event isn't as important as they think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vampire squid to place it tentacles from a different location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shush. Only ex KGB agents are supposed to subvert a foreign nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly a compilation of existing stories, commentary, information etc. A prosecutor might call it a circumstantial case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey confirmed a 'probe' not a finding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'foreign interference' is Clinton and the State Department installing musician Mickey Martelli as president of Haiti.

And yes pay to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically a big 'what if' using a lot of existing information, stories  and/or commentary out there.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Country leaders in this region of the world have realized for decades that terrorism and/or certain sects   factions of the Islamic faith is virulent, savage and brutal in which they must be dealt with in a similar fashion. It's not right but it is a motivation.

Yes their tactics are wrong, illegal etc but their motivations may not be as clear as one thinks. Saddam was an a hole but how many problems did he have with ISIS or other factions of the Islamic faith. His tactics were illegal and unethical but in some respects his motivations are more clear now than in the past. Keep in mind motivation does not make one just or right.

The true nature of the terrorist threat in that area of the world might explain some of their actions and policy although it does NOT justify them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Control the flow of information. It's that simple. The EU might be dying but Europe is alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe 'karma' tells him it might be true.

https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20150927/02130732376/gchqs-karma-police-tracking-profiling-every-web-user-every-website.shtml </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is 'interference'-altering/manipulating votes   tallies? Leaking true or false information about the politicians and parties? Spying on campaigns not governments? Not maintaining a publicly neutral stance and opinion? What is 'interference'? And if so is it actually illegally or a 'practice' used by many countries, parties, politicians, organizations etc.

What is 'interference' and is it something illegal or something we don't like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They skipped something. I know an entire 8 year administration called Obama.

GW is legacy building now because Trump who is in power questioned the Iraq War and 9/11. He is trying to accumulate 'not me' points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think since Jones and Trump did things like question 9-11 and the Iraq War I can see why the Bush administration kept taps on them.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30% penalty or higher premiums for one year after not having insurance for a few months. It's a gift to the insurance companies.

The problem with the ACA and Ryan Care is that they are insurance bills, not care bills/legislation. They both look for money to throw at a health care system with exorbitant costs. Until the COST of actual CARE issues are addressed they could impose a 100% penalty and costs still wont' be under control.

In the meantime one is still forced to chose between rent, utilities, car etc which one needs to exist on a daily basis in the here and now or a medical event that might occur in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the student-ATHLETES who want to be exploited/noticed by the NBA? 

There's a reason people talk numbers ie scores, statistics and not letter grades on a report card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who relies on the government providing or subsidizing their personal health care or any other service is dependent on the government for that service. 

The 'independence' would come regardless of who provided or funded the service. The benefits, needs or desired goals of health care are different than who is funding it. Combining outcomes with one source of funding is dependence on that source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind this also gives the police a dna sample.

 Coincidentally San Diego is already being sued for their 'Stop and Spit' policy of getting young minorities to give them a dna sample/swab with no crime involved.

http://www.vocativ.com/403313/stop-and-spit-lawsuit/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Diego police go after drugged drivers with new mouth swab test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about what this includes. Swabs, saliva and coincidentally a dna sample. What becomes of that dna/saliva? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Diego Debuts Mouth Swabs To Detect Drivers High On Pot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amid probe, Pakistan bars German CEO of national carrier from leaving country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like the UK doesn't have it's own massive data/electronic communications collection programs in which compiled data could be retrieved and/or given away later.

https://theintercept.com/2015/09/25/gchq-radio-porn-spies-track-web-users-online-identities/

Or the UK hasn't spied on foreign politicians before.

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/16/gchq-intercepted-communications-g20-summits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'citations' preferred, desired or required?

http://www.newsmax.com/DeneenBorelli/America-entitlement-society-Obama/2012/10/10/id/459470/

http://www.westernjournalism.com/socialism-destructiveness-dependency/

http://blog.luxurytreatment.com/tag/entitlement-and-drug-addiction/

Just one example of government dependency issues would be the battle over Obama Care v Ryan Care . It is one thing to help those who really really need insurance/CARE but another to try to cover those who could get some kind of care or insurance on their own. There are a lot of  issues with costs and no one answer. Because of Obama Care the health insurance industry has become dependent on government subsidized premiums which just enables their policies and pricing schemes.  The health care industry has also become dependent on third party/insurance based compensation and priced accordingly. Government subsidization has enabled the same environment that needed fixing/change to begin with.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism leads to government subsidized entitlements. Entitlements lead to dependency. Dependency leads to reliance on others.

 The government should be there as a back up or do things individuals can't do completely on their own. The problem is now the government is frequently stepping in before it is needed. People want it but do they really need it in all cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maddow always over builds a story or takes way too long to set it up. She'd be better off covering more topics on a show. It's covered and there for future reference. Time to move along. 

I thought there was hope when she started covering the Boston Marthon  Bombing suspects including the guy who was shot dozens of times by the Feds for pulling a stake knife or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The deep state and/or shadow government wants a mail it in environment along with their job security, power and what ever prestige government work carries these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alleged small government conservatives fighting to keep the government bigger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NSA programs confirm capability and things like the IRS targeting conservative groups confirm motivations and how far not just Obama but staffers   zealots will go.

I don't even know if specific surveillance had to be set up. They could've used the previously obtain/mined data after the fact. Remember Obama ok'd increased distribution of NSA obtained data.  There might not even be paper work/request with the NSA but another agency that the data can be shared with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are actually paying attention now? If so to facts, headlines or sound bytes? To those pesky things called detail or context, nah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I am for disclosure I think federal election reporting requirements with criminal penalties should be enough at the local or federal level. If the candidate has an IRS or tax prosecution they'll be records available.

If candidates are forced to give up things like tax and health records  you don't think they'll require the same of private citizens one day. Or will the best candidate tolerate those requirements.

 People don't pay attention to news spoon fed to them now do they think many will take the time to read and analyze a tax return? Really, the physical tax return is what a decision is based on? How many people have taxes done for them or even know what capital gains or carry forwards are?

This legislation is similar to the populist nature of many candidates today. Sounds good but will the best candidates surface to the top and will it affect voter decisions?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has an hour to fill. But yes agonizingly long set ups. She like several other prime cable pontificators simply spend too much on one subject. Sometimes it's on purpose to drive home a point or ratings. Although subject matter bludgeoned to death on one show tends to chase viewers. Or maybe stories with that much set up are not as big as she thinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK or GCHQ theory has some legs anyway. GCHQ has data mining programs and capabilities just as encompassing as the NSA including KARMA which graps a lot electronic data transmissions.

https://theintercept.com/2015/09/25/gchq-radio-porn-spies-track-web-users-online-identities/

The UK has been caught spying on world leaders in the past as has the US ie Merkel.

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/16/gchq-intercepted-communications-g20-summits 

Maybe no additional or targeted surveillance was needed but rather a 'request' for previously mined or captured data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Was car locked? If this was a residential neighborhood how did one know this was a SS agent? Crime of opportunity?

Sounds like it's being down played with the layers of encryption and self wiping drive.
 
Or part of the resistounce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if Trump or Trump Tower was specifically targeted but there is plenty of mined data and archived communications from these operations that all Obama, a staffer or someone with pull could've requested existing information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK has already been caught spying on some allies at a G20 Summit in 2009

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/16/gchq-intercepted-communications-g20-summits

The UK also has the capability for data mining quite similar to the NSA called KARMA.

https://theintercept.com/2015/09/25/gchq-radio-porn-spies-track-web-users-online-identities/

Went so far as hacking Google and Yahoo accounts for private information

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/uknews/10416175/GCHQ-hacked-Google-to-collect-personal-data.html

And apparently found a way to tap fiber optics.

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/21/gchq-cables-secret-world-communications-nsa

So what would've stopped the Obama administration to ask for existing files/data on Trump and friends rather than initiate and/or target Trump with new surveillance of his communications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump shouldn't take it personal like other world leaders.

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/16/gchq-intercepted-communications-g20-summits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and No. GCHQ Operation and/or Karma sucks in everything it can get so Trump shouldn't take it personal. Just like other world leaders.

https://theintercept.com/2015/09/25/gchq-radio-porn-spies-track-web-users-online-identities/

https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2013/jun/16/gchq-intercepted-communications-g20-summits

One would assume the mined data is eventually available for analysis   distribution of some kind.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HORROR IN PARIS: Unspeakable Murder Takes Place In Broad Daylight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 302 documents from an investigation of the meeting? Time to release them. Election's over and most participants out of power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also note Obama had a 'surprise' visit to Hawaii with in a week of this ruling. 

http://newsenter.org/honolulu/2017/03/15/34646-obama-pays-surprise-visit-to-honolulu.html

Just a coincidence-right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He issued a 43 page ruling less than 2 hours after hearing the request for a restraining order. When were those 43 pages were written again?    

Typing 22 pages an hour is a tall order let alone sometime for legal research and/or citations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same day a shooting at a school in France as well, eh-just a coincidence...

Just a coincidence like last week in Germany where on one day they had a tear gas on a train, a machete attack and an axe attack all with in 24 hours. Eh, just a coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii Judge That Blocked Trumps Travel Ban Wrote 43 Page Decision In 2 Hours  The Alt-Rewrite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bomb parts found at Port Authority Bus Terminal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump saw too many movies. Wiretapping in this day and age is obsolete. Trump Tower probably wasn't 'tapped'. Was Trump or his associates data mined by NSA and/or associated equipment is another story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Than You for your service Mr McCain but it's time to leave RINO land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much new here actually. She normally over uses and exploits facial gestures, tone, cadence and biased set up/background for her "stories" in order to elicit a desired biased response. She frequently lectures to come off as a person in the know and authority. 

Still wondering if showing the physical return and not just information will lead to prosecution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local officials are saying that but there was a letter bomb at the IMF office shortly before and the teens had several guns along with at 2 grenades. They seem to go directly after a headmaster so it could be personal beef. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would've had more credence if he had used the word 'bugged' but wiretapped is an outdated term in the day and age of the internet. Fiber optics or coaxial cable can't be 'tapped' the same way phone lines could be decades ago. Data is encoded and/or multiple frequencies/bands and there is limited technology to actually "tap" a fiber or coaxial phone/data line. One would assume Trump Tower has high speed internet which means very few old fashioned two wire phone lines and phones.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon and other BOCs have been dragging their feet on fiber and/or high speed internet for DECADES. Not even able to honor earlier commitments implied or direct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let get this straight the criminals stole something they couldn't use and blame/kill the victim? WTF. 

Manual Transmission is one of the best anti theft devices out. Even if the criminal thief people can drive one it still would be a tough sell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was she one of the ones that implied Trump may not have paid any tax in decades? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time and last time-lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most inner city utilities especially phone and power use/have an existing system of ducts or electrical conduit to pull cables between streets and manholes. An existing underground infrastructure could be used to get near the property. Instead of pulling a copper wire cable through the conduits they could just pull some fiber optic cables instead. 

The only street digging might be to get from a manhole to the building's phone room. And since many buildings in NYC might have as many utility cables in them as a small neighborhood there might even be a spare conduit or an old cable they could pull out. Or since fiber is thinner they might be able to pull in along side a copper cable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Al Gore-"the guy that invented the internet" want or foresee fiber optic service to every school in America by the end of Clinton's term? Didn't he also want volunteers to help do that-a union company like Verizon must have 'loved' that idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her shtick including excessive facial gestures, use of sarcasm and extremely prefaced 'stories' didn't work this time. For street cred anyway. As noted she is still going to the bank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rachel Maddow and news??? The queen of the facial gesture and one who uses a mile long set up for her 'stories' in order to elicit the desired response? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans to save on health care or INSURANCE by having money left over for rent, mortgage/shelter, food, utilities, transportation to get to work or do things for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama administration spent record $36 million in FOIA legal costs in final year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind the UK has an NSA mass data collection/surveillance program. One is called KARMA

https://theintercept.com/2016/04/20/uk-surveillance-bulk-datasets-gchq/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Helped Obama WIRETAP Trump? Insider Explains FBI, NSA Coup (VIDEO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A prosecutor from Pennsylvania who got their pound of flesh and knew that Penn State and/or football program was an institution and money train for many people? The perp and those covering it up are basically two different sets of people with different interests and priorities. What one says about the other is mostly irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She also said that dealing with the rebels would be no picnic either. Both sides are hardliners.

 In the meantime ISIS is exploiting the situation. If it was straight up civil war without repercussions beyond their borders I'd say let them have at it but their is already third party involvement and the consequences have spilled over beyond their borders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ruined the Republican party in California, had love child and just as many claims/baggage against him wether it be steroids or groping women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama Care is failing because it was an insurance bill, not a care or cost bill. It found/manufactured money to throw at a problem. Third party money helps perpetuate inflation along with creating dependency on it. 

Until the actual way care is delivered and billed for not even Trump Care will work because it's focus is insurance as well.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the house Democrats signed off on the trip. It was deemed a fact finding mission.

She must of done or said something because US Marines were deployed there/near Raqqa last week, a combat unit, not special forces or advisors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing is it THE gene or a combination of other things like environmental exposure, age, toxin etc along with 'that' gene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh, let a porn star write legislation that actually screws the public </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget accident forgiveness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since insurance isn't used for one catastrophic event like it was intended "insurance" the term is meaningless if not exploited. 

A 'wellness plan' should actually be like a service contract for a refrigerator or car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enabled and/or in ahoots with the government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Words have meaning AND purpose. Notice how they use "wellness programs". If one is against the genetic testing they don't care about being well. Just like those who would oppose the Patriotic Act are unpatriotic.

If they had just said something like to be used to determine risk and premiums it would be more palatable. I still would NOT agree but they are very slick and "wellness" will have a positive connotation with many which is exactly what they want-sold  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Next? Mandated removal of body parts that might show a potential for cancer there via gene test? And cancellation of the policy if one refuses?

All to steer or manufacture increased premiums for the insurance companies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screening, storage, informed consent and private medical records are different things. As of that article only 12 states had long term storage.

 The problem in California and probably others is that they  are/were not even telling the parents their rights or offering the sample back. That sample should be considered part of ones' private medical record. That means if law enforcement wants it they get it with a formal search warrant.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Law enforcement already keeping their very own dna data bases.

http://www.chron.com/news/science/article/Police-departments-across-US-amass-their-own-DNA-10976855.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this lead to mandatory procedures or fines for things like a mastectomy if one has the breast cancer gene even though other family members never got it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big government in California has been quietly collecting infant DNA since 1983

http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2015/11/09/dna-data-from-california-newborn-blood-samples-stored-sold-to-3rd-parties/

It can be sold and is available to law enforcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops Face Lawsuit For Stop And Spit, Coercing Kids To Surrender DNA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently in California this is child's play-literally.

California has been 'quietly' collecting newborn infants dna at hospitals since 1983.

https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2015/11/12/california-collects-owns-and-sells-infants-dna-samples/

Police have access and can be sold later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of police departments maintain private DNA databases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Bill Would Extend Taking DNA Samples To Some Misdemeanor Suspects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot of costs are cya and some patients figure they're paying for insurance and they sure as heck will use to it's fullest. And yes everybody wants their piece of the pie that 'insurance' helped bake. 

With any service if you see "Accept Most Insurance" that's a sign the price will be higher than it has to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes dad put himself into a cold war collapse episode that is still shaking itself out. Yet not too much said when NATO and US deploy troops to protect Ukraine over the last few years. Military support isn't a show of support I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partially because the providers know there was third party money to be tapped. Third party money helps creates inflation. Somebody else is paying for it syndrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The concept of insurance was lost long ago and not just by Republicans. 

Insurance was ment to cover a/one catastrophic event at a time. It was not ment to be service or maintenance plan like one buys with a car or washing machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that what insurance, some general knowledge and/or one knowing the providers in the area period is for. With in three miles if not comatose and I can choose between a hospital or 1 of 3 urgent care clinics let alone a gp. Along with numerous specialists in the area. I've gone to specialist right away skipping the ER for a leg injury. Don't need an ER doctor and $5K bill to tell me to see an orthopedist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tear gas attack on packed train Hamburg Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More up front pricing   disclosure are needed on provider services and insurance plans. 

One of things Obama Care did well was classify the plans with metallic labels bronze, silver, gold etc. Every insurance company should have a classification on their plans as to what they include. So if a consumer wants to shop a certain type of plan that fits into a particular category they can do it. Can have as many types or classifications as you want  but there should a standard as to what the coverages and costs are with in a type of plan.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence a bill written by the insurance lobby. Insurance was always the preferred but mandated form of payment. Third party funding leads to inflation. The medical care industry gets third party insurance money and the insurance industry gets employer/corporate money. Somebody else is paying for it, who cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Thomas Massie: GOP Obamacare repeal 'stinking pile of garbage' written by the 'insurance lobby,' and it 'will fail' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill introduced by Virginia Foxx R-NC.

https://www.extremetech.com/extreme/245707-new-gop-bill-lets-companies-force-take-genetic-tests-share-results </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Access to emails and Seth Rich? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspect In House IT Security Probe Also Had Access To DNC Emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who slipped in this particular piece of legislation.

 Hence the secrecy. Or for those old school-smoke filled backroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is smallER government but it is BIG business. There has to be at least one bureaucratic entity in charge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less government with more corporate intrusion instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which in turn are codependent on government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even those so called 'wellness' programs which already have a degree of exemption might not work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if was officially sanctioned or zealous employee did it on their own wink wink.

Also this is not the only time over the last few years that the NYT has edited/altered their stories after the fact.

http://nypost.com/2016/11/15/new-york-times-edits-its-election-apology-letter/

http://www.politico.com/blogs/media/2015/07/new-york-times-alters-clinton-email-story-211176

Same management and editors? Same IT person in charge of the archives?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did an 'edited on' date pop up as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now the DNC views the CIA as a useful tool, not a dangerous one. If they should take Trump out and they get back in office the CIA will be a dangerous tool again, only to be used against those who threaten their tenure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eeeek! When professional establishment politicians attack! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gentrification 101. California will become like NYC west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did say it but the montra and/or rhetoric became 'repeal and replace'. That's all half the public is going to see or hear. They are not going research, verify or pay attention to context or detail. Saying it in public once was bad enough but once it's repeated it was game over for a clean repeal. 

The Republicans who put 'repeal and replace' into their sound bytes boxed themselves in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repealing it is one thing. Replacing is another. The administration will own it. They could've won sticking with repeal only. Instead the pandered for more votes with 'repeal and replace'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The parents will remember that this 'protest' inconvenienced them more than the public will remember or care about this day even a week from now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and establishment Republicans/RINOs want to be loved and re-elected silly. They don't care about realistic and practical solutions or adhering to true conservative ideology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theatrics and chicken poop professional establishment politicians that didn't have the guts to stick with 'repeal' instead kowtowing to potential voters with 'repeal   replace' which sounds great until the practical application phase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a start. Something like clinic style medicine or urgent care facilities are cheaper alternatives to a hospital emergency room. It's about how health CARE is delivered, not how it is paid for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is there is no one answer because of multiple issues including indoctrination that says insurance based compensation is the only way to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bill is exactly that 'a bill'. Is it about affordable health CARE or insurance? 

Obama Care failed because was misused/interpreted as "the" answer to affordable health care but it wound it being about insurance. Since when did 'insurance' become the only way to pay a medical bill. Controlling or subsidizing insurance companies won't control costs. Third party reimbursement creates/festers inflation-someone else is paying for it.

Access to health CARE is about COST, what is the cost of care. Focusing on INSURANCE diverts attention from the cost issues associated with health CARE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just something to keep in mind. Republicans and/or conservatives were the first to propose an individual mandate to buy insurance back in 1989 when the American Heritage Foundation recommended everyone buy insurance. Even the Democrats weren't thrilled at first. In 1993 the idea was modified a little but went away when Hillary Health died.

http://americablog.com/2013/10/original-1989-document-heritage-foundation-created-obamacares-individual-mandate.html

They're recycling some of the same old stuff.

Also they are currently trying to sell the mandate under a false premise comparing it to auto insurance. But it's a false comparison because auto insurance only kicks in after a/one catastrophic event. They don't pay for routine maintenance and/or normal wear   tear repairs/replacements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much focus is on insurance. The problem is cost of care. Insurance is just one way to pay for it. Both patient and provider have become hooked on insurance as the preferred form of compensation. Third party money ie insurance will help create and perpetuate inflation.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
