<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leorio is strong. Leorio's ability warp punch is one of the strongest abilities we've seen thus far. Using sonar he's able to warp blasts of nen, probably not as strong as gings blasts though, into whatever part of someone's body he wants. Leorio probably doesn't have it in him to attack the heart and kill but if leorio can stay away from the Enemy he might as well Win always by just warp blasting certain muscle tendons and the like. He may not the same mastery of nen that gon has but if you look at how long he trained and how long gon trained there's only about a 2-3 month difference when you look at the month of no training gon had. Also leorio was definitely training because he had a fully formed hatsu by election arc, I doubt he could do that unless he was training hard. I would put leorio's mastery of nen at the same level as gon close to the end of greed island. Which isn't crazy good but it's enough to block some attacks and give him the chance to take out muscles using his OP ability. Leorio in my opinion has a better chance of winning a fight than gon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 00:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree his hatsu is overhyped but you cannot deny that it has the possibility  to be OP at times. Also maybe because palm had an amazingly defensive ability. High defense is the counter to his ability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We actually don't know if illumi is stronger than Killua still. Although we can agree illumi must have high aura due to the scene on top of the building and has a couple years more of experience he still has a fairly eh ability of its a 1v1 alone which is what I'm guessing we're talking about. I think illumi is stronger than Killua but at this point in time illumi hasn't actually shown us much at all in terms of real fighting. It wouldn't be right to just blindly believe Killua could not defeat him based solely on powers and tactical prowess. I think Killua is a character like law from one piece in that he has an ability with the possibility of defeating most people but due to him being a novice or having inhibitions the writer can make him lose any time without tarnishing him while also making him win easily if the plot allows it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tokyo ghoul manga is worth reading but I personally wouldn't put it as high as HXH. Although many on this list like Monster i do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit you're right. For some reason I thought she had his limbs. Thanks for correcting me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This all of course my understanding of it so take it with a grain of salt. Basically hisoka has more aura due to his nen strengthening after death. You could say this because he feels he has enough aura to maintain two limbs worth of bungee gum at all times. If he had the same amount of aura as before there would be no reason for him not to let machi sow him up.  I think by giving him more aura it leaves him with much more options with bungee gum but doesn't make him Too powerful. Before he usually made bungee gum with his hands and feet and the most we ever saw him make was a small shield from butler coins. Now he could most likely create nets, large sheilds, armor etc. with his excess bungee gum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 23:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay it wouldn't make sense for silva to stomp chrollo prior if he felt that  Zeno was needed, wanted or even slightly necessary for the kill. Also yes they weren't trying their very hardest ever but they weren't waiting for illumi either. It was a race to kill their target first. Actually I would bet they REALLY wanted to kill chrollo first because I'm guessing the dons paid more than chrollo. If illumi kills the Dons first then no pay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 21:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote
 I see no way of paghan, someone not skilled In battle and with no really fighting hatsus, of defeating this guy before he can create someone to fight for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 23:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I'll admit my reasoning May have been wrong the point still stands that gon normally could not kill pitou with a normal jajaken. Gons kick alone was stronger than a normal jajaken. The jajaken normally would never give pitou the exertion needed to fly even close to that high. If we are to assume that a blast of a lot of pure nen by Netero, although that may even be stretching it, is the same or slightly more damaging than jajaken then pitou would still in the end survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about this being a possible strategy but in the end gon is too weak to kill or hurt pitou. Think about how many gon San punches it took to actually kill pitou. Gon normally is a tenth that strong and can only use 4 jajanken. Killua could hold her off but gon wouldn't be able to finish it. That's the problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 01:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If leorio could warp punch anywhere then he can instantly win. Warp into the body and punch the heart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a temp hunter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is a temp hunter? They've been mentioned ever since the election arc and I still don't know. I must've missed something. How does someone become a temp Hunter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think monster would be the better anime for sure but hunter X Hunter is something enjoyed more. The same can be argued for FMAB. Both monster and FMAB had very little mistakes but neither brought me into their world the way HXH did. It's been 2 years since I watched the HXH anime and even now I can't get over how amazing the nen system is compared to ANY other shounen. HXH is something that just makes you want to experience it forever. The others may have been made "better" but neither had the same affect on me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 21:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really glad that all of you hold it in high regards. I just never understood how the people I've talked about irl had such greviences  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is wrong with the original anime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is strictly talking about the old 1998 anime. No movies. I couldn't give two shits about the movies. My first experience with berserk was the 1998 anime and now a while later I'm reading the manga.  I'm almost to the eclipse in the manga. 

I've heard many people shake their head or kinda look down on me for watching the anime before even knowing about the manga. They say the anime was trash. I absolutely loved the anime. But here's the question.

Can someone give me an in depth reason for why the 1998 anime didn't meet expectations for manga readers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm intp too and leorio is my favorite of the main 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you joking? Leorio uses godly nen for his hatsu warp punch. Leorio is the only man who tonpa can even fathom as a rival. Of course this God has a god hatsu. Warp punch seems to be one of the strongest hatsus to me. It has potential  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 16:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her power is meaningless to him now. That's what this was all about. He doesn't need stitching. He left her as a threat to the rest of the troupe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be wrong but every ability ging has shown to have "copied" was emmitter. That would make me guess he has the most affinity to emmitter abilities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gon has an advantage due to the area and he will plan ahead because he knows he's weaker.
Phinks has much more experience fighting and has more or the same level of nen mastery as gon.
Phinks also has an undeniably stronger hatsu. 

With those I think Phinks would win even if gon has a trap. Phinks is much more experienced than genthru and is less likely to fall into that kind of trap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 07:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he said that because a lot of people think gyro and he just wanted different answers from the usual ones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 22:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winners in my opinion:

Phinks, 
shalnark, 
machi, 
hisoka, 
bisky
, feitan, 
chrollo,
 kurapika, 
morel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like this. A little kid wants a toy. The parent says no. The kid finds one of the toys unpackaged and takes it home without the mom knowing. You shouldn't look good on someone for that. Sure the kid "got it himself" but they shouldn't be looked at as good for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was given the dragons eggs. Was lucky the hatched. She was given daarios group because of her looks. Also Khal: we gonna rape you. Her: I'm queen of dragon. Khal: ok? Her: oh and a widow. Khal: oh my bad ill never lay a finger on you. She looked really damn cool when killing the kahls but she's basically just gotton things through luck and just for wanting them. Also once she gets things she's fucked every one of them up.  She just isn't smart. It all comes back to her luck. She can look cool when she needs to and has other do work for her usually and when she actually has to settle important business herself she's too stubborn to actually compromise while tyrion was able to subside something she could deal with for months in a few days. She's childish and lucky basically. She doesn't deserve anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 19:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't decide between rob stark and daenarys targaryan. Both are pure idiots. I thought rob deserved his fun at the wedding fully and set himself up for failure. Now I'm waiting for daenarys to finally meet some people who actually care about her ideas rather than her titles because that's all she has going for her. Titles and things given to her. Fuck them both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 18:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't my home but once on vacation I forgot to lock my car at night. When I went outside and looked everything was open and laid out everywhere in my car. After scrambling through I saw that nothing was stolen but a thing of pepper spray was left on my seat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of all the zodiacs bobotai was said to be closest to Netero in power. That's why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
