<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 16:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very well done. Don't be ashamed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This giant straw is actually a vertical bladeless wind turbine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 02:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 00:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cabaye is rumoured to be available for about 10 million which would be a really good deal, would strengthen the midfield.  Song will be available for about the same I imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude has completely lost it. Feel sad for NFC fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU to investigate claims McDonald's avoided $1bn in tax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN calls for suspension of TTIP talks over fears of human rights abuses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN calls for suspension of TTIP talks over fears of human rights abuses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN calls for suspension of TTIP talks over fears of human rights abuses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN calls for suspension of TTIP talks over fears of human rights abuses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 23:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 19:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe people think I'm religious proselytizing, but I'm not a Buddhist, I'm a Catholic.  I've just found the buddhist techniques for dealing with unwanted thoughts and emotions incredibly helpful for treating my ocd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would personally recommend meditation and buddhist techniques for dealing with emotions in general before going the surgery route.  I have gotten a remarkable amount of healing in the last two years from this, especially going on meditation retreats for a weekend.  It has really changed my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 23:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was funny, fuck em if they can't take a joke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he's doing this serially, he creates relationships with women in every way except sexually, knowingly strings them along till they become heartbroken and leave.  Why would he do that if he has no interest in them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 01:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> finally someone sees it!  He's deep in the closet. All those trips are where the real him comes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 02:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I saw a poster for a stand up comedy gig he's doing in Cork recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's an overhyped player, that he's won the award is symptomatic of how the premier league has declined in the last few years.  He couldn't lace the boots of Saurez or Bale, the two previous winners. They are both in Spain now, of course, and will be playing in the champion's league semis, which have no English team this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benetton on Dublins Stephens Green is being occupied this evening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 22:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 03:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really beautiful artwork, well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online program to combat OCD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 03:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 13:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm amazed I haven't seen a picture of it before.  Mind you, I was only in Donegal once on holidays when I was a child. It looks beautiful, thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 02:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel dumb, but where is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Courts to get power to overrule banks under new Coalition arrears plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no objection to being a part of it as long as we don't have to acknowledge the Queen as been our head of state a la Australia.  I mean, we'll always have huge ties with Britain, there are tens of thousand of Irish and second generation Irish there.  The Brits: a great bunch of lads!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A German politician writes about Irish debt in the Irish Times, interesting perspective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irelands -la-carte Catholicism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa's Curiosity rover finds water below surface of Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gareth Thomas film relocated to Ireland for US viewers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gareth Thomas film relocated to Ireland for US viewers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gareth Thomas film relocated to Ireland for US viewers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article describing a different approach to crime in Glasgow, formerly the murder capital of Europe, by giving violent offenders a second chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glasgow smiles: how the city halved its murders by 'caring people into change' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw the link I knew I recognised the name but it wasn't till I was half way down the article I remembered who he was.  I'll never forget when he listed 'wannabe' by the Spice Girls as one of his top three songs of the year, I thought it was unbelievable for a serious critic.  He was a contrary fucker, but I enjoyed reading him.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 21:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's he didn't charge us a fee, he's great for support young local talent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record Number of Migrants Expected to Drown in Mediterranean in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record Number of Migrants Expected to Drown in Mediterranean in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 02:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pascal Scott, he's best known for playing the guard in Killinascully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 02:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair play! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is!  A good actor and a nice guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pascal Scott, really good actor, we were lucky to get him.  He's best known for playing the Guard in Killnascully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taoiseach rejects water-charges criticism from 'man with two pints in his hand' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cynthia Lennon dies at 75 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a cannon dslr mark 111 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't tell you what lenses the cinematographer was using, but the camera was a cannon dslr mark 111. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  I just thought it was a good title for something so I used it.  I guess the film is a play on the whole boy meets girl thing, but that's post rationalization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things I learned from Clichs - a short film I made down in Cork, Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things I learned from Clichs - a short film I made down in Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things I learned from Clichs - a short film I made down in Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fintan OToole: The crisis is over  so when does the cruelty stop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 00:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if they had stayed out of government the last time they could be around where Sinn Fein are now in Poll Numbers.  It was like they were passengers in a car crash, they didn't cause the crash, but they still got crushed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It will take 100 years for the worlds poorest to earn $1.25 a day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 23:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It will take 100 years for the worlds poorest to earn $1.25 a day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 23:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guess so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they are at the bottom, they're on the dole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't worry so much about what others think of you if you realized how seldom they do. Eleanor Roosevelt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so we have no need for writers, musicians, painters and poets?  I agree that's the attitude we have and I think it's a tragedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they govt. do this, they will be signing their death warrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've a hugely talented musician friend who's giving up music after a lifetime of trying, it's nearly impossible to make a living out of it.  This is how good they are - https://youtu.be/h9Tbhl9cWXQ

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like nurses, teachers and guards, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mick Wallace: Irish bands need more support so they dont rely on the dole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsantos Roundup - Most Popular Weed Killer in US - "Probably" Causes Cancer, WHO Report Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 01:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to drink to cope with my obsessions (I wasn't diagnosed yet, I though I just had depression).  It helped relax me a bit, but the ocd was ten times worse in the morning, I would have to pop some xanax to get under control.  It became a vicious circle for me until I gave up drinking altogether.  Since then, I've been getting better, before that I was disintegrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's obvious to anyone the explanation is corruption.  It won't come out until after Fine Gael are out of government and everyone is retired on a fat pension.  There'll be an investigation but no-one will be held accountable.  It's the past repeating itself before our eyes and there's nothing we can do about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Religious OCD: 'I'm going to hell' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you are using sweets to quit smoking, make sure they are sugar free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave up smoking about a year ago and switched to Polo mints, I was eating three packs a day. Now I'm in the process of getting ten fillings and two extractions, my teeth are fucked. I wish someone had warned me I would have just chewed sugar free gum instead.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would appeal to you all if you're trying this to use sugar free gum.  I gave up smoking about a year ago and switched to Polo mints, I was eating three packs a day.  Now I'm in the process of getting ten fillings and two extractions, my teeth are fucked.  I wish someone had warned me I would have just chewed sugar free gum instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish YouTuber calls his granny to chat about the marriage referendum, gives us all the feels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fintan OToole: Stability can only come from radical change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting story about a fascinating man who lived homeless for years in Austin, scavenging rather than begging, and became somewhat famous blogging about it.  Now he has inherited a mansion and some millions after the suicide of his mother, but whether he can keep it together is now his biggest challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mad Mike, the homeless blogger who became a millionaire overnight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish Water may deduct unpaid bills from wages and welfare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy Shit!  Sorry....I couldn't resist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gold in faeces 'is worth millions and could save the environment' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does our Government like vultures so much? - Gene Kerrigan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 01:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draghi to go to Italian committee but not Irish bank inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 17:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Des Walker's son Tyler makes his senior debut for Nottingham Forest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 03:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized trying to control my thoughts was only creating more spikes so I let go and spikes have reduced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rio de Janeiro's Christ the Redeemer statue glows green for St Patrick's Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The drugs might not work, but neither do the laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 20:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statues destroyed by Islamic State in Mosul were copies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noonan says repossession threats are to get owners to engage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 00:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 01:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should just speak your mind with them.  Like say 'I noticed you sniggering and throwing looks when I'm talking and it made me feel like you're all laughing at me behind my back.  I really don't want friends like that.'  Now maybe you've misunderstood them and you can clear the air or maybe they'll be embarrassed and learn a lesson in life and leave you alone from then on.  Either way, it's a good result for you and you won't be seething from having to make polite chit chat with them anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evictions bring home to us the cynicism of Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 00:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 17:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are a lot of guided meditations on streaming sites.  There are also some [here](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) and [here](http://www.tarabrach.com/audioarchives-guided-meditations.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 04:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faith and meditation has helped me the most.  I find meditation calms my anxiety and exercisse like tonglen help me calm my fears.  I have a religious aspect to my ocd so believing in a loving God who understands my illness and supports me through it helps a lot.  A book that has helped me a lot is 'comfortable with uncertainty' by Pema Chodron, a buddhist nun.  The Buddhists have great technique for stilling the mind and helping you deal with anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 04:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand how you feel, I've been there too.  OCD is a really horrible beats to struggle with, but there is hope.  Meds help, cbt helps some people.  Meditation is what's most helped me calm my anxiety and escape the prison of fear in my head.  A book I found really great recently is comfortable with uncertainty by Pema Chodron, she's a buddhist nun.  It's helped me deal with my fears in a healthier way.  If you ever need someone to talk to you can message me.  I'm happy to listen, stay strong, brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vinny Bs alarm went off live on Radio One and he couldnt turn it off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power to the people: why does Ireland make community energy generation so difficult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former financial regulator Bill Black, just back from a trip to Ireland, discusses his testimony and the challenges Ireland faces acknowledging its financial crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garda whistleblower urges mature debate on legalising cannabis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 21:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David McWilliams at the Banking Inquiry: Irish economy 'set up to fail' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 22:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Leeson: Lack of appetite to take bankers to court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Leeson: Lack of appetite to take bankers to court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Leeson: Lack of appetite to take bankers to court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unthinkable: How good are we at spotting propaganda? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 21:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> good article from the BBC about how Suarez is getting on in Spain (I still miss him!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 22:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 18:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen an interviewer try to put words in the mouth of an interviewee as often as Tubridy did with Paul Murphy the other night.  Fair enough, ask him hard questions, but don't answer them as well.  I thought it was patronizing to the intelligence of the viewer that Tubridy thought we could see his transparent agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Is The Dark Side Of Meditation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 19:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 22:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a look at some of your posts, I get that you're 17 and maybe you don't realize how you come across sometimes.  But when you title a post 'does anyone here think Irish people are really ignorant when it comes to music,' you are going to get people's backs up, straight out the gate, you've called everyone ignorant.  Maybe everybody isn't into the music you like, hip hop is popular with your age group but less so with others.  Anyway, if you want to provoke a discussion I suggest you try a more neutral welcoming approach.  Like 'who here loves hip hip, or what else are you into.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin wife beater and drunk letch, German documentary claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 20:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantnamo torturer led brutal Chicago police regime of shackling and confession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantnamo torturer led brutal Chicago police regime of shackling and confession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guantnamo torturer led brutal Chicago police regime of shackling and confession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of Inmates Are in Solitary for Using Facebook in South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 16:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of Inmates Are in Solitary for Using Facebook in South Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 16:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 02:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Persistence is key to getting through depression.  Try and do some little thing every day that makes you feel like you're making progress.  Treat getting better like your new job, dedicate yourself to it.  Never give up on the hope that you can get better, you can! and hope is like a life raft in a stormy sea. Look at the roots of your depression, what do you think is causing it?  What can you do to lead a happier, more meaningful life for yourself.  Feel free to take a trial and error approach to your life, do more of what makes you feel better, cut out or reduce what makes you feel worse.  Always play the long game in this, some things like exercise are hard in the short term but pay off well in the long one.  Other things like vices play off in the short term but can be disastrous in the long one.  Consider yourself a work in progress, you are building a new, better you, it's an oppourtunity to look hard at your life and learn and change, it can be a good thing if you make it so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 02:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you're doing sounds a lot like cognitive behaviour therapy, have you ever tried it?  Here's a [site](https://moodgym.anu.edu.au/welcome) that gives an introduction to it if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 15:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have similar obsessions.  I am learning to embrace the anxiety rather than let it provoke thoughts and obsessions.  Buddhist philosophy is helping me a lot.  There's an exercise called tonglen where you breathe in your anxiety and out love. It's counter intuitive, we want to get rid of our anxiety, but flight or fight response only strengthens it, non judgemental acceptance of it eases it, I find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big gap in health between rich and poor young Irish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps being overweight was just a physical manifestation of your feelings of inadequacy and self loathing.  You have solved the physical problem but the psychological problem remains.  It's time to take a different tack, it's clear no amount of weight loss is going to address your feelings about yourself.  Perhaps get some counseling it may help you to work out some issues and trace back to where this feelings began.  Also try to begin to learn to love yourself as you are, flaws and all.  If you can't love yourself with your perceived flaws you can't do it at all, as everybody has some.  Try to view yourself with compassion, the same compassion you would give to someone you love very dearly.  Give yourself credit for your positive characteristics.  You're at least as good as the next guy, give yourself a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think now that you have come to this realization, the next step is to begin to learn to love yourself.  Try to look upon yourself and all of your negative characteristics with compassion, the kind of compassion you would give to someone you love very dearly.  Everyone has negative characteristics, if you can forgive and accept this side of yourself, they will exert much less control over you.  Loving ourselves is a hard lesson but one we must learn if we are to be able to love at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISSOLUTES - Storm Gonna Lock You Up [hard rock] [2014] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISSOLUTES - Storm Gonna Lock You Up [hard rock] [2014] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 02:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish tax policies are 'antisocial' to developing countries, says UN expert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish tax policies are 'antisocial' to developing countries, says UN expert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once, I could see no way out of depression. But now Im going to fight for my life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrizas 40 point plan for Greece (some interesting ideas here) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrizas 40 point plan for Greece (some interesting ideas here) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrizas 40 point plan for Greece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US, it seems, couldnt care less if it causes a humanitarian crisis in Somalia, one of the worlds poorest countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 23:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italian investigators seize suspected da Vinci portrait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 23:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italian investigators seize suspected da Vinci portrait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 23:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labours Anne Ferris due to vote against Government on abortion Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 23:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First straw homes go on sale in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 20:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First straw homes go on sale in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 20:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First straw homes go on sale in the UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 20:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transatlantic flights for 149 en route as Wow enters market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 01:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 03:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If what you are saying is the case, then why would European and Asian countries want to sign up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syriza Official Vows to Kill EU-US Trade Deal as 'Gift to All European People' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 02:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syriza Official Vows to Kill EU-US Trade Deal as 'Gift to All European People' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 02:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syriza Official Vows to Kill EU-US Trade Deal as 'Gift to All European People' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 02:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  VIDEO: An English pub in Ireland: inside Wetherspoons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 01:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 03:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that he's sure there's no chance of them ever happening, Obama's proposing lots of great policies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see, this adds to it.  The tune is an old Irish tune called 'The Derry Air.'  An Englishman wrote lyrics to fit it about his young son who he had lost.  So it kind of encapsulates the mixed up nature of Irish culture in a sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 19:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny Boy.  I've been saying it for years, it's such a stirring and powerful song.  Could you imagine it been sung by thousands of fans in a stadium at the start of the game?  Also, everyone knows the words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Gerrards replacement? Valuable Bundesliga star Lars Stindl interests Liverpool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 01:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hatem Ben Arfa: Nice player ineligible for rest of season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 01:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 700,000 fail to register for water charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 01:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to eradicate grey squirrels without firing a shot ( nice to see Ireland referenced as an example for how to do things) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 00:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece shuns debt talks with troika </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 23:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 03:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a lot of good goals in there, of all different types. I feel somewhat reassured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 05:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guided meditations are what helps me most with anxiety. There are some [here,](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) and there are loads on streaming sites.  I have a friend who has panic attacks and he finds xanax help ameliorate them when they come on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the worst thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clergy Send In Photos To Replace Images Of Black Youth Police Were Using For Target Practice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 20:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks demands answers after Google hands staff emails to US government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> run the numbers again!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU has squandered last chance to make euro workable, warns Ex-Bundesbank chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU has squandered last chance to make euro workable, warns Ex-Bundesbank chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalist Barrett Brown sentenced to 63 months in federal prison, must pay $890K in restitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalist Barrett Brown sentenced to 63 months in federal prison, must pay $890K in restitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifa loses three key sponsors as Castrol, Continental and Johnson   Johnson sever ties with world governing body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 01:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 17:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gave a mea cupla [interview](http://www.theguardian.com/media/2015/jan/02/johann-hari-interview-drugs-book-independent) with the Guardian a few weeks back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Davos oligarchs are right to fear the world theyve made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fascinating article by the author of a book about the origins of the drug war and how some flawed experiments lead to society adopting an ass backwards approach to drug treatments.  He suggests a new approach both individually and collectively that has proven to have better results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Likely Cause of Addiction Has Been Discovered, and It Is Not What You Think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 99 PER CENT Man United fans would prefer to keep De Gea than sign Gareth Bale says Manchester United Supporters' Trust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 01:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countless women have been raped by male gaurds at Texas for profit jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two new planets bigger than Earth found in our solar system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryony Gordon reveals her experiences of OCD [x-post from health] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GCHQ captured emails of journalists from top international media from Snowden revelations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally have pure O and what has helped me most is meditation and mindfulness, it reduces anxiety and can slow the racing of the mind.  They're lots of guided meditations on streaming sites, maybe you could suggest it to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 16:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to Will Hughes, he was supposed to be the wonderkid we were supposed to be interested in, looked very good too?  He must be 20 now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the 2014 Oscar nominees' posters told the truth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 02:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've a similar story, a breakdown after some heavy soft drug use birthed OCD in me.  The best thing I have found for coping and reducing anxiety is meditation and mindfulness.  I listen to guided meditations every night.  I would recommend anyone with OCD or an anxious mind try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 former government ministers receive pensions of over 100k </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Great Food War Will Be Won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Great Food War Will Be Won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Great Food War Will Be Won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye opening and comprehensive article exposing propaganda and misinformation used to promote industrial farming at great cost to our health and environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Great Food War Will Be Won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The TTIP trade deal will throw equality before the law on the corporate bonfire | George Monbiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The TTIP trade deal will throw equality before the law on the corporate bonfire | George Monbiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The TTIP trade deal will throw equality before the law on the corporate bonfire | George Monbiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool animated short Yearbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 17:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool animated short Yearbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 17:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to lift veil on Saudi Arabias hijacking of Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 01:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to lift veil on Saudi Arabias hijacking of Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 01:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Stanford University found a cure for Alzheimer's disease? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 04:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you take the prize for inhumanity, well done!  Somali is a failed state, if people from there aren't entitled to asylum, who is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The little known story of a former Wall Street hotshot who exposed corruption in electronic trading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Led Whistle-Blower Haim Bodek to Expose the Biggest Scam on Wall Street? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 01:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [echo](http://www.liverpoolecho.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/exclusive-liverpool-fc-set-reach-8380227) is reporting we're going to bring in Origi this month for a 3 million fee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enda faces humiliation from Greek sabre-rattler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Somali man deported from Ireland to Tanzania died within hours of arrival there, beaten to death, apparently, by police. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 22:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bishop Calls On Catholic Church To Recognize Same-Sex Relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 00:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bishop Calls On Catholic Church To Recognize Same-Sex Relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 00:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bishop Calls On Catholic Church To Recognize Same-Sex Relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 00:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chattering magpie: Ireland has just destroyed500M who cares? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 22:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardly anyone knows it, but since its earliest days the Obama administration has been pursuing the most important initiative in the history of federal attempts to use evidence to improve social programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 22:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardly anyone knows it, but since its earliest days the Obama administration has been pursuing the most important initiative in the history of federal attempts to use evidence to improve social programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 22:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardly anyone knows it, but since its earliest days the Obama administration has been pursuing the most important initiative in the history of federal attempts to use evidence to improve social programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 22:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 14:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  make the public sector public

eh, what does this mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 14:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they see a gap in the market to be the same kind of centre right party as FF and FG, as those two brands are toxic now.  People who would normally have supported those parties, but feel disillusioned with them, can vote for this crowd.  They'll get the same policies, but under a shiny new brand name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Terrible Things That Were Supposed To Happen By 2015 Because Obama Was Reelected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 17:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 14:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can bet the guy (oh yes, it's a guy) who put up that sign is the little tin pot Stalin in that house.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 00:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's my own personal rule, I might be alone on this :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 21:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's forgotten the first rule of the internet: no-one gives a fuck about your cat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taming corporate power: the key political issue of our age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 00:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taming corporate power: the key political issue of our age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 00:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
