<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2022</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 08:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did it reddit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 07:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see his eyes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 07:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Tv show. A superhero show at that. If you want realism, go watch The Wire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else groan inside whenever Daredevil fought ninjas in season 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I love this series to death and I immensely enjoyed season 2...but the Hand storyline fell flat for me. Especifically when those ninjas who couldn't kill their way out of a plastic bag came on screen. UUURRRGHHH, watching Daredevil battle a bunch of ninjas was seriously very lame. And to me their storyline made no effin sense. What are their motivations thorough season 2.
To me it felt like they were just there to provide cool fight scenes that felt stale after a couple of times. 

Other than the Hand, s1 and s2 are excellent IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sucked your mom's dick last night. It was good. Small like mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 01:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking sellout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 00:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fucking horny now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 00:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to the people that waited a month for each issue. I think they were roughly the same amount of time at the prison in the comics as they were in the show (maybe even more)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 23:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one thinking this won't be as good as season 1   2 of Daredevil?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 22:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh

Will you continue to visit this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 21:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next gen is upon us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 09:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 7 is just gonna be a black screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 09:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop having Negan and FTWD in the same fucking titles? Who's writing this shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 05:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't be black please don't be black please don't be black godfuckingdamnit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 01:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man turned out to be some wako who's now dead. Can we stop acting like he's the best villain ever?  I don't have enough fingers to count the amount of villains I find more interesting than this wino. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God snaps his fingers and a bunch of kids die of starvation over at Africa. God snaps his fingers, a rich politician gets off without chargers. 


Do you still love your God? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 09:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell are you talking about? Seasons 4, 5, and 6 are considered the best seasons of the show. 20 seconds don't erase the rest, which I happen to think was damned good. I'm sure Season 7 will have some great episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 05:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Season 6 as a whole, except for the last 20 seconds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 01:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene was perfect. Absolutely fucking perfect. And then....yeah :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok what's happening now I'm getting fucked in the ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 20:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't lie, this is definitely me when season 6 ends on a cliffhanger 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 10:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 06:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the people thinking the viewership will shrink or something are delusional. Chances are it will be the most watched episode of the whole damn show or at least it'll have a solid comeback in terms of views, and let's be real, after that we'll move on. People saying they quit the show on the internet will hurt AMC as much as a bird crashing into an elephant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 06:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way they will come even close to redeem this unredeemable action in my eyes is if Season 7 is 10/10 with no filler, no bullshit episodes. We know the first episode is gonna be good, it always is, but I want them to treat every other fucking episode of that season like a fucking boon to us fans.

I want Season 7 to be insane and I want these two assholes to make it up to us. I know we still have a lot to cover up before All Out War, but these fucker better make it up to us in some way. Season 7 needs to be entirely something else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 02:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott Gimple and Robert Kirkman should feel ashamed of themselves. The fans aren't the only people they disrespected. Every single actor included in that scene gave their 100% and brought the scene to life in a way I couldn't imagine. But, alas, all that's been looked over because these two clowns decided none of that mattered as long as they got their sweet, sweet views next October. 

Fuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 06:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll allow you to paint the wire instead of using real one. Everything else must be done by the book though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 04:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man the fear on Rick's face... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just sharted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your weapon of choice for the inevitable ensuing Riot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They most certainly will adapt it. Remember the Governor centric episodes? Some of that was taken from the Governor novels.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 21:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Puerto Rico so I can't help you there. Want any dick pics though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there movies you don't like just because of one mistake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 09:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 09:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what Greg? I'll fucking take your word for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 00:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that idea. Maybe season's 7 cold open could be him shaving, the he walks over to Lucille and makes sweet love to her and then he does something a little bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 20:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude stay with your Dad and watch the finale. You came out of his white juice, you owe him that much. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 20:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys I want this really bad. And it's not because of Maggie's head gag I'm not into bondage I swear it's  not that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 07:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved him. Even in his...darker times  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 03:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on, is he the one who comes out of Kruppe's asshole in chapter 4? I knew it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Heboric. Just STFU you rambling old fool. Even other characters are like, "WTF are you even trying to say?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens when you run into a group like the Claimers and they decide to gang-rape you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro Beth is supposed to be like 15 in the show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The woman slashed at Maggie's stomach while they were locked in a fight. The woman hesitated after that, realizing what she had done, but she had only cut the shirt, then immediately dies by Carol. I'm think the pain Maggie is experiencing  comes from the bruise on her side, that Glenn saw when they were showering,  which she may have gotten during her time of capture. I hope the baby is not lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know there are people out there that are willing to pay to get their dick sucked, right? And to a lot of them, it doesn't even matter how who does the sucking looks. Do it for TWD :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 00:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite all the characters being amazing, I could never continue after s7. To me, Michael Scott was the heart of the show, while the rest of the cast were the necessary organs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 22:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man how the show has changed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 02:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Rick throatfucking Joe shocked me as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who is freaking out over Negan actually showing up?

Yeah what's up with that? Ever since Negan was confirmed to be in the finale /u/AlanSleeper has been the **only** user in this entire subreddit freaking out. What's wrong with you people? Why is no one else freaking out about this? Is /u/AlanSleeper literally the only one? I'm disappointed!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 05:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carol should've responded with 

"Look into my eyes, I'm already dead"

Ooooh shit I should be a writer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they stupid or something?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, these saviors surely are friendly people! They just wanna chat in the middle of the road or in the woods, nothing else  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man you guys...should not get your hopes up. Please, do it for your own soul  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 00:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try Deez Nuts!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 22:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was not the question. He wants to get in touch with these peoples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meme is too strong for him to embrace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watch the videos. Nothing else is expected of you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of you are talking shit about Leafy. Let me make something clear: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Neither of them are right. Theres no moral high ground in this banal debate. Just because we are loyal h3h3 fans doesn't mean we can't be pragmatic about this whole thing.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 21:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's when some guy driving a white van with strange glyphs all over it can hit you and send you flying to another fucking continent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 20:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever tried heroin? It's like having really good heroin and then noticing a vast drop in quality for the next two batches. Have you tried meth? It's like having the best meth ever and then experiencing shitty meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 20:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why they have 1M+ subscribers and you don't. Please please let them do what they want. Don't ruin it for the rest of us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 08:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly there's no other way about it than to show them the first episode and then ask them if they want to continue. (And who wouldn't after that kickass episode?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 08:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 6 years of loyalty from the fans, Scott Gimple and Kirkman make the most important scene of the entire show so far into a big "fuck you, see you in 7 months."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you serious? Those guys couldn't kill their way out of a plastic bag  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 09:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Trull would be able to hold for some time, but then Karsa would do something unexpected and kill him
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 09:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this ends in a cliffhanger I'm denouncing Scott Gimple and AMC in the name of our lord Jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 23:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hot would it be if they kiss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 22:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moral of the story guys, don't start shit unless you really have to (looking at you Ethan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malazan doesn't hold back on how ugly life can be. If you don't like that can kind of stuff, I recommend something else, like Discworld or Narnia lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethan won't be making an appearance soon. He's waiting for the drama to blow over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 10:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I will. Every episode can end in a cliffhanger of Glenn dying over and over again and I'd still watch it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 01:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It ends in a cliffhanger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll believe it when it when I see it. 

You have to accept it now and be done with it. Otherwise, your path leads to destruction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 22:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao. What's funny is that before this the suspense for us was about "who's gonna get Lucilled" and all that stuff. Now we're scared...about whether this is gonna be a cliffhanger or not. 

Negan's legendary introduction is coming people. Are you ready for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 21:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you guys hear that? The sound of hundreds of fans dreams being crushed under AMC's heel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 21:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if you're being sarcastic but I thought s1 finale was decent, and s2 looks promising. We'll see... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 21:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say there is a big chance this is false  (and there is) but... looking at past cliffhangers this wouldn't surprise me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 21:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no you won't. You'll be back on October with the rest of us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just tried this with my brother. It's possible if you open your mouth very wide and slip your lower jaw under the underside of his crotch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
