<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8860</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you just goldfish this, you find that it fails the most basic tests of deck constuction.

It doesnt even matter that this is a legacy deck, this Fails at beating a draft pile with any sort of consistency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you think it would be helpful to post links to the top 8s you got the lists from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool to see that article! I'm only slightly upset that my list and name didn't get mentioned, but i understand Tezzerator is maybe more standard than dead guy and that there's only so much space in an article.


I actually recognized that decay cacks thoptersword pretty bad, so i cut 1 thopter/ 1 sword from my list before the tournament. Chalice needs to stay though obv if you have no force of will, and is so good when they don't have an answer that i think that its fine to still play this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah we have weekly "duel for some legacy thing" and it draws a pretty big crowd. it doesnt have to be nuts,
just playing for leovold or wasteland or EMA karakas is probably good enough, and a set of those things instead of a dual for first place in a monthly is probably good enough if the community is smallish.

honestly, 8 man event - $20 buy in 8x20 = 200  200/40 = 5, so that gets a set of wastes for first, and $40 cred for second. EMA wastes are less than that on scg right now even, so you can run it yourself and take a cut.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the most inconsistent things I've ever seen. not even a green brainstorm can fix it.

For reference: Ant is a combo deck that looks to win on turn 2-3. it usually plays 14 lands. Those lands all produce colored mana. Ant also has 4 other free sources of mana. Ant also has 4 brainstorm, 4 ponder, 4 probe and a Sensei's divining top or preordain in order to filter through its draws.

This thing has nothing resembling any of that, and has less land, some of which cant cast spells on its own.
This is a disaster waiting to happen.

So in the interest of constructive criticism, here is how i would build what it seems like you want to do here.

dorks  
4 birds   
4 hierach  

locks:  
4 thalia heretic cathar   
4 winter orb  
4 root maze  


interaction:  
4 swords to plowshares  

green suns package:  
1 dryad militant  
1 dryad arbor  
4 green suns zenith  
2 scryb ranger  
1 quasali pridemage   

beaters:   
4 greenbelt rampager/greenwheel liberator / dependent on windswept heath  
2 thrun the last troll  
3 knight of the reliquary/  dependent on heath  

mana:   
4 windswept heath  
4 wasteland  
9 forest  
1 plains  

the rest are up to you, but honestly this whole idea seems like a worse version of sylvan plug. I'd consider that unless you are under REALLY tight budgetary constraints. The deck i listed has it's own set of problems.

cards to consider:
renegade ralier  
tarmogoyf / I assumed budgetary concerns










 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> related question: do the 1v1 queues ever fill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first pass of my new list, based on my experiences playing in magic onlines very special brand of legacy meta and tournament structure. 
4 chain lightning  
4 bolt  
4 rift bolt  
4 swiftspear  
4 guide  
4 lava spike  
4 flame rift  
4 price of progress  
2 exquisite firecraft    
4 ankh of mishra  
4 fireblast  

18 mountain  

sb  
2 faerie macabre  
2 relic of progenitus  
4 smash to smitherines  
3 scald  
2 exquisite firecraft  
2 sulfuric vortex   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after playing more games, vortices dont do much. switching to 3 firecraft main, 1 firecraft side, 1 vortex side. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna try ankh main over something for a while, do you think should i run 3 or 4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scald is the only reason i was beating miracles at all. i want more scald not less.

Also, I'm definitlely not putting searing blood in the maindeck unless i see more creatures. in twenty matches i played against delver twice, to give you perspective. I played against deathrite 3 times, never saw mentor or confidant, and played taxes twice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> b ring is wretched without fetches. ive been keeping track, threshhold happens on turn 5-6 on average.

After playing 4 leagues, I've only played 5 matches where i would want a burn spell that targets creatures, so if i play searing blood at all its a 2 of in the board at most.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would obivously rather play taxes, but would rather buy reserved list stuff than online port. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this at hairy t? i meant to go but last minute financial surprises meant that i didnt have enough money for entry. 

Which sucks, cause i wanted to rock tezzerator again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daze looks so bad with ankh in play.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can sell the pyroblasts for 10 - 12 tix too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suboptimal burn list then I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure, I'll try it there if you can present a reasonable argument for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After playing against delver exactly zero times after the first, I think i'll pass on basically anything that has to target a creature.

Edit: Lol just lost to delver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after playing miracles multible times, can confirm they are absolotly not the same card. vortice can be hit by force and counterspell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 bucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eidolons are 20 tix each 4 x 20 80 tix. i have 11. Lavamancer it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero to Hero: Burn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i just got into legacy on magic online today. I bought the fireslinger precon and 30 tickets,

spent them on some fringe burn choices, and went 3-2 beating UR delver, miracles and miracles, and losing to turbo-depths and merfolk.

list as follows:
4 chain lightning  
4 bolt  
4 rift bolt  
4 swiftspear  
4 guide  
4 lava spike  
4 flame rift  
4 price of progress    
2 exquisite firecraft  
2 sulfuric vortex  
4 fireblast  
2 bedlam reveler  
18 mountain  

sb   
2 pyroblast  
2 ankh of mishra  
4 smash to smitherines  
2 scald  
2  exquisite firecraft  
2 meltdown  
1 sulfuric vortex  

got 120 play points and a rugged prarie( 11 tix)

My question is : What should i spend that on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is Matt was likely not present for the art decisions that went into dawn of war 2, certainly not for dawn of war 1, and  Nick's last project was mobile.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloom effects so heavy-handed you can't see units being shot at, health bars that cover hero's so you cant see them, units virtually indistiguishable from other units.  

To start with. Do you want photo or video evidence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is, when something goes wrong people blame the whole team, and it might help if that didn't happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No witchhunt, they just weren't ready for the task.

Responsible  was perhaps the wrong tone of word, but they were the guys in charge of the things that people are complaining about the most, and people gennewrally cant understand how things turned out like this.

Well the lead animator last worked on a mobile game, and the art director was probably not in a position to
know what decisions even went into the art of dawn of war at any point in time.    

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dawn of war 3 being pretty unclear despite clarity as a stated goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried to do some research to see whos responsible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> suppression field is insane in that matchup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so is marit lage :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grass is a bridge card to confinement, which is only a bridge card to doomwake giant/ sphere of safety. suppression field can work to fill gaps and buy time, and post board you have lots of options, including discard and creature removal, in addition to humility/ moat/more doomwake/ engineered plague. Also, green suns for melira if you want it.

I'ts not necessarily favorable, but by no means is it an autoloss like some of these real combo decks.

sneak could be okay depending on your build, but the games over once omniscience gets involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  no, if it relies on attacking, it gets blanked by any number of things.

the only reason elves gets a pass is reclamation sage recursion. prior to that, the matchup was very favorable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infect and delver are pretty even, actually.

loses to storm, elves, sneak and show, omnishow, pox, BR reanimator, mud, 12post.

basically anything that remotely resembles a combo deck or goes over the top of what enchantresss is trying to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yeah too true.

It's so much worse here in canada too, i have to pay the +%30 excange rate on mtgo tickets.

Which reminds me that there are other countries that have things worse in that respect, lowering the appeal of mtgo in a worldwide market, but thats another conversation.

How much worse is  draft ev at $17.25?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about the name mis sspells.

I did put two spaces at the end of the line, I'm looking at the line breaks right now, save 2 that i missed by accident.

Forgot darksteel citadel and flooded strand in the list.

Also, you wrote in 4 revoker when I wrote 1.

I wanted to sort the list by card role rather than just by card type, given that people unfamaliar with the archetype were going to be looking at it.

Wrote this list up while tired as hell and went from memory. Serves me right . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, that's the point. no taxes makes this a more reasonable option.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jiminy chrismas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also 7-0'd the freaking legacy challenge.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can't you therapy it off a narcomoeba? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am i reading this chart right? There's more chalice than goyf, counterbalance, or stoneforge mystic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are mtgo results valid at all for anything but figuring out the mtgo meta? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked and Death and taxes has only 5-0 d 4 times out of 96 undefeateds, which gives it around the same win rate as dredge.

We know that's not right, but the source has it as a deck to beat and has done so for a while.

I know why theres no taxes, thats not the issue.

I don't think we can use Mtgo results when prepping for paper tournaments.

Come to think of it, I don't think wizards should use mtgo results when considering
 bannings, and I think people should consider paper legacy and online legacy two different formats when discussing the health of the meta. 

I'm willing to be proven wrong, this is more off the cuff than anything.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your best green 2 drop is visionary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably can't beat any reasonable taxes curve, but my point was that D T looks to be a much less prevalent archetype online.

A cursory glance at mtgo 5-0 lists shows only 4 taxes lists in the last 14 days.

thats 4/96, not counting the legacy challenge.

dredge has 3/96, which means "dodge D T" is about as valid a plan as "dodge dredge." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dragon stompy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not unreasonable to freeze and the blue suns zenith with the emrakul trigger on the stack. 

Doesnt look like this version can beat a resolved leovold in game 1 very easily. cunning wish for bounce looks like the only out and that costs...

Actually, thinking about it, it doesnt matter. high tide- cunning wish - snap means youre only down 1  mana more than you would be anyways,  and the leovold decks dont have that much interaction anyways.

If the mtgo meta looks anything like what i saw in the dragon stompy post, this could be a good choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what happens if you board in price of progress with this deck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remember that rishadan port is 200 tix. Might be why you see no taxes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> List is:

walkers  
4 tezzeret, agent of bolas  
3 daretti, ingenious iconoclst  
1 dack fayden (This guy is getting cut so hard. I lost almost every game where he resolved.)    

grind combo  
2 thopter foundry  
2 sword of the meek  

sweepers  
1 toxic deluge  
2 ensnaring bridge  

guys   
1 phyrexian revoker  
4 baleful strix  

locks  
4 chalice of the void  

mana rocks  
4 mox diamond  
2 dimir signet  

interaction  
2 izzet charm  

spice   
1 thopter spy network  (this was great too)  
1 trading post  ( this is never coming out of the 60 )  
1 batterskull(craneo machacador)    
1 padeem, consul of innovation (drew me at least fifteen cards that day)  
1 transmute artifact  

lands, fetch  
4 delta  
2 strand  

lands, utility  
1 inventors fair  
1 academy ruins  
2 wasteland  
1 urborg, tomb of yawgmoth  
1 darksteel citadel  

lands, dual   
2 usea  
2 volc  

lands, basic  
1 island  
1 swamp  

lands, ramp  
4 ancient tomb  

lands, budget  
1 darkwater catacombs  

Sideboard:  
2 winter orb  
2 blood moon  
4 force of will (never boarded it in today.)  
2 grafdiggers cage( this either)  
1 trinisphere  
1 cursed totem ( elves / taxes/ deadguy. Yeah, that last one IS necessary.)   
1 keranos, god of storms  
1 ghirapur aether grid  
1 toxic deluge  

cards that have been good in the past:  

gloom (i want to resolve this against miracles so bad)  
chill ( lands and burn and aggro-loam)    
rakdos charm  
massacre  
wurmcoil engine( Is now batterskull, not sure if correct)  
necromancy(heavy reanimator meta, turns out they don't like getting beaten to the punch.)  

I borrowed someones abyss one time and it was bonkers.  
Want to cast nether void just once in my life.  
chains i can see being actively bad sometimes.  
need another transmute artifact, will replace dack.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't reccomend this guide enough. 

The change i would make to the no fetch burn list in the article is -4 searing blaze + 4 flame rift, but thats just me and I'm sure others will tell you different.

also, if you see too much opposing delver, please test ankh of mishra. 5 damage per fetch and 2 per daze seems way above rate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great plan. Ur delver likes its basics anyways, though you will need a volcanic to start.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> burn is also an absolutely fantastic way to get a hands on feel for the more subtle ways in which the power level of legacy differs from modern. as well as learn which play patterns are open for punishment and how.

You'll learn that cracking a fetch at the wrong time can be exploited by burning to play around counterspells, and that price of progress is possibly the most terrifying burn spell ever printed.

If you stick with burn, you'll learn that the deck has a suprising amont of flex in how it attacks a meta.  

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pox is at an all time high locally. Not a real data point, but might make you feel a little better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't try at home. I traded miracles for this thing.

I got home too late to catch the stream. You started a little early.

As per our arrangement, I owe you a donation. I couldnt have beat grixis in the swiss without you. just tell me when you have it ready.  

Yeah that top 8 was pretty representative of the local level of playskill here. 

Note miracles did not make top8, and sometimes that happens here. There were 4 miracles players that i saw, one of whom was another GP top 8 contender, and more that i didn't see i'm sure. 

I'll have to ask about, but i think miracles has been underperforming lately for the last few months.

I want to believe we've hated it out, but I realize I gotta check the numbers. 
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jtms isnt even good with lash. and this is another thing, if a deck is going through this stage of development, it probably has at least three variants that differ wildly from each other.

pointing to a deck at that point and saying "this is thought lash" is
 counterproductive in the extreme, its like if miracles was still in the dev stage and someone pointed at Quadlazer Miracles and judged the archetype based on how playable or not that version was.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trying to make it happen. The resilliency, power, and flexibility are there for sure. The deck can be hard to play, a mix between high tide and show and tell with counter top for protection and a moat type effect built in. 

you play a game where you try to stick top, bait with counterbalance, then jam thought lash with backup. 

thought lash + top will find you lab man while blanking your opponents attacks, then when you play lab man  your instant speed cantrips proceed to be protection spells by virtue of putting "you win the game" triggers on the stack. Even top just sits there and makes them cringe.

post board you get access to back to basics as a haymaker. 

I want to try a black splash for fatal push and lim duls vault.

btw, I don't see why stuff that hasn't been tried in a while gets blasted so hard on these boards.

its unplayable until someone top 8s with it, then some guy goes and scrubs with it because he doesnt see the decks interactions, deems it unplayable on camera/ stream, and then anyone who brings it up gets laughed at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right i forgot you have US money. cdn dollar is still garbage. all that stuff costs way more for us.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for what its worth, i top 8ed the 1k losing to delver in the semis. 6 rounds of swiss, 50 people, top 8 was from what i remember:

1st landstill, 18 points. Lam Phan of GP jersey top 8 fame, cocreator of canadian thresh
2nd deadguy ale, 15 points. Wilkin Chow, local legacy pro and the only reason deadguy wont stay dead
3rd grixis delver, Boston (really sorry cant remember your last name) Grixis delver Expert.

I know I came sixth, but rankings are hazy and i didnt take notes. there was Brian bogdon on deadguy(disciple of chow) Josh Trank on lands( pretty good lands player), Someone on reids leovold thing, and i cant remember the 8th person.
miracles missed top 8 on breakers of %3 or something.

I beat miracles twice, grixis once and a close one to pox for my win and in. lost to bogdon on deadguy,
and unintentional drew with trank due to my own incompetence.

I played grixis tezzerator.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
