<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely my thoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminded me of an absurd episode of Adventure Time where Jake had this complex game that he made Beemo and Finn play with him, and when anyone else won he would throw a fit. It ends pretty cutely. Your brother is immature. Like the boyfriend I broke up with about an hour ago. He doesn't know when to stop talking, or just stop at all. Don't bother with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Sexual Assault Reports Jump By 50 Percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 20:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They claim they took it down for "inappropriate commentary," but... our  commentary deemed rather appropriate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you love her, don't let her buy the alcohol. That's my only suggestion, coming from a 19 year old with an alcoholic mother. Nobody could convince her to change and the only thing that seemed to stop her was when I was ten and switching the vodka with water. Tell her to stop. She needs someone to make her stop before she's sucked in too deep to listen, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 06:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good points, but your first statement is unnecessary. University's are smart enough now to know that you CAN be a risk, but want to see how hard you will fight not to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 06:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will accept it. It's sincere, and sounds like it's coming from the heart. They want to know you want to come back and they want to know you want to change and make yourself better. This happened to me last year, and my essay looked a lot like yours. Here I am, chillin the weekend before finals. 

By the way, I went from a 0.0 GPA last year back to getting A's and B's, one year later after a medical leave. Thank you, 225mg of Venlafaxine daily.

Also, throw in some things about how you were before the depression happened, if there were better times and better grades (I'm sure there were), and relate that to what you want to do in the future.

Random things that help my severe depression that I never thought would help: Positive notes to myself in a place where I can see them. One says, "Breathe. Drink water. Rest." Whatever helps you man. Every day is an achievement so keep going. 

I also had to add, message me if you'd like whenever you feel like going over the edge. I can help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 06:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this what LSD is like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 02:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To whoever thumbs downed me in the first ten minutes of upload, rot in hell. Just trying to do something nice for my home state. CT represENT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A "Remember Newtown" sign I made for my window at school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 02:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you guys think you're going to do as careers, forever? Making trap? Let us know your ideas! From your biggest fan at Skidmore College </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the drugs that people don't eat, the ones that expire, the ones that just simply go in the trash.... who digests those genius?

HOW IN THE FUCK AM I GETTING SO MANY DOWNVOTES FOR BEING LOGICAL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 08:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you seriously asking that? Of course people do that. Get metabolized by what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING: Two RADCON 5 Alerts On West Coast Within 48 Hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 07:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Youwouldaguessed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 05:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.change.org/petitions/the-tribal-chief-and-council-of-the-eastern-band-of-cherokee-indians-stop-the-inhumane-treatment-of-bears-in-cherokee-nc PLEASE GUYS :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 05:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watched the show "Damages," you'd get a pretty good idea just how bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 04:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 04:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi to all. Please take the time to read this.

I'm not from Cherokee, but my roots are. My grandfather resided there and passed in 2009. I have many fond memories of the Eastern Band of Cherokee. I spent a lot of my childhood exploring the reservation, the Cherokee river, watching the casino in progress, and many others.  

To anyone bothering to read, I have been to this park as a child more than once. I have seen these conditions and remember leaving with a pit in my stomach every time, like I left that (or my heart) behind in the zoo. I'm going to try to find petitions to start or find links to but...

PLEASE please thumbs up this!! 

The news NEEDS to be spread as we are a rather quiet and not media-centered tribe. However, we are one of the only tribes with a semi-strong economy, and we can do much than this treatment with our resources, and reddit's help, if the people want a zoo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 18:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if people like YOU would stop giving kids media attention by posting things like THIS, we wouldn't HAVE A KNOCKOUT PROBLEM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 23:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean immigrants from like the Middle East and Spanish-speaking in particular, I didn't think anyone would pay attention to my comment and should have clarified. I have heard of lots of people complain about practices of trafficking and crime with them to America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 19:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why people don't like immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to type as I read along. 
"i don't feel like i have chronic depression"
^buddy, you really wouldn't have a clue if you did or not. Believe me.
You sound like myself, life story wise. 19F. 
Dude, don't sit at home, that's the worst thing. I never do. Do you have a car? I drive around and smoke weed a lot, stay at my boyfriend's, friends houses, or just myself. Don't be afraid to walk around your town and ask about jobs if you think you can handle a second one (it's less free time, but it's something to do with benefits.)
I'm sorry buddy. I went through so much like you did, I was diagnosed MDD last year and doubted I was depressed before that. You gotta get used to solitude because a lot of people just don't know how to do that, and don't even try until they get out of bad places in life. What do you like to do? Can you afford to pay for a few community college classes? Just try to do whatever you can to have yourself juggling. You'll get back in the swing of life and you'll feel better. Reconnect with a few old friends, sometimes the best ones may have been trouble in your life, for whatever reasons, but a few are worth keeping if you take some time to think about who's good for you.
Loneliness sucks but you gotta embrace it, we're adults and its new but it's something that isn't as bad as it seems later on. Trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty you don't have to have anything further to do with your mom. You're an adult now and can decide who you don't and do have relationships with. Tell your mother to go royally fuck herself AND when she has her 80 foot pole thats up her ass removed, she can come talk to you. You have to value your self worth and work on wiping her out of your mind, she's only done bad things to you and from here on out you deserve good things.

And if he does that again to you, walk away without looking back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang out with your mom and a few close friends. And some animals. Lovely cuddly animals. This fall, before I went to college, I was very nervous about going away for my sophomore year because my freshman year, I got my MDD diagnosis and had to take a semester off. About three weeks before I went to school, there were four baby squirrels in my yard that had fallen from their nest. Three survived, one did not, and my boyfriend's family took care of them from that day on. They were the most precious things and it really takes your mind off of things just to have something young to take care of (that's not a child, I suppose). If you're a nurturing type, consider adopting something. I promise that it can help. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 15:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. These people just need to be reconditioned into acceptance. The racist, wild west days are old, and a great majority of America has moved past that phase, but a good amount have not. These are older generations teaching the young, and like you say, they do not supervise like they absolutely should. These things hit home fast, but I'm happy there are people like you around to take a few minutes to acknowledge and react to this. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 09:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all I can do is sit here and think, "Look at this world's messes, this country's security issues, and here's the NSA fuckin' around listening to the Norwegians." 

I think their heads are made of toilets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 09:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They better get their asses in combat, they deserve it! It's embarrassing how far behind we are with gender equality in the armed services in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 09:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? It's been like that ever since... forever. Until say around 1988 when the first actions were made to let US women join the armed services. They only this year became allowed to fight in combat, but with these promises come catches; they won't get to actually FIGHT in the combat/infantry devisions, they can do background work like janitor work or nursing work. I wish I was kidding. Otherwise, they can still fly fighter jets and be rescue pilots and things like that, away from direct interference. Women in the US services are just not included, and put off to the side as much as possible. You should watch the Invisible War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 09:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EBCI kid I found this offensive. The ignorance in this country never fails to astonish me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 07:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will get better darling. Give yourself not too much alone time and get yourself to do stuff every day. Do happy things. Take it a day at a time and you have so much time ahead of you to get better and flip this around. It's possible, trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) Thanks, let's wake up and do this tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a friend like you. Most people would think that sounds stupid coming out of a females mouth but I really mean it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 20:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a shit head and you deserve better. Way way way way better. He took a cowards way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 19:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just put in a post just like yours. I know how you feel. Been trying at it all morning for one class that I probably won't go to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need something to brighten up my day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 19:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19 and since it's right before Thanksgiving, I have some work I have to keep up with. I've been crying all morning over loneliness and other things that tie with that. I told my boyfriend of almost a year not to call me and I reject his calls because I feel annoying. His texts have 20 minute intervals, and that alone is enough to make me go back in my shell. 

I have class in less than an hour and I hope I can make it, let alone stop crying. I take medication but it seems that I'm just too emotional today. 

I'm beyond lonely in person, but know I'm not alone in this subreddit. 

A tip would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
