<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 19:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome restoration! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 05:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> half million in cash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 05:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think that one is so boring and menial that it is the perfect lie for a few hours of suspicion-free meth stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 05:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think that one is so boring and menial that it is the perfect lie for a few hours of suspicion-free meth stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 08:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [40 lb box of rape, don't open it!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Z7SafOiCXM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 06:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you buy the reflective tape from?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 10:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://img.pandawhale.com/post-24143-chris-farley-wtf-smile-dafuq-g-mrMk.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 22:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The important distinction is which 1/3 you were with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 07:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on Dan, get with the times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 08:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone in my college class did something similar. He also has a pair of lips tattooed on his hip because of a blackout-night of drinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 08:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porn? 

Or you could hook them up to an arduino or raspberry pi for additional storage for whatever other projects you have brewing. Or you could set them up as dead drops around wherever you live: http://www.networkworld.com/community/node/83855 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 02:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the poop smear

Never forget the [poop smearing robo-toilet](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v-g3X3fAS8I). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 15:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But webfilters... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 16:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? You're their biggest seller! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 08:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, I've had no less than 4 mohawks. 1 of which was quite tall while the rest of my head was shaved. Hair grows back, and my parents knew I was a responsible, smart guy. The best one was during finals week at my engineering college. They didn't care at all that I changed my appearance, they were just disappointed I didn't take pictures of the biggest mohawk. 

I love my parents :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 05:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texting and unicycling isn't very hard if you know how to ride (plenty of experience with both here). Having a stroller as a support would make it even easier. Sorry dude, not very WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 04:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meatspin.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 06:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only after he masturbates with them, so it's not weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 06:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do that constantly. That and bite my nails. I just do it to kill time I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 01:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contrails? Nah man, they're *chem*trails. It's an aerosolized mind control solution that the corporations put up there for the government. It's a huge conspiracy man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screwdriver car key? Yeah, I've done that. Picture tutorial inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 20:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 08:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sup Dan. I'm halfway to drunk right now. Thought you should know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 07:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're a girl (or guy) giving head for the first time, do [this](http://25.media.tumblr.com/3c8023c7ff3043d4c4742f688ce4abca/tumblr_mrhftt6wzW1sqryh2o1_500.gif)

And not [this](http://31.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lui6if9PgI1r2h21to1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 21:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://images.wikia.com/simpsons/images/9/9d/Cereal.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 04:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fuckers need help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 23:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You put the fire to the grass, give a little puff, then drink some water and chill right out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 22:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or slapped. But those stories aren't told as willingly as marriage ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 02:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here you guys go:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=PGHfTstfWwk#t=75

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 01:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know how often kids get sick? If you took them every single time they showed signs of anything the bills would add up real fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 10:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrible... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 08:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It will follow you. And it will hit you. And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again.  And again."

"The spoon thunders down with relentless, merciless, bone shattering fury, pounding and pounding several soft spots into your skull until it cracks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 05:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hell is repetition](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1lxmkl/reddit_what_is_your_personal_hell/cc3xtdc)

[Stephen King](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1lxmkl/reddit_what_is_your_personal_hell/cc3xtdc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 04:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wahla

[Voil](http://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/voil%C3%A0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 23:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/DXULqeP.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 08:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I was hoping that materials engineers wouldn't show up to this post ;)

I simplified my explanations so that most people could better understand what I said. Most of the shots were taken at 20x, but the closer ones were taken at 50x magnification. And I agree that the structure was alloyed, although this isn't my specialty (I'm I Mech. Engineer, so you probably know more than me). 

Since this was almost a year ago I can't quite remember what grit we polished to, but it was more than 1000. 

And yes, my hands did lock up a bit after polishing those samples. It takes quite awhile to get a good sample! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 02:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mechanical Engineering at Colorado School of Mines. The equipment is fairly standard so I'm not surprised that it looks familiar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 02:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Everyday I ride the Tour de Fuck You!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hgCqz3l33kU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 01:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the barrel for free and used my university's equipment and got an excellent grade for my work. Time and energy well spent in my book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'll jump on the gravy train. I sectioned, polished, and analyzed an M1919 machine gun barrel a few months ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 00:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A darn good demo album: National Park Radio - The Great Divide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 04:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 04:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't you the guy who burnt his dick with hair removal gel? 

http://i.imgur.com/A8uE3Y7.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 02:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Da tree fiddy was her weight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 00:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7.25, and it's only 6.875 for cousins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 05:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that 202 lbs of hamburger is only from 1 shoulder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 10:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. But aren't we all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 09:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [All yall mothafuckin' Dans just got tagged](http://i.imgur.com/QgJjDYv.png)

But seriously, if I run into any of you outside of this thread I'll be sure to name drop. Hopefully by then you'll have long forgotten about this thread and you'll just think I'm some creepy person you know who is stalking you online. Maybe I'm that person who sits on the street corner and stares at you every morning. Or maybe I'm that slightly overeager neighbor who gives off pedophilic vibes. Or maybe I'm that cute salacious person you've been dreaming about for the last several weeks. 

Or maybe I'm just an internet stranger who likes calling people by their names to give them pause.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 20:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ice Soap](http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/jinex/shower_to_go/)


[2am chili](http://imgur.com/7mwNY9v)


Both these relatively stupid ideas popped up at the same time and the result was inevitable:

[2am ice chili](http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/jlbdf/2_am_ice_chili_shower/)


Edit: I may as well throw the toaster grilled cheese on here too

http://i.imgur.com/u8H2T.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 20:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accidental discharges happen when somebody isn't paying attention and puts their finger on the trigger when they didn't want to. Those are entirely operator error, and almost never have anything to do with the gun itself. 

[Every manufacturer repeatedly drop tests their pistols](http://oag.ca.gov/sites/all/files/pdfs/firearms/regs/chapter5.pdf). The pistols are dropped from 1 meter onto a concrete slab and from 6 required drop-positions (see page 6 of link for requirements), and any failures are heavily scrutinized and may require rework or scrapping of the entire batch or entire pistol design. 

Firearms manufacturers take safety and reliability very seriously. Firearms don't go off on their own, it's incompetent owners who are the ones causing negligent discharges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 19:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firearms don't just go off in their own, especially if they are in a pack. They are quite safe when being used with respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 02:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made grilled cheese in my toaster. It worked fantastically because I have a toaster oven. 

Went really well with my 2am ice chili too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 02:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate almond-milk and oatmeal. Mix them at approximately a 2:1 ratio of liquids to solids and throw it in the refrigerator overnight. In the morning you an eat it cold or microwave it a few seconds to make it hot. 

Almondy, oaty, chocolately goodness right there. Add some berries or other ingredients if you're feeling fancy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 01:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know several people who are extremely passionate about horses. They're big, smelly, and they can kick you to death if you don't treat them with respect. I don't understand their appeal at all, but I would never think about taking a horse away from its loving owner. 

I pretty much only shoot competitively, making neat little holes in a piece of paper some distance away. I enjoy the zen attitude I get from controlling my heartbeat and breathing while holding the rifle steady and gently squeezing the trigger. It's my stress reliever. 

I have guns, others have horses. I don't understand their viewpoint, and several of them don't understand mine, but that's the beauty of having personal choice. Do what you enjoy and don't hold others from the things they enjoy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those wondering, it's [bass](http://www.findingareason.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/upright.jpg), not [bass](http://www.usbr.gov/mp/ccao/newmelones/images/activities_largemouth_bass.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 08:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the old semen you're smelling, not the corpse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 08:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derailleur hangers are meant to bend before your derailleur because they are much cheaper than a new derailleur. So yes, if it's been bent in a crash you can try and bend it back to straight. 

If your derailleur hanger is made of steel it can generally be bent back to straight with a [DAG tool](http://www.amazon.com/Park-Tool-Derailleur-Hanger-Alignment/dp/B0028YWHPW/ref=sr_1_cc_1?s=aps srs=2529177011 ie=UTF8 qid=1377571554 sr=8-1-catcorr keywords=park+derailleur+hanger+tool) fairly easily. If it's aluminum, you can bend it back a few degrees, but generally they snap. Aluminum is much more brittle and will strain harden much quicker than steel, so once it's bent, it's usually done. 

If you break a hanger, just buy a new one from your LBS. They range from $5 to $50+ depending on your bike. Most are pretty cheap and are very simple to install. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 07:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking lost it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 05:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Either bleed or replace your pads. Juicy 3s are fairly good hydraulic brakes, you shouldn't have to squeeze very hard. 

If you don't like your brake pull, just find the tiny 2.5mm? hex-head screw at the base of the lever and adjust as necessary, but that doesn't sound like your problem   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 19:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/DXULqeP.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 00:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out [Skratch Labs](http://www.skratchlabs.com/). I personally know one of the founders, and they make some fantastic products. Definitely head and shoulders above any other drink I've had. They also have other products, but their drinks are their flagship. 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded v=BPBggWHaEK4 t=0

Before I switched over to Skratch, I used Hammer and Clif gels which were alright, but I much prefer having a drink than a gel. Honey Stinger chewies are delicious though. They have some good flavors and if you want to you can just lick and stick them to your handlebars if you don't actually want to stop to eat (I wouldn't recommend that for mountain bikers though, unless dusty chewies are your thing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 23:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean the queue advances by one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 19:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens all the time. We'll be walking and having a wonderful conversation, sun setting over a beautiful landscape of mountains with the clouds aflame while a gentle breeze tousles our hair. A veritable perfect evening. I'll turn to her and lean in for a kiss and suddenly I'll wake up in my bed, alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 07:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you couldn't have sex with him for 2 weeks? 

Bummer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 07:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... the ex-gf and I had a wonderful night alone in a hotel room but she didn't know she was allergic to latex (after 3 months of dating and sex mind you). She reported back with blisters :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 07:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well hello there... I have some candy back in my van if you'll just help me look for my lost puppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the bright side however, in Arkansas it's acceptable to give sexual favors to your cousins to land a sweet Wal-mart job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 04:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mmm... Sacrilicious...](http://paatk.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/sac.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 04:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much, just working and biking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 03:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 15:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand there, fidget around for awhile, then walk over and grab a drink or some food to occupy my time. If prompted, I answer questions as quickly and efficiently as possible. Then I repeat the first two steps until the new human encounter is over. 

I'm a hit at parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that's me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 05:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I'm so pasted right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 23:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool, so you're down in Los Alamos? That's an awesome part of the country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 18:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure do go to Mines! Lately I've been riding trials bikes with him more than unicycles, but it's always a good show when he's got ahold of something with wheels on it. 

Do you go to Mines?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 09:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rad suit, rad-x, rad away, and a rifle for the rad roaches. Boom. Tomb searched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 09:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was riding over all of that water? I've tried waterbiking and it's just not for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 36ers are large and unwieldy, and may the lord forgive you if you pop a tube. 26" would be the largest tire I would ride, but currently I just ride a 20" which is good for both MUni and trials. Since the wheel is small I don't feel the need for a brake, and most of my friends who are big into unicycling don't use them either (I ride with Max Schulze if you've heard of him). 

To answer your other question, I could hop around moderately well at around 3 months in, and I was fairly good at trials at about 1 year of riding. After 3 years I got sponsored (which is surprisingly easy for mountain unicyclists), and the rest is history. Since I started college 4 years ago I've ridden much less, but I still like to hit a trail or two whenever I can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 07:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is. Mountain unicycling is a ton of fun!

Source? This is me.

http://i.imgur.com/pDCrp.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/LkWwh.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 03:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a super exciting concept, I look forward to hearing more about it!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 03:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [sup.](http://26.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lsrnikytPP1r4ws9wo1_250.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 06:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [DEM MOTHAFUCKIN' BOOTLEG FIREWORKS, SHIT!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NRItYDKSqpQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 01:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/LipsThatGrip  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU get a tag! And YOU get a tag! EVERYBODY GETS TAGS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 19:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then when you bring it in for service the tech working on your car will post it on /r/Justrolledintotheshop  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 19:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Kings?](http://fallout.wikia.com/wiki/Kings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 05:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mountain Toad and GCB are where it's at! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have warrantee anymore, it's super easy to fix (and no, don't wrap the damn thing in a towel) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 03:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company makes pumps that Siemens buys. We make Siemens pumps. 

That and stripper feed pumps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 14:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not much anymore. He has aides to do that for him now

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 05:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the mustache. My rifle has one too. 

http://i.imgur.com/LJyDFh.jpg

Whole album: http://imgur.com/a/Pp912#ioeOj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never knew so many people wanted to study the Darwin effect firsthand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 00:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's right there on the internet already. All you need to do is use the wondrous Google  


http://i.imgur.com/TWLWb.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 08:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have exercise-induced asthma, so 99% of the time my lungs fail first. I'm talented at descending quickly and climbing really technical terrain, but every one of my friends can easily pass me on the uphills. 

I feel like an engine running too lean. I work harder and harder until my lungs just overheat and explode, leaving me coughing and jittery on the side of the trail. For this reason I often like riding alone. I can ride slow as shit uphill and save myself for a balls-to-the-wall descent, or I can keep trying an uphill rock garden until I clean it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 04:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a microwaved melon with a hole bored in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 04:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does a condom count as a layer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read you can put liquor in one and take it to work. Fun times in the restroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm digging the frog lube shirt. Great stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 06:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several people have said that airplanes are over-engineered. The safety factors on their frames are around 1.25. Just sayin'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 04:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that if you mimic shaking salt onto your outstretched tongue you can really taste it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 02:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm imagining a screaming, fuzzy penis going "YYEEEHAAAHAAAAHAAAAAAA" as it first enters. Good god why am I laughing so much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 01:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work bringing it up and revitalizing this community! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 20:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of rifle did she buy and why is it so much better than this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 04:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's somewhat acceptable when you're a single freshman in college and you're too hungover to function, but any other time you should at least try and make yourself somewhat presentable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 08:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was planning on killing my cheating no good wife of mine, but I instead chickened out and drank myself into a stupor. It turns out some asshole who was just there to rob my house killed her and her lover that very night and they picked me up for the crime. I tried to plead my innocence, but the evidence wasn't in my favor and I was convicted of double homicide.

The first few days in prison were the hardest, but I made some friends that knew how to acquire certain items from the outside. I had one friend get me a small rock hammer and a gorgeous photo of Rita Hayworth, and I began to dig in secret for years.  In the meantime I managed the prison library and on the side did some tax preparation work for some of the guards. My tax services were very popular, and I was eventually called upon by the warden to help manage the dirty money and bribes coming in from contractors who didn't want to be underbid by the prison's free labor. It was a genius plan, I even created an entirely fabricated persona who controlled all the ill-gotten funds. Over time though, I came to realized the warden was fully aware that I was an innocent man and covered up the evidence that would allow me to be free. For speaking my mind about the matter I was put in solitary for months on end. It was a living hell of isolation and dispair. Something died inside me in there... 

When I finally was released, I told my friend where I would be after I broke out (although I didn't let on that I'd be escaping soon). That night I peeled my poster back and chipped the last few inches through the concrete wall. Luckily there was an extremely loud thunderstorm, so my noises weren't heard. Unluckily for me though, the only way out was through the prison's sewer line. 500 yards. 500 yards of shit I had to crawl through. It was terrible, but I'd crawl for 10,000 yards in a heartbeat just to feel that elation that overcame me when i stepped foot into the cool river running past the prison. 

I cleaned myself up and got myself as far away from the prison as I could. The next day I put on some nice clothes I'd stolen from the warden when I made my escape and made my way to the bank where my fake persona did his business. I cleaned that place out, bought a car, and drove myself down to a beautiful little town in Mexico. But before I finally left, I made sure to mail the details of the Warden's scams and blackmail to all the newspapers around. That motherfucker ended up shooting himself in the head instead of facing his punishment. I just wish I could've been there to see him do it. 

After some time of living in Zihuatanejo, my good friend Red ended up being released on parole and came to visit me! It was the second best feeling I've ever experienced, and we sat around on the beach for hours and talked as only best of friends can. 

So that's my story of false imprisonment, escape, and finally my redemption of Shawshank prison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 08:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I'm in the GoldenCO too. I wish you the very best of luck in your endeavors!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 08:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 wheel (stacked) unicycles are actually quite easy to ride if you know how to ride a normal unicycle, it's just a tad higher up than normal. The really tricky ones are the 2 wheeled unicycles (2 wheels stacked) because when you pedal forwards you travel backwards and vice versa. Total mindfuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 09:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the intense warmth you feel down your esophagus when you take a shot or two of everclear 190 proof. Great for after a long day of skiing or camping! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 14:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those robes get awfully hot after awhile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
