<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3202</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Look at the post again, then at your comment, then look at yourself in the mirror. What do you see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if a certified clean whore invited you to her place to watch movies and eat each other's genitals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if a bang bus with a popular pornstar tries to pick you up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if a married friend started sending you stuff like "treat me like a dirty whore" and "take a pipe and pipe my ass"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Muslim Playing R6S </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, when I'm home alone and naked, I like to do stuff. Dirty stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been wanting to play The Witcher 3 for a while now. Thing is, I've never played a Witcher game before. In fact, I don't know anything about the universe other than he hunts monsters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi reddit! What do you think about fucking her when she doesn't want to fuck you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 10:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if someone you really hate started convulsing in front of you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't put your teammates down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I've played with 2 kind of people . I'm not by any means good at this game, so when I had to clutch it in a 1v4 on Ranked I was nervous as hell. My teammate in that match disagreed with every decision I made, and he let me know of that fact with somewhat strong language- calling me an idiot, a dumbass, ect...

He just was very negative and I ended up dying without killing anyone. But a couple of games later, the same situation arose in a different map, Oregon. This time though, I had a supportive teammate. I knew I made some screw ups, but
 let me know in a friendly manner. He checked the cams, gave me info, and was generally very supportive.  I didn't end up clutching it, but I managed to take 3 of them with me before getting killed by Mira. And we still won 4-2. We can learn something from that: being a standout teammate isn't just about soaking up kills. Sure, the asshole teammate ended up with a bunch of kills, but we lost. While this positive guy ended up negative, he made up for it by providing special support to our team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is the next time you gonna masturbate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you react if a distant hot cousin started sending you dirty pics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you react if a woman squatted on the urinal next to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever it is you have down there, what makes it wet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you know about your parent(s) past that they don't know you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you react if your best friend told you to fill him/her the fuck up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did you do with what you just did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have to consider that since the Saviors were allowing it to happen, then there's nothing any of them could have done to stop it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Americans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
