<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3268</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-28 23:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Let them hate, as long as they fear](http://legacy-cdn.smosh.com/smosh-pit/052011/hater-prime.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-28 21:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My laptop spazzes out and crashes if I watch that video. Repeatedly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-22 00:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tres bien, golden upvote for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mom just told me something very Slendy-esque, she's fucking 52 and knows nothing of Slendy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 23:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lil bit of a back story. I live with my partner but my mum always visits us with my pa, sometimes they stay with us. Their room faces out onto a back yard that then leads onto an ''urban forest'' if that makes sense, trees planted in suburban areas to try and preserve the green belt etc. All that jazz.

Well last night was a usual night, we all went to bed at about 10pm, nothing out of the ordinary as I was working today.

At about 1am in the morning I was woken up by what sounded like stones being ''pinged'' against my window. I was instantly freaked out; my bedroom overlooks a church that has no gravel driveway or indeed anything that could be thrown at the window. 

It went on for about three minutes, a steady tapping that kept shattering the silence that I sat in. Bricks were shat, my friends, bricks were shat.

I managed to muster up the courage to peek out the curtains. As I moved across the bed I woke my partner up, he sleepily says ''that tapping was there last night too...'' 

As I pull back the curtains, I see a streak of... I don't even know what it was. Shadow, I suppose. I see a dark shadow kid of 'blend in' to the darkness. The road outside is lit by dull lights on the church, but this darkness seemed heavy, almost like I was trying to look through deep murky water. This shadow just dissipates into the darkness, I can't compare it to anything because it is unlike anything I've ever seen.

I sat on the edge of my bed looking through the curtains for what seemed like ages. I felt guilty, an unusual feeling like I had intruded on something. I felt cold and isolated...

I manged to settle back into a fitful sleep, punctuated by images of long, thin fingers entwining around my neck, my back, cradling me. I knew what I was experiencing. I knew what it was.

Morning came and fuck... I was scared. I felt afraid. My fear must have hung in the air like a bad smell because everyone seemed to be avoiding me today, tiptoeing around me. 

My mother called me today. Says she had a fucked up dream of a tall, faceless... thing... stood at the end of the bed. Just watching, silently, calculating it's next move. She laughed, says ''he was supremely terrifying, but he was dressed impeccably, in a suit that would not look out of place on a King.''

I know... I have nothing to fear, I know that he's just a fucking figment of over active imagination, but that doesn't stop me from seeing Him stood in the corner, yet when I turn he isn't there. Fuck knows what will happen to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 15:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought Florence And The Machine - Ceremonials. Bought it because it wasn't out on Spotify at the time it was released :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 10:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking hell. It's terrifying. What the fuck is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 22:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must be rather small if you and your penis would fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 10:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This rock thingy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 10:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fell off my chair laughing at this rock thingy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 10:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 10:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is being heard all over the world, if you go to /r/paranormal and look at the top posts you will see similar. Very freaky indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 18:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Properly speak here please grammar ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I respond to facebook ''post this if you care'' posts... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-07 00:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/facebook is awful glum just now. Here's a pic to cheer you up - my take on people who posts statuses asking others to support a dumb cause... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-06 22:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 22:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does bull Semen become like a fine vintage cheese, the longer it is left? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 20:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to school with a guy who openly admitted he cut holes into Teddy bears so he could have his way with them. In our sixth year at school, people were calling him Steiffmaster after Steiff bears. His mom came home one day to find him balls deep in her Steiff.

I often wonder about him now, last I heard he collected mannequins from shops and had them posed all around his house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 19:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Guy Gina has a cute button nose for a hermaphrodite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 19:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck is Good Guy Gina and what has she done with Greg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
