<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9958</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warden if you take the game seriously. Orochi has no offensive capabilities against defensive characters and his defense is laughable. He is a noob killer at best. You will go a lot further with a warden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you nerf that then what do you buff? That's all he has going for him so nerfing that without any significant buffs will just kill the conqueror as a class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. Bs nerfing characters like that. Why not just buff weak ones instead and bring them up to par.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you nerf the conquerors shield bash then you need to buff him in some other ways. The shield bash is really the only thing he has going for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a negative thing or a positive thing? Not sure how you mean that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I've probably played a handful of duel the rest has been Dominion. Just love that moba feel to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm sure there's people out there that play it and somehow enjoy 1v1. Dominion is life though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love revenge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way I despise 1v1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And very true about the ledge. Main reason I hate 1v1. As an orochi against shugoki on maps that favor ledge kills it is very frustrating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. If I'm in a group of 4 why would you take one of my teammates to balance teams? Not a good design choice at all. If you are unbalanced just think that the other time is grouped and separating them is redundant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not your tin can, Viking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just surprised people actually play 1v1 lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree with most. Just think the orochi needs something more. All he can do is parry and deflect but that's a defensive stance. He really has no answer to a defensive character and I think needs a bit more. Maybe make deflection slightly easier to make it more useful? As it stands his light after deflect is trash and his heavy after deflect can still be interrupted or countered even though it shouldn't be.

Edit: I know my suggestions don't help him against defensive characters but it'll at least make his defense somewhat formidable since his offense is a joke once you know their kit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dominion  Elimination  Skirmish  Duel  Brawl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have Walmart internet to disconnect that frequently lol

Oh and 1v1 is shit anyways so who cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't ban because if the developers fault. They should have something in place to prevent this from ever happening in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone pointed out kicking anyone who doesn't leave spawn in a minute. That is good as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True that's good as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well don't speak for everyone. I enjoy Dominion and elimination the most and find duels and brawls to be extremely annoying and shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing Dominion exclusively right now and loving it. I can't stand duels and 2v2 and my connection issues are raw, limited to once or twice a night and I play about 2 to 3 hours nightly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if that's the case it'll atleast stop it from console community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How afk farming can be fixed. Without bans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to say that I understand why people need action. I personally do not experience this really because I play with a full team every night and therefore no one on my team farms, and I think it's mostly in PvE which I never do anyways.

But, I also understand why these farmers do it.
I can't tell you how many messages I've gotten from salty players who are trying a new character, get smashed by my 108 conq, then message me that if they were on their main I would've been killed.

That is the problem right now. With how the game is structured you are punished when leveling a new character because your gear is so low and you get matched up against people with a very high or maxed out GS which means they have plenty of experience with that character.

Now, I also don't find this terrible personally but I can see the argument. 

Instead of Ubisoft warning, then suspending, then banning, which I do not agree with. All they need to do is kick players who do not ready up before a match. This will simply kick anyone who is attempting to afk farm.

TL;DR Just boot anyone who doesn't ready up before a match and you will stop afk farming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is if you want to try a new character you get smashed by 108s and purple's.so the ideal and fun thing to do is play on your main when you're home and then afk farm the new character while you sleep or go to work.

I don't afk farm myself because I personally only like 1 character but for those who like playing multiple this is really their only way without pulling their hair out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gear makes the game fun lol that's probably the only reason I still play lol leveling up with the end goal is strong gear at the end of the tunnel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infront. To my right. To my left. Behind me. Everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what 1v1 seriously I'm so confused. I swear I never see any invisible walls or anything preventing me or anyone from taking part in the 4v4 they queued up for. What am I not seeing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow idk it's the strangest thing. My elimination matches start off where it's 8 people in a 4v4. I mean, that's why I go into elimination anyways to do a 4v4. If I wanted to 1v1 why not just go into duel. So odd. I guess my game is broken because my elimination does not have any 1v1 enforcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then why can I go attack someone else if it's set up for 1v1? I don't understand please explain seriously I'm confused. Every time I play elimination I swear, I guess it's just me, but it's a 4v4 where anyone can attack anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At no point does elimination start with duels. At the start of the fight my teammates and enemies are all around and I can go where I please to get in group fights etc. I'm not sure what elimination you play that start with a duel and then is followed by a 4v4 are you sure you are playing For Honor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but PK has insane fast light attacks that drive any defense insane. The orochi can't do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I like gear stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are more of us than you'd think. After guard break change on console it has been impossible to open up any that turtles up besides feinting which is nice but not unique to the orochi. Other classes have bashes and pushes and charge attacks and unblockables etc to throw at you when you aren't buying the feints. The orochi ONLY has feints. That's not acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes man he can definitely use a buff. At high level play orochi are a joke. They do not have good mix ups and some of his most damaging attacks come after deflects and GB which just get countered anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I mean? Just block and GB and move on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can block is and get a free GB why even complain about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should just go fuck yourself.

*Spams zone attack* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally love revenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the only way they can contain us is 2v1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is great go cry yourself to sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post is so dumb and pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More experience, less fun. Or not. Idk. But more experience, definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or an invalid point. Depends on your angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or an invalid point. Depends on your angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't make it any more invalid either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Titanfall is a point and click shooter. Completely different ball park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not. StarCraft has a great esports scene but no player base. Esports doesn't guarantee increase in playerbase.

They can focus on the esports scene eventually but right now they need to improve the experience for the masses so they can go spread gameplay and word of the game and more and more will play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see it that way.

I see they can cater to the competitive scene and watch their player base dwindle until the esports scene for the game takes off, which is questionable.

Or, they can cater to the majority of the player base which is casual, and have a higher chance of increased player size since more casuals will try and love the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
