<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #3

Two is good for specific concepts, sidequests and such, but is too few for it to be called a classic D D party.  
Four, the classic figure, while perfectly fine in a dungeon crawl, dilutes the spotlight a little bit too much for my comfort.  
Five+ is diablo and not D D.

Three, IMO is the perfect number. It allows for everyone to be involved practically all the time. It allows that characteristic party dynamic to emerge. It allows splitting the party(with two, splitting basically means solo mission). It allows politics and backstabbing(with 2, if there is interparty conflict the game falls apart). Each player's niche gets wider.  
Technically, it allows me to manage the game better and use single monsters effectively, since they're not overwhelmed by the action advantage. It lets me adjust encounters more broadly, since I have more wiggle room with regard to what the party can counter or is weak against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, you made all the correct calls there.

Or at least I'd have made the same ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh. What you describe is not flavour. It's crunch. A mechanical change. It's a house rule. Those need to be disclosed prior to game if the DM wishes to keep his players. Not the way OP found out about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many, many "veteran" DMs have absolutely no clue what the implications of this rule are, and how it affects  
a) the different classes in the game;  
b) the fun of the players forced to abide by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the mark of the newbie DM.

Fret not, 'tis but a phase most DMs outgrow with experience.

Usually this is handled, but not being in the game at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discovered you earlier. Just wanted to say, they're all awesome atmospheric music. Thank you for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck no. I read and respect these things. He had just given none.

We were level 8 or 9 at the final boss battle and we were just charging up the mcguffin to take down the big bad 150ft tall demon. I thought I'd take on the mooks to charge up myself too(funky build). Little did I know, the "mooks" were CR20 themselves. For reference: [this](http://mechanubis.deviantart.com/art/Let-s-do-Doom-pt-11-Spider-Mastermind-354596703) is what I died to. I was 45hp out of 60-something. Thing did 30d6 damage as standard attack. I saved. No evasion tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stormwrack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As party tank, from 75% hp to charred skeleton in 1 second. AFTER I made my save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Know your party is the first step.

It depends. Some parties blindly rush onwards regardless of odds, expecting the DM to adapt or plainly not caring(they're playing a game after all and merely expect the DM to keep his word by delivering that game). Others are more careful and actually engage with the world. For the first one, you as the DM need to warn them, since they don't pay attention to the world.

Out of the others, some need to be forewarned with anything from environmental clues to someone ingame straight up telling them "you can't handle this".

And if you're really lucky, you will have a disciplined, proficient party that you can throw shit at, that they will have the sense to react accordingly to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoying your summer, do ya? You dirty bastards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only half-way through and he's already got it down pat. He must be a prodigy or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does not work 99% of the time due to human psychology.

Rare is the group where multiple people can come together and collectively ignore lifetimes of social programming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amusing in how ridiculous it actually is.

If you wanna see more watch [this numberphile video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wo19Y4tw0l8). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of me playing LoL. Being a noob at it, the only reason I find it enjoyable is because I only play it with friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just gonna list the things I did:

StartIsBack  
OldNewExplorerCfg  
7+TT  
Disable Cortana  
Enable Quick Launch  
I have 2 monitors so I use this the old interface to set my wallpapers: "C:\Windows\System32\control.exe /name Microsoft.Personalization /page pageWallpaper"

The one thing that has actually changed for the better is that I don't need to do the old hack to make explorer open in "My computer" by default, you can now just set it from the folder options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual design is enjoyable. The grunt work is basically slave labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, no.

I installed Win10, then spent a day making it work like 7. There's a bunch of silly little things that are missing, that you never notice until they're not there anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should at least allow group policies to manage that effectively.

It's not the a feature the average user will ever use(exactly the same user who couldn't be bothered to update in the first place). But it will allow the power users, those who know how to operate with technology effectively. What MS is effectively saying is "We trust nobody, not even the power users."

P.S. User stupidity and laziness is basically why defaults are so powerful in the software industry. They should trust that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing I did when I installed win10 for the first time these days - go into every relevant group policy, task or registry entry and disable every update thing there is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work like that some days. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, the novelty of actually portraying hacking with any amount of accuracy faded real quick. By the end of S2 it was just a slog to finish the series for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we have clear visual evidence. I'd say that counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more like meta-archetypes.

Haven't actually read that section in the 5e DMG, but 3.5's DMG2 had a whole chapter dedicated to player motivation, incentives and archetypes. Wouldn't be surprised if 5e's version is a copy or abridged version of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just this artist's specific style.

You can't quite tell a lot either, since the picture is so low resolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm... might I suggest taking a more direct, interventionist approach in a couple of sessions.

Basically... show them how it's done. If you ask them "how do you persuade this person" and they get stumped, take over for them, suggest a method, even take over their character briefly.  
Normally I wouldn't recommend that for a whole slew of reasons(you shouldn't take away player agency, it's not your job to play their characters as well), which is why I suggested to only attempt it once or twice to see if they bite.  
But in your case I believe a little demonstration of what it actually looks like to act a role, to immerse yourself in a fantasy would be beneficial.

If they still don't bite... well, they seem to enjoy being led along the rails. You mentioned they play video games religiously, and most video games are linear experiences, where you are guided along, being subjected to the story, rather than driving it yourself. So offer them the on-rails set-piece action they seem to crave. But do it for yourself, in a way you enjoy.

If that doesn't work for you, well then, I guess it's time to look for a more active group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't know. That's kinda why you ask.

Assuming, one way, or the other is silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which in no way prevents it from being the spiritual sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should watch this movie.

Saw Ex machina. I think this is the spiritual sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting cyriak.

Edit: Nvm, [there we go.](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/5ppyzw/adult_swim_is_at_their_weird_shit_again/dctfhrl/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gMiA8AIX03Q) count as a valid response to this thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Curate a group you enjoy rather than treat DMing like free therapy for the maladjusted.

The secret to true gaming happiness right there.

Not even limited to tabletop. I've ocassionally played a certain online game called League of Legends casually(meaning I was bad at it). Usually with my close friends. A few times I tried it alone. Boy, was I in for a surprise. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, hasn't happened yet.

But I do plan on running a more mature game sometime soon, where all of the macabre things don't actually fade to black. Including sexual stuff, which really doesn't deserve any special treatment in the presence of all the other ugliness. (Frankly I am baffled by why so many people make a distinction. Maybe because it's the most prevalent form of uncomfortable topic that crops up and has become the poster child for all truly grizzly subjects? Dunno...)

Thing is, with these topics, you just gotta make sure everyone's on board, before even starting the game, not just dropping it on players out of the blue mid-campaign. That's what session 0s are for: setting expectations/the tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the most interesting original spell I have is actually the 8th level [Telepathy] psionic power *Mindmeld*. It's exactly what it sounds and allows you to live out your fantasies of being a vulcan in D D.

Most other completely new spells I have are rather boring and just fill gaps in story or mechanics. For example *Flame Pop*, which is the missing fire-based cantrip.

Other than that, the one homebrewed spell that sees most use is permanency.  
Homebrew because we allow it on almost every spell. It acts as an intermediate step between items and duration spells. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a rather potent early-game save-or-die, with a flat, high save DC.

Remove the flat DC fix your templating and wording and it might be okay.

Not terribly OP, but is there a need for MORE save-or-dies? Get more creative, SoDs are a dime a dozen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should provide an awesome background against which the call-to-action can be established. For me at least, this puts me in the proper frame of mind to come up with cool shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 07:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use the [Same Page tool](https://bankuei.wordpress.com/2010/03/27/the-same-page-tool/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 07:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people in this thread seem to suffer from the fundamental attribution error, so I'd like to add a more balanced explanation:

Being a stickler for the rules is but a symptom of the underlying conflict of expectations.

Some of you may be okay with a more free-flowing structure, but I for example, and seemingly this player would be *miserable* in a world where I would be unable to make correct predictions about the outcome of events. We rely a great deal on the rules, to provide a frame of reference upon which we can correctly reason about the world and our character's interactions with it.

Furthermore he simply seems to expect a different style of play that what the rest of you are engaging in. Perhaps he wanted a serious game, where everyone can focus on the immersion of the world, rather than lollygagging around with their characters.

Also, when he says "THE worst gaming group" realize he's speaking strictly from his own subjective perspective. A better expression would probably have been "[...] this is THE most unfun *I've* had in a game [...]". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My critical/fumble system.

Please don't look at me like that, I promise this one is *actually good*, even fun to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan mine like a TV show.

The campaign has multiple seasons(arcs), each of which is a series of episodes(sessions) that eventually come to a climactic resolution, that could easily act as the end of the campaign for all the players know. The motto however is "the rabbit hole is always deeper". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not being a fan of moral absolutism, I tend to view necromancy as merely a tool, rather than some objectively wicked practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the peasant railgun, there's also things like the [Bag of Holding warhead](https://i.imgur.com/Gfq4q.jpg) and the [Voidstone Arsenal](http://www.giantitp.com/forums/showthread.php?480986-The-Voidstone-Arsenal-For-when-you-really-want-stuff-gone).

\*You* are not the first engineers to play this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.d20pfsrd.com/gamemastering/other-rules/called-shots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose everyone is entitled to their own epiphany. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.

This sub's mantra has been "anyone can DM"(along with "talk to people"), but that is simply not true. Most people do not have the drive or presence of mind to take up that mantle and carry it with any amount of the respect or maturity it requires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even gonna pretend I understood that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I like the idea of the Ivory tower. I myself have yet to reach the part where you say it will bite me in the ass, but I sure as heck will try my damnest to avoid that moment.

I do understand your position though. It's about choosing the right tool for the job. That I can afford to engage in the complexity of the ivory tower, doesn't mean everyone can.

And you know... I've seen many people bash the designers of the game, but I think they were fully aware of what they were doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3.5.

Hands fucking down.

Given enough downtime, miniomancy is the boss in that game. And necromancers have one of the best tools for that job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Review and playtest of course. What other way is there? Consulting the crystal ball?

Once you play a particular game system and party enough, it should become fairly obvious what's missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've stayed with 3.5. :D

Chock full of beasties. 5 Monster Manuals, 3 fiendish books, and quite a few other gems scattered throughout various supplements or web enhancements. Also Pathfinder.

Now, as for actually being helpful...

Run monsters with class levels. Have them encounter a greater variety of intelligent and organized foes, who possess much the same resources as they do. Tarrasque with wizard levels and a retinue of monk mariliths should be enough for any party. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the nature of probabilities that it will happen to someone, in some game, in some session.

Congratulations, you are the one and this is the session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Image size. 'Course, it could be the silly reddit image hosting. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, previous ones posted were much bigger.

It's actually kind of a general trend with a lot of art recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does 5e not have the ability to delay your action?

What's up with that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed a trend, that the images keep getting smaller. What's up with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had my character switch genders as part of a deal with some witches once. It was mildly amusing. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great tips... for coming off as a vindictive bastard.

Great GMs we're creating here. Marvellous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even sure what point you're trying to argue...

Maybe I wasn't clear in my post either. I wanted to note that, unless you are a professional game designer, chances are, someone has already done what you are trying to do better. And it behooves one to do their research before pulling things out of their ass.

The fact that the only downvoted post is the one with the rule for holding back with frivolous houserules only seems to reinforce its point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...  the artist has clearly defined the class, the running gag is with the elf's gender. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't suppose the 3.5 free adventures do you any good? I've been tracking those down, since they disappeared from the WotC website. Got a few missing, after which I'll sort them out and put them up for download. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever seen minority report?

You just need better organization and a good prefetch routine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, you mean [THIS](https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/elfwood--artwork/5d9ec440-2715-11e4-9ecf-d547aae57bd2/the-bard-and-the-beholder.jpg)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That leaves 0% for obstacles that don't have HP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed almost all bad house-rules arise from a misunderstanding or lack of knowledge of the rules already present.

Therefore I have sort of a cardinal meta-house-rule: Never introduce a house-rule for anything, unless you've thoroughly checked and found that a certain situation is not covered, even marginally by something already published. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This only helps with combat-heavy games, where dealing damage is a significant part of a character's contribution to the party.

Martial's problems, and conversely caster's strength has always been versatility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, I provide guidelines and welcome any such addition. Just as the story is a collaborative exercise, so too can worldbuilding be. More input certainly makes the world a more lively place than one single mind can ever dream up.

For example: This here is an archipelago nation of trader gnomes. They're known for this, this and that. Their culture is broadly such and such.
This over here is a nation of nomads, who roam the steppes, value freedom, honor, etc.

Everything fits somewhere. If it isn't in the guidelines/world overview, you just ask and we find a place to put it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Blaz's style. Very soft.

In more ways than one(he likes to draw his chubs). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) Is this your alt?  
b) Yes, I thought you were referring to the player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, this is one case of the reversies:

Don't solve ingame problems with out-of-game solutions(i.e. kicking him out).

There is no douchiness here, just a great opportunity for roleplay, provided the party has the presence of mind to pull it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once a game starts, the **DM has the authority** to qualify their alignment.

I'm pretty sure saying "you're now chaotic good/evil" is pretty easy. Problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this today. Removed the fuck out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Old D D has its roots in wargaming.  
It was about a very specific style of play - get your 10-foot pole and bag of sand and in the dungeon you go. It was a puzzle to solve. The whole "wide world", "character-driven" and narrative bits came later.
- It didn't focus on good vs evil, rather law vs chaos.
- AD D specifically had lots of interconnected material, something that changed drastically with 3e, where you needed only the core books to play with any supplement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lovecraftian horror disguised as a sweet kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I let it write itself.

I'm not kidding.

I've got a specific world with specific values, magic and race distributions and I have a few major plot points/tensions.  
Then I put all the actors over here and have them run through the stage to their goals.  
The campaign opens up with a classic call to action based on the PCs backstories. I never do "chosen by the gods" however, unless the character is specifically focused on his divine devotion. More of a fan of the "chosen by fate/circumstance", since that allows more freedom.

That is the abstract method, the minutiae are another matter entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No contrived excuses. Either have a good one, that advances some story in the game, skip the session or someone else gets to play that character(mostly for combat scenarios). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she was just trying to fit in... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing to do is acquire some funds.

Then since I don't age, I'd sleep, shit, eat and learn all with time stopped.

In a century or so of me-time I'd be a genius. Cue my best Ozymandias impression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 16:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, one of them is into the same thing as me, the others are pandered to by other aspects of the game.

The beautiful thing is, due to the extreme prevalence of the cliches, especially the idea of human-dominated worlds, no one really misses them. Reactions range from *"Meh"* and *"Sure, I'd be okay with a change in scenery"* to *"Finally some diversity"*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, in all latest editions humans have been some of the most mechanically sound choices, from 5e's variant human to the general utility of an extra feat in 3.5/PF's version, among other things. It's just that having the world be human-centric is a particular pet peeve of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they overlap? :)

My dream setting is a monster-heavy world, where as a player I could play all sorts of unconventional characters and leave the boring elves, generic dwarves and god-awful humans behind me for good.

As a DM it's arguably even more fun, as I get to subvert every tired old D D cliche and trope that's accumulated through the years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'm not sure if it will be case sensitive and not catch words that have that as a substring as well. I know regex, so this was the easiest way to tell it to do exactly what I want.

Also, by definition I can't notice false positives, since they'd be filtered out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> filteReddit won't filter keyword regex in r/all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Chrome Version 55.0.2883.87 m (64-bit)
- RES v5.2.2
- reddit beta: no

*Example:*  
[res filter not working](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/8262590/21739070/64c8ad60-d499-11e6-8145-5791f3e34ae0.png)  
This is **/r/all** btw.

Anything obvious I might be missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cuz you weren't trying.

Besides, it's the next level that you really want - shadows, allips and [TDC](http://archive.wizards.com/default.asp?x=dnd/fw/20040221a). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a european thing, not just german. We got it here too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cuz it is one. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it ain't special anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While we're on the subject, here's some more relevant reading:

http://arstechnica.co.uk/science/2016/11/revisiting-why-incompetents-think-theyre-awesome/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I understand your player, as I'm probably the same. She seems to approach her character builds as puzzles to solve. If you indulge her, then a thank you on behalf of all of us who enjoy that aspect of the game.

Since we're talking unofficial, I personally allow that feat to straight up reduce the effort it takes to wield a weapon, since it opens many new options, without unduly increasing the power of the feat(i.e. using 2H weapons of your size as 1H or 2H weapons of +1 size as 2H).

By itself however, RAW especially, the feat is not that noteworthy. It can however be both superceded or combined with Strongarm Bracers or the Powerful Build racial ability of Goliaths, if one really wants to go all-in on the big-ass weapon style.

And if you allow the expanded version, a character could potentially feasibly dual-wield 1H weapons(albeit with an additional -2 penalty for the offhand, due to the feat), like say, scimitars.

My personal assessment is that if a feat can be one-upped by a 6K item, then it is in dire need of some buffing(the norm for an average feat is 10K gold, as per A EG). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In older editions(read:3.5) creatures between you and your target provide (soft) cover for it.

In general there is no other specific limitation for fighting in small spaces. Freedom in the spaces you occupy is all that is required for effective combat.

And while we're on the subject, same deal with wings. If a character has wings, it's hardly concievable that a 5-ft space(for a medium creature) is enough for them to function effectively, but nothing in the rules prevents them from providing flight normally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, both you and she need to familiarize yourselves with the concept of the SRD. Which is, in essence, the "official content". All the popular places for D D rules have such content clearly marked.

Second, your refererence to "OP character" makes me think you are a new DM. If you'll allow me one tip: As a DM you should strive to make damage the least of your worries. There are far worse ways in which the game may be broken, 3.5 especially, than a character's raw(not even applied) damage numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This issue exists outside the game. You are trying to bring outside issues into the game. It never works out well.

The point is, you are human. You might not think of something or make a mistake. If the players out-think you, do not deny them the satisfaction. Let this one go, and try to catch them off-guard with another scenario. Trying to forcibly preserve your precious moral dilemma is likely to bring them out of the game and cause them to resent you, the person, instead of the actors in your world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH a 1d6 increase in damage in the best case seems rather lousy returns for an entire feat. The notion of swinging anime-style oversized weapons notwithstanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure where you're getting these other versions, but I've seen only one in the books. And it is quite restrictive(and could stand to be less so).

It also deals with sort of a "hidded statistic" of DnD - weapon *effort*. Instead of reducing the *effort* to wield a weapon by one step, it only specifically allows you to wield a weapon one size category larger than you with the same effort. The vagueness of the concept and it's overzealous specificity make it a trap choice in most cases, barring certain very focused builds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks better than shots big movie studios spent millions on not 5 years ago.

Mostly on account of the 60fps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 15:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, that one was odd. Better off sticking to game-related content.

I don't know about the "god ideas" thing. I think the assumption is, the audience can see past that and think for themselves. And I too have my fair share of disagreements with some of the stuff they do. Once, I disagreed with a video they made so much I stopped watching EC for a year. I don't dispute the "mixiness" of the bag, but over the years I learned to simply ignore the blatant silliness and take only what is valuable. I think that's the best way to approach that series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm a bit behind the curve here(I'm -1 year or so on EC), but they've delivered both entertaining and insightful videos on a pretty consistent basis. Besides, they've never been about the technical side of game design, if that's what you're referring to.

What I do find irritating is PBS's Game Show. It started out promising way back when. But very soon after all the politics and PC bullshit got old real fast. By the time I unsubscribed I honestly couldn't stand that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's even more amusing when you figure out that the video doesn't end with an ad for audible or some such western youtuber shit, but advertises some russian football betting site! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need this in my life!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One can only hope. After all who wouldn't want to have all the free time for nothing but hobbies and never even bother with working for their livelyhoods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. The future is here. This is the kind of thing's we're gonna start seeing with proper AI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured it out actually. Look [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/starcraft/comments/5kkpc3/how_do_i_place_a_desktop_shortcut_for_mass_recall/dbooc4u/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I figured it out on my own with some tinkering.

1. Go to "*SC2Folder\Support64*" folder(or just *Support*) if you only have the 32 bit version of SC2.
2. Make a shortcut of *SC2Switcher_x64.exe* wherever you want your Mass Recall shortcut to be.
3. Go to the "*SC2Folder\Maps\Starcraft Mass Recall*" folder, hold shift and right-click on "*SCMR Campaign Launcher.SC2Map*". Select "Copy as path".
4. Go to your shortcut and go to Properties. At the end of the Target field add a space and paste what we copied.
4. [Optional] If you noticed, the mass recall map folder had another file in there, an **.ico** file. While still in the shortcut properties, click the "Change Icon" button and navigate to that **.ico** file.
5. ???
6. Profit. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The latest guide video said you just launch the hub map in the editor and press "Test document".

But I had it installed before when Legacy of the Void and I had a direct launch shortcut for that map from somewhere. Now with my system drive having exploded, obviously that is gone, among other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
