<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9425</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 19:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was today, was doing my SL5x5, but havent done it in two weeks because ive been cycling. Gym doesnt have a bar rack, right arm gave way on bench press, dropped it on my neck with 55kg on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your biggest "Oh Fuck" moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 19:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was a time you screwed up really badly when exercising? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, from what I've heard and read, time under tension does not effect muscle growth in any way. So, why are planks so effective, because is t that exercise just time under tension? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pins and needles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 23:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, so for the last two weeks I've  cycled 24 km to work and back every week day (12 there 12 back). Ever since I started ice noticed that in constantly been getting pins and needles. I have lost 2kg in the last month.
Could cycling be the cause, or am I paranoid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im trying to get lean and toned for the summer, but since ive been late for work getting the bus, I decided to start cycling. Its not far 11km, but as someone who isnt speciallised in cardio, its super tough. Last week was my first week, and on wednesday i was a little late because i wasnt prepared for the fatigue, and got so much shit for it. Also they knew i was supposed to be eating high amounts of protein, now i get shit for eating carbs and less protein.
Point is, I'm the healthiest person where I work, and everyone else is trying to determine how I eat, and give me shit for trying to cycle in and get to work early. Pisses me off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 22:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily condoms are free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SL 5x5 assistance exercises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey people; just wanted to know, what assistance exercises do you do with 5x5 and what returns the best results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does alcohol affect fitness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 01:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So tonight I had a house party and of course, at a house party I decide to drink, cos why the hell not. What effect does alcohol have on fitness levels. I n or that the sugar in those drinks has a ridiculous amount of sugar, and doesn't do too well for the liver but what other effect does it have? I will be exercising tomorrow st the gym, as I've cycled about 120km over 5 days, and only gymmed once. But yeah sorry about the shitpost just needed to ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does alcohol affect fitness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 01:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 00:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the last day of the week and I pushed my self a bit, got to work in 30 minutes which was nice. I left super early so I got to work early. At work had to climb stairs like 10 times nearly fell down three so I said I'm not going upstairs. Was very tired in my quads and almost fell asleep ahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 18:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my bike is definitely not 3-4kg, although it feels that light picking it up, it's probably around 12-14kg, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice on cycling everyday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 01:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there; firstly I'd like to start by saying I know it isn't healthy to exercise everyday, but hear me out.
So for the pas couple months I've been getting the bus to work, doing so is very unreliable as I've been late a solid 80% of the time. So this week I said no, I'm going to cycle because I can get to work quicker; and it's true, it takes about 20 minutes less. Anyway, I don't have too far to travel; only 10-12 km depending on the route I take; but to work it's about 35% downhill to 50% uphill and 15% flat. Even then, the hills aren't massive, but they are unavoidable.
So this morning when I cycled to work, it took about 15 minutes longer as my quads were exhausted. What techniques do you have to overcome this?
I'm using a road bike, nothing special, but it's about 3-4kg I think, so it's not much to push. I have to carry extra work clothes and showering stuff so it's about an extra 10kg on my back.
Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 18:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reason I work out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 14:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im really not squatting much, 30kg on top of the bar. Getting the bar to my chest isnt a problem, its the jerk bit after that causes issues sometimes. Im just worried about when i begin to do 50-60kg and i wont be able to lift it :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5x5 Without rack technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 23:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, so the other day I posted something about how I dont have a bar rack at my gym. For exercises such as the squats, to lift the bar above and behind my head I have been doing a clean and jerk; Is this okay? it puts a lot more effort into doing the squats, and makes it a little hard to keep correct form. If not, i could use dumbbells, whatever is necessary really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SL5x5 IAP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 12:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was waiting until today, payday, to buy the 7.99 power pack IAP. So I bought it, and I only got charged 1.58, and had the full package, anyone else have this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 17:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went from not having much to having about one and a half chicken breasts a day and a can of tuna. I would eat pasta as well so I'd get my carbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 15:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking dieting! I tried to start a high protein diet so I can bulk up a bit, lasted one week and I get people having a go at me for not eating high protein. I've ended up making two protein shakes a day. But it's not me I'm pissed off at, it's the others! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 09:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like me except I'm 76kg (168lbs?) tryna get to 70kg before I get lean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 23:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fitness = happiness :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your endgame goals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 23:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As title says, what are your endgame goals, and why are you going for that goal?
Edit: I never put a goal myself, but I'm an 18 y/o male going on holiday in 24 weeks, so I'm working hard to get a good body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 19:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other gyms but this one is the most convenient to go to, it's 10 minute walk from home and it's on my way home from work. I could try to use the smiths as a bar rack :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5x5 with smiths machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, so my gym doesn't have a bar rack but they do have a smiths machine, would I still be able to do the 5x5 program with it, or is there no point. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 09:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, super combat potions; Mage, range primarily, you can make them and they're super cheap. Buy a couple thousand supplies and don't forget to use scroll of cleansing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 17:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When doing dumbbell chest presses, or any chest presses, make sure the weight is directly above your elbow at all times. Don't be tempted to lean in a bit of lean outward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 13:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that impressive, but I havent had to use my asthma pump at the gym for two weeks now. (I have exercise induced asthma) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 12:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not the point, they've buffed the oyster so in february, well get better rewards. plus why would you want to use a dnd reset on a medium clue, when u can use it on god statues or invasion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrack guides? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 10:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'm looking for a decent arraxi guide. I went in there a couple times and I die when i get to the poison puddle bit. I don't know what the paths are and what's the best.
I have t80 range; magic; and melee weapons, and have the t70 gwd armours to suit. Maxed combat and herblore.
I'm not that wealthy, I find it quite difficult to hold onto money.
Is there a good beginners guide to arraxi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 22:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add cel sharing like in borderlands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Text] The only way humans have figured out of getting somewhere is to leave something behind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 22:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newton's third law, paraphrased in the movie interstellar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a good workout routine to become a mesomorph? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 20:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, so I'm an 18 year old male; I did sport studies at GCSE and began to do A level sport studies. During my A Levels I stopped exercising and lost what could be described as the ectomorph/mesomorph build. I wasn't ripped or anything like that.
 Anyway, I don't know what I did to get there, but whatever I did I enjoyed it. I used to workout with my mate, and us being 15/16 was focused on lifting, which, yeah it helped, but we had a routine. In the end I lost that routine and began to decline in fitness.
 I've been watching a lot of Joe Weller (British youtuber) and he has the type of build that I'm aiming for. I know it's not an overnight thing and it may take a good year before seeing some results.
These are some rough numbers
  6"0 tall
  85 kg
  15% body fat
  Can run at 13 kmh for about 5 minutes
  Can lift about 9 kg Dumbbells and do a fair amount of exercise
  Can bench about 35kg
  Can't row
  Can cycle

I also have asthma which is why my long distance running is not so good. I am earning, but after payouts I only get about 200 of which I'm going to start using on a healthy diet, as I currently just eat anything. I will buy a kg of whey protein to repair the muscles after a good workout
 I absolutely love going to the gym, every time I'm there I try my hardest to the point of nearly being sick.
What is a good workout routine and eating routine for the goals that I want to get. I know I wasn't very specific about what I want to achieve.
Will post pictures if needed
Thank you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need Cheap build - UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 17:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I live in the UK and am looking for a new computer, so i thought, why not build one. I dont earn a lot of money, currently 660 per month, since I'm only an apprentice. So what I'm looking for is a build that costs around 200 - 250. I dont *need* any keyboard or mouse, but it would be nice.
What im looking for is a computer that can run a game like BL2 on the normal settings, without dropping below 30 fps.
Im currently on an HP 2022UK and it is just awful when it comes to games.
Im not planning on buying every component right away, because i simply cant afford it, but my next payday is on christmas eve, so hopefully i can get the more expensive parts around then.
So Im just looking for a build that costs around 250, and can run games such as Borderlands 2 smoothly, on regular settings. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's just nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dreadnips/gloves - Fastest way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 22:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone, what bosses are the easiest, or what is the best strategy to getting Dom gloves and dreadnips. I've maxed combat, but haven't  actually got any of that yet. I don't have t90 except for drygores, and I will be using war priest as it is hybrid. But what bosses, or strategy is the easiest, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 01:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck do I lose my money so quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 13:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're a member, just do slayer, if not then go kill lesser demons, iirc they're the best f2p xp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bananas cure cancer... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 23:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
