<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject966</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just waiting for someone to say Family Guy so they can lay into them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That dog cares very little about the winter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a beautiful place to receive the devil's verdict  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the most elegantly quaffed Nutella I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by the aura radiating from the top of the picture, this was taken the exact moment he descended to our planet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing my luck, it will become a handpick during some unfortunate mishap  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legislation should be made to prevent Google, Time-Warner and Disney from getting any bigger. Their combined influence is on the same level that past monopolies have been.  And since corporations are now people, thanks to Citizens United, the average persons voice is less than it's ever been. Fuck Google for thinking that having that much influence is an okay thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's MY HEAD, SCHWARTZ!! I'll see you in court! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see Samuel L Jackson walking a naked man through that field at gunpoint, just let it happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I camped overnight there once. Just hung up your ENO hammock and hoped I didn't get robbed or raped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Springs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only 25 here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misleading? The rural roads look exactly the same. I live in a rural area and travelled to town where I took the pic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the answer for any amount of snow has always been to just wait it out till it melts. I only know of one plow/salt truck in town. They almost anticipate the towns inability to function when we have winter weather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sheets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably will here soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the amount of salt trucks in the area is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How little snow it takes to cancel school in Arkansas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those that don't know what Ryan Air is, it's a discount airline where the flight attendants are broke students, which sells cigarettes and lottery scratches on the plane and regularly have drum circles form in the middle of the plane. If you ever fly it, do yourself a favor and get a seat in the back of the plane so you can watch all the festivities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arkansas won't cut you off, but we'll do 10 under the speed limit in the passing lane and won't move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you don't have access to an iron, you can steam/soften the wrinkles out by throwing your clothes in yhe dryer with a fabric softener and a wet washcloth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound a bit obese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Cretan-style gyro with tzaziki, fresh fries, chicken, red onion, and tomato </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you find raisins in a package labeled "grapes," don't  eat them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is her campaign platform more belly rubs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vaporizers. You end up spending tons more just using cheap ones till they break. I prefer Storz-Bickel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone mention weed yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am me.  I am the beginning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd make a hell of a salesman, with that deal-shakin' hand 'a his </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McCain's policies are terrible, however, look up the amount of torture that John McCain endured for the sake of America's existence. He was on the USS Forestall when it had a mishap that changed the way the Navy does business, forever.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how she smelled his junk to make sure he was him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pigeon will "fly" the human soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's had a long night and he hates the fucking Eagles, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely real. Let that sink in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The conditions in my sister's windowsill support the growth of plant life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banana was to add some healthy sweetness and to mellow out the sriracha. And I won't food sext the particulars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 03:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe

2 dozen wings
1 really ripe banana
1/4 cup of Sriracha 
Salt and pepper to taste
Juice of half a lime
1/2 a cup of pickle juice

Wash wings.  Place in container with pickle juice and allow to brine in fridge for at least one hour.  

Remove peel from banana. Remove chicken from fridge and drain remaining juice. Place dried wings and banana in smoker. Allow chicken and banana to smoke for half hour between 225-275F. After one hour, remove banana and allow wings to become crispy to preference. 

Place banana and Sriracha in food processor. Pulse until smooth. 

Remove wings from smoker and toss wings in sauce. 

Eat them all by yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Hickory-smoked wings topped in a Banana Sriracha sauce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 03:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The grim reaper should really chill out on his quotas this year... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BUDS dud Merkel i.e. HM3 Merkel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you are being down-voted by idiots. You are exactly right.

To OP: This would be similar to him giving you his report card from middle school. It just means he didn't get any NJP or court martials...basically, other service members from his day and age would probably give him shit for not "having a good time"

Thank your grandfather for his service for me. He truly served in the last valiant war, if war can ever be such a thing. Just know that your grandpa is either a goodie-goodie or just really good at not getting caught having a good time.

For example: I had a great time. I was in the Navy eight years and I only received one good conduct. I had a good time. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 00:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume a quiditch would be easier to catch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7-year-old Me doing a hell of a Great Cornholio impression (1996) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Pierce found out about Reddit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was stationed in Japan for two years on an aircraft carrier there.

If people dont think Japan can handle itself doesn't know their history.
 
US forces don't need to be there because they don't need to have their military force constitutionally restricted anymore. Japanese nationalism is no longer radicalized.

They deserve to be able to have the same defense capabilities as us and they deserve to fight for their own liberties. 

The continuance of forward-deployed American combat forces has to come to an end, as it holds back the intended influence of the UN.

A Trump-Mattis duo is far more dangerous a proposition than Japan calling their own shots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If cigarette company's should be forced to put the vile effects of their product on their labels, fast food companies shouldn't be allowed to have skinny people in their advertising </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. He seems sassier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a Democrat or a Republican, find a third party you most agree with and change your registration to that party. It's not a vote...more like a negotiating tactic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up the USS Pueblo. It's a US surveillance ship that was captured by North Korea in the 60s and is still in their possession and on display in Pyongyang  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We like to hide death from children, but I'm pretty sure never seeing death as a kid makes people overly mournful when a loved one passes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 06:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone's ever called Rowdy Ronda a pussy before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 06:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cone of shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 10:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically it's 85, the first year counts for 8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 09:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and a buddy had a dance party with booze, house music and were wearing sailor hats.  Someone knocked on my door and I answered it with a big dumb smile on my face (I thought it was more guys) to see my landlady and her chuckling husband.

Now that I think about it, the husband actually died a month later. Him and my father are two people who I think went to their grave thinking I was probably gay

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 09:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunni-Delight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This man has never seen a bukkake video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dems disenfranchised most of their voter base this election cycle. Not too sure what you mean there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or wise-cracking blind guy with a big, scary dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ellen Degeneres taking a solo selfie? Wouldn't be authentic without a guy that looks like Bradley Cooper or a girl that looks like Lupita Nyong'o. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ain't no party like a snow day party! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternate Headline: Bewildered Birds Break Bad For New Nest Egg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just called poor planning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to see some politically themed chocolate that's nut-free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would probably be the only time I would pin-prick some condoms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the cats are more interested in the strumming motion of his hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ritz on top of Ritz. This is a Mitch Herbert special edition Ritz  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men of Reddit: who among you has tried romantic comedy hijinks in order to attempt to win the girl; what was the end result? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a very good chance none of the athletes will survive this match, Cotton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe for Moon Moon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 06:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just in: Vice Admiral in Charge of Nuclearized Fleet"s DickSl Still World's Largest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 02:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the scene above is from the Westworld movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
