<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4083</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opposite impression here.  There was enough flashing of that Subaru logo that I wondered how much they coughed up in production costs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Spacey, Jon Hamm, *Flea* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M3 has a smaller engine as well IIRC.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preordering games in 2017 is for people of questionable character.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  I finally stopped by to check them out in person.  Much better looking than in pictures.  I still dislike the :- look of them but oh well, everything else is great.  The vents look fantastic when looking out from behind the wheel and the B pillar isn't nearly as obstructive as I expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Production quality is fine for a first vid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a good car for the money especially used ones

I've seen some used 2011 S550s for around 25k, depending on mileage.  Tend to be pristine due to being a grandpa car.  Just lacking a bit in the tech goodies I'd want.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue with turbo lag in slightly older cars isn't so much as the turbo lag being the problem but the slower automatic transmission.  It sometimes takes about a second to shift from high gear down to low, and then maybe a half second to build up enough RPM to get that turbo torque.  That's what you feel the most and is the biggest problem.  

MB's 7 speed auto suffers from this.  The newer 9 speed is a bit smarter and quicker.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  not the point of selling cars.

I guarantee you that everything they do is to sell more cars.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FCA doesn't need the Mito since they have the Fiat.  I'm not terribly upset that the hatchback didn't make it over immediately but I imagine it will come eventually if the Giulia and Stelvio pick up the brand enough for them to start pushing more into the market.

I really wish they'd have brought over the 8C though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I just don't understand the point.

People like to buy them thus they make more money thus they stay in business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it different from the US Spec'd C Class?  That engine is a work horse.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly this is the case.  Though isn't the A Class also FWD based?  If so, not missing out too much in the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a manual transmission so there is no dedicated neutral so instead you slot between 1st and 2nd.  So assuming he did that but the important part is that the Porsche e-brake is "reversed" from other brands.  In my two Mercedes you pull the e-brake lever under the steering wheel towards you to turn it off, push to turn it on.

Guy in the video forgot about that (new Porsche).  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here own a 2014 and up MB CLS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious how these drive considering they lack a Sport + mode. I've never driven one and all of the MB' I've driven, Sport mode by itself was basically Comfort +, Sport + a requirement.


C300 has Eco/Comfort/Sport/Sport +.

CLS has Eco/Sport/Manual

Sport mode in C300 is worthless. I'm curious if the Sport mode in the CLS is the same as the Sport mode in the C300. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C300 has Eco/Comfort/Sport/Sport +.

CLS has Eco/Sport/Manual

Sport mode in C300 is worthless.  I'm curious if the Sport mode in the CLS is the same as the Sport mode in the C300.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about how you play the game.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a Queen themed action adventure game that took 11 years to develop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you don't want there to be a turbo model because you're self conscious about people seeing you with a "base model"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What have you been doing specifically that you have learned better?  Just curious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guarantee you that parents will snatch the hell out of their kids for various reasons.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't, but I rarely every see slab bacon offered anywhere other than boutique shops.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non AMG models.  They're the ones lacking Sport +.  Just wondering if the Sport mode in these is analogues to Sport + in, say, a C300.

Sport mode is unnecessary in the C300.  If Sport Mode in the CLS is basically the same thing, my interest in that model is pretty much killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, and that's generally the whole reason you have the Japanese luxury brands and why Hyundai has the Genesis line.  

"I want space and comfort without the German tax and maintenance".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncut uncured "bacon" is just pork belly, which has an amazing amount of uses.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GOWFlp0M7QM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your tag doesn't say ASSMAN I'm not interested.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and no I have no idea what that means.

I had regularly encountered people who wanted their slaw microwaved or grilled so it would take some of the crispness out of it.  IE, they wanted it to taste bad.

These people would also ask us to pull our house chips from the fryer early so they were "soggy".

I hated these people.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wife thought quality cars were pointless until she drove one.  Then she took my C300.  But that meant I got to get me something even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible it's the rumored update to the S660? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jacked up F150/1500/Silverado/etc with a "These Colors Don't Run" or equivalent sticker on the back.

Usually bad drivers, probably bad people.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I make Portland jokes?  

I just want a cup of joe and a side of dough.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its already a thing in Portland, OR.

Gonna be hitting up either Portland or Seattle near years end.  If I end up in Portland I'll look for it, or maybe PM you for a name if you don't mind.

My favorite Thai place here has a section of the menu specifically reserved for Southern/Eastern Cambodian/Laos/Vietnam influenced Thai food and its awesome.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meat Popsicles?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving dynamics of the CLS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious how these drive considering they lack a Sport + mode.  I've never driven one and all of the MB' I've driven, Sport mode by itself was basically Comfort +, Sport + a requirement.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NP.  Some folks care a bunch about engine sounds, and that's fine.  But if you care about performance, eventually the v8 and big block v6 is gonna have to go.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My previous car was a 4300 pound Hemi that was awesome and while I consider tracking one down again, the C43 has been a significantly more fun and more agile car to drive.  Other than the Hemi being a station wagon, the C43 seems to be significantly more usable in day to day situations. 


edit

And the C43 has a much better transmission compared to the C450/C300.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see this article for a couple of reasons.  1 The Switch is being used as intended, that being a portable console that also has local multiplayer capabilities.  2 Adoption in a market that increasingly has less and less to do with consoles or local multiplayer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nintendo Switch Makes Its Japanese Classroom Debut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edit: so what should I have done? Like grab the piece of food myself, then put it on her plate? Because I'm not bad with chopsticks, but there were some slippery foods.

If this were at a restaurant that has those "lazy susan" type round tables, which has been my experience 100%, you just spin the plate back in front of the mother and insist.

But don't blame the girl either.  Judgemental Asian Parents are impossible to please.  If they so deem it there will not be any correct behavior.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only white people who get mad at white people jokes are those who know they do the thing the joke is riffing on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   "you're supposed to eat first"

Bzzzzt.  You're offered to eat first, but the etiquette is that you then take what is offered to you and insist on lao ma enjoying it before anyone else. 

Also while you can use your chopsticks to grab food from communal dishes, absolutely do NOT pick through it.  Grab one thing and grab it quickly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To me that comes across as "You're not giving it back if it breaks down on the way home."


Completely reasonable given what you're buying.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than the commercials they're riffing on for sure, but still a bit silly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1988 535is

 1991 535i

 1996 328is

 1998 M3


I find this kind of funny.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like convertibles/targas/soft tops, FYI.  



1989 Ramcharger Soft Top

1991 Wrangler Soft Top

1995 Jeep Grand Cherokee

1997 Chrysler Sebring Convertible 

2002 Chrysler PT Cruiser Convertible

2003 Mitsubishi Eclipse

2005/2006 Dodge Magnum SRT8

2015 Toyota Prius IV

2015 Mercedes C300

2017 Mercedes C43 Cabriolet



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commute in my city is a mother fucker and I got tired of being worn out by it every morning and afternoon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couple hours, tops.

Drive one well?  I dunno, it just eventually clicked.  And then I stopped buying them... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything produced in Norway that uses corn products will see a price increase.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, yeah, I figured it wasn't the same thing, but that's usually what I think of when I see this type of syntax.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you also told it to bridge vlan 24 on bridge0 and you also setup bridge0 to bridge vxlan traffic?

R1 to A is already a trunk so any vlan 24 traffic will be broadcast out that trunk link as well so that's why no config change is needed on A/C.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly with the likes of Bourdain talking it up, I imagine Vietnamese and Thai are next on the list for getting the hipster treatment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you made no configuration changes on R1 and R2 how would they know to listen in on that multicast group?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  By the way, how do you like the C43? I've heard it's a fantastic car, but I've also read it doesn't feel quite as powerful as you expect an AMG to be.

If you're coming from a C63 then yeah, you'll notice it.  However, I wouldn't get too worked up over it not "feeling quite right".  People complain about that since the industry has gone from NA 8 to forced induction sixers.  C43 is a fast enough car, you're only gonna miss out on torque and that v8 sound.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being able to find parts, mostly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Korilla and the Bob and Jo Korean food trucks are fantastic.  There's a good Trinidad food truck in the financial district that I really dig as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So R1 and R2 uses the bridge0 interface to carry the vxlan traffic, which is forwarded across the proper routers due to the multicast group?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  C43 4matic Cab, C300, Prius IV

Check the flair.  Affordability isn't really an issue.  ;)

But I'd rather drive it more than it sits in a shop.  Or not risk getting stuck on the side of the road like my buddy does every other month with his older Lotus.

I make a 700 mile trip back home once or twice a year and would want to take it with me on at least one of those.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Verts

They started here in my city and are all over the place.  They do have some quality falafel.  

We had actually gotten a MOD clone here (Blazin') before we even got MOD.  Both which I like because they tend to be cheaper and smaller portions and have decent quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't jack shit about Linux Routing so I'm gonna ask some I Don't Know Jack Shit comments to figure this out.  Please forgive me.

 set interfaces ethernet eth0 vif 30 address 10.7.50.5/24

Performed on R1 and R2.

This tags eth0 with vlan (virtual interface?) tag 30 with the ip address of 10.7.50.5.  You essentially did the same thing on R2 but instead changed the IP to 10.7.50.6.



 set interfaces bridge br0

 set interfaces ethernet eth0 vif 24 bridge-group bridge br0

Performed on A and C

Top command creates the bridge0 interface and the bottom command associates the eth0 interface with vlan tag 24 as well as bridge0.


Now these commands:

 edit interfaces vxlan vxlan0

 set bridge-group bridge br0

 set group 239.0.0.241

 set vni 241

These are run on both A and C.  Why do you use edit interfaces instead of set for creating the vxlan interface?

Wouldn't you also need to run the above commands on R1 and R2 as well to bridge the virtual layer 2 doman across R1 and R2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have two absolutely exceptional Thai places that I frequent here.  Would love to see some more open up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burmese food is pretty good judging by that tea leaf salad I had recently in SF.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texas.  Ramen is just now starting to roll out here over the past year or two.  Poke as well.  What do you think is gonna be the next fast casual fad?  

I don't care much for burritos but I love me some ramen so I'm good with the ramen craze.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy has a 2013 BMW M3 Convertible for sale locally.  45k miles, asking 37k for it.  I'll get a PPI and all done if I really do want to bite, but I've heard that these v8 M3's are one of the least reliable cars that BMW put out.

Thoughts?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I've noticed while travelling around lately. The Next Big Fast Casual Restaurants are gonna be Poke themed and Ramen themed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a revelation to me but maybe you all knew it already.  Seems like right around the time I saw a Chipotle or two pop up we suddenly had three or four competitors within six months.  

Now the same is happening with Poke and Ramen.  

The best thing is when you get local places that jump in with a similar offering to compete as well.  Though we had a home grown ramen place here first and now we have Jinya opening up and two others (Agu and one more chain I can't recall).  Same with Poke.

We even have a local Panda Express clone here called General Tso'boy which basically adds sandwiches to the menu.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How well do the old Galaxie's hold up?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carrier grade generally hasn't been very receptive to automation and for good reason.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it ain't broke, it ain't listed as a vulnerable tract, and you don't need a feature that it lacks, it ain't in need of upgrading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That baby is gonna chew through that 10k in hospital bills FYI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It blows my mind that people don't take advantage of a retirement match.

People don't understand that just because that money isn't in their bank account and they can't see it when online banking or at the ATM, it's still their money, it's still accessible to them if they need it.  It's just not at chase.com or where ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That.... sounds terrible.

A buddy of mine went through that at some big online game company.  Ultimately he was responsible for a handful of servers and if they were humming along just fine he did absolutely nothing but... play their game on their time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he was honest.

Though if he is a manager chances are you aren't gunnin for his job anyway.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I brought my account executive a multi million dollar/multi vertical deal.  She over promised on the timeline in which she would get pricing to the customer, she missed that time line by about three weeks, and she keeps doing the "we all dropped the ball here" and I see her potential replacements sharpening their knives.

I got brought on to relieve some other SEs who are over worked but not much is actually thrown my way, so I basically spend my days taking cert practice exams and not actually working.  This would be great if I were still an 18 year old stoner but even if I'm not under threat of being canned for being redundant, I don't like not working.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to know that next time you have an hour to spare.  :P   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is Rob Dahm and what is the Rob Dahm situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look on the bright side:  Once it comes time to trade it in, you'll have a very low mileage high valued car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what it looks like.  But like on most cars you pull to release/push to engage.  On Porsche it is the opposite.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually one of the first things I did before asking.  I couldn't find one with just the three diamonds.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think pre 68 Bonneville/Pre 69 DeVille is my favorite due to those years having the stacked head lights.

No later than 72 for the Pontiac, but the Caddy is nice up until the late 70s.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know where I can find high rise Chinos?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.redditmedia.com/mqeJA8yU0h643bu6F-bWG0OHEDe17Z4elngvWi7dpTs.jpg?w=1024 s=ff106d798991e231b78cf1df42567b62

Can anyone identify the 3 diamond shirt on the left? Or one that looks similar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strangely enough the Cadillac seems to be easier to find parts for and is cheaper than a similar Pontiac.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about a Pontiac Bonneville Convertible. Tell me about it. Tell me if I'm crazy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious if this would make a great little cruiser from time to time, reliability, etc.  Looking at the market though, prices seem to be absolutely all over the place regardless of quality.  I see some low mileage ones in solid condition in the 20s, I see a low mileage one slightly better interior for 100k+ on eBay.

If the Bonneville isn't a good option for whatever reason, what's another option to look at?

I am not opposed to a Cadillac DeVille either.  



Mid 60s to mid 70s.  Though in the case of the Caddy and the Pontiac the late 80s models aren't terrible to look at either!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice looking driver slip ons without an ugly heel

New pair of wing tips

More SNK/Neo Geo themed t shirts

Another deconstructed jacket

High rise Chinos in fun colors if they exist
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.redditmedia.com/mqeJA8yU0h643bu6F-bWG0OHEDe17Z4elngvWi7dpTs.jpg?w=1024 s=ff106d798991e231b78cf1df42567b62


Can anyone identify the 3 diamond shirt on the left?  Or one that looks similar?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On PDK it does.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0zOqmG1Sfck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buys brand new Porsche and forgets to engage the parking brake when returning home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there something mechanically incorrect about leaving the car in neutral or is it just a better be safe kind of thing?

No, not particularly.

But in this case he left it in neutral **and** didn't engage the parking brake, leading him to this situation.  Had he at least parked in 1st he wouldn't have had a mini heart attack.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That and the charger that I thought was the pedal push to release style...it wasn't, it was just broken and all I did was engage it as hard as possible.

How did you release it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and his BMW's parking brake is the same as every other car, other cars that auto engage the parking brake, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he seems alright.  Comes off as a nice guy through and through.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 991.2 owner forgets to engage the parking brake... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 991.2 owner forgets to engage the parking brake... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/j5qG8aa.mp4


Because the parking break on Porsche is engaged opposite of every other car.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats your budget?

I'd go with Ubiquiti or Ruckus if you can afford either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TY, and they've gone on record saying that it will look very similar to the XC90.  Hopefully the XC40 does as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you are very much the exception to the rule.

They're also not "using their money to make money", they're just managing their monthlies in a reasonable (?) way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non Cisco certification tracts tend to focus on the open standards and protocols.  OSPF over EIGRP, VRRP over HSRP, etc.  I know that if I interview someone with a JNCIA instead of a CCNA, they may lack a bit in the syntax of Cisco specific hardware but otherwise they know their stuff and probably might end up slightly more useful in certain situations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Who are they and why did it plummet.

Young rich kids with access to expensive cars talk about them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty much exactly what it was/is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C Class was updated in MY15 with the MY16 GLC refresh having the new interior.  E Class was updated MY16/MY17 so MY18 GLE might get the refresh as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volvo 40.1 Concept: Meet the Next XC40 - Car News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly the GLA isn't an SUV.  It's a hatchback through and through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anxious to see the new interior.  This is definitely on my short list of SUVs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GLA isn't much larger at all, nor does it sit much higher, and it drives worse.

Go with the C300.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senior Systems Engineer + Sales Support.  Wife is CPA.  

C43 Cabrio, C300, Prius split up between my wife and I.  

The Cab may be traded in for a 911 at some point.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowbell.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I volunteer for Vault 69. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
