<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also men work longer hours, and tend to go into jobs that have a higher risk but ultimately pay a higher wage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 13:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a polish elementary school teacher with the last name Skrzypek. Not actually that hard to pronounce but no one could spell it right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 16:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The dance floor is murder tonight" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 15:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know if you're joking, but it's actually spelled "Tourette". I think OP spelt it phonetically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 18:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I Recall Correctly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 13:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being offended on twitter is obviously more egregious than whatever the Saudi's are doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 13:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nit-picky footnote. Electrocution by definition is until death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 01:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I remember correctly, Bill Clinton would be "First Gentleman."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 16:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it's a Balrog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 15:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does Godwin's law make the comparison wrong? I'm not even saying it's right, but you have yet to actually explain why the law makes it wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 15:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it's in the link you provided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 15:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "As an online discussion grows longer, the probability of a comparison involving Nazis or Hitler approaches" 

It's a law of probability not content. It doesn't make the comparison wrong.

Edit: "Godwin's law does not claim to articulate a fallacy; it is instead framed as a memetic tool to reduce the incidence of inappropriate hyperbolic comparisons. "Although deliberately framed as if it were a law of nature or of mathematics, its purpose has always been rhetorical and pedagogical: I wanted folks who glibly compared someone else to Hitler or to Nazis to think a bit harder about the Holocaust", Godwin has written." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 15:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw it happen a few times with freshman kids in high school. They don't have a piece, and are too afraid/unable to buy papes. So they get the dealer or a veteran smoker to roll a joint for them, usually smoking it with them as payment. Thing is they would almost always buy the weed then get it rolled, never saw a dealer cruise around with all of it pre-rolled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 01:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually had someone use that to lend credibility to the anti-vax ideas. Something about the establishment rejecting things that go against big pharma, i don't remember I kind of checked out. It was some conspiracy theory level mental gymnastics.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 01:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same as telling a man not to wear bright, flashy, and/or expensive looking clothing in a bad neighbourhood. It's not his fault if something happens. It might reduce the risk of it happening though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 14:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "/u/gandhikahn was the best prostitute i've ever had. Cheap price, great service, willing to do anything. 5 stars"


Reviews don't have to be negative to be slanderous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good shrooms + best buddy + Dark Side Of The Moon + Animals (the album) = Incredible spirit journey. 

I don't want to touch them again for a while but holy shit was that a ride.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 06:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So quantity  quality?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere that the US calculated the estimated death toll for an occupation of Japan at something like a combined 100 million (can't remember the source though so take it for what it's worth). An occupation at even half that death toll makes the atomic bombs seem like the better option in terms of casualties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact a corpse would actually provide a net benefit to microbes,
insects, and scavengers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a similar situation. Chinese workers were brought over, paid about a dollar a day and died very frequently. It wasn't necessarily slavery or indentured servitude but it was extremely dangerous and the workers weren't compensated very well at all. 

Canadian history footnote: The Canadian rail road system is actually partly responsible for Canada entering into confederation. The first railway was built in 1836 but by 1860 the local governments had pretty much run out of money building more. There was also the issue of western Canada being essentially cutoff from the east due to the sheer distance involved (Toronto to Vancouver is ~4,300 Km). So the promises of more regulated funding and an intercontinental railway were used to help unify the separate colonies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 14:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you count pre-confederation Canada as Britain then you could say they were involved with the use of cheap Chinese labor. No idea if they were involved with the US though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 18:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding was that Sweden doesn't consider torrent sites themselves as infringing copyright as they don't have any actual copyrighted material on their servers. As far as i know this was the loophole that has allowed TPB to exist for as long as it has. However, I'm not sure if it's changed since I last read TPB's legal page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 14:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the response. I just felt it was very short-sighted to completely dismiss natural suffering as "irrelevant". Thanks for clarifying your POV though, I see what you were trying to say now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 13:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wait, cancer, AIDS, and any other disease is just people causing other people to suffer? How does that work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay, fair enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, meant to use /u/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be wrong but I think /u/N8thanEL was saying that a psychology degree would be better than WGS degree with regards to helping the victims of rape and domestic abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 06:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, girl pooh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 16:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switzerland has more lax gun laws

I know this doesn't represent all of the US but you can legally buy a gun in Florida with only a drivers license so long as you aren't on public property. No background checks, no notifying the state, no registry, nothing. Just a drivers license and you have a gun. I don't know if you can get more lax than that. Also Florida alone has twice the population of Switzerland, which is one reason it's hard to apply Swiss-style laws to America. 320 million people is a different animal than 8 million people.

Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gun_laws_in_Florida#Firearm_sales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! It was bugging me that i couldn't find it. Thank you very much kind internet stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 18:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the rap PaulsEgo did? I heard it last night and can't find it on the video. Did they cut it out? It was dope as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 18:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya its a bit redundant looking back at it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in the unconscious void of a coma the beetus still cries out for the sweet embrace of high fructose corn syrup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 19:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like winning a race against someone who's bound and gagged behind the starting line. You win but how exactly were you ever going to lose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 19:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think she should blame herself


Nor should she feel it was her fault that he was killed.


So wait, should the mother blame herself or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 19:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about %70, so more than 2/3 of the deaths were male. Also 39 male:16 female gives a ratio of ~2.4:1, so twice as many men die for every women. Seems like a fairly big disparity to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 18:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never said it was supported, only that it can be installed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 17:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can already install adblock on android. You have to enable third party software, but it can be done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 19:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned the term from the movie of the same name actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 04:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: a nickname for human flesh is "long pig" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 05:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More Americans visit Mexico than Japan, SK, or Cambodia. I mean some of the most populous states directly border it (California, Texas) so naturally you are going to see more deaths there even if it were as safe as Japan. 

Per capita would be a more accurate representation of the actual danger. I mean who knows it might actually be worse than the raw numbers show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 17:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP is da real MVP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can explain it for you, but I can't understand it for you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 23:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just a would-be troll, best to just ignore them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 17:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those thoughts documented by police or a mental health facility though? I mean how is a gun store supposed to know his thoughts if they were never officially documented? Read his texts or listen to his conversations? 

To be clear if these things were officially on his record (which i still don't know one way or the other) then you are absolutely right in being upset at the gun store. However, if they weren't, then how does anyone have any way of knowing his thoughts or mental status outside of family and friends?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 17:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Holmes have a documented diagnoses, or documented instances of mental illness? If he didn't I don't know how a gun retailer can reasonably know his history of mental illness if it wasn't documented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 18:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Singer" is not really mutually exclusive from musician, that's kind of like saying "he's not a musician, he's a guitarist". Singer refers to his instrumentation, musician refers to his career.

The definition of musician is "a person who makes music a profession, especially as a performer of music." ([source](http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/musician)) So even if Nicki Minaj had no hand in writing anything, by virtue of her career as performing music, she is by definition a musician. 

I also edited my earlier comment to highlight some things.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 17:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So Frank Sinatra? 


[Songs Recorded](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_songs_recorded_by_Frank_Sinatra)

[Songs Written or Co-written](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Category:Songs_written_by_Frank_Sinatra)

Out of 1200 released commercial recordings, he had a hand in writing 7.

edit: Funny enough Nicki Minaj has written or co-written 99 of her own tracks https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Category:Songs_written_by_Nicki_Minaj

By this standard Nicki Minaj has more of a claim to musicianship than Frank Sinatra.

Also wouldn't something like the London Philharmonic Orchestra not be musicians then because they largely play classical pieces written by someone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 01:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Spiraling up through the crack in the sky*

*Leaving material world behind*

You guys are so awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 16:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All it takes for evil to prosper is for good men to sit idle and let it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily he came back to warn us so they won't be getting a click from me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care who knows, Doxy is a god. He (she?) is so exceptionally talented at giving me boners. 

Tumblrites also generally hate when people get things based on merit and Doxy absolutely deserves the patreon success. So it makes sense that they'd find a reason for him (her?) to be problematic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you do it, then it's the worst thing in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say their relationship is so open, it's practically gaping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are the yin to our yang. We are the shitlords they want, and they are the morons that created us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *screenplay by Stephen King* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't break everyone's phone, so hopefully someone else is filming by the time it escalates to that point (like in this case https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3ORXh85F5tM)


Though that doesn't help if you get pulled over somewhere secluded or something. Plus in some places you can't record without permission, for example California bans audio recordings without consent IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man who put penis in lego-gina is cock-blocked, Confucius say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that personality natural or did they choose that as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from Mein Kampf.

(ctrl+f and search "propagandist" it's the near the bottom)
http://www.mondopolitico.com/library/meinkampf/v1c6.htm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hrrrrrrrrnnnnngggg" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a finnish word or phrase thats equivalent to deepthroat? Asking for a friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 09:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know how much alcohol you need for it to work? You said flood your body but does that translate to an alc/weight ratio or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 08:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you're not a robot. Begone normie, go play outside like a pleb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 08:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may be using the word "animal" differently. Perhaps a more accurate word is "monster"? I'm using animal as a scientific classification, we are included in that. So we are animals, even just technically. Honestly though, i think we agree each other, i'm just kind of being pedantic and insisting on technicalities. 

I agree that we should strive for betterment, and continue to learn how to control our instincts. But i think we need to at least acknowledge that they are present as a motivating factor. We still want the same things instinctively that we did 200,000 years ago but the way we're allowed to express those instincts is radically different. It does us no favors to deny what is there. I think we're really going to have to work at it but i also think we're capable.

"Maybe we are still animals, maybe we do not deserve what we have made for ourselves. I have to believe, however that what we have made for ourselves, what we have done since we started to walk upright was not all in vain so we could continue to slaughter one another and continue to act like the barbarians we once were. Death is a necessity, we should not flaunt it."

Agree completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 07:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon there will be no gods or kings, only pepe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to approach it from the angle that we're all animals and therefore all have the ability to become like them. I think it makes it easier to empathize if we accept that at the heart of us we are all still animals, with animal instincts. I know it's mostly semantics, but that's my (unsolicited) two cents. Also empathy doesn't equal sympathy, I can empathize with their situation, but i don't feel they deserve any mercy outside of a swift death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 05:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Many FP-45 pistols were never distributed and were destroyed by Allied forces after the war; most of those distributed were lost or disposed of without any combat use."

Didn't really seem to help all that much. I guess it would be doable, just seems like a waste if most won't even see combat like the ones they tried to use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were they ever able to point to people who *do* represent the movement? I always hear that radfems don't speak for the movement but i never hear specifics about who actually does. Honest question, if anyone can answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Maybe if you weren't exterminated in the worst genocide of the 20th century, during the bloodiest war in history, you might have bought "baby" on iTunes."

What a twat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we give him cancer and then not give him chemo, I feel that's a poetic enough way for him to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya i noticed, I got a little overzealous, I edited my comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I indicate a joke? Does every joke need to be announced? Also isn't part of humor simply being untrue? Like if i say the sky is green would you not assume i was joking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you own a cat, and know that it isn't true, why did you assume i was being truthful? Cats are more aloof and solitary than dogs, the joke is then that they are less caring towards their owners and so they are likely to eat them faster. There is a running gag on the internet about cats being evil masterminds as well. The fact that it's not true is the joke. 

And Also what do you mean by delivery? What should I have changed so that you can understand it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is in how you choose to read it. Is it not? I didn't personally dictate it to you, using the tone of voice I had in my head when I wrote it. You were the one who read it as a statement of fact. What am i honestly supposed to do? Write "just kidding" after every joke? Look i think the mere fact of its absurdity should have at least made you consider that I could be having a laugh with it. 


I don't know maybe the joke is only something cat owners would understand? I thought it was funny :I  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn, well disregard that portion of it ahaha. You were dealt a pretty rough hand man, if you don't mind me saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 02:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean if you take everything on reddit seriously, then sure I guess it could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the word for that? I think it's called "a joke"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swimming is full body cardio, so it tends to burn a ton of calories. Michael Phelps eats like 12,000 cal a day lol. Maybe you should invest in some high calorie protein powder? I'm not sure how expensive it is, but shakes and smoothies are a good way to get calories and they're easy on digestion. Weed is amazing for appetite if you're in to that sort of thing. Besides that, red meat, dairy, carbs, and nuts are all calorie dense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow i can't imagine the politics between all those cats. It must be similar to Game of Thrones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 01:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a metabolism issue? Like have you always been a low weight? Either way it comes down to calories, you need to eat more than you burn. Working out will help make that weight muscle but you still need a surplus. However i understand, that it isn't that easy for some people to eat enough for that to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a bad motherfucker is not really about size, and more about surviving in the face of adversity. Also ya that is pretty light for your height, but i have friend who's the exact same size, so there's some anecdotal evidence that it's not too out of the norm. But what do i know i'm drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause you're a badass motherfucker and your body just hasn't gotten the memo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than cats, they sometimes love you and they wouldn't even wait until the bodies cold. They would probably eat you even if they weren't hungry, simply as a power thing.


(i have 5 cats so what does that say about me)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 00:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can i say, I'm a poet at heart. Also your boob is really cute.
Also x2 Is that a mustache tattoo on your finger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems sometimes that justice is relative to what side of the gun you're on. It's a human concept though, so i guess it leans towards humans tendencies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 22:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big D 

It's free

Come see 

My wee

Slap thee 

Love free 

Only D 

Big D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this analogy, I'm probably going to borrow it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the dictionary definition of Feminism is correct! Unless it isn't convenient, then it's obviously patriarchy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also he never existed, and I didn't actually leave the house. But it could have happened!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the difference, but I wasn't paying attention when I wrote that. I guess I'm the one whos garbage lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
