<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8710</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Van Der Sar

25 trophies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NFL *needs* to come to Toronto. Toronto, the metro area, has over 6 million people. It's one of the biggest markets in North America. Toronto shoud be getting a NFL franchise before Las Vegas and even Los Angeles since no one shows up to LA's games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUPER BOWL WEEKEND 

What do you guys have planned? I'm probably going to consume lots of beer   chicken wings. Speaking of beers, what beer(s) do you guys usually drink? 

I stopped drinking American pisswater beers like Budweiser. I've started liking beers like Kronenbourg, Shocktop,  Guinness, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bauza is a traitor. He will pay." - Maradona </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AFA manager Edgardo Bauza to finally meet Mauro Icardi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSG tell Inter   Juve Verratti will cost 100M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care for either Liverpool or Chelsea, this is just the facts. Lampard won more trophies, scored more goals, provided more assists. Please tell me how Gerrard was "better". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is posted every week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lampard was better. Gerrard never even won the Premier League. Lampard won it 3x as well as the Champions League. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know Lampard had that many goals for West Ham. West Ham legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manolas agrees 5-year 22.5M deal with Inter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see Leenock doing well in the GSL. But I have my money on TY or Maru.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter offer Roma now 42M + bonuses for Manolas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would he move to a midtable club? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter rejected official 30M bid for Candreva from Chelsea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maradona to give speech at Harvard University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until you've dated a few of them   realize they're crazy   discover Russian girls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still *much* less than Diamond/Pearl/Platinum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I watch Napoli just for Marika Fruscio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forza Pioli

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Thanksgiving-Christmas isn't that bad for a breakup. There's Christmas parties, gatherings, bars, everybody's out, you can meet women easily. The pre-Valentine's Day breakup is much worse because of all the couples you'll see around. And you said you've had sex *once* in 3 months? This relationship is hanging by a thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the worst time for a breakup. Super Bowl this weekend. Valentine's Day a couple weekends away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of drinking your typical American beer (Budweiser, Coors, etc.) I strongly recommend you guys try some European beers. I suggest:

- Shocktop (Belgium)
- Kronenbourg (France) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally, I'd say it's a mistake to drop out of college. But Snute has made over a quarter-million dollars playing Starcraft. That's about 5 years worth of salary if you're at an entry-level career out of college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Napolon   Hitler: Why'd they fail invading Russia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone that isn't too knowledgeable about military tactics, military technology, military logistics, military supply lines, military innovation, etc. I'm genuinely curious why Napoleon's Grande Armee failed at invading Russia. Then Hitler's Wehrmacht failed at invading Russia this time with superior technology, equipment, modern tactics, etc. What are the reasons for this?

I'd also like to share one of my favorite quotes about Russia from Winston Churchill:

*Russia is a riddle, wrapped in a mystery, inside an enigma. It is a part of Europe and a part of Asia, yet separate from both. It is rich with natural resources, yet its people have historically been grindingly poor. It has been invaded and overrun by Goths, Huns, Mongols, French and Germans, yet remained uniquely Russian. It has been a superpower and a nearly failed state, a monarchy, communist dictatorship and democracy - all within a span of 100 years.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna hold em like they do in Texas please

fold em, hit me, raise it, baby stay with me

luck and intuition play the cards with spades to start

and after he's been hooked I'll play the one that's on his heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Icardi said in an interview lately that all the big clubs in Spain wanted him as a youth player. Real Madrid, Atletico Madrid, Sevilla, Barcelona, etc. But ultimately, he chose Barcelona. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so you're a Bayern fan, a Browns fan,   a Pistons fan? Please explain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search Kurt Warner's achievements on wikipedia. He's one of the best QBs of all-time hands down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shit is at 200 comments. I didn't know r/nfl would feel so strongly about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eintracht Frankfurt announce record turnover of 109M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eintracht Frankfurt announce record turnover of 109M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what about England's history of hooliganism, child abuse, and corrupt FA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Wolfsburg, Stuttgart   BVB have all won in the last decade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundesliga CEO says NFL is "dramatically over-commercialized' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundesliga CEO says NFL is "dramatically over-commercialized" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My source is girls from U of Leeds on Instagram. I don't live in England so please enlighten me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leeds is hated? Can English fans explain why? Leeds has the hottest birds as far as I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still more European Cups than other "major" clubs you listed like Arsenal,  Chelsea, Spurs, Man City, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shakhtar Donetsk complete deal to move to new 40,000 stadium in Kharkiv </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Branislav Ivanovi will earn 82k per week at Zenit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's because this sub is EPL majority and most EPL fans dislike Arsenal. I doubt fans of other leagues care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everton reject 16M bid by Newcastle for McCarthy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inter needs to raise Icardi's release clause to 200M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say Leverkusen are in fact a big club. They've been a Bundesliga staple for many, many years. And they're reached the Champions League finals which is more than most clubs in Europe can say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he really worth 20M or is it because Zenit has money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zenit's 14M bid rejected by PSV for Davy Prpper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna bookmark this the next time some EPL moron says racism is a problem in Italy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atltico Madrid set to offer Snchez 250k per week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  #MontellaOut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bergkamp didn't "fail" at Inter. He was the UEFA Cup top scorer when Inter won it. Anyways, the '88 Dutch team (Rijkaard, Koeman, Gullit, Van Basten, etc.) would all be ahead of Robben. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such an insightful post. If it means anything to you from a Canadian, Sofia   Varna are beautiful   I'd love to visit someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China has "saved" Starcraft. From tens of thousands more fans watching to Chinese companies like Alibaba sponsoring $400k tournaments. I for one love China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoichkov   Nedvd won the Ballon d'Or themselves with uker coming 2nd for it. There were all top 3 players at one point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was the best Eastern European forward of ~~all-time~~ the modern age? Shevchenko, Stoichkov, uker or Nedvd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could address the impact on the Eastern Bloc nations more in depth, it would be appreciated. And not only the Eastern Bloc nations, how did post-WWII impact Yugoslavia, Austria-Hungary, Balkans, etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hecking: "Lads, it's Neverkusen" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Blizzard fanboy, this makes me happy. I played Team Fortress for many years but Overwatch is *much* more fun. I had no idea Overwatch would even be this successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USSR, Russia,   the Eastern Bloc post World War II-present </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Canadian and most of my understanding of World War II was taught from an America perspective in school growing up. However, I've been dating a Russian girl for some time now and recently we got into an argument because she tried convincing me America is "evil".


Essentially, she argued that America and Germany worked together post-World War 2 to keep Eastern Europe and Russia down via exploitation and the likes. Now, I am not too knowledgeable regarding this. I'm a business student in university and my WW2 knowledge is limited. She explained to me the Marshall Plan whereby America helped Germany and such. 

My question is: How exactly did America keep the USSR, Russia,   Eastern Europe "down" exactly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Liverpool. Blackburn, Leicester,   maybe Sunderland will win the league before them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top foreign goalscorers in Bundesliga history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HuK vs. NaNiwa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Terran player, I'd like to ask the community who do you think the best foreign Protoss player in Starcraft II was/is?

Of course, both have been successful in foreign terms in Korea. Both have reached the quarter-final of the GSL. Only Jinro and IdrA did better in Korea and I guess Neeb although that was the KeSPA Cup.

But ultimately, who was the better player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milan were better than Juventus during that era. Then of course English clubs got really good during that era (Arsenal, Chelsea, Liverpool). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GKs with 100+ apps in the UCL: Casillas (162), ech (111), Valds (106), Buffon (101) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are 2. Bundesliga clubs are making so much money without English-esque deals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain the "fuckery" that went on in Eastern Europe? How did the USSR affect [Eastern Bloc] (https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/cd/Europe-blocs-49-89x4.svg/812px-Europe-blocs-49-89x4.svg.png) states   itself? Also, it was more of a debate than a fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundesliga breaks 3B in revenue, 2. Bundesliga breaks 600M in revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I got into a fight with my gf the other day because she tried convincing me America is evil. She's Russian.

She said that America   Germany worked together post-WWII to keep Eastern Europe down. So I was thinking, is this how Russians   Eastern Europeans feel about America?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wolf, Moonglade, Valdes 

dream team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you tell us how you keep sending me private messages? Are you gay? go get a girlfriend dropout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Canadian myself and I sorta feel the same way. I recommend supporting Green Bay (see 1997). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are these clubs that can afford him? Atletico won't sell to a rival La Liga club   last I heard Man U were offering 100M.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monchi said you need 3 things to convince a player: football, lifestyle, and money.

At Inter, he could win a treble. At Inter, he could live in Milan, one of the best cities in the world in terms of lifestyle. At Inter, he'll earn Chinese money which as you know is ridiculous money. I'm not saying Inter *will* sign him, but we've signed Ronaldo in the past. Is Griezmann bigger than Ronaldo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Inter doesn't have a history of breaking transfer records. Multiple times. I know this is hard for Juventini to digest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moratti era part 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [article] (http://www.calciomercato.com/en/news/from-spain-griezmann-s-atletico-madrid-release-clause-revealed-42017) says 110M. Idk really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter ready to pay Griezmann's 130M release clause </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter owners Suning Group ready to pay Griezmann's 130M release clause </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> QB's have to eat sacks. Imagine being 40   having a 275 pound linebacker wreck you. GK's don't experience that thus Buffon could play until 45 no problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Brady is still an elite QB at 40. Being a GK involves virtually no contact. I could see Buffon playing til 45. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Champions League, will we ever see Eastern European clubs dominate again?

Clubs like Red Star, Partizan, Steaua Bucuresti, etc.? And what would it take for them to become powerhouses again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's Indian   thinks he's German. I'm laughing too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> England marketed themselves globally first which is why they're making so much money. 

Money never = success. No one knows more about this than Inter. Inter broke transfer record after record   didn't really win anything. Look at clubs like Atletico. They're much less wealthy than clubs like Arsenal, Manchester City, etc. yet they've surpassed their success in Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man U ready to go deeper in debt to qualify for Europa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BVB CEO Watzke says he'd consider "an 80M offer" for Aubameyang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know the Russian Premier League was competitive. I thought Zenit won every year.  Can the Russian PL be a "big" league? In terms of size, money, players, etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf introduced me to [her] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cedoBlUvBlI). She seems popular, idk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorta off-topic but how popular is Era Istrefi in ex Yugoslavia countries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much would Dinamo sell Benkovic   Coric for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dinamo Zagreb reject 30M bid from Newcastle for duo Benkovic   Coric </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never gotten into MOBA's either. And plus I prefer Blizzard PC games. I love Halo too, though.

But the Bundesliga is investing heavily in esports. Germany ahead of America yet again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NFL is behind on this. Soccer clubs like Schalke, Wolfsburg, Bayern, etc. are already investing in esports.

There's a ton of money in esports. Personally, I love Starcraft and there was $2.5M in prize money in Starcraft last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt Torino ever accepts 50M. 50M isn't that much in today's market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrea Belotti's release clause is set at 86.5M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federica Fontana disagrees </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rutgers is a good college, always felt it was underrated. It's one of the oldest colleges in America, anybody that goes to Rutgers should be proud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ruud Gullit: "I think Italian is one of the most beautiful languages in the world. In general, in Italy I learned to appreciate the beauty of life. Because the Italians love everything that has to do with beauty: women, cars, food, fashion" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That [2002] (https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Bayer_Leverkusen_vs_Real_Madrid_2002-05-15.svg) Leverkusen team was so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highest win % in Bundesliga history by player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why you'd compare to Inter to Real Madrid or Bayern.

Inter aren't exactly winning everything right now. And Inter is a club meant for everybody regardless of race, religion, etc. It's a club with a philosophy - fratelli del mondo. Inter is a symbol of the Sforza family of Milan. Inter is a symbol of anti-fascism. Inter is tradition   history   unlike most clubs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Wolfsburg sell all their good players (Dzeko, Perisic, etc.)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roma signed him for just 11M too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edin Deko: 20 goals this season so far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ronaldinho was an attacking midfielder, not a striker though. Still an amazing achievement by Neymar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Giggs is overrated according to r/soccer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flash dominated in ProLeague   won an IEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America would fall apart without Mexico, China and Canada. Meanwhile, Canada would fall apart without America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 wins in a row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real Madrid prepare 30M Summer bid for Courtois </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Juventus is already trying to buy him. He'll most likely remain in Serie A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Ben vs. Tom Brady (playoff career stats) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aubameyang: "I will never go to Bayern, that is for sure" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> escorts   Xbox games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manolas will leave Roma in Summer to join Inter for 42M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AC Milan's Donnarumma demands 10M per year to stay at club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lewandowski has scored his 60th goal for Bayern in his 80th game - faster than any other player in Bundesliga history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liverpool's youth team will never win another title again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter   Roma agree 40M fee for Manolas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Payet really worth 30M? I don't know much about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to visit ~~Syria~~ Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between this   other incidents like beating up Puyol, why does Ramos act like an angry 13 year old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20M? Classic Bundesliga lowballing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Serie A goals since 14/15: Higuan (67), Icardi (51), Dybala (36), Belotti (31) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pirelli sempre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIGC's official site says 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cesena reach Coppa Italia quarter-final for first time since 1970-71 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equally as impressive, Bara making more revenue than Real Madrid. La Liga has changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundesliga set to break 3B revenue mark for first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bundesliga set to break 3 billion revenue mark for first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Spurs fans told me they're a big English club now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Canada, you see *way* more Arsenal kits than Chelsea, Liverpool, Man City, Man U, etc. Real Madrid, Barca   Bayern I believe. In Toronto, I think Milan, Inter,   Juve are very popular, too. Lotta Italians in Toronto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> degaard reveals Bayern Munich wanted to sign him but he chose Real Madrid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Blackburn aren't a traditional "big" English club. Blackburn have won the Premier League   Liverpool, Everton, Spurs, etc. haven't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say never, maybe someday. We had Blackburn   now Leicester win the Premier League. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprised. People post "news" from some sites I've never heard of here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter have won 7 matches in a row for the 1st time since 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inter have won 7 matches in a row for the first time since 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forza ragazzi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ESPN: Manchester City will pay 100M to sign Messi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. Brady has the GOAT coach in Belichick. Rodgers has the highest passer rating of all-time for a reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essentially 20M per year. And yesterday Van Gaal rejected 50M over 3 years. Just shows that even millions aren't enough to convince some people to move to China.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodell: "More commercials!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Juventus: employing unemployed art majors everywhere

because seriously, what can you do with an art degree? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's why it's an *even* greater play, Rodgers drew it up at the huddle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike McCarthy on Rodgers clutch sideline pass: "One of the greatest plays" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he should've won in 1996, too. Too bad Juve were on roids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Dallas is a bigger market than New England. Could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN: Packers-Cowboys most watched NFL Divisional playoff game in 20 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much time do you spend posting   stalking me? This is why you're single </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article written by: Tottenham Hotspur board members  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BVB will consider an offer of 70M for Aubameyang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Wikipedia, Frankfurt's metro area is Germany's [2nd biggest] (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frankfurt) (5 million+). 

According to my cousin, Frankfurt is more 'modern' than the rest of Germany. What's your opinion on this? And how does the rest of Germany compare to Frankfurt in terms of culture, nightlife, etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised Eintracht Frankfurt isn't higher. Isn't Frankfurt Germany's biggest city after Berlin? I've heard it's one of the best cities in Europe, too.

source: my cousin in Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Rodgers has 6th 300 YD post-season game matching Joe Montana's career total </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monday: NFL announces Lombardi trophy to be renamed McCarthy trophy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Green Bay Packers advance to the NFC Championship Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AARON RODGERS THE *TRUE* GOAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King Crosby of House Green Bay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alibaba has done great things for Starcraft. And they sponsor my favorite soccer club Inter Milan, too. I love Alibaba. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's made all of Maru's prize money with 1 tournament win. Congrats TY, you deserve it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TY now among the top 10 earning Starcraft II players of all-time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Rodgers has tied Dan Marino for 5th all-time in post-season pass TDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100M + Kroos for zil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FORZA FIORENTINA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Inter bought Lcio from Bayern Munich to do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English money is crazy, I wouldn't be surprised. We live in a world where an English 2nd division club pays more than a big La Liga club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao we'll buy all your players with this Chinese money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea ready to spend 75M on Mller to replace Costa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I heard you guys have the biggest debt in Europe at 400M  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
