<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6420</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh God, I don't know if I should laugh or cry at the fact that you think it is something from sci-fi to have people be "disappeared". It's been done before in South America to people who disagreed or didn't conform with the Military coup of Argentina. Google the 1976 coup of Argentina. Maybe have a read at the book Nunca Ms (Never Again). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have something similar here in my Fish and Chips shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you DON'T have roundabouts in America? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I remember driving a Banshee up to the enemy base and basically doing donuts in the air while dropping bombs into it. Racked up about 20 kills in a few minutes before I crashed and got stuck in the hole in the middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, this is almost the exact same trick that some "magic boxes" use to make the box seem empty while hiding something in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 09:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is "All good". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flash games. Used to play them all the time. Now they charge you for them on Steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, turn this from a post in r/TIFU into a post in r/ProRevenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then there's me, who spent like 25 minutes adding a dong on Darth Sidious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because you are a decent human being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a pun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry that this has happened to you. Hopefully this will teach them a good lesson. Would have been great to see their "Oh crap" faces when you pulled out the gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one at the Fish and Chips shop I work at is the simplest one, just one machine where you enter the amount and hand it to a customer for them to swipe the card and enter the PIN. I'm assuming this is the same one OP used, since it is very possible for a customer to enter their own amount if they know what they are doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creme brulee and creme caramels are the first ones to come to mind. If you want more savoury ones, homemade mayonnaise, aioli, or hollandaise are pretty good for using up egg yolks.

PS: I think stores sell liquid egg whites, but I'm not sure if they are good for meringue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matcha Matcha Matcha Cupcakes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my experience (two semi-failures): 
Have clean and dry equipment. Don't let water get into the meringue from your whisk/spatula. Have a piping bag with a wide circular tip. Use a template and don't forget they are going to spread a bit. Let your macarons dry after you pipe. Let them cool a bit before you peel them off the parchment paper. They are the best a day or so after you sandwich them as a little of the moisture gets into the cookie and it gets chewier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand of the argument, I have seen videos from StJohns (New Zealand's more prominent EMS/Ambulance company) where some of the friends of the patient started assaulting the EMTs (admittedly they were reenactments, but for them to be concerned enough to release something like this means it's more common than they would like). Not a clue of what the guy was thinking but with alcohol and high emotions people tend to not think clearly. Add in the fact that guns are really common in Texas and I can see EMTs carrying guns for safety. Of course in the situations where you described above you are not in danger of other people assaulting you/shooting you, but what about in more urban cases like a traffic accident where someone wants you to treat their friend/family first regardless of the level of injury, or a party where someone doesn't feel like you are not doing everything you can for their friend because of alcohol/ignorance/not thinking clearly, etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It even looks like they called someone to take him away and then he just starts playing with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hairless cats? As far as I know, most people are allergic to the hair in animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
