<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5873</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you sleep in a given day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just wants to know your favorite color. Maybe it is blood red? Or creamy white? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>         . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a lot of fun. I don't think I am suited for the job but hopefully others will be on board with it. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HealthLink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beep.

Beep.

Beep.

Beep.

Eventually you no longer hear it even though it is there. Alarm fatigue. 

Beep.



Beep.





Beeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeep.

They hear that one. Nurses rush around, doctors bark orders, but nothing can be done. Time of death is 10:58AM.

-----------------

I work in a hospital in a large city. There are almost one thousand beds in this gleaming white palace which means almost one thousand beeps every minute. With so many patients and so few staff alarm fatigue is considerable here. There isnt much you can do about it, even I have it.

That is why when another patient was not cared for properly and resulted in a possibly avoidable death the big brass at the top brought in a consulting firm. They assessed our staff individually and collectively, our equipment and core systems, our IT infrastructure, even the patient flow from common departments like the Emergency Room, Surgery, ICU, and Recovery. 

The reason I know about this at all is because I was part of the team to install all of the new equipment we bought from the firm. It was called HealthLink and it was an all-in-one system that connected every single piece of equipment from the handheld thermometer to the largest MRI room. Every piece of pertinent information about every patient could be transferred and viewed regardless of where they went in the hospital. Even the new wheelchairs recording their vitals as they were pushed from one room to the next. It also didnt use beeps or obnoxious flashing lights to indicate issues because those could be silenced, ignored, or disturb the patient. Instead, each patient was assigned to staff via their employee badge and a connected earpiece relayed information.

I have to admit it was impressive. The cost for something like this would be unimaginable but I suppose bad press would damage the hospitals image enough to warrant such a drastic change. We sold all of our old equipment off to other hospitals and clinics via a large auction once HealthLink was up and running and I was sent off for three weeks of extensive on-site training.

---------------

When I came back from training I was amazed at the transformation with the staff. Nurses sprang to life as soon as their badge alerted them. Doctors buzzed happily from patient to patient to check in on them. Physical therapists led yoga classes in the atrium. Even the custodial staff grinned from ear to ear as they turned down rooms to make ready for a new patient or hauled the trash out to the compactor. 

Now dont get me wrong, I am not saying that our staff were a bunch of angry monsters that hated their jobs, but everyone can get burned out from time to time. A verbally abusive patient or pushy family members can bring you down pretty quickly if you are caught off guard. 

Seeing everyone in such a good mood helped keep me up high as well and I breezed through my day for several weeks. I bounced from repair to repair whistling away when I realized I hadnt heard an overhead page for a stroke or stemi or code blue all day. In such a big hospital you get at least one stroke and several code blues. Come to think of it I couldnt remember hearing a single page since the training. *Maybe they dont need them anymore with the new system*, I thought. I decided I would try to pay more attention, maybe I had just missed them or tuned them out.

The next day I was down in the Emergency Department checking the calibration of one of the new monitors when several ambulances pulled up, ushering ten people in on gurneys. There was a massive multi-car pileup on the highway and several others were being life-flighted in. Our ED was already pretty full and I could see the stress break through a few of the staffs faces as they tried to get the new patients into rooms and their basic needs met. 

I flagged down one of the nurses and let her know the room I was working on would be ready soon and they would be able to put one of the patients in now while I finished up. 

Ill stay for a bit to make sure it all works with the new patient, just in case.

Thank you so much. Youre a life saver! With that she sped off to bring one of the worst-off in. 

Being in the middle of it all gave me a certain perspective that I probably would have missed otherwise. The busier nurses looked to be in pain. Tightened eyes and grimaces now appeared on their once smiling, cheerful faces. The nurse wheeled in the transfer gurney and the paramedics helped move the patient onto the trauma stretcher. She scanned the patients wristband and then her own badge to link them to each other and she immediately groaned out in pain. 

She asked the patient questions in a rapid fire succession to assess the pain level and immediate needs, verified name, date of birth, and then rushed off to get some pain medicine and an air compressor for the patients legs. 

By this time the ED was filled with moans and groans from all the new patients and staff alike. Nurses rushed from room to room trying to fill each of their needs as quickly as possible. I noticed that those with the fewest rooms didnt look pained anymore but the lead nurse covering the room I was in, Stephanie, was slowly becoming overwhelmed with requests. By the time she made it back to our room with what she needed her face mirrored that of the patient. I couldnt tell who was in more pain!

Stephanie, whats wrong? Are you alright? Stephanie. Hey, can you hear me?

Panic set in when she turned up to me slightly in response before crashing down to the floor. Pills scattered across the gleaming linoleum. I crossed the room in two strides and bent down to help her when I noticed the square bump high on the back of her neck in between now-parted braids. 

HELP!! 

Her breathing was increasingly shallow and sporadic and her skin was paling quickly. Just as two other nurses came over I realized that the patient had stopped groaning so I turned to look at the vitals  they had stabilized.

[Update](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61sqmp/healthlink_part_2/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the advice. Right now my wife and daughter are staying at her mom's house and I am trying some of the suggestions out to flush the bastard out/secure the home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooooooooh snap!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sign me up. I'll go out "swingin" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So. Freaking. Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the stinky hands... ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours must have been a much more severe fall than mine. I had some bruising but after three visits to the chiro I was pretty much good as new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was curious how she was walking around and going up stairs if she was so frail so being a ghost made perfect sense at the end. I would like to believe that you saw your real grandmother in the end but since she appeared to you as an old woman I am not sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, that is horrible to hear! I have back issues as well AND slipped down stairs last winter helping a friend move. It was incredibly unpleasant to say the least. I wish the fastest recovery to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely my favorite of late. I can't wait to hear about more guests and how you survive the next three months! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit those are tough little bastards. Very nice, OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is amazing how quickly the fear can overtake you, isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so I've deleted my comment about twelve times because I'm honestly speechless. First off, thank you to the wonderful person or people to nominate Patient 314 and secondly, thank you for all of the votes.

I never thought I'd see my name in one of these threads because the community is so incredibly talented. It is humbling, encouraging, and motivating to keep going. Thanks for giving me a place to express myself! 

Congrats, Opinionson! I enjoyed reading every one of your updates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have to try a few of these and get back to you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh well. That's cool, you know. Do your thing. Nice uh, nice name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodgeball the Movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is called rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not much of a hugger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. But can you dodge a wrench? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are Nipples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A true No sleeper. I don't understand why people want to try and eliminate sleep.

I LOVE SLEEP. It is amazing. Sure, you get nothing done, but that is the beauty of it. If you are awake and get nothing done you are lazy and wasting your time but when you sleep it is OK.

Enjoy your sleep! Embrace it. Just not me. Don't embrace me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just big enough. My first one ripped so I made one out of blankets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also get a royally botched job because they are just students. We have a great dental school nearby that a lot of people I know go to. It is pretty much a crap shoot, 50/50 chance of good work. 

IF you take this LPT make sure you get a senior student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you are just trying to drum up his business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say thank you for your story. Can't wait to read the last part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bold move, Indeed Pepper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hide and Seek on Halloween </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halloween was always my favorite day each year. You get to dress up in fun costumes, eat candy and homemade treats, play hide and seek into the wee hours of the morning. 

This year was no exception! I went out with all of my friends and went door to door gathering our treats. Within an hour I could barely hold my bag up off of the ground it was so full. What a great night! 

My friends and I ran with our bags of treats to the woods were we always play hide and seek. I carefully navigated the three miles to my usual spot. It was very hard to find so I usually won 

Out of breath but full of excitement I emptied my bag out onto the soft forest floor and five little boys tumbled out, whimpering with fear.

A huge smile plastered across my face. *I am going to count to 100 and then I am going to come find you. If you last more than two hours you get to live!*

Plopping down amid the leaves with my eyes closed, I began to count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True enough. If not I am sure we will have a great NoSleep story about how one less Andrew completely destroyed the name balance and sent our world plummeting into apocalyptic ruin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe iia has stock in a direct competitor to sunflower seeds... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is going to be Andrew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably so. I wonder if I changed my name to Jacqueline... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She covers every angle. I haven't ordered mushrooms on my pizza ever since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said I haven't written about my exploits already?

Ok so poopop is out. I guess your given name will suffice. Of course I will need to reference this thread on a weekly basis to try and remember any name at all anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I mean it is hilarious and all but after about 1,000 similar encounters I just want to punch them in the face for using my name in the skit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I JUST put new gutters up and new windows in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In her crib, safe and sound, thankfully! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone ever call you A-N-Drew? Or ANDDDDD Roo!

Just curious because I am getting way too many A-A-Ron's this past year or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the party, Rebecca! From what I understand impulsive ukulele buying is a sign of literary genius. Just saying. Speaking of which I should probably get rid of mine...

Anywho, I can't imagine helping in any way BUT I am glad you think so and very glad you liked the series! Fingers crossed that another good idea pops into my head one day.

Ok so poopy is out. How about poopop? Thank has a nice ring to it, don't you think?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool, thanks for popping in Andrew! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they took Nicolas and made him into you. I hope you recover soon and find out more about this situation you got yourself into. If you can get your hands on that contract you might want to read it a little more carefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always though Sloppy Joes looked like brains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me now!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! I am confused, though, about how someone from the past can alter the future if they are still in the past.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A is for Alright alright alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The baby took too long of a walk :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are definitely a lot of rainbows, sunshine and infinite happiness, thank you. I miss Cali, not as much as I thought I would, but the beaches are all I really think about.

Not to worry, I'll be here! Or maybe worry, I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to think so ;) I was tired of being frustrated and annoyed with players just running into every battle or even just ordinary situations with the point end leading the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Kristy, I am glad that it worked out for you! I moved to Kansas in the name of love and found another love in my bed. It was the poops. BUT I did end up staying and met my wife so all is good. 

Custody is a hard thing. I am sorry to hear about that :(

Ever live in southern California or Kansas?

Whenever I see Poppymoonray my inner voice says "poopymoonray", can't help it, can't stop it. 

Glad my post was so well received. It is a lot of fun learning more about the mods and veterans of this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do somewhere but mainly it is just in my head. Basically it forces players to be a little more political and sneaky than stabby stabby. One gunshot will probably kill you so you need to be smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much for him. System failure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with the brake lines being cut is that usually they leave brake fluid in the driveway. Hopefully you cleaned all of that up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3.5 is where I started and have the most love. My favorite is actually a  home brew that I created. I call it DnDR which stands for realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite DnD version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, you rolled a bard in real life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never fully dismiss your fears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a habit of sleeping with an arm or a leg hanging off of the side of the bed. For whatever reason it was comfortable to me. Then I watched Childs Play. The little psycho doll hiding under beds and slashing peoples tendons. I was probably eight or nine when I first watched it and my habit came to an abrupt end.

For years I was fearful of something hiding under my bed poised to attack the moment I swung my legs over the edge or dangled a hand down. So I began jumping out of bed. I was not afraid to be in bed and go to sleep and I was not afraid to grab my toys out from under the bed or even play under the bed IF I was already on the floor. The unknown, the hidden, out of my sight lines - that is what scared me. 

As do most childhood fears like being afraid of the dark or the deep end of the pool I grew out of my need to jump off the bed and my habit of arm or leg dangling off the side of the bed slowly took hold once again. I dont know whether it is the fact that as we age we become more rational or become bigger and stronger and more capable. Every so often the movie would pop up on TV late at night, usually around October and November, and I think about my silly fear and chuckle. But without fail that very first morning I would hesitate slightly before getting out of bed. Just for a brief flicker that fear would rush to the front of my mind and I would need to push it back. 

The last time that happened was probably a decade and a half ago, maybe even longer, because I cant remember the last time I hesitated. Until this morning. 

I am 31 now, married and have a child of my own. I would like to say that I run my household but I dont. My little girl does. Every drawer has a special lock on it. Every corner has rubber coatings. Baby gates dominate the landscape. And my king sized bed lies unceremoniously on the floor. No box frame, no box springs, just a low profile mattress covered in pillows and sheets. Why, you might ask? So that our sweet little girl wont fall off. 

Now you may be asking yourself why any of this matters to the story at hand. Remember how as I child I would be afraid of things under my bed? This morning I awoke with a start. Heart racing, feet and palms sweating, and blood dripping from my outstretched arm. Thin, deep cuts ran the length of my forearm. The cuts began at the point where my arm extended off of the edge of the bed. 

It is hard to be afraid of something under your bed when it is lying flat on the floor with your body weight pressing it down but at that moment I was terrified. My eyes flicked around the dim room trying to see the culprit. When nothing jumped out at me as obvious and all hiding places appeared empty I slowly made my way out of bed, trying not to let any more of my blood further saturate the sheets and attended to my wounds in the bathroom.

After a lot of gauze and athletic tape my arm was bandaged up so I began searching around the house for anything out of place, missing, uncharacteristic. After finding nothing I tried to calm my nerves and settle down. I tried the logic approach - The alarm was still on, nothing set it off, what did this to my arm?

I went in to wake up my wife and explain to her what happened when I saw a glint of metal coming from the grate next to our bed. Sprinting the last few steps I pushed the bedside table out of the way and ripped the vent right off of the wall. A few drops of blood on the back of the vent cover were all I could find but I swear I saw something inside of there! 

My wife woke up startled from all of the noise and saw my bandaged arm and torn up wall. Her first words were along the lines of what the hell are you doing? but she was cut off when a low, soft chuckle made its way out of the vent and into our ears.

---------------

UPDATE:

First I want to thank you all for the amazing suggestions given in the comments. I never would have thought of most of them to try. Honestly I was too afraid to do much thinking at all other than to get out. 

I wasnt able to get any chlorine gas but I did hook up my car via a very long hose. I went through the house and closed every vent except for one and dropped the hose down into it. Once the car was running I ran around the house pouring salt around each vent to try to further force whatever this thing is to stay inside and suffer the fumes. 

Once that was done I set our motion sensors on the highest setting and armed the house. They should pick up any movement the size of a bunny or larger. I opened up the app to my security system and watched for any motion notifications while I circled the house, making sure nothing escaped from a vent or window or hole in the ground. Who knows, right? 

I ran my car for a full gas tank worth just to be sure and then let the house air out while I walked to the closest gas station with my spare tank. I watched my security notifications all day, all night, and all through the next day as well without a single alarm. I figured the house was probably cleared out by then and safe for me to walk around in. There was still a funny smell in the air but I opened up all of the vents and turned the attic fan on and opened up all of the windows. None of the salt was disturbed so I know it didnt make it out of a vent. 

Thank you so much for the great ideas, guys! We are going to wait one more day to really clear out the air and then move back in. My wife is looking forward to sleeping in our bed once again and so am I. 

[Later](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/626b1o/never_fully_dismiss_your_fears_part_2/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffered years of it, trying to be nice, be a friend, whatever.

What part of trying to be a friend are you missing? I never intimidated him and I continually told him we were fine. No hard feelings. 

BECAUSE HE WAS A BULLY HIS MINDSET WOULD NOT CHANGE. 

He felt he had to act that way because of who he is, not because of what I did or said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't let kids call you out, chica. Put them in their place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffered years of it, trying to be nice, be a friend, whatever. 

I never bullied him after, either. He was just so afraid of what he thought I would do to him (because that was his mindset) that he just buddied up to me and tried to appease me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe in an alternate dimension you are a drum set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you please stop releasing monsters into the world?! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you my wife? ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy seems to have some kind of vendetta to the neighborhood. I would definitely warn your parents and have them stay at your place if they can. You need to contact the authorities and just give them anonymous tips if you have to. Tell them a bomb is going to go off or whatever you have to do to get them to go out there when the guy is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Alex! Good to see you are finally getting some writing in. My first foray into writing was literally copying Goosebumps books with my buddy and changing the names to our names. We were legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very glad to meet you, Kristina. What is causing the pain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping this was about the grocery store. Nope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carsner needs to be put in isolation for the rest of his life with no food or water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was made in the early 90s so... everybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many players did you have? We had 4 and made it about half way. I think with 6 you'd have a chance. It was fun, just frustrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have the board game. No one wins. Ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is "Do you know that Valentine's Day is actually a day to sacrifice virgins?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Alex! Thanks for coming in and introducing yourself. Mess with my head all you want :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The More You Know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at all this amazing stuff we are learning today. Now to use it all against each other... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct, sir!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're lucky I'm cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recite 10 All Reddits and all will be absolved my son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much are we talking about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to meet you, local authorities advised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://imgur.com/a/rcEk6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zordon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything. Parenting does that to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how they used the word "whomever" yet wrote it out in crayon. Those just don't seem to match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be a brand guy. Nike, Samsung, Vans, whatever. Now that everything is so cheaply made and designed to fail I just get the cheapest I can with good ratings. Sometimes they last an amazingly long time, sometimes they do not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, it will be filled with spam quick enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughing at your own joke. Classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That jizz stain wasn't, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interest is calculated off of the remainder of the loan, not the original amount. Therefore putting additional principal down early pays off the part of the loan that the interest is calculated from.

If you make the minimum payments the "expected loan amount" that they calculate in the beginning would be correct. **BUT** if you pay extra it will go down. 

For example you have a $100 loan at 10% interest. If you pay $20 dollars it would drop to $80 plus interest which is $10 so now the loan balance is $90.

But if you then paid an additional $20 of principal it would drop to $70 without interest being added on.

Then your next payment rolls around and you pay your $20 which drops the loan to $50 plus the $7 that the interest tacks on equaling $57.

If you did not make that additional payment your loan would be at $79 ($90-20=70 ... + the $9 from interest) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what brings you joy. For some it would be a kitten cuddler. Forrest Gump would mow lawns. Someone else would be a hitman because killing people is his jam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job working out those issues! I've had my own addictions to battle. It ain't easy. I am on steam: aintgottyme 

Mmmm virgins. It's been awhile, my pretties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Restaurant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes sir. Specifically in Lenexa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of YAY's in there and for good reason. Congrats again on all of the wonderful things going on in your life right now. Enjoy it all to the fullest! 

I would most certainly add you if I had a PS4 but I don't even have a PS2 anymore. Or any gaming console. Life, blah. You'll find out. Heh heh heh heh

That was ominous, sorry. Donuts and coffee are that way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll... no, of course not. Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your emphasis on subtraction is what bothered us the most. But again, thank you for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm yeah could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a 24 hour lab so there are always a lot of people running around but yeah, not many have a need to go to the walk-in so I am very glad to have gone that day. I think about it from time to time and just cringe with the possibilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I FOUND ONE! GET IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were a test don't you think they would have a faster response time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if Keith wanted to play patty cake or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for accepting my child. I regret to inform you that we are going to place her into a different school at this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A sad tale, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I most certainly will :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice to meet you! Marital status had me busting up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now I am giddy and impatient. GREAT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah very cool. Looking forward to seeing what you come up with! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
