<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7391</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jump 3 feet to the left and you goin' in da o-chin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is exactly what happened to a bunch of scotty's employees in Indy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always imagined this is what my dog's tongue actually is, a sentient pink tentacle monster thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is illuminated, family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> vv rare hawaiian husker pupper dos a heckin relax after long flight to Indiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at a boutique hotel and we have a pretty popular lounge that a lot of locals frequent. I had a man call me today saying he was thinking about proposing to his girlfriend in front of one of her favorite art pieces that we have at the hotel (they had their first date in said lounge). I helped him set up a little 'scavenger hunt' from the lounge to the art piece using our art cards we give to guests when they check in, the last one asking "will you marry me?" I love going out of my way for guests to do things like this. He was nervous about the whole idea but i reassured that the thought was incredibly sweet and she was lucky to spend the rest of her life with him. She said yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to the [NPS website](https://www.nps.gov/grsm/planyourvisit/temproadclose.htm), they have a map of affected areas, and the extent of damage - they also have a list of all closed trails. I am actually going to Gatlinburg area for my birthday (mid February) and did a little research just so I could make the most of the trip after everything that has happened there. From what I read, Gatlinburg is recovering well and a small chunk on the park was affected, near the Chimney Tops trail.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wonderful, i will provide a wonderfully moist fruit cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> month/day/year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> edit: might </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got really excited when I realized I will be alive for 1/23/45. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's the only thing i looked at the 30 times i watched it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
