<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 08:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the single page web design which is selling only one product I would like to suggest you to see most famous website which is https://www.kitkat.com/android </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft puts AI to work in Office 365 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 07:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 07:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing is impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie pirate? Dont trust Plex Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 07:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite Privacy Concerns, Google Allo Scored More Than 1 Million Downloads Already </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plan for future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jasmine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Cheap Wildcard SSL Certificate Providers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 11:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 10:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people suggest to use .htaccess for redirection process. Even I have read recently one discussion at [google group](https://groups.google.com/forum/#!topic/manchester-wordpress-user-group/Q7UQ9Nj0aIU) too about this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asia markets lower while awaiting Clinton versus Trump debate, OPEC meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 10:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to apply for Social Security Retirement Benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 10:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 10:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For wildcard ssl certificate I would like to suggest you Comodo, GeoTrust and Thawte certificate authority. There are lots of other providers/resellers and certificate authorities you will get, which are offering wildcard ssl cert. But one thing keep in mind before taking this product is that decide on for which domain name you want to take for Wildcard SSL. Because it secures first level of sub domains of primary domain name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 11:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, small business websites which only show business information like website url, its social accounts, about us, phone number etc. may happen that they could becoming obsolete in the future because why people pay $500 to 5k for simple one page website. 

This type of thing happens because many business must have to create online identity for their offline business and also they are not much aware that they can also create this type of single page website with free website builder tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a world of free operating systems, can Windows 10 survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 11:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 11:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Television. Because younger generation mostly have attachment with their smart phones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 10:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strictly following rules and regulations of government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 11:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely yes for 'brighter future for web designers' as per more businesses are coming online because to entertain their customers and put their online identity towards market.

You can build your own website through various website builder tools but still there will remain some limitations as per website requirement. So for that organization/company/individual will need web designer to make their website unique. So don't worry about web designing future because it will grow day by day.

Read more on [pro and cons](https://designshack.net/articles/business-articles/sitebuilder-pros-cons/) of website builder tools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 10:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My children (When he and she becomes sad and crying). I have twins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-Driving Cars Gain Powerful Ally: The Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 10:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mozilla slowly grants multi-process Firefox to more users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 10:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Allo's generic auto-replies can't handle life's tough conversations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 10:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France just became the first country to ban all plastic plates, cups, and utensils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 10:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 14:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are designer either have well experience or junior level experience for web designing and you are going to show your work to people or other clients then to add your photo to your portfolio site is not any bad idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 13:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything, but specially my kind nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hands-on: Opera's free, unlimited browser VPN is ready for secure surfing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 13:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 13:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to submit two different certificate requests because many certificate authorities are giving unlimited server license. 

 I have a standard "Standard UCC SSL Up to 5"

If you are using UCC SSL certificate then you can secure multiple domains with it but how many number of domains you will secure with UCC SSL certificate is different form one provider to another.

You can read more about this [unlimited server license feature](https://www.clickssl.net/blog/unlimited-server-license-certificates
) to know how it will be beneficial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google's new acquisition makes building chatbots easier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 11:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked Google Pixel phones might look familiar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 11:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johnson   Johnson Buying 100 Megawatts of Texas Wind Power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intel Raises Third-Quarter Guidance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check how Google Chrome Beta allows Android to play YouTube in the background </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon Go Plus: Where to buy the Pokemon Go device </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get 44 nutritious food which comes under only $1. Read more [about it](http://greatist.com/health/44-healthy-foods-under-1). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think for girls, personality matters a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are some iPhone 7s making hissing noises? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Succession Planning: Why Every Entrepreneur Needs To Prepare For The Worst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 10:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best place to be a Social Entrepreneur 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 10:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 10:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can get one through SiteGround. It's called a "wildcard SSL". I don't know what that means...

If you want to know about wildcard ssl in detail then refer this thread where [my reply](https://www.reddit.com/r/nginx/comments/4odbbl/why_doesnt_a_wildcard_cert_cover_tld/d4cunen) has already listed.

 I just want 1. people to feel like they can buy things from my shop securely. 2. No pop-ups warning customers that the site's SSL or whatever else can't be confirmed and so they should "Go Back". 3. 404 error messages on "My Account" sub-domain. Number 3 might be an unrelated issue...

If your payment page, account page are on sub domain of main domain like payment.maindomain.com, account.maindomain.com then wildcard ssl is the best for that to provide secure connection to your website's customers/users.

 So, do I really need Encryption on EVERY sub-domain? Wouldn't I just need it for the parts of the website were users/customers enter personal information? And, wouldn't something like that be cheaper than this wildcard SSL?

Wildcard ssl secures one level unlimited sub domains of the main domain so it is good to enable it on all sub domains inplace of only parts of the website where user/customers enter personal information.

If still you want to secure only pages which accept personal infomation and number of that pages are only two then you can go with single domain ssl certificate which price remains less than wildcard ssl certificate but still I would like to suggest you wildcard ssl certificate because maintainance of diverse ssl certificate will become lengthy process.

 "Enabling SSL is a good thing but I would outsource the encryption of payment details to your PSP as dealing with PCI compliance is expensive and a big headache for SME's". Can someone please explain this sentence to me like I'm five.

TheNick22 has [replied](https://www.reddit.com/r/Entrepreneur/comments/52wzhh/noob_questions_about_ssl_certificates_for_online/d7oxf6v) recently on this comment  for more explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenovo pokes fun at the iPhone 7 as it tries to remind people the Moto Z exists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 08:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reviews for the iPhone 7/7Plus, Apple Watch Series 2 and Air Pods are in!: Apple Byte </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 08:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Initial Stock of Apples iPhone 7 Plus Has Sold Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, in nearer future chrome will give warning for websites who are not using ssl certificate. This update will be effected on Jan 2017. As per update on [Google online security blog](https://security.googleblog.com) it has stated that "Starting January 2017, Chrome 56 will label HTTP pages with password or credit card form fields as "not secure," given their particularly sensitive nature."

It is good update for all online users and to improve data security over the web. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the iOS 10 features that guard your privacy and security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 08:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 10 best wireless headphones for your new iPhone 7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 08:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft's Windows 10 'Redstone 2' build 14926 adds minor new features, many fixes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 08:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> eBay Launches 'Quick Sale' Smartphone Trade-In Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 10:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have knowledge for 'how to select colors for your web design or web site' then you should first understand the basics of color which you can read from here http://blog.hubspot.com/marketing/color-theory-design#sm.000013jptyh7hhfozu3i5oaknin07 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 10:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Google Search console is new in google analytics which shows keywords through which people comes on the website. You can also take help of google webmaster tool for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 09:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I came to know that 'he spent too much time with his new friends' by other person (who is well trusted). Thus to get involved chances are zero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he got new friends and was spending too much time with them in place of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung Galaxy S8 might ditch the headphone jack, too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exercise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. household incomes soared in 2015, recording biggest gain in decades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AdBlock Plus Is Launching a Marketplace for 'Acceptable' Ads, but Will It Just Infuriate Everyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Common Prostate Cancer Screening Method Is Obsolete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 09:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to read a book without opening it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 09:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 08:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was told that maybe my CA can add an alias with my old domain as the value, so traffic to my site via the old domain is secured.

Certificate Authority (CA) can't do anything like making an alias for old domain.

 Is this alias strategy valid? If not, is there any other way to get me out of this pickle?

Alias strategy is not valid.

There two ways with you :

1.   Either renew/purchase new ssl for old domain.

2.   Either redirect your old domain to new domain (which has already secured with ssl certificate).

Normally, basic process to [get ssl certificate](https://www.reddit.com/r/ssl/comments/50ht1z/are_ssl_certificates_simply_signed_csrs/d754m41) is very simple but as per validation type it requires different documents for authentication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 08:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spend 70% on expenses,entertainment etc.

Spend 10% for needy people

Spend 20% on future investment
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 7 Plus Vs iPhone 6S Plus: What's The Difference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 08:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10: 10 new features worth the upgrade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 07:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do reading about latest things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think about google that if it will know about user's future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I have also seen this type of logo with many sites but it is not any SSL CA site seal but but it can be customized logo to show clients that they are on the secure site. But do not know why people put this kind of logo instead of the certificate authority site seal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most certificate authorities like rapidssl, symantec, geotrust, thawte provide free site seal within ssl certificate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Know Your Ovarian Cancer Risk -- and the Symptoms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it stinks that the iPhone 7 has no headphone jack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Stop Solution for SSL Certificates Renewal at Discount Price </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One year later: Can Android 7.0 Nougat save the Pixel C? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 07:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont Wait To Update Your Apple Products </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 07:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Photos will compensate for your shaky-cam Live Photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 7, iPhone 7 Plus, and Apple Watch Series 2 preorders are now live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's understand with an example :

If you have one client and he/she has multiple domains like 1.com, 2.net, 3.info etc which has hosted/not hosted on same server. 

Then it is possible to secure all those domains with single multi domain ssl certificate because most certificate authorities are giving feature of unlimited server licensing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also think same. It's upgraded version of cheese on the bread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best resource to understand about search engine optimization in detail.

Ryan_77

But for how to use Google analytic you should read [this](https://moz.com/blog/absolute-beginners-guide-to-google-analytics). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's depend on particular situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My smartphone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Maps' App Adds Alternatives to Booking an Uber Ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 07:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter now acts more like a messaging app with read receipts, typing indicators   web link previews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 07:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 07:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sometimes context can help.

Yes, off-course. It's my pleasure.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 11:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give design and layout to resume will not hurt your chance but it looks quite unprofessional as per I think. Because I usually prefer to make resume on simple white background to easily read for interviewer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beware: The 32GB iPhone 7 soon won't feel so roomy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 11:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 11:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Positive Thinking' to look at anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 11:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $10 per month is very high but for reliable and affordable ssl certificate you should checkout at [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/web_design/comments/4vjiec/bestcheapest_place_for_ssl_cert/d655hj1).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple has quietly cut the cost of replacing a cracked iPhone display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 7 Vs iPhone 7 Plus: What's The Difference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then people will remain on Reddit. Doing new research and analysis to write new articles, share them on reddit and provide quality replies for getting upvotes that will increase popularity of reddit as well will take the world to the next level of technology . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give forgiveness for mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon has launched its restaurant food delivery service in London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 11:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 11:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For any business website or news site, ssl certificate is good to deploy at each and every page in spite of enabling it at only login or payment page. There many other benefits of ssl everywhere like increase trust of customers/users towards website including boost in search engine rankings etc. etc.

If talking about to deploy ssl in online/ecommerce business in general benefit sense then ev ssl certificate remains the best for it and which benefits this type of certificate provides that you can read from [here](https://www.clickssl.net/blog/ev-ssl-certificate-helps-to-increase-revenue-and-profits). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon's latest Prime exclusive phone is the $99.99 Moto G Play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 questions we have before Sony's big PlayStation event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When me and my wife had celebrated our first baby birthday.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instagram is killing its awesome Photo Map, sigh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smartphone apps account for half the time Americans spend online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 09:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why this happened to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple patches OS X to fix serious security flaw discovered in iOS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 08:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 10 growth slowdown has bright side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 08:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 11:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I become angry when someone become rude to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 11:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 11:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep quite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia confirms first Zika case, victim had visited Singapore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HTC makes $5 million investment in VR gaming startup Steel Wool Studios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, to get ssl certificate is not only just sign CSR. It requires many things. When you go to buy ssl certificate then which basic things will require are listed below :

Unique IP Address

Domain name

CSR

Business Documents

How to go forward step by step from generating csr to installing ssl certificate for your domain, you can read from [here](https://www.clickssl.net/blog/how-do-i-get-an-ssl-certificate). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenovo will ditch hard keyboards in planned Chromebook and 2-in-1s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 07:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is using ev ssl certificate for its login page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Is Offering Influencers a New Way to Make Money on the Platform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 09:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google's new In Apps search lets you look through your Android apps for information </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 09:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 09:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your website purpose is to send or receive confidential information through email only then it's good to protect it with ssl certificate.

Email on server have already encryption built in or not is depend on have you secured your email with ssl certificate or not?

**For example :**

If you enable single domain ssl certificate for your domain name xyz.com and your email is mail.xyz.com then mail.xyz.com will not be secured with single domain ssl certificate because single domain ssl certificate secures only one domain name.

But yes if you enable ssl certificate on mail.xyz.com then it will secure your mail only but will secure your main domain name which is xyz.com

**Three types of ssl certificate you can purchase for your email :**

**1.**  Single domain SSL Certificate (Secures only one domain name)

**2.**  Wildcard SSL Certificate (Secures main domain name and its unlimited sub domains)

**3.**  UCC/SAN (multi domain) SSL certificate (Secures multiple domain names)

Read more at [SSL certificate for mail server](https://www.clickssl.net/blog/ssl-certificate-for-ms-exchange-server-2007-2010) security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is also some limitations for wildcard ssl certificate based on weekly basis https://letsencrypt.org/docs/rate-limits/ And after 90 days you have to renew your ssl certificate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What just happened to Apple, explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Self-driving) car wars heat up between Google, Uber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon Dash - who wants to live in a push-button world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon tests 30-hour week for some teams of employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 09:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 09:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checkout http://www.technorms.com/33240/tools-to-aggregate-social-media-updates to get top 10 free social media aggregation tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In place of cheaper but for free alternative you should go with 1 1 where they are offering free private domain registration with each domain name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I slap you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am falling down from my home's stairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Stocks Rebound, as Financial Shares Rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Note 7 review: Samsung nearly achieves smartphone perfection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Cast now native to Chrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy groups call foul on WhatsApp sharing data with Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dollar at 3-week high, bonds and stocks sell off on hawkish Fed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber, Careem Suspend Services in UAE Capital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven Predictions for Cognitive Analytics in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google taps Airbnb exec to turn self-driving cars into a business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philips Hue now has a motion sensor that can turn on lights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you?

How are you? 

What do you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WhatsApp's Plan To Share Data With Facebook Could Be A Turning Point In The Battle For Trust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft makes it easy to report hate speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What am I missing about self-driving cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 13:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is something done by me the wrong way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung Galaxy S7   S7 Edge Receive August Security Patch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pinterest acquires Instapaper, which will live on as a separate app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha ha. I think many person like you and me are here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Makes it Easier for iOS Users to Tweet in the Dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 12:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomi To Launch Smartphone In The 'Near Future' And New Product In October In The US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The person who speaks lie to prove himself true always. I have met this type of person many years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holidays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's how to install Android Nougat on a Nexus right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you purchase domain from one provider and host it with other provider then it is ok. No need to domain transfer for it. But yes you also want your domain with dreamhost then it is compulsory to transfer it. Read more at https://help.dreamhost.com/hc/en-us/articles/215250318-How-do-I-transfer-my-domain-registration-to-DreamHost- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If class for people then I don't believe in any class because there is only one class that is humanity, which is at the top of each class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are you trading the rally in oil prices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before marriage... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook resurrects its 2004 model in new app to connect classmates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 07:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 09:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are confuse about table and lists elements of HTML then learn more about it in details with example from here https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTML/Element

CSS (cascading style sheets) which is used for giving style to your website content and structure.

To know about more for CSS you should visit https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/Learn/CSS/Introduction_to_CSS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo says Pokmon Go is driving 3DS Pokmon game sales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dollar edges up, but on track for weekly loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 08:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
