<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people here just link their biotroofs.

They come here to directly bash on BPers :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *TF2menu.wav plays on the background* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed most of your post revolve around that.

Don't take me bad, but honestly I don't even feel like answering that considering that we both will end up disagreeing and you seem to have a pretty "passive aggressive" manner of talking (might just be your "normal way", but to me it reads as such), so... I think you'd probably have better results asking that on another sub not related to BP/RP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, I think r/purplepilldebate would be way more open for that than here considering how it is infested with other RPers disguised as BPers.

^It ^feels ^fike ^I'm ^writing ^about ^TF2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I met 0 women with ADHD on my entire life.

But men? About 6 already, and that is, 6 who are *officially diagnosed*. There are probably a few more who also have and never did a checkup because think that's "for pooftahs" or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RPers inside this sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the heck the sudden wave of redpillers inside this sub came from?

I mean, just... don't they have weights to lift or something instead of coming to a sub they don't even like?


*[Spyoverhere.wav]* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> individual human cases

Wat

I mean, most people I met _in general_ can't STEM well, so of course both sides will much probably end up on the "individual class" type. It's not even that "women tend to not STEM well", it's people in general because they either get tired of it quickly, can't get it, DON'T want to get it or have small attention spans. Hurp de durp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see your point here, but still, he says as if every woman ever has ADHD or something of that kind when, in fact, that's bullshit. It's like the same fallacy they go against of "men don't pay attention to anything" said by elder women, but with the opposite gender. 

What a bunch of jeenius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went there two years ago to laugh a bit from times to times.

6 months later I started to dislike it because it was turning pretty much into facebook but cringier (I mean, I do have an account on facebook, but at least I can avoid the cringe; on 9gag, cringe was the entire first page) and with more reposts than daily Reddit. I saw the posts of the kind you mentioned, and back then, I didn't mind them at all. I can say for once that I agreed with some of them because the "THEY are like that, I'm different" kind of thought came up lots of times on my mind.

Then, I decided to finally leave 9gag after a video that made me unconfortable had a bunch of comments bashing the girl on it -- and mind you, I was still transitioning, so the thing was *really* bad to have me reacting like that --. I don't really remember a lot of it, but heh, I tend to completely forget things that make me feel extremely bad.

It was probably the best choice I could've taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, you surely haven't met my closest male friend. I'm a rock compared to his rainbow of emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/im14andthisisdeep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot to add that he doesn't reply to women because to him we're probably unworthy and trying to manipulate him.

I think we better stop wasting our times on this dude, seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bad boy theory

Like that one that says women like bad boys? Fuck no, I never ever once wanted a "bad boy". In fact, most that approached me were bad boys and I plain rejected them. Feels like I only attract this kind of dude, and it's annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A woman (...) expects that you're going to say everything SHE wants to hear.

First off, one thing I noticed happening the most are women who hate guys who act normal around his friends and suddenly change around her because "she's a woman, you can't be yourself around one". It's not even that she expect people around her to act the way she wants, it's just that it gets tiring after some time to notice men feeling at ease around his friends while being a non-interactive rock close to women *simply because HE thinks women wouldn't like him the way he is*. I can say for myself: I had a bunch of guys act the way they were around each other with me; it was the best thing possible and I laughed along with them. But you know what people said about that? That "they were interested on me" (they were not), that I was "their bitch", that they were "acting incorrectly around a woman" because you're not supposed to just be yourself around the opposite gender apparently... and to my side, the list is waaaaaaay longer. The amount of people trying to force me the idea that I was being a slut or shouldn't be talking with men was high. Also, the things they said were even worse than the ones I mentioned there, and most involved the idea that I was going to turn into a whore even though I didn't sleep/have a relationship with any of them.

Social norms are what makes it that way, not "women" wanting you to be the way you want or "men" applying filters. If you notice the amount of people who feel odd at seeing men and women being themselves around each other here instead of following these norms, you'll get why it happens. It's not the girl who approached you who's at fault here; it's those who teach that. And it's not only women who teach that; in fact, I've seen more men keeping this ideology flowing than women.

Ah, and just to let you know: nobody really feels at ease when meeting someone new. Everyone tries to present themselves while not being an open book, so if that's what you mean by "filter", everyone has it. The problem is when this filter makes you be someone completely different like you're saying there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course people would react if a woman suddenly kicked you out of nowhere, son. If nobody didn't, there's something off happening then.

Also, if it feels better, I was kicked by dudes lots of times before. And you know, I don't believe in AMALT because these fuckers were assholes, just like you happened to meet an asshole woman, too. Assholes are everywhere and on every demographic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes do.

And it has the oddest sense of humour I've ever seen :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy little trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the second question: people aren't like your porn characters who have 1 dimensional personalities. People are, well, *people*.

Paraphrasing a certain brit, *"ALLLLLLLLL THE PEOPLE, SO MANYYY PEOPLE"*... and they're all fookin' different.

^^^All ^^^my ^^^people ^^^right ^^^here ^^^right ^^^now, ^^^d'ya ^^^know ^^^wot ^^^I ^^^mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I'm not even at Uni (decided to wait some more until I feel comfortable  with a fucked up sleep pattern + more than 10 hours studying everyday again) and landed the job. Why? 'Cause as my boss said, I proved to know more than others that came before me to try getting the job and was much more chill than them around certain situations. He also said I proved to be extremely effective compared to the other people he hired before, so... hooray for me :P


EDIT: typing at 3AM makes me not English well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes it funny is that I was/am more STEM than these two together.

I mean, I am the one working on an IT+admin job rite now while they don't :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool and uncool at the same time. From one side you can get awed at his incredible abilities at *fuckin' remembering tons of Portuguese rules from now and before* and know how to apply them, along with a huge grasp of grammar and proper knowledge around Literature... but be a complete asshole when it comes to reading other texts that have mistakes that not even Professors identify at first try :^D

On the good side, *free puns*.

EDIT: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7th grade

 *xD*

Something seems off here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So close, yet so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noice trolling, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think these things need to be started by the parents, though. If there's one thing I noticed on recent years, that'd be parents who teach nothing about behaviour to their kids and expect school to do the service... but forget their children don't respect "authorities" like they should because at home they don't have to.

Hell, the thing I saw the most recently is completely "submissive" parents with kids that do whatever they want around here. I'm not saying they should be tyrants, but fuck, these kids didn't knew *the basic* about certain stuff, man, and it's saddening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets three times funnier considering that "granola" here can be a slang for "gay" :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "groping males" thing is pretty high up here during "High School" (we don't name it like that, but anyway) years, too, and it's generally males doing that to other males... and if you're one who goes through that and dislikes it, you're the one who's a "gay bitch". They generally tend to not care mostly (or act like they don't but actually do), but they're also the ones who have homophobic tendencies unironically.

Trust me, I have a friend who's on the equivalent of High School here. He just stopped having the problem of being groped by other "hetero" dudes after he finally became so enraged he broke a table with his fists to not hit them and told them to go away -- and mind you, he's the most chill dude I ever met on my life... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny to read that considering that both people I went on a relationship were nerds.

One more of a geek culture/linguistics nerd and the other more of a Philosophy nerd. Unfortunately, both went into a TRP mode and neglected these sides of them because "not STEM enough". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Holy grail* dick size

Nonexistent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ever hear the tragedy of Diogenes the Cynic?

It's not a story Plato would tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
