<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7048</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should be able to read Champion lores at the loading screen when mousing over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 02:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make the waiting way more interesting and also it's a nice approach to understand more about the League world while waiting to play it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seven Lions and MitiS are probably my favorite musicians of the last 3 years or so. 
It's because of them that I work with music today too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amumu's concept and kit is so on point. His ultimate is about wanting everyone around to keep close to him so he doesn't feel so sad. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 07:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not blaming anyone, just asking.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't we accept a match just by hitting ENTER? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 07:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title, and give me reasons to why not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 02:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only because of that, but mostly the scripting that was really smart. It was pretty surprising (not like those predictale questions) and understood the community memes really well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 02:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best fix would be to switch his W with his R really, make the Abyssal Voyage CD around 20 and with decreased range in the first levels; make the Devour an ult with around 50 seconds of wait time, but with a small buff: now he gets movespeed while devouring both enemy and ally champions.

That way he wouldn't be able to spam the ability of saving his teammates all the time and in laning phase there would be more chances of the enemy bot to kill your AD pre-6. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Riot should keep up with IEM Interviewer (Kristine Leahy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 02:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like how confident she looks and how she brings polemic questions right in the face of the players. I think that is something we're missing in e-sports and it quite brings some joy to the audience. 
Oh, and my, she's gorgeous. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporting some Tahm Kench weird bugs (Pre-Season Patch) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 16:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I played only one game with him after the pre-season launch and found out 2 bugs already, and one of them has happened twice with me in the last 2 patches. 


1 - I couldn't cast my W (Devour) on my teammate Yi for the entire game. If it weren't by the bug, I would have saved him from death SO many times. (Almost 100% sure this bug was reported in reddit before) (I think it has to do with the meditate interaction, but not sure if it can happen with other champions though)


2 - Sometimes when I cast the Devour on enemy champions, they could still use skills or autoattacks inside of me. 
Ex: I used it on enemy Caitlyn and after ~0.5 seconds she used her Piltover Peacemaker inside of me and got out, even before I could spit her.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 02:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a good team to pair with TSM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 01:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Olleh is still in China playing for HKEsports </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 01:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can easily confirm its Rush behind the other misterious guy not only by looking at his hands and wrist, there's a tiny leak of black hair on top of Hai's head which sells the information. Or it could be the coach.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Can't find!! [Song Name/Video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 01:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=06VftHnEwpE

Does anyone knows the name of this song?! I can't find it anywhere, even Shazam couldn't do the job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 05:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A better interaction than Lamb and Wolf already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 6 incoming, still no given priority to Taric </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 20:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riot seems to have forgotten about Taric at all. They said there was a rework incoming together with Poppy, but we are still waiting. 
His models are really bad in comparison to everything else. Look old and messy. His gems definitely aren't as bright as before.
 
I know millions of posts like this one were made before but... 
Can't we just have them already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 19:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winter? Then you mean Westeros teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Competitive Match Bug Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 18:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I was playing a competitive match and I noticed after the first round that a lot of things were not behaving right. 

1 - Smoke bombs were not appearing after being launched to the ground, and I could see everything behind it. That was the most gamebreaking bug. 

2 - Music in the game gone. 

3 - Couldn't see who killed who, only the money being cashed in.

4 - At the end of every round, nothing showed up, it just moved to the next round.

And I lost that game, mainly because the screen froze after round ~6 and I had to relaunch the game, losing two full rounds. 
I've never seen anything like that before and I don't know if it's a common issue, and also can't quite tell what caused it. Just felt the necessity of sending here for you guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 22:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " Ok guys, let's just destroy the inhibitors all games, go back to mid and capture we all using ult to reach and destroy the nexus, since olaf's video made sucess, we'll probably do too. "

Sorry, don't want to hate, but I couldn't see the fun/originality with this one. (Maybe its just me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't we see gold earned between the two teams in the middle of the matches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 13:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
