<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3967</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also was able to explore most of the recommendations I've read in /r/travel about London. I've tried my best to summarize in my blog post here: http://urban-trailseeker.blogspot.com/2016/05/london-our-gateway-to-europe.html

I know I missed plenty, but I thought it'd be worth sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Originally from Seattle, I particularly enjoyed this gray view from the London Eye! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just would like to thank you for sharing this. If I hadn't stumbled upon your post, I would have missed out on one of the most breathtaking sights I've ever seen. 

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 05:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad how we just let this happen to us. I mean, future generations will look back at us and wonder why we let big business fuck us over so badly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 21:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to make this walk from my bus stop on 3rd. I worked down near the ferries in Post Ave. It was very cool to see things just starting to open up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find [your TDEE](http://www.fitnessfrog.com/calculators/tdee-calculator.html). Add 300-500 to that number and consume that amount of calories. Track your food using [MyFitnessPal](http://www.myfitnesspal.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! 2 hours right before close is the best time at all the gyms I've been a member of (except 24 Hour Fitness, for obvious reasons). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 22:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncle Ike's on Capitol Hill has a glass shop that has selections from many local artists. You could try there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 21:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find [your TDEE](http://www.fitnessfrog.com/calculators/tdee-calculator.html). Subtract 300-500 from that number and consume only that amount of calories. Track your food using [MyFitnessPal](http://www.myfitnesspal.com/).

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 21:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you. I've got a family member who was born and raised in Seattle, wore a Seahawks jersey during our first SuperBowl, visited Boston for a couploe months, then all of a sudden became a HUGE Pats fan. Sold his Seahawks jerseys, buys nothing but Pats stuff, talks so much shit about the Seahawks... I don't understand people sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 21:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhat related, but I abhor fans who call others "bandwagon" fans just because they can't recite the play-by-play statistics of some game in back in 2002.

There are *new* fans every season, and I feel like it's our responsibility to "train" them into the fans we hope to be ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 21:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I also tend to get into huge arguments with my brother, who is a Pats fan. I'm going to try to not let it get to me so much.

Yea, I've got some Pats fans in my family. Since they won that SB, they have all the rights to talk all the shit they want. However, I can't wait for the rematch... I hope we demolish Beli/Brady into retirement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 21:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez... this'll be a tough one for all of us, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm 25, roughly 280 5'9''

First and foremost, *fix your diet*. You will see a huge difference by doing that first! I'd also pass on the supplements for now, trust me they won't help you at this stage.

Start by [calculating your TDEE](http://www.fitnessfrog.com/calculators/tdee-calculator.html). Then, keep calorie consumption under that number. Track your food using [MyFitnessPal](http://www.myfitnesspal.com/).

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel like I'm not very filled out.

Bulk. Bulk until you hate how "fat" you've gotten. Then cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I'll start:

I'd like to improve my ability to recognize the opponent's pre-snap formations and play patterns better. Sort of like playing "defensive coordinator" in my mind.

I was also really negative early on in the year, thinking we wouldn't even make the playoffs. This season, I want to be more optimistic, but *cautiously* optimistic, as the old saying goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will you, personally, improve as a fan this season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this conversation with a couple of my close friends. It's easy to talk about how the Seahawks will improve this upcoming season, but how are you improving as a fan? Is there something you were absolutely wrong about last season? Were you overly negative? Too optimistic? Didn't go to enough home games?

I'd be curious to see what /r/Seahawks has to say! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 00:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got great results out of the stock headlights by simply upgrading the wiring. I ordered one of these [Putco harnesses](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B001P29X4G) intending to upgrade the bulbs later, but I got enough a big enough boost in light that I haven't found the need to upgrade the lights themselves.

If you decide to upgrade the bulbs, I'd recommend a more reliable harness, but this is a cheap/quick alternative.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 21:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/CherokeeXJ/comments/49v0p4/any_other_5speed_xjs/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How can I go about motivating myself to improve myself?

Motivation is overrated. Discipline is everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 18:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike some software engineers I know, ayeeeeee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 18:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Box jumps, if you do them correctly, activate much of your core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 00:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say Seahawks fans aren't as "hot and cold" as you seem to think, even during times of mediocrity. Attendance has been [fairly steady](http://www.statista.com/statistics/249667/average-home-attendance-of-the-seattle-seahawks/) since 2008 (or even since [2006](http://espn.go.com/nfl/attendance/_/year/2006)).

I can't say the same for [Mariners fans](http://www.baseball-reference.com/teams/SEA/attend.shtml), seeing as to how attendance has been in decline for a long time now.

I'm not big on hockey, so I don't know much about the Thunderbirds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most dramatic impact? How's your diet? Most folks can feel and look good if they simply fix their intake, whether it's eating healthier or restricting calories. You can't out-cardio a bad diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ran an 8k in the wind and pouring rain, with about a week's notice. It was kind of miserable, but I'm glad I was able to finish. Portland is gorgeous even when it's gray! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 06:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These shoes are meant to be worn on the decks of boats. You can read more about the [history of boat shoes here](http://www.gentlemansgazette.com/boat-shoes-guide-buy-style-history-care/). It's a "crime" because it wouldn't make sense to wear socks with shoes that are likely to be near or in water.

If you like socks, wear just about any other shoe, perhaps? Sneakers? If you like the look of them, get some [Blucher Mocs](http://www.llbean.com/llb/shop/11575?page=mens-handsewn-moccasins-blucher-moc) or other types of camp/moc-toe shoes/boots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 04:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant the blue ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Sperrys. I can't quite verbalize why, but they seem more "fun" and casual to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). It's a short read and very easy to follow. Don't overcomplicate. Want to lose weight? Eat less. Want to get strong? Lift heavy things. Want to be fast at running? Run.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested to see if it could work. Seems fairly athletic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since they are accessory, add anything you feel like targeting. I happen to add bicep/tricep workouts to Workout B and lat raise/pull-downs to Workout A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any "stretch" chinos/khakis that fit similarly to the stretch Levis 514s? I've tried the Alpha Athletic Fit w/ Stretch, looking to give JCrew Factory's Sutton w/ Flex a try.

Any other recommendations in this "elastane" pant material much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 06:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the weather being what it is, you might actually find some solitude at some of the generic "car camping" spots. However, camping is popular out here. So, of course, the farther out you can hike/drive, the more solitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 23:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forest green masterrace! Sorry, had to. Welcome to the club. Have the wrench handy at all times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing this, the biggest gripe I have on my Weekender is the lack of a "date". Looks like the Chrono might be a suitable replacement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know how to drive anything else...

http://i.imgur.com/JUYQcxl.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you could approach them and ask? I prefer them to those folks who pander me the entire block trying to shake my hand and get me to sign a petition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to give you the benefit of the doubt and trust that you've already read [the wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Seattle/wiki/index) for all the basic spots most tourist enjoy seeing.

Drink coffee: do a Google Map search of "coffee" on Capitol Hill and pick one, most are good. Yes, I know there are coffee places outside of Capitol Hill, but some of my favorites are here. Also, checkout Vivace South Lake Union and Seattle Coffee Works downtown.

Eat pho: apparently, Pho can be hard to find outside of Seattle, hit up a Pho spot. There are plenty.

Drink beer: breweries are everywhere. My favorites are Fremont Brewing, Georgetown Brewing, and Hales Brewing.

Play this game: only go to a place (restaurant, convenience store, bar, etc.) that you CAN'T go to in Eugene. Have a 7-11 in Eugene? Can't go there. Have a Starbucks in Eugene? Can't go there.

Goodluck, have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shakes are supplements to real food. If you're getting protein through food, then no need for shakes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My rule is: if you're running anything longer than 5k, get dedicated running shoes. Go to RoadRunner (or other specialized running stores) and get properly fitted based on your running style and arch.

For lifting, you want minimal heel-toe drop. I have a pair of Asics for running and Inov8 for lifting/training.

Goodluck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo.. Forest green master race! Really though OP, really nice XJ, welcome aboard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 20:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to live right above my gym. Now, I have to commute to the gym like a normal person. I wish I could live there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 01:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there's anything wrong with lifting without shoes. Minimalist shoes try to emulate a flat, low-drop surface. That said, I prefer to lift in shoes to protect my feet from objects I might cut myself on in the gym. Meh, it's more of a germaphobe thing than anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 07:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that's true. I've been in there when it was quiet, but I recall the music being super loud at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 06:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cafe Vita is a good one, but it can be busy even during the workday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 00:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Watches/wiki/buyingguide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 22:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I did boxing for a short while and fell in love with jump-rope. You might look into plyometrics (mainly box workouts) if you're interested in getting a good workout "jumping" on/over things. Also helps with explosive athletic movements, if you're into that kind of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 22:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are pretty effective. Fat loss can be done without either, assuming your diet is on point. If you enjoy jump-roping more, do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found these two videos especially helpful for learning deadlift:

[How to Deadlift by Alan Thrall](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y1IGeJEXpF4)

[How to Deadlift by Art of Manliness and Mark Rippetoe](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4AObAU-EcYE)

If you have access to a trainer, don't be afraid to ask him/her. If you have access to a camera, post your lift here for a form-check.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start by reading [the wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). It's short and will answer nearly all of your questions. I'd stress that you don't need a super strict diet to "drop extra weight as fast as possible". It's crash dieting and isn't going to be sustainable. Patience and hard work, it'll take time.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also how does one add photos to the post? I have a couple clothing items I'm curious as to whether not they fit correctly

Use [Imgur](http://imgur.com/) and directly link the photos here.

 So, do I need to change it up to something else other than sportswear and activewear?

I'd avoid heavily branded clothing, as it can look tacky. You don't have to dress like a runway model to impress the ladies. Just find clothes that fit. Getting the right fit, alone, will make you look much better.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 04:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your diet on point? If it's not, start there. Commonly recommended supplements are creatine, protein powder, and a multi-vitamin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 22:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to avoid big clubs nowadays, I'm more into bars/lounges. These are subjective, and I'm sure people have their own opinions on them, but I often hit these spots up:

Capitol Hill

* 95 Slide
* Linda's
* 500 East
* Bill's on Broadway
* Still Liquor
* Sun Liquor

Fremont

* 9 Million Unmarked
* Ballroom
* Norms
* Red Door
* Fremont Brewery

Ballard

* Shelter
* King's
* Hattie's
* Matador

And I'm sure there's tons of spots in between that are good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try a different neighborhood? I mean, Capitol Hill is pretty lively in terms of hopping from bar to bar. You could try Fremont or Ballard as well. Lots of bars within walking distance of each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, it kind of depends. When I'm high, my judgement is definitely off. But some of my friends can smoke before physical activity, and I wouldn't be able to tell. I'd say it depends on the person.

Post-workout, though, I feel like everyone could benefit from the effects, despite how "impaired" they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not recommend taking any "metabolic enhancers" or "fat burners" at all, especially to someone starting out. In fact, I wouldn't recommend *any* supplements to anyone until he/she fixes his/her diet first.

 My goal is essentially to lose weight

You can do that without any supplementation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't eat anything that would impair my ability to *safely* lift weights at the gym. Why would I endanger myself and those around me? 

However, I occasionally smoke or eat edibles after the gym. Helps me relax and sleep. Also, the munchies help when I'm bulking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 20:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I just couldn't get over the fact that the changing rooms have no privacy and the older men there just treat it as a place to hang out with their wangs out. 

You could change into your clothes before heading to the gym. Or change quicker, I can't imagine it taking too long to get geared up for a workout. Or... grow up a bit? Wangs are normal.

 I like my privacy a little too much.

You could start building a home gym. It'd be expensive, but you'd be able to work out in the comfort of your garage. If you aren't doing anything with weights, you could try a living room program like P90X/Insanity.

 a simple, easy to follow workout plan for me to follow.

Visit /r/bodyweightfitness or check out the many programs listed in [the wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started#wiki_adding_exercise).

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's fair. Just know that you can lift weights, eat right, and NOT gain too much muscle mass. That said, I recommend the [wiki page](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started) from /r/fitness. It's a great primer for people starting out.

I'd also recommend looking at a beginner strength program. The one I see touted all the time is [Stronglifts 5x5](http://stronglifts.com/5x5/#Summary_of_Stronglifts_52155). It focuses on the basic compound movements.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer to do 5x5 if I'm looking to add more weight to my lifts. If I'm looking to get a burn in, I'll switch to 4x10 or 4x7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, "you won't accidentally Arnold." Don't be afraid to lift weights, maintaining strength is important as you get older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there's a lot of hype around it, but a standing desk might help you build some strength in your legs throughout the day. They ain't cheap though. But yes, find something you love doing, it doesn't have to be extremely exhausting. Hiking can be fun and really rewarding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 21:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How heavy is the weight? Do you have access to a gym? Caloric intake will also dictate how much mass you are putting on. Are you eating above TDEE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 21:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an excellent article breaking down the anatomy of the shoulder, how the muscles are used, and recommendations on which workouts target each part: http://www.bodybuilding.com/fun/built-by-science-shoulders.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 21:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand weights? How heavy are we talking? In any case, with the very limited information you provided, push ups would be a good workout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started) pretty much answers all your questions. My advice is to keep it simple. Start be eating clean at maintenance TDEE. If you're looking to gain strength, give [SL5x5](http://stronglifts.com/) a look. It's always recommended for beginners here. If you want to get into running, check out [Couch to 5k](http://www.coolrunning.com/engine/2/2_3/181.shtml). If you'd like to do bodyweight fitness in the comfort of your dorm/room, visit /r/bodyweightfitness.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make sense to increase your calorie intake and maintain a good amount of protein. So, definitely eat more. Don't forget that rest and recovery are also very important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 07:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start with [the wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). Seriously, it's VERY helpful for beginners. Now, with 3 days, you can structure all kinds of workouts. Most people here recommend starting with [SL5x5](http://stronglifts.com/5x5/). It would fit your 3-day split and would be a great starting point for someone trying to get stronger.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 07:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat and continue working out. What have you tried? I find dips, rope push-downs, and skull crushers really work my triceps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 07:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this were a 5-speed, I'd highly consider it. Gotta love a low-mileage XJ, like spotting a unicorn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 06:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are just itching to get out there and play, you could sign up as a free agent with [Underdog Flag Football](https://www.underdogseattle.com/sport/Flag_Football)? Sounds like a blast though, I'd be interested in a Reddit-organized event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 00:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really want to appreciate running even more, I'd suggest reading [Born to Run](http://www.chrismcdougall.com/born-to-run/) by Chris McDougall. Not only is it fairly informative about running, but it's just a great story overall.

Keep hittin' the pavement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 00:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd knock it down to $4200 and see what he says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 00:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A watch and my wedding band are my only "must-wears". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 00:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'd be fine. If you start seeing a losses on your main workout days, then maybe hold off. As long as you're still making gains, I don't think it hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 23:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably isn't the nicest of areas, honestly. I'd recommend going up further away from Benson AVE (104th?), closer to Soos Creek or Sunrise Elementary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 22:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give it time, dude. You said you JUST started, you aren't going to be able to put up impressive numbers. You'll get there eventually. Don't be embarrassed to lift at your pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 22:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like this approach, but I've found the most success for staying under my calorie limit with it. Sure, we can say "just be disciplined and don't eat", but I love my pizza and beer!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of my family resides in Kent and it's generally pretty safe. I'd stay up on the Hills (East Hill) and further away from the Kent valley.

edit: Also feel free to PM me, I'd be happy to answer any questions you have about specific areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's too much of an issue to warm up or stretch in the rack if you intend to do squats in it. 15 minutes might be the limit, but it certainly isn't something I'd get all heated about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  how has fitness helped you maintain/improve your mental health?

When I go for a run, it feels like I'm meditating. I'll breath in and think about anything that stressed me out that day, then breath it out. It's very therapeutic.

When I hit the weights, it's a great outlet for anger or aggression, for obvious reasons. Also very therapeutic.

 What are some fun, cheap ways to get into fitness?

Does your university have a rec center or gym? You could check it out. You could also just get outside and walk/hike/jog around campus.

If you've never worked out before, there's a ton of great information on getting started in the [wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). If you are just looking for a routine, the wiki has a [section with workout plans](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started#wiki_adding_exercise). Just pick one and stick to it.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While a book would give you in-depth details about getting fit, it really is a simple concept described in [the sidebar wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). Want to lose weight? Eat less than TDEE. Want to get strong? Lift heavy things. Want to run faster? Go and run, a bit faster each time.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just browse /r/malefashionadvice and copy the outfits in there. Seattle "fashion" is about as basic as can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't out-workout a bad diet. If you want to lose weight and gain muscle, you'll have to do a lot better than 3 cheat meals a week with 2-3 beers a night.

I'm not saying not to party, just know that it directly conflicts with your fitness goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be drifting into /r/personalfinance territory, but I would consider moving to Tukwila or getting a job in Fremont. If relocation (job or home) isn't an option, I'd consider getting a car to reduce commute time. Personally, 1.5 hours of commute would kill me too... That said, I'd do my best to buy an economic, used car (preferably in cash). I'm really just shooting at the hip here, but that's an idea of the approach I'd take in your situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sitting on the bus on your phone for 1.5 hours might be a little less soul-sucking than sitting in traffic from Seattle to Tukwila. How much time would you save on your commute? Did you factor parking for home and work into your costs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 23:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamstrings - stiff-leg deadlifts, good mornings

Calf - calf raises (can't really replace these) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the Levi's 514 have a stretch version. Usually "stretchy" jeans aren't recommended, but they are really comfortable, especially if your legs are at full pump after a workout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on that! I've seen crippling debt rip apart families and friends, it's great you put effort into digging yourself out. My wife and I are currently working on killing her student loan debt (low interest, but we're debt averse) and we'll be done with it this year. It'll feel great not to owe any money to anyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's replaceable. I'd say the biggest reason for keeping him is that he's a veteran with RW3, and that chemistry would be hard to replicate with someone brand new. I don't know how big of a deal that is, but it's a reason nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably not ideal, as you usually want to stay away from highly processed foods. Calorie-wise (for bulking), it probably doesn't matter much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please read this first: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started

For healthy cooking tips, check: /r/MealPrepSunday/

For beginners, to keep it simple. Don't overcomplicate. Eat less. Move around more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told not to reduce more than one size (32 - 31), otherwise the pockets start to look off. Might vary depending on the jeans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 08:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Arms - dumbbell curls and skull crushers
* Chest - bench press or flies
* Shoulders - overhead press
* Back - rows and pullups

And I'd still recommend squats. It's a basic, fundamental compound movement that forms a solid foundation for strength.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 08:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maintain a diet full of protein and don't do anything to hinder your recovery. 2 weeks ain't that bad. Rest up and get healthy again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 08:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you upgrade to Win 10? Or was it a fresh install. I was experiencing very weak performance. A clean install of Win 10 brought the game back to life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 23:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take the water taxi from the water front to Alki and back, doing fun things in between. Walk around the water front, get a good view of the city from the water taxi, walk along the "beaches" at Alki.

edit: I realize these are touristy areas, but less so than the other tourist traps in the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google around for the Big-4. I always hear those are the compound lifts you should focus on for strength. I've heard variations of it, but I consider them to be:

* Bench Press
* Squat
* Deadlift
* OHP

I've also heard of clean+press or power-clean as part of the 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this not an old article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My HS football coach said something that's always stuck with me in situations like this:

 Avoid, at all costs, getting into a fight with another person. But if you get into one, don't fucking lose.

If the person comes over to you and threatens you again, tell him kindly to leave you alone. If he lays a finger on you, fucking destroy him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw this. It would break my heart to see him go, but I'm getting tired of the whole situation. And his cryptic tweets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're suffering from [analysis paralysis](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Analysis_paralysis), which is common for beginners. Keep it simple, dude. Read [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started) and don't overcomplicate.

Want to get strong so you can carry her? Lift and carry heavy things.

Want to lose weight, lean out? Eat cleanly at a caloric deficit.


It doesn't have to be hard, just do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if it's one bench/machine/rack, I'd be ok if someone "reserved" it by laying a towel down or something. I don't think it's ok to reserve multiple spots, though. In these situations, I ask if I can work in, since the occupant isn't going to be using the machine the whole time.

You should definitely let your owner/trainers know about this person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 23:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. There's tons of meet-ups right along your interests. You just have to go out and find/attend them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do mine on pull day. I like to have my core/base fresh for deadlifts and squats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 08:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radial head fracture the past 5 weeks. Did nothing but cardio. Something is better than nothing, as long as you aren't putting yourself at risk for more injury. When in doubt, rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 00:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only really had any "kick" from Cellucor C4. That said, I've stopped taking it due to stomach issues (could just be my own reaction). Now, I just make a strong half-cup of black coffee. Any light roast will do, as light roasts have more caffeine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching instructional videos and posting form-checks would probably be a good way if you can't afford a trainer. I learn a lot from these two:

[Art of Manliness - Mark Rippetoe Series](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CnBmiBqp-AI)

[Alan Thrall Youtube Channel](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y1IGeJEXpF4)

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to go to A J in Upper Queen Anne, I think it's B E now. They specialize in high-quality meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on finishing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 21:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compression. Shorts and tops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 01:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally forgot about the Gold's Gym on Broadway. It could also be worth checking out. Though, from the website, it doesn't appear to have Olympic style weights.

To me, the price tag at Rival is worth it for the 4 power racks, Olympic style weight set, and relative proximity to my apartment (which might be different for OP). Best of all, it's never anywhere close to being as crowded as any commercial gym I've been a member of, even at peak times.

I'll leave it to OP to see if it's worth it to him/her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 22:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do you wear an undershirt?

Yes

 If you do, where do you buy it?

[Alfani](http://www1.macys.com/shop/product/alfani-mens-underwear-cotton-spandex-crew-neck-t-shirt-2-pack?ID=452113) and [Express](http://www.express.com/clothing/men/stretch-cotton-crew-neck-tee/pro/5051421/cat430030)

 Do you wash your shirts or dry clean them?

Wash

 If you wash them how many times do you wear it between washes?

Approx 3-4 wears

 Do you wash with your other clothes or separately?

Seperate

 Do you do regular wash and then air dry?

Delicate then air dry

 If your shirt shrinks is there anything you can do to unshrink it?

I'm gonna go with no, but I'm sure you could Google this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
