<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 21:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about Joanna Champion's combination that finished Esparza? 

Jones taking down Cormier twice consecutively in the 4th round was also awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 21:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Another great moment from that fight is when Chad misses his first takedown attempt and Conor throws out his hands and puts on a shit-eating grin.

His mouthpiece really made that moment. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 20:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a phenomenal game. I honestly love *everything* about it. I could quite literally gush over Life is Strange for pages and pages, days and days, til my fingers fall off from all the keyboard clicks. Buuuuuuut I'll refrain from that and just say that it's one of the most meaningful and incredible experiences of of my life, and it's given me new perspective and made me a better, more open, more motivated, and more passionate human being. It isn't just a video game to me. And this isn't hyperbole. I'll always keep my memories of Life is Strange with me. Onto 2016! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imma link you to [this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/lifeisstrange/comments/3wiuyi/ep5_spoilers_guilt_but_no_regrets/cxwiw8l) and [this comment (which is mine btw, hehe ego)](https://www.reddit.com/r/lifeisstrange/comments/3y9nxj/ep5_spoilersfeelings_about_ending/cybwlz6) because I feel they make valid points about why Max, or anyone in her position, might not make the same choice you did. But to sum them up briefly: 

Sacrifice Arcadia Bay = Guilt 

Sacrifice Chloe = Regret 

That would be my logic behind my final decision anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 19:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do. It's a beautiful movie, in many respects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 18:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's one of the best, if not the best problem solver in mma.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 18:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because let's face it. We humans can relate more to our closest friends / families / loved ones a thousand times more than anyone else.

There's a character in the movie "Interstellar" (which I will not spoil) who says:

*"...it would be (impossible) to get people to work together to save the species instead of themselves. You never would have come here unless you believed you were going to save them. Evolution has yet to transcend that simple barrier.We can care deeply - selflessly - about those we know, but that empathy rarely extends beyond our line of sight."*

And he is so brutally correct. "Interstellar" has a team of astronauts searching for a way to save the human race from the impending death of the earth. And although the mission is to save mankind, the main character is driven *solely* by the hope of seeing his children again and saving *them*. He's not trying to save the human race, he's travelled across the galaxy to save his family.

The final choice in LiS echoes this quote: *"We can care deeply - selflessly - about those we know, but that empathy rarely extends beyond our line of sight."* Looking at it this way, the writers at Dontnod were actually pretty generous in even giving us the option of Sacrificing Chloe. Very few people would be capable of choosing that option in reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautifully written. *Guilt but no regrets.* I like that. Hope you don't mind if I hold onto it for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Square probably saw potential but didn't want to go all in. An episodic adventure game with two female protagonists? Not exactly the kind of game that ships millions of copies these days. It's very likely that they were just treading lightly. They were prolly just being business-smart. (And LiS was a new IP, another reason for Square to not fully commit to it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *No, I won't trade you!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your loss. I honestly have no idea what it's like to lose your best friend like that, and I wish you didn't have to through this, and on Christmas of all days. Life can be a bitch sometimes, as you know, but it does go on. And she'd want to keep going on. Losing someone that close to you is awful, but don't let it hold you down; let it be a reason to move forward. If you ever need to talk or vent, don't hesitate to come here. The people here are *awesome* and super nice and will definitely be here for you when you need them. If you ever need an internet hug don't hesitate to ask, for ye shall receive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. I think the Bae ending really is a case of "less is more". I've seen some of the fan edits that include the kiss and some more dialogue and stuff in this ending and, while it was nice, it never really felt right. The kiss is the big one. Before I played Episode 5, a YouTube thumbnail spoiled for me that Max and Chloe would/could kiss in the episode. I went in with that expectation (pricefield trash), and that left me initially disappointed with my ending because there was no kiss. But looking at it later, now, that would have been *so* out of place. 

I love the Bae ending though. I think they showed us just enough and just the right things. I honestly think it's perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 03:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loving this so far. Also HOLY SHIT THIS FIC IS LOOOOOONG. Nice work dude! And on Christmas too! You has my respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 14:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see this happening. I can see it very clearly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 14:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kind that grows up to be huge, because then Chloe will ride it around Arcadia Bay like a horse when its older and Max will regret buying her the puppy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 03:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no real plans. Got some work to trudge through. Not expecting Santa to swing by Casa del Yarf anytime soon. 

Next week, Monday through Friday, I intend to replay LiS. Right on time for the new year. It'll be my way of commemorating what an amazing year it's been, and also my way of letting go of LiS and moving on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 03:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a Chloe New Year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 02:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chloe would need to pick up Max for her to put the star on the Christmas tree.

Chloe would strategically hang mistletoe everywhere Max goes.

Chloe would buy Max the biggest dildo ever and put it in her stocking. 

Chloe would start a snowball fight indoors. 

Chloe would drink too much eggnog. 

Chloe would somehow get herself killed and Max would have to rewind and save her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Maxmas, /r/lifeisstrange! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 01:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was mice neme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he means Bisping will say something that greatly upsets Anderson and then he will forfeit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why is it when people are in a certain mood they go straight to music?

Well, not everyone does. But yeah, most of us seem to do this.

What it is literally is knocking out your sense of hearing to disconnect you from your surroundings. When you've got your earphones in (or the music turned up really loud) the sounds of the world around you are completely drowned out, therefore disconnecting you from the world and taking you somewhere else. Call it escapism. Sometimes you'll just close your eyes to do this. But more often than not we turn to music, because music has the ability to convey emotions. I don't really have an answer for why music can evoke certain emotions (it's probably got to do with certain frequencies and vibrations that hit the brain in just the right ways, I dunno), but it does, so we use it to take ourselves away from reality. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very odd list. Not saying there's anything wrong with it, but it is very different to all the other GOTY lists I've seen. It's kind of refreshing actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.

Would've been nice if some of this side of Jefferson made it into the final cut. He came across as a very 2-dimensional villain in this episode, so even a little pinch of dialogue like this could've made his character feel a lot more fleshed out. These lines are actually perfect in that they give you a reasonable glimpse into his motivations without turning into a stereotypical villain monologue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Everything* she does is cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper lanterns I believe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 18:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This scene literally made me drop to my knees. It fucked me up real good. 

  I honestly thought that time travel through the photo was a one time deal and I broke Chloe forever :(

Me too. I was so worried. And I felt guilty as shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 14:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The universe better get ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you didn't spend 3 whole months worrying about whether or not you'd ever see Chloe again. 

Though now that's what all of our lives are now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 01:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your natural color? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 00:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got stuck there for a ridiculous amount of time as well. I was convinced that the key was the owl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 00:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goldglove called it while he was in the Dark Room. [Here is the video](https://youtu.be/2Y8d0D6YD18?t=3h7m55s). Fucking crazy moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of [this](https://www.fanfiction.net/s/11681645/1/Outside) fanfic I read yesterday. 

The tears were so real reading this. Even realer now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at this, I feel like I can hear a 1980s cartoon type theme song playing...*"Partners in crime, partnerrrrrrs in time..."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look awesome! I'll be done with school for good in a few months, and as soon as I am I'm gonna dye my hair blue. (My school has pretty strict rules regarding this type of thing) For Chloe! And because blue hair just looks fucking cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *CHEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEESE*

Nah, go for the umbrella. Max really likes deers. And she is tiny, so...tiny deers! Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. It's incredibly atmospheric, has one of the best soundtracks (both original and especially licensed) you will ever hear, touches on some very poignant, relevant, and relatable issues, and features some excellent characters. Every single character in the game begins as a walking stereotype, but by the end they've all become real *people*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 20:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #ColinWasRight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 19:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think talent exists, but I don't think that it's just straight "hard work" that gets you to the top. A lot of it has to do with your personal situation, what kind of scenario you were born into, your experiences, etc. There isn't some general equation for success that applies to everyone. He's right when he says that you can be whatever and whoever the hell you want, but just know that hours upon hours of grinding isn't what gets you there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 19:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just skimmed over your DeviantArt. Loving the two Breaking Bad drawings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 12:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my knowledge, the lighthouse was the only part of Arcadia Bay that wasn't in the storm's path. It wasn't explained all that well prior, but in the Bae ending you can clearly see that they're safe from the storm at the lighthouse. In the first vision, I believe Max says that she has to get to the lighthouse. Somehow, she knows that the lighthouse will grant her safety from the storm. How she knows that, I got no clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 12:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After all the awesome contributions you made here, it's kinda sad to see you go. You've been awesome, and I thank you for that. I wish you all the best in your future escapades through time. And always remember...

***I WAS EATING THOSE BEANS*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 12:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Misfit", more like "Miss Fit". Have you seen dem abs? I mean DAYUUUMMMMM

...I'm done. I'll see myself out.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 01:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was only bothered by it on that one instance. It was an incredibly emotional scene, and a certain person's lips weren't moving in sync with her words. It was the only time I ever actually noticed the it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 01:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [YAY](https://youtu.be/cVtDabPihKQ?t=1m54s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 01:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the goofy ass dialogue served the practical purpose of giving the game and it's characters distinct personality. It's super weird, sometimes cringey, but would we have as many memorable and memeable lines of dialogue if it weren't? Prolly not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 01:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly have no complaints about LiS. It has flaws, both technically and artistically (not the right word at all, but fuck it), but none of them ever bothered me that much. The only obvious aspect that I'd like changed, or more accurately improved upon, is the lip syncing. It wasn't a problem for me most of the time; the only instance where it did pull me out of the game was in the most important moment, the final choice at the lighthouse. It wasn't a major inconvenience or anything, but it's a little nitpick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Holy shit.

[For you](http://i.imgur.com/HOdsTNo.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAAAAAA CHLOE NOOOOOOOO

So yeah, pretty good so far. You could say I'm riveted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found this after seeing Chapter 2 on the front page of the sub. Liking it so far :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's *hella* sweet of her/him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for the long form, Number 1. If you want to strike an emotional chord, hit us in the feels, or just stir up our memories of the game, the last thing you want is the videos to be separate. Nothing pulls you out of the experience like having to come back to reality to click on a new video. 

As for songs, I say roll with Obstacles, Mt. Washington, and Spanish Sahara. Those three are essential.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was awesome. The illustrations worked perfectly in sync with the music. Hella nice job by the artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 17:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw "60+ hours" my mind immediately jumped to photorealistic, huge, insane. I kinda forgot that there are other valid art styles :P

I really like it. Love the style, the colors, all of it. Reminds me a little of...fuck I can't remember the name. One of those 20th century art movements. It looks good is what I'm saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 17:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike you, I didn't have the strength of character to let her go. I'm still clinging on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 11:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These comments are incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 01:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **YES**. Absolutely **YES**. It's been thrown out there before, but this is the first time I'm seeing a post about it. I think it's one of the biggest themes of the game, present from the outset, and a HUGE part of building up the world of Arcadia Bay. In Episode 1, we are introduced to a series of stereotypes; the typical nerd, the bitch, the rebel, the drill sergeant, the rich kid, etc. We see little glimpses of depth, but for the most part they are nothing but caricatures. But as the story progresses, we begin to gain insight into these characters. We start to understand Chloe, we start to understand David, we start to understand Victoria, and we start to understand Nathan. They stop being 2 dimensional. By the end of the game, there are no more stereotypes. We are left with *people*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 01:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hella yes. Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely; Dontnod, Hannah, and Ashly really made Max and Chloe into real people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2015 has been a pretty incredible year for me in general. It's been the year where I feel my life and identity really started to take shape, and Life is Strange was a big part of that. I'm sad to leave 2015, but I'm looking forward to the future even more. *When a door closes, a window opens.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As weird as this is, all I could think while watching is how friggin pretty this game is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never really been much of a shipper. I respect all ships, but initially I didn't really ship anybody. As time went on though, I started to fall into the idea of Max and Chloe being together. It was just a natural progression for me, it wasn't intentional at all. That's just what I saw their relationship evolve into. Now I'm all "Pricefield 4eva". 

Other than that, I don't really ship anyone. There was no other pairing I saw that seemed natural. I'm sure Warren and Kate would be super cute, and Max and Victoria would actually be great, but I never saw them as natural character/relationship progressions. That's just how I think about things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I wasn't here for Episodes 1 and 2 (my only regret in life), but the experience I had from Episode 3 on was amazing. The theories, fanarts, and chit-chats that happened during the waiting periods made my experience of LiS so much more special. This community is just so awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your theory. Plenty of us, myself included, have been beating the "the storm is a metaphor" drum for months, but I think you're one of the first people to *actually* dig into what it means. And personally? I think you hit the nail on the head. 100%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't ready for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 22:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH MY GOD FOXY PLUSHIES GIVE ME NAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is Strange inspired me to pick up the phone and call my best friend (who I had been away from for 5 years) too. I saw a lot of parallels between the relationship of Chloe and Max and the relationship of me and my best friend. It's what actually got its hooks in me and drew me into the game. It made the story feel very personal. I think everyone found some kind of parallel between Max's story and their own story, and that's why we all got so damn attached to this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never have and never will choose Bay. For my own sake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of those things that they can take liberties with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who don't know who she is, Karlie Kloss is an American fashion model, former Victoria's Secret Angel, and now YouTube vlogger ([channel link](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCH5Qu8Sd-m-7Zk4xc_J5VzA) ). She also featured in the music video for "Bad Blood" by the one and only T-Swizzle. 

In case there was anyone else who didn't recognize her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd sure fucking try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what he's trying to say is that he's always in fight mode. If Big John, for whatever nonsensical reason, tried to attack him, he'd be ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that an Until Dawn reference? ~~If so, *shut up Chris*.~~ 

^If ^not ^plz ^forgive ^me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stook in dee mud division  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta throw this out there: I haven't read over the edited sex scene so I don't know if it's still there, but Chloe opening the window to air out "the smell of pussy" was really funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 03:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of my favorite LiS videos out there. It just gets me every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 03:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been following your story on tumblr for a little while. I think it's pretty awesome! Those first few chapters are pretty intense (so is the last one, buuut that's a different type of intensity *wink wink*).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 03:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warren: pics or it didn't happen

I can't decide whether Chloe would reply "perv" or actually oblige.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 03:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. But Conor also has a little power to go with his precision... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 02:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am sure even Kristen and Fernando (her best friends in Seattle) would provide a much deeper support for Max.

Where were they mentioned? I've never heard of them before. 

Anyways, I agree that everything in Arcadia Bay will just be a reminder of Chloe. I'm just questioning whether or not that would make Max want to leave. It could go the exact opposite way that you're saying; maybe Max will never want to leave Arcadia Bay because it's the only connection she has left to Chloe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 23:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precision beats power, put to the test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 00:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you were expressing your (and many other's) personal opinion, I just felt the need throw that out there. I totally get why the ending may have been underwhelming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 17:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not *everyone* thought it was a letdown... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 17:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think having the episodes spread out through the year benefited my experience of game significantly, but there are also tons of people who binged played the game in a week (or a day!) and still got a great experience out of it. I think that in my case, having gaps between each episode let me really think and grow with the characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can be a moderately lean 145 at 5'11", then I can totally see someone who's 6'1" weighing in at 145 after cutting weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta be honest, I thought Episode 3's ending was way more of a gut-punch than Episode 4's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just worried that we'd find something awful inside and Chloe would get hurt. 

I was right.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 02:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm honestly not sure I want to stop feeling this way. Finishing Life is Strange is emotionally draining, but underneath it all there's a certain feeling of...peace.

You're the first person I can recall hearing (reading) this from. And you are 100% right. I've recently been pulled out of my "ermagerd LiS is over my life is void of meaning" phase by necessity, and it doesn't feel good. While you're under it is emotionally draining, but it's also kind of nice. It's weird not having been constantly thinking about Chloe and Max for the last two or three weeks. All I want to think about is the good times we had in Arcadia Bay, the lessons learned, all the memories. I guess what I'm saying is that I just don't want to forget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 02:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ermagerd yas, I can not contain my excitement for that misfit skull shirt! I'd love if they made Max's black and red shirts too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 01:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

*sob* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half a bottle of 418? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 17:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay strong, and know that you always have friends here bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 17:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What page is that on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 17:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for your loss. Just, focus on moving forward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In My Mind" is a pretty happy song, right? 

*oh god don't tell me that has some super sad hidden meaning too* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 16:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleeping Booty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 16:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very atmospheric.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 14:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't, but that's because I haven't had the option to. I've been really busy for the last 3 weeks or so, and I really haven't even had the time to think. I was feeling empty alright, but it was a result of something completely separate. But now that I'm on winter break, all that I can think about is LiS. So maybe? I was actually feeling a little bad about not feeling bad anymore, which is kinda funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 13:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 03:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! I was getting worried for a little while that we wouldn't see the chat return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 03:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends entirely on when he gets the ability to rewind. I think he's too far gone by the time Max gets her powers; if you gave him the ability to rewind during that week, it'd probably turn out to be the straw that breaks the camel's back. I don't know a lot about mental disorders, and I've never really tried to look into what Nathan might be suffering from, but I'd say his perception is already pretty fucked up; having the ability to create alternate timelines might make him completely lose his grip on reality. 

Now if you gave him the power at an earlier stage, maybe before he was under [EP5 SPOILER](#s "Jefferson's") control (he's not his loyal servant, no, but he is under his control), he might have ended up using the power for good. He might have saved Rachel, he might have rebelled against [EP5 SPOILERS](#s "Jeffershit"), he could have used the powers to impress Papa Prescott, and he probably never would've ended up holding Bae at gunpoint. Maybe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 03:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty thought provoking game alright. I've pretty much gotten over the emotional trauma at this stage (by way of distractions aka school and exams), but I'm still constantly thinking about the game. It's left a very defined mark on my mind. I don't think about anything the same anymore; my views on my friends, my family, my self, and my morality especially, have all been altered. Sometimes it's a little scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thank you Mark Jefferson for becoming my muse

This can't end well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
