<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject72</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man. I don't think 'Naive' is the word for it. You probably never got to this SR so don't talk about things you did not experience. Plus in my experience a lot of low levels that cannot rank up use the 'K B' excuse as a way of justifying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. You can add me abn_alkaabi, if u think I am lying about my rank... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH a solo Pharah is extremely bad, even in the low-levels. Except if Pharah is pretty well coordinated in terms of attacking with the ground heros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you know what you are talking about. By reading what u said you clearly aren't anywhere near masters or GM. In the entire T500 leaderboards there are literally less then five people that XIM4. And on top of that, it is quite unlikely they will all be playing at the same time. BTW the xim4 is really bad on console, because you cannot adjust in-game sensitivities like PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm as well. Pharahs are picked mist of the time. But I am a GM/T500 player. And up here Pharah gets countered fairly easily by just having a but of communication. Players up here also have got better aim the most (ofcourse) considering their rank. But I would suggest to get Mercy-Soldier to counter a Pharmacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get the joke. Can someone please fill me in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you understand me. HOW DOES PUTIN HAVE POWER OVER TRUMP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am telling you, you're vague. How in hell does Putin have POWER over the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by 'Has Trump in his pocket'? Really vague. Plus many people are calling him a fucking TRAITOR. So far I haven't seen Trump do something that would make him a traitor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the insight. I shall buy one at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I found one (http://www.dxracer.com/us/en-us/product/1/gaming_chairs/racing_series/oh-rv131-nb/) but I am particularly interested in the one used in Apex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One type did you buy?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not joking but if you are a spelling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him that when you get to top500 yourself. A t500 Pharah on PC is as good as it gets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Ana is Ryujehong  Explains everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like "Tactical Nuke Incoming!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then pay close attention to the subreddits that post content u don't want and unsub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unsub from the politics subreddit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is why you don't stand still boys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing happened to me, but with Roadhog's. Healing potion.  Did not heal and went on cooldown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
