<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Fall of Gondolin

Oh my lord.. Give me a full length tale Christopher. I needs it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit do I miss the days of seeing something and wondering if I'm actually a monster for laughing. Why does it have to happen to every fucking sub... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of his latest special Make Happy, he had a song to close out the show and as the song progressed he opened up quite a bit IMO, and it was clear he had no intentions of jumping back into standup, and it seemed to be an inner battle he was having.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and if you've seen the ending you see that he's is, or at least was at the time of filming, in a very tough spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lovato did that one shoot that straight up had her asshole showing at a high even res. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. If you're arguing with someone who's dumb enough to say this shit, it's pretty clear they won't understand the ins and outs of sharing common ancestors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck is the president of the most powerful country on the planet in an argument with a celebrity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where you live, and what your situation is. I saw it like 6 days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  like they went out of their way to make it R, which hurt it overall

This is the problem. The movie could do with the rating, but making it over the top will leave people wondering if it really needed it, like now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's completely fine, he's just not my cup of tea. In the way that some Tucker, Boogie, Kwebbel, may not be the right taste for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god do I miss Bo. Really hope he's doing good lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Killing Joke definitely needs an R rating. The animated movie was just awful so it feels unnecessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxes amiright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Morena Baccarin was in Firefly

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone talking about Scarce being a great guest and I'm here wondering what they see. All I've heard so far is a real shitty attempt at money bragging, and how it's lost value in his eyes. How he's genuinely considered liposuction because the hot women he spends time with tell him they've all done it, and he wants to look good but enjoys food too much. Although admittedly he said he's been losing weight recently so props to him on starting somewhere. 

All of that, and to top it off with his channel basically being a modern day Keemstar, I'm baffled people want him on here. 

I'm also not finished the episode, so my opinion on him may do a 180, but as of right now I really don't see the praise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably one of the best looking shows currently airing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one in the background looks like his retarded brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Split maybe.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also on r/nsfw_gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't miss anything. I've seen the movie 3-4 times. For it to be an x-men movie it has to be relevant to the x-men world in some way. Yes, deadpool had 2 characters in it, but it wasn't an x-men movie. Just a superhero movie. Was Batman vs Superman a justice league because it had 3 members? No. 

Logan however, is an x-men movie, considering it takes place in the x-men universe, has charles xavier in the actual movie, and talks about past events involving what happened to the mutants. Deadpool has some references and passable x-men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine playing on different "switch people". The characters you create for the console itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to turn off the motion control when aiming in zelda? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it's in the same style pouch as a normal capri sun? Tbh at this point might just rob one of them bloodbag-drip things from the hospital and fill it with as much capri sun as it can take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, Postman 1 delivers to the house of Postman 2, while postman 2 delivers to the house of Postman 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The media really ticks me off... The way they try to embarrass me by not editing what I say."

Well doesn't that sound familiar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um... Deadpool was most definitely not an X-Men movie. It's very clear you're a fan of Deadpool, but it's very much not an X-Men movie. There are multiple cases throughout the movie when he's actually mocking X-Men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part of the finale? The final fight? Afterwards? 

I understand it may be a US thing, but I'd lose my fucking shit if someone was shouting out during my viewing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the other people had viewed it. I'd reccomend waiting for dvd on this one too to make sure you know when the eye covering is coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted a happy ending for him, but I never gave it real though. The idea of him starting his own school will forever haunt me now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the 9 year old.

This movie has a very, very significant amount of limb chopping, a lot of skulls end up with claws through them, and the swearing is made very noticeable. 

It's probably a bit darker than deadpool in terms of violence, the story is pretty heavy overall, and there's a slight bit of nudity. 

All in all.. I'd skip this one with him. Or at least see it once yourself then make the judgement call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I don't expect a mass death of heroes in IW, I was simply asking if the books themselves are worth reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ain't gonna say QT is better, because... Well he's just not, plain and simple. But if anyone here feels that was a fair game to compare, you need to be checked in somewhere. That was a 2v1 if I've ever seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I got you fam] (http://www.pornult.com/videos/517/khaleesiwilde-sageness-public-finger-fucking/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that series worth reading? 

I remember before Civil War I tried to read it and people said it's pretty bad and not really worth reading. Does IW follow the same pattern, or is this an actual great story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we talking about classic Old Man Logan, or Lemire's Old Man Logan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with it being a fuck you to other movies though. Marvel's cinematic universe to me is the upbeat, go to action flick that will be enjoyed by most of the family. While I'd absolutely for a whole bunch of the cast to be killed off in Infinity War, I feel the MCU is the place I go to get that "they can do anything. They are true superheroes" kinda feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty certain it had to do with Charles' whole "I'm fucking 90" thing. The guy needed a real rest, and yes, I'm sure both he and Logan knew of the risk, but Charles had one goal throughout this movie. To make sure Logan realized what happiness was, and staying with a family, embracing that bit of life for however long, was a risk worth taking in his eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must be a pretty shit situation, but at the same time, and I understand nobody plans on recording before opening it the first time, but something about having it be a closed up version of the box, having already been opened, leaves an iffy feeling with me. 

Shitty internet fame grabs have jaded me to this kinda thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they were expecting a teaser, they just needed the time to compose themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it really didn't. 

Given that the movie was about his daughter that was bred to be a killer, I don't see why seeing the next step which was a clone of him (easily the most known mutant in the universe), along with the clone's creator being the son of Logan's evil doctor.. It really makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That final shot may be one of my favorite endings of all time. 

I was already crying as she gave the speech from earlier in the movie (Which is when I realize he was going to die. It was wonderful foreshadowing)... But when she turned that cross into an X, I can't describe the feeling that hit my gut. One of the saddest endings I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I legimitaly have hundreds of hours in the game, you don't need to spend any real money to buy a horse. It's a skill you learn, like with most mmos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then don't. It's that simple, but IMO, this is quite easily the best Marvel movie to date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it didn't, but believe me when I say most people seeing this movie will want to sit there til the credits are done rolling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've actually seen him in Uncle you know he'd make an incredible superman/Clark given the right writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was for best makeup.  Cut the "fuck DC amiright" gig, it was well deserved in that category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if it was 5 seconds from any other big release coming up that didn't have Snyder's name on it, you bet they'd find a way to make the topic of the thread about the progression of the universe being built, what the scene could mean, how they feel about the casting, whatever the fuck they wanted, but god damn do they know how to nit-pick Snyder related content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shitty, shitty thread to create.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "is this(travel talk) better or worse than grammar talk"

"eh, we always bitch about travel"

It's a paraphrase, but damn, just because it's something that always happens, doesn't mean we like or care for it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id rather not fight galadriel or tree beard, because... You know, good guys and whatnot. 

Then a Baltic and Sauron... Id rather not fucking with angelic level beings. 

The only reasonable boss there is the witch King, and even then.. I just dont ever see this being a good idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont even seat the problem here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How he was a common browser of r/dankmemes, and they're watching this sub turn into the new r/funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on pc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By turning it down, are we going from hard to normal, or normal to easy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play on an old enough pc and always maxed at 60, but for the most part, it caused me to bounce between 20-55 or so. Once I set it to lock at 30, it was 30 constant. I really don't get why people act like this is death. 30 for 90% of games is just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't make praising Witcher an outcast thing to do. The reason it's so highly praised is because of the true quality of the game. I'd hate for it to end up as the "moon is a hidden gem" of this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know RT was, I'm saying the Youtube channel was created in 06. 

Considering we're talking about the branch of channels under the RT name, and you said RT feels 05, I assumed we were discussing the YT side of RT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Any advice for a first timer learning the combat of Origins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm starting to be thrown into combat fairly often now, and up until the combat started, I've loved everything about the game. But.. Organizing a party during combat, along with having my camera control key be the same as the movement/attack key.. It feels odd to say the least.

That's why I'm here though. I'm sure you guys could help in someway to ease the learning curve of battle in this game. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their channel didn't launch until mid 2006 what the fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying it's a great question, I'm just saying it's from the Honest Trailers guys. I don't expect a high level of question when they're doing an interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think any of those comments on the Taylor post are actually making fun of him, in a way he'd be unhappy with, you're way too sensitive. It's mostly owl/head jokes and both of which he makes himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politics talk, gun talk, hockey talk.. Don't get me wrong, I enjoy the topics 90% of the time, but damn is this a way to alienate the national audience.

EDIT: Could someone clue me in on the downvotes? I thought I was stating a simple fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if one thing is true, it's that the retarded kid in class always has the best sense of humor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said I was being forced to read or reply, but you did imply it felt like such with you. I made a simple comment and it appears to have really irritated you. Oh well I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even close to what I'm saying. 

Would you criticize Jim Jeffries because of a misogynistic joke? Or a Shyamalan movie for having a twist? Sure you can accept not liking it, and say it's dumb, but it also fits the bill. 

Critiquing is all well and good, but when it's critiquing something that is very clearly the norm for said thing, sure, go ahead and do it, but a lot of people are completely fine with it the way it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I know, and you're right about the skulls of course, I'm just implying he has no reason to hold interest in them yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd kill for a guild like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..When I said you shouldn't expect ___. I didn't mean it in a forceful way, I'm just saying if you've seen anything by the channel it's kind of obvious where they're going with their style. 

Also, nobody is forcing you to watch their interviews. A lot of people on Reddit appreciate the channel's style and their trailers, so just off that they're going to watch happily and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying it's been asked in other professional settings. I'm saying you're watching a video about the guys behind Honest Reviews, interviewing the cast of JW2. You shouldn't expect a high level of professionalism going in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qyburn has no reason to want Valyrian steel though. He's a curious mind, sure, but he has no idea what's going on far north. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And to ask it in a professional setting?

You must be new here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he didn't. He said he heard about it being historically inaccurate, and while that may be the case, he simply doesn't give a fuck because he loves the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has easily been the most confusing 2 months in politics history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the idea of not having to use ad-block, because as much as I like not having ads, I also like the idea of paying the content creator in some way.

Also, doesn't it let you download to have some on the go content?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you really don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a real fucking shame because damn I'd love to have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made you suggest it though? 

PKA is definitely a pretty off the beaten path podcast, so I'm curious what you said or did to convince someone to try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested to hear why she does this, does she pull any significant profit yet, or if it's ever come up IRL. And who knows, maybe she fits perfectly with the guys and joins in consistently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of understand you. I however, am definitely in the minority on the matter. I love DLC. No unnecessary dlc, but a real expansion of the game/world. I'm also happy giving money towards a f2p game, because it's the only way the company would actually know I support them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You rent. If you look into going VIP, you'll see a lot of benefits, and when the month is up the only thing that gets revoked is the quests in each zone. That being said, you can still 100% do the main quest, and visit those zones, but you won't have all the side quests or achievements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some must do zones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm leveling an alt for the first time, ans considering my first time round turned into dungeon spam, I can say ive missed almost every quest outside Broken Isles. 

So now on my alt, I'm trying to get some world exploring done. Going for actual explore achievements too along the way. 

But sadly, its clear than in doing most quests, I'll be a pretty high level going to the following zone, and after 2-3 zones I'll be outleveling 4-5-6. 

So to avoid missing the great quests or beautiful zones, id like to know I need to go to them when im on level. 

So Reddit. What are those zones?

EDIT: I come back to the thread realizing people assume I'm horde. Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you get decks in Duels? I've heard its pretty paytowin on steam so.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the fact that many people are acting like Tolkien scholars when I doubt some of them have ever touched a Tolkien book and are just criticising the game for the sake of having a popular opinion

You are browsing /r/lotr. While I'm sure a few occasional viewers of this sub are movies only, I'd imagine the vast majority of the comment on this post are from those that read the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but there are definite ways to go without paying, it's just a grind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did people ever actually do this though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Like, they adapted The Lord of the Rings into a film and did an amazing job!!!!

Yes, for those of us that loved the movie. 

The guy is not a dick for not liking it. He dedicated his life to the work of his father, so when someone gets the chance to adapt it, and it doesn't come out how you expect, or it leaves out something, or worse yet, adds something in.. You can't blame the guy for not liking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um.. No you don't. You can play the game free for the most part, up until it sucks you in and you're completely fine going VIP. 

The Shire/Bree/Thorins Gate are all 100% free, and if you manage to run through that content/achievement system, you could easily afford the next zone or two just off the store currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before watching the trailer I read the comments about it being painfully inaccurate to the lore...

But holy shit did that look incredible. I'm honestly reconsidering trying the first game again and forcing myself to get over the thoughts of it basically being fanfiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, my bad then. I guess the frequenting websites/forums can make it appear like the appeal is bigger than those of the potter books, which were of course before this mass-agreement to share all thoughts and opinions online. I was wrong. I'll stand by the rest of my point though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backspin is also a factor. It's fairly easy to kick a ball, causing it to land in a way that has itself already spinning in the direction of the kicker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's it.

I believe he had a story. A truly great one, but the show crushed it. Not in the sense that the show is better, but the show gathered a following nobody ever expected, and it gave the books a popularity it quite frankly would never have seen without the adaption being so big.

Then, along with all the new readers, it became a very popular thing to theorize about the future of the series. He himself said he stopped reading fan predictions because of something like "if they say this happens, then I can't actually right that in like I planned because he said it". That may be a drastic paraphrase, but nonetheless I'd imagine the point stands.

He started a story that has gotten way beyond his reach, and he is absolutely terrified to finish it. Like, when is the last time the release of a book has been as big a deal as Winds of Winter? ~~Maybe Deathly Hallows? But even then, it absolutely pales in comparison to the following of Winds~~. As palindrome has stated, I'm way off on this and my sphere of opinions/information is pretty warped compared to what I knew of the Potter releases.

Now, for the riskiest part of the comment. I am fine with him not finishing it. He gave us the world, he gave us most of the story. He has no true obligation to finish the series for us. We did not pay him for an entire series. Of course it's truly heartbreaking that he may never finish it, but after what he has given me personally.. I'd rather he admit his plans to not finish the series, and move on to something that will make him happy, rather than aching and stressing over a story, that because of the fanbase, already has hundreds/thousands of endings. One of them has to be his, and because it's already out there somewhere I don't imagine he'd ever be happy putting his own words to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be in the minority here, but Pandaria is easily the best looking zone in the game IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why in the world do you need your phone to take a bus? Id get if you were driving, it could be GPS.. but literally all you have to do for a bus is show up at the stop, and listen until they announce the stop you get off at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abort it or run and never look back. 

Really. The odds of it working out positively are slim to none.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's the entire reason for r/movies.

If its a rhetorical question about a movie based event, it really has no purpose being here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen DBZ or played smash bros, but damn even I like the sound of that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems like either a 3 hour movie or a complete flop. 

If that were to be the plan, just a slight flashback to the events of the task. The idea of the task is better than it could ever possibly be on screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read American Alien the. He wrote it, and quite frankly, I'd say it's a safe bet to assume it will be a classic Superman story years down the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather it be further out..

Giving us it in 2 weeks just means we have shit to poor over for the next few months. I'm finally accepting the baron wasteland of reality and now you're telling me to surrender my life once again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shit, shit feeling the cast and workers on La La Land must be feeling right now. 

Grats to Moonlight and everything, but fuck is that a terrible way to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...I genuinely can't believe that just happened. My stream cut off and it's 5am so I'm out, but holy fuck.. What a truly disgusting feeling that must be for the folks that put in the work on La La Land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well deserved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That song intro for the La La Land nomination always gets me excited. Still though.. Holding out for Hacksaw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how Best Picture works though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want Hacksaw Ridge to take it home, but it's going to La La Land, and being realistic, it's rightfully so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit it's Casey Neistat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odds on Emma but I'd love to see Meryl win just to prove how absurd her nomination was to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inb4 Meryl wins. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denzel looking real fucking angry right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Viggo just because it's Viggo, but odds are on Casey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not it at all. 

I said it's okay to say you don't like it, but what you're doing is calling it a terrible movie. It's very clear that its not. On top of that.. Chazelle just won best director, so that's even further going against your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "underdogs" dude.. Be real here. 

It's not a terrible movie. It's far from it quite frankly. It's an incredibly well made movie. Just say you don't like it. Nobody will argue with you on that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck gets pumped at someone losing? I get being pumped for a win, but getting excited at the idea of someone else losing.. What did the movie do to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best original screenplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is waaaaaaaaaay funnier than expected. Holy shit it's so well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing the Kimmel-Damon bit was coming, I can honestly say this is funnier than I expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, Alan Rickman and David Bowie were respected in the 2016 oscars... Yes it has been that long sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in the 2016 segment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in the 2016 tribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The segment was most likely finished weeks ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in the 2015 tribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in the 2016 tribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right... It's shocking that probably the best musical in the last decade is taking home both music based awards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because lyrically, How Far I'll Go is very, very bland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck man.. Why did he have to over do and rush it so much?

EDIT: Then cut it back to slow style.. That pacing is baffling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh.. I get that John Legend has a much better voice than Gosling, but the song really, really doesn't fit him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize it's okay to say you don't like the movie, right? Calling it the most hollow movie in 50 years is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump jokes may be a bit recycled tonight, but that Sweden joke was pretty fucking good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, Arrival and Silence looked incredible, but La La Land was fucking beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure he didn't actually see it. His answer to like 7/8 questions was yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck was that racist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mel Gibson

The answer is in the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got kicked outta hollywood a few years back for some racist/antisemitism stuff. I don't know the details, but some people aren't past it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Amy Adam's acting = wooden, bland, and uninspired

Welp.. You lost me already. Oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying you find a movie boring doesn't mean you're incapable of understanding subtlety and tension. It just means you're uninterested in whatever you're watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. 

Manchester by the Sea is a very simple story, and it is not for a lot of people. I loved it, but definitely agree that it's a slow movie, and a lot will find it boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most uncomfortable I've been watching live tv in a loooooooong long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Moana, and the songs were painfully catchy, but in terms of animated Disney movies, it was pretty on par with the rest, and followed a basic enough plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone celebrates what it means to live a life. 

These guys just get a bigger mic to do it because they're the biggest names in cinema.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a real winners speech. No goals other than showing your true emotion and gratitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they're not, but I'd imagine if his SO saw this she'd be pretty upset by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well a semi-celebrity boyfriend that openly talks about how great another chics boobs are, on a podcast that gets over 100k viewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with this, and quite frankly I really support it, but dear god is this gonna be an interesting year for speeches right? I wonder how many will get political with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck can I trust at this point... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also have a wild lifestyle in some cases, such as being teachers, doctors, road workers etc.

Don't get me wrong, I'm with you, and I'm not religious, I just feel it's only fair we acknowledge those that believe in a god who are perfectly normal, functioning members of society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  La La Land had such a crazy, profound effect on me that I can't really explain. For me personally it's probably my favorite movie I've seen in a really long time.

This always amazes me. I didn't expect much going into a musical, but I left with a true sense of awe that I've never really felt leaving the theater, but when it comes to explaining to a friend why he should give it a shot... I can't explain it, and I'm always left speechless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I really didn't like the "least deserving" option.

Gibson got 49.% for it.. Like what did he do to cause such a clear agreement for him being undeserving? Are people still mad at him, or is there a director that got snubbed by his placement? Because sure it might not be on par with the other 4, but god fucking damnit was that a well directed movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' casuals man.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, but I'm really not a fan of Woody straight up lying/exaggerating because there's a topic he's not key'd in on.

Kyle and Taylor's adventure through gaming/magic is easily my favorite part of PKA right now. It's why I fell in love with PKA. Just a few guys talking about the games they play and why they're so into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... Jesus did actually exist. He was just a liar. 

Pro tip: if you're gonna try go anti-religion at least say god isn't real or do the research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So um...Kyle is clinging way too hard with Trump right? 

I may be wrong, but it's very, very fucking clear at this point that he tries to flip any news of him into either way too insane for a serious talk, or something that benefits him. Playing on his own course because "imagine if he didn't". Being overweight is okay but once he's fat it's not okay anymore..Pretty sure he's fat. Also, relating to him on a level because he eats shitty fast food is crazy IMO.

EDIT: Lol at Woody saying life ain't fair though, considering you know, the whole world was against him and his channel when he was trying to make it work. Rather....Unfair even, if you asked him back then.

EDIT2: [8/10 folks] (https://i.gyazo.com/61c9728ab0ec29ba2436503f86e2b1b4.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's close to opposite actually. I was naive growing up because i was convinced otherwise by very, very manipulating person. 

Also, the family is fine with me. Its the actual house situation that will get me. My sister has a dog that has been fucking up furniture real bad for a while now and there's only so much I can do considering she dropped interest a few weeks in. 

Along with a negligent mother.. the place isn't exactly clean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right? How the fuck are these cunts getting the shot to play against straight up the best players on the planet, but are using that chance to spread toxicity.. Blows my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with nominations, no matter how many you have... As long as you fucking deserve it, rather than have a bunch of people circle jerk over you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woody really needs to let up on his visitation thoughts when on here. It's clear at this point that he's on the sub quite regularly. At least once a week given recent shows, and I really don't get it. The comment was something like "i was on the sub ^^ThereWasSomeHate" or whatever it was..

Don't get me wrong, I'll admit to being critical, if not over critical of him in the past, but the hate on this sub is incredibly hyperbolic when he mentions it.

EDIT: Also add in that he himself commented on a post wishing him a happy birthday. The sub was pretty much nothing but nice to him this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you for the most part, but I wholeheartedly put it down for Meryl when she came around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. All episodes are pretty much stand alone. This episode in particular "White Christmas" is probably one of the most captivating hours of any show I've seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he definitely did. The only problem is nobody really saw the Nice Guys. As much as I love Russell Crowe, I don't think he draws the same crowd as Emma Stone, and in comparison, one is a noir-buddy cop kinda movie, while the other is a classic, romance based musical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to contact support without logging in to my account? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm stuck in a loop here. I'm trying to get my account back after a year or so of not playing, but I can't remember the password. 

Reset, right? I need the serial code and character name. It took a while to find the serial among my thousands of emails, but I have absolutely noooooo idea what I'd have named a character. 

So I went to support to submit a ticket, but what do I need to do for that? Log in.. 

I'm stuck in a loop and I'd love some help!

EDIT: It's solved, and I feel like a baboon, but I'll leave it up just for those using the search feature in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not aiming for the quickest way there. If I did I'd be spamming dungeons already.(believing that to be the fastest way) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a kid I'm not ready for, only to let him/her down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is what I'm looking for. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course GTA Online is going to play a part in their making of this game, it made them millions upon millions of dollars and is quite frankly the reason people still play the game and it's supported.

I'd also like to believe they have a team devoted for single player, and another team for mulitplayer. R* isn't some 12 man, garage based company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on an old ass laptop. Yes I know it's not ideal. Yes I am saving up for an actual pc, but for right now, this is what I've got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. [here ya go] (https://gyazo.com/b63227efc27ffe946a9e33f56f5c4bd7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved azsuna.. The story of Farondis was pretty great IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well juggling work, family, other games, and then levelling without spamming dungeons.. Of course it's not some 1000 hour drag, but it's definitely a time consuming game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..So I take it high mountain is notoriously disliked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying I suddenly hate the game, but the fun I had in rolling around tanking 5-6 mobs at a time seems to be gone for me. It also could be the current zone. I'm not a big fan of this area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever got a class close to max, or fully maxed, only to realize you desperately want to main another class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 107 right now on a BrM, but lately I've been very, very tempted to play Shaman. But when I play on my BrM now.. As much as I enjoy Legion, I'm not enjoying it anymore, but feel I should be playing it simply because it's where I've given all my time, gold, and crafting resources. 

But..Fuck me does Shaman seem right up my alley. 

I'd love to hear if you guys have ever had a similar feeling or scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should make you feel better imo. 

I did art like this in high school. You render the image, map it on a page and paint inside the lines.

Dont get me wrong, it may be freehand but quite frankly, given Reddit history with reposts/ fake titles... Id call bluff on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?

Any time I brought it up, I was followed by "you can only polish a turd so much" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't understand why they added an rng factor to crafting though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No one uses that shit. 

As someone who can't find a guild outside those that want you strictly dor player count.... I'd use that shit if it was any way useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've clearly been playing him differently, if you have at all before this announcement. His clear is weak, of course, but so is the champ. It's still totally manageable to get at least 4 camps before backing if done right with the right setup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And playing across realm with friends? Do you know how serious it is? I imagine it makes it almost impossible, but once we're in party, all loot picked can be shared right? I don't plan on playing at M+raids with these guys, so is there enough reason to move? I don't know the ins and outs of cross realm partying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on characters on multiple realms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I'm starting to play with friends, but my main is on one realm, while his main is on another, and when making alts, I'm not sure if I stick with mine, or jump to his for it. It could well become my main down the road because I like the look of the class, but I also feel somewhat loyal to my current realm because of passing gold around when needed, along with crafting reagents, and just in general I like having them on the same realm. On the other hand, I know if we're on different realms we can't really trade anything unless in a dungeon. 

Thanks for any advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was confused about this. Why is it on /r/television? just because of the Netflix name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking the Kyle route to any sport is a batshit crazy idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While on the topic of mages, what is arcane like? I've considered playing it but after trying class trial at 100, frost really doesn't appeal to me but can't find anything to show what arcane mage is like as a class, instead of the classic guides and fully set up action bar with no thoughts for the uninitiated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a look around on this site is incredibly useful. I may not go with your suggestion after all. A lot of these seem pretty nice for just a few dungeon runs or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd you find that? I'd love a plain ass white setup. Or plain anything. I just hate running around as a monk with huge ass horns on my shoulders with an embroidered chestpiece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't exactly tank related, but where can I go for some good BrM transmog? I've looked into some MoP raids but they seem straight up not designed for solo runs. I've tried SoO and HoF so far, and the way it looks is that everything after Cata requires more than 1-2 people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're down for some funk, check out Childish Gambino's latest album. Or just look up Redbone and feel it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always preferred consistent damage because of the whole leather armor thing. I guess I had the wrong mindset, my bad. Thanks for clarifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't money come with the lack of kids?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked it up.

Gonna warn y'all real quick, you might not be ready so stay safe seated when searching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a stem in the right direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reviewing poorly rarely ever connects to profits when it comes to well known brand names. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I've been playing it. Im 750ish right now but I just wanted an overarching opinion as I come up to late game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that much easier said than done? I've been invited to a few over time, only to realize there is no activity at all in them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even then. How in the world do I find a raid group that is understanding of the situation? All I've heard of LFR is how much of a joke it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. That's why I'm terrified of raiding. I know how to solo most world content in the game, but when it comes to dungeons/raids, I hate being unprepared. A lot of research will be done before ever setting my foot in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That WA seems wonderful. I've always wanted to use it, but never truly understood it, and given my low ass res, it's been a difficult setup (along with ElvUI) so seeing his explanation for each one, along with the sizing setup... Thanks for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. 

I've felt the opposite about it. It was my first tank, and I always imagined because of stagger it was a much easier class to make mistakes on. I don't mean with huge hits, but the fact that we could delete damage was great for me. The only time I really find the class hard is when there are huge hits incoming, and as far as I know, that's a very wellknown issue among the class. The fault with as other specs have faults.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. And how's the current play rate? I saw that at one point, although not BM, WWs were at a 5% playrate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is Brewmaster doing these days? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I searched up a few terms on here to see how the class is doing because it's my main right now. And by main, I mean it's the only class I have above 100, quite frankly about 30 (my pally) and so far, I've really, really enjoyed the class. I love how mobile it is. How easy it is to aggro, along with the self efficiency for soloing. 

Then I saw [this] (https://www.reddit.com/r/wow/comments/54wiy7/blizzard_can_you_just_remove_brewmaster_from_the/) and started questioning what's up. Is the spec really in that much of a bad state? Was this before 7.1.5? Was this hyperbole, or realistic with slight exaggeration? 

I'd love some thoughts on the spec. Not so I can abandon it, but so I can get an idea of if I should juggle in another class or not. I don't plan on any high level raids, but I'd love to be considered as a reliable addition to the party. Thanks for any opinions,

(PS: I tried frost mage once in class trial and didn't enjoy it. How different is arcane? the class interests me, but I'm not a fan of early game mage so the grind is something I'd avoid if it turns out I don't like the class) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
