<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2866</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 at 18, I felt the same way. It does get better, but honestly it takes a lot of work, and a lot of bad days before you see the good. 

In the beginning of our relationship, my husband didn't understand my BPD diagnosis. We had a fight where I ended up disassociating, and cutting myself. I ended up with 104 stitches on my legs and arms. We started couples counseling before we got married, and then after our second son was born, we restarted again with marriage counseling and individual therapy. That helped both of us tremendously. My husband learned to deal with his family of origin stuff, that was separate from my mental illness. Then, we could deal together, as a unit, on how to move forward as parents, as a wife, and as a husband whenever we had issues.

No joke, it is really hard. After my second son was born, we took some drastic measures dealing with family members (we don't have a relationship with my husband's parents or siblings). A big thing we both learned was that I needed space to vent my emotions, and he needed to create a space to just listen (instead of trying to fix things immediately). 

So now, we do a lot of talking - I'll tell him I'm overwhelmed and need him to listen. He'll hold up a hand and tell me if he's being flooded and can't process everything I'm pouring out at him. We also learned to agree to disagree. Being parents, we have to talk a lot to each other about how we raise and parent our kids, so it's imperative that we have a common base of communication, or else the household just falls into chaos.

My husband also has hobbies like woodworking, and soccer, as outlets for his frustrations. Our therapist really encourages both of us to do self-care and have individual hobbies as well as do things together as a family. My self care is origami, gardening, crafting, photography, and listening to music while walking the dog.

I hope that answers your questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone can understand BPD, unless they are diagnosed with it. Even amongst people with BPD, it differs from people to people. For myself, I had past childhood abuse, and how I coped with it was to learn to disassociate from myself, and to self harm in order to feel anything again. I don't drink, smoke, or do drugs besides caffeine. My main release is self harming. 

What I tell my kids is that mommy has really big emotions. For people without borderline, they may experience something from the scale of 1-10. For me, with borderline, it's more of a scale from -100 to +100. With therapy, I can usually tell what will send me into a triggering episode (for a small example, I know I could never watch Jessica Jones on Netflix, but i can watch Daredevil). 

Again, this is just my personal experience, everyone's dance with their mental illness will be different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
