<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely IBS. I have it too. Go see a specialist or something. My triggers are caffeine and chocolate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure if I have this installed my premiums will go up a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm local and I don't like local food. I have an aversion towards cilantro and lime, and those are in so many local dishes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. It costs $41m for a 4000sqft home in HK and only $8m here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 11:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Polestar is available in my country. But even so it's not for my model. I've read quite a few online reviews (mostly for BMWs) regarding RaceChip and could not come to any useful conclusion as to whether they were actually effective. I'm not trying to make my car faster, just less slow. It currently does 0-100km/h in 12.8s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 11:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't really do any performance upgrades if I want to keep the factory warranty. And there's lots of laws with regards to engine modifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My S80 D2 averaged 5.5L/100km over 20000km of 65% expressway and 35% city. Best runs are around 3.9L/100km.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone using RaceChip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 10:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone of you out there using any products from RaceChip? I'm quite interested in installing their RaceChip One on my Volvo S80 D2 to improve its performance, which is honestly quite lacking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got this game a few hours ago. Constant crashes. I have a G29 and it only rotates about 180 degrees in game. That's ridiculous. And also the lack of SLI support, which is perplexing given how Microsoft was touting all kinds of GPU magic for DX12. Went ahead and got a refund. Will buy again if the issues are ironed out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 09:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are the physics? Stupidly arcade or close to the normal Forza series? I hate NFS because of the arcadey physics, I'm hoping this is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 18:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel anything here. The desensitisation I've gone through being a frequent visitor of that sub  has sucked all the empathy out of me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 09:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure. These private schools were setup with the intention of allowing more students to go through the university experience. So, its raison d'tre is not to be the very best. Unless it can shrug off this image, and ipso facto its original mission, I don't think these 'degree mills' can improve upon their standings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 09:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say both. Private schools won't be able to attract top quality faculty staff. And since the entry requirements are much lower, the students will not be as academically strong either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 05:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rightfully so. Let's not pretend that SIM is anywhere near to being on par with NUS or NTU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Tampines. I like how convenient it is to drive to anywhere as my place is right next to the Bartley Viaduct and 5 minutes from Ikea/Giant/Courts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know of current members who pray everyday for KH not to go to jail. WTF. Is their IQ 0 or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 06:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had an Indo friend that mentioned how his family sold medical products that basically are rubbish but are marketed as miracle cures. He said that their population are dumb and gullible so it's easy to make a fortune there. He mentioned how every few months they'll repackage their medical ointment as another brand claiming to provide additional benefits, and people will flock to buy it. Rinse and repeat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy brings a GoPro to a store in North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did and there's not much of a difference. Everything's slightly faster. I like the new home button but the camera's been a disappointment. The noise reduction is way too aggressive. Everything looks like a watercolour painting. Maybe shooting in RAW will help. I like being able to wash my phone though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Seems like capturing with RAW is much much better. I'd rather have noise than aggressive noise reduction. I've only tried Adobe Lightroom Mobile (which supports DNG capture). Any free camera apps that support RAW?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 13:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, you just have to zoom in slightly to see the muddy image quality. The photos do pop with the wider range of colours but it's really not as sharp as I'd hope. Quite a disappointment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 09:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was at only 32000 miles after 9 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 09:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who thinks that the new camera's making everything blurry like it's painted from watercolour? It's definitely worse than the 6 Plus I had.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 03:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if the screen is as durable as the iPhone 5 series or as bad as the iPhone 6. Had an iPhone 6 Plus that scratched within 3 days even when it was used with extreme care. The iPhone 5 was so durable I tried scratching it with a metal ruler and it came out unscathed. I don't know if I should buy a glass screen protector for the 7 Plus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 17:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well TouchID isn't always used. In any case, there should at least be an Accessibility option to make the Home button more sensitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone think that the force needed to activate the new Home button is too much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per title, I feel that too much force is needed to activate the new Home button. I have to really mash it down to get it to recognise my input. Wished that Apple went with a touch-sensitive activation like with the jailbreak tweak VirtualHome instead. That means one tap: home button; two taps: reachability.

How great would that be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must I use the newer cable to benefit from this? Would the old one from an iPhone 6 Plus work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 12:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driving in ETS2 helped me to become familiar with LHD roads and cars since I live in a RHD country. Was useful when I rented a car in France. ETS2 also taught me to drive more economically, by lifting off when I want the gearbox to shift up, and accepting slower acceleration in my car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Search Indexer is already disabled by the SSD software.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just Dropbox and WinRAR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Windows Defender only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a new one? My computer is set to receive automatic updates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an SSD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Renaming a new folder takes forever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the Anniversary Update, it takes forever to rename a newly-created folder using Windows Explorer. It can take from 1-2 minutes before the spinner stops spinning and the name sticks. If I kill explorer.exe and go back to the folder, it remains unnamed. I've tried using WinRAR to create a new folder and rename it, and that works immediately. What seems to be the problem here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Renaming a new folder takes forever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 12:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ventilated seats in South-East Asia where it's hot and humid. Even S-Classes sold in the region don't have ventilated seats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family combined US$300+K. Volvo S80 and BMW 2-series Active Tourer. Yes, boring cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a SMART Energy at Mandai and at Serangoon. Not very inconvenient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Chrome and soft suspensions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 07:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will people think if I blared classical opera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 05:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My university </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should put the 5 litre V8 from the Mustang into a Focus. It'll be hilarious and Ford will win the hatchback power competition for years to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 11:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not his fault right? When he made the Hara-kiri comment, IIRC, it was for the AHPETC case which was directly the result of WP MPs' doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why you people keep joking about Khaw committing Hara-kiri. Even if that's the practice, shouldn't it be SMRT's CEO?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The calendar's spazzing out when accessed on mobile though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple Maps lack detail and in Singapore. I use Waze all the time because of its very dynamic routing and police alerts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't the driver use the parking brake/engine brake/retarder? If the service brakes aren't working there are plenty of other options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be smart. Don't need to study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it as a warning not to commit crime again. Are you expecting others to sympathize with you? Because I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember on one occasion he pissed a few of us off (NSFs) and we just walked off, ignoring his task. Our boss (a MAJ) sympathized with us and told him basically to piss off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because your wages didn't go up doesn't mean others did not get a pay increment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. I only worked with him for about 3 or 4 times and each time he was disrespectful to anyone ranked lower than him (even just slightly). And those interactions should already have been nicer since his career promotion could easily be influenced by my team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame that he got to SWO with that kind of attitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 08:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this trend too. Lots of expensive watches and Prada glasses. Funnily though, I've been taught since young to think about how much everything costs. I'm quite frugal and will hesitate before spending $11 on that new McDonald's meal even though my family seems to be in the top 1%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 17:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bloody annoying when pickups or vans go at 70km/h and hog the 2nd lane. I always flash them and even sound my horn at them but they don't get the idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea humans in lorries. And yes, I'm comparing to countries more similar to us like those in Europe, also maybe Hong Kong and Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 20:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. But definitely present in the Beta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 110km/h? Amateurs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's smooth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Singapore the only country that does this? I've traveled around but haven't seen anything similar overseas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 08:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Albert Chen. Never liked him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 08:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FFS, this game is more than 3 years old and on its 25th update. I don't think many game developers do this anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Albert Chong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diversity for the sake of diversity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of engines knock with lower octane petrols. Best to read the car manual and use what's recommended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 18:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like leaving because the weather's so damn hot. And no work-life balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err I like Chrome. But then again I'm Asian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's the most gorgeous and elegant car I've ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a new citizen but I'm racist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I foresee a flood of Vabis steering wheel mods... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never cared about freedom of speech. What does this new bill mean for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since they're fully committed to making an SUV why not go full on and put 7 seats in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it in real life. It's not that much bigger but damn the front just looks like a shovel. That kind of design just doesn't work on a Honda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm the only one that thinks the fronts of all the new Civics look absolutely ghastly. It's like trying to look wider than it actually is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 10:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hate the weather here. And the idiotic drivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's called coil whine. I get that with my monitor when I set its colour mode to sRGB. Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. Never heard of cameras being stolen here. Usually the camera light doesn't light up when you're driving, only when it's in parking mode. And you can turn that off easily anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't use Play Store or add Google Account? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, my car has an Android infotainment system running 2.3.7 (yes, can't update that) based off the Parrot Asteroid Smart. It's rooted and I used to use an app called Market Helper to change the device identifier to access the Google Play Store. I don't know what I did, but in the recent weeks I can't access the Play Store anymore. I tried changing it back to default in Market Helper and it gives me a 'No Android ID found' error. 

Trying to access Play Store will throw up an error saying 'Server Error' will pop up. I've tried clearing the Play Store cache, clearing the Google Framework cache, removing the Google Account and re-adding it, but to no avail.

As a last-ditch attempt, I removed the Play Store and the Google Framework and reinstalled them by gaining root access. Now the Google Account is removed. I tried re-adding my account but it says during the account login process that it 'Can't establish a reliable connection to the server'. I searched around and found that a common solution was to edit the etc/hosts file but that wasn't the problem. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really care. I only listen to music on my phone 3-4 times a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the one in Rambouillet, France. Everyone got food poisoning lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain why most people in the US and in Europe prefer stealthy black dashcams? Here in Asia we like it to be noticeable, especially when parked (with flashing LEDs) with the sole intention to tell people not to mess with our cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like LeBlanc. He's too American and unfit to present a British show. That accent is just so jarring compared to the other presenters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the main thing is that you have to speak French in France. Something about their national pride and you taking the effort to speak it makes them willing to help you. I spent two months in France and never got ignored or insulted. Maybe getting taunted by the blacks was the only negative thing, but they do that to everyone. 

Overall the Brits and Germans are the nicest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 08:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks much better than a Miata to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 05:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't get why people cheap out on tyres all the time. It's literally the only contact point your car has with the ground. Where I live a lot of people, some driving Mercedes, like to go for cheap-ass Chinese tyres which are not just a hazard to the driver, but to others on the road as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only I could drive alone on the entire stretch of PIE... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think it was a good idea. The reason behind eugenics is scientifically sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanging the American flag everywhere all year round.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of how stupidly overpriced this is, the cheese does look good though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make the most expensive sandwich - Guinness World Records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 12:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They actually made one! China's Elevated Bus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 07:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people like to hate on Singtel, but I've been on Singtel Fibre for more than 4 years and haven't had any outages for in the past 2. I'm on 300Mbps and can download reliably at 40MB/s (~320Mbps). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the most surprising thing is the Citroen C6.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are CVTs The Best (Fastest) Transmissions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 16:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the worst offenders are taxi drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 11:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then play. My car has autonomous braking. And a dashcam. Or I'll just overtake them when I'm more rational.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 09:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they do this in France and Germany but it doesn't seem to work here. Thing is people don't even check their mirrors when driving, so they won't see your indicators flashing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hate the driving culture here. No one knows how to keep left unless overtaking. When people are hogging the fast lane, I'll not hesitate to use my high beams. Some will then refuse to move left. I'll just use the horn then. It's not illegal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think we'll get anything. I have two of those cards. Will be great to get US$60 but I must say they've been solid performers for the past two years in any case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 09:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistic probably an S Class. Unrealistic Rolls Royce Phantom. I live big luxo-barges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds just like the Chinese. I'm sure you've heard about all the fights they get into on planes. Oh and taking selfies with artwork that specifically says 'No Photography'. I mean, it's hilarious when you see that French museums hire Mandarin-speaking Asians to control those unruly Chinese tourists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my experience, the Chinese are indeed the worst tourists. As a non-China Chinese, I feel ashamed when I see them. My only solution is to speak English or French. I would say the Italians are a close second in being bad tourists. They are obnoxiously loud and have no respect for others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 10:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does someone crash into a tree when the road's so straight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 05:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. I hate Hondas because their designs enable and encourage ricing. Just look at the new Civic Type R. Tasteless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they look like shit and are basically poverty copies of European trucks. Look at any developing/developed South-East Asian country, the richer they get, the more Scanias/Volvos/MANs you see. 

Edit: I hate old Mitsubishi Fusos and Isuzus with a passion as they still run around where I live, spewing cancerous fumes wherever they go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've updated the drivers and cleaned up all the dust that's possible to clean. My card is still under 3 years' warranty so I'm not going to mess with the thermal compound. I don't feel confident in doing that either. I think the overclock's good enough since I have the 970s in SLI. Yes, the BIOS is modded but just to increase the temp limit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 13:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MSI GTX 970 Gaming 4G. I can't use those clocks on very well-optimized games running at 99% GPU usage. For those I can only get it to run at around 1400MHz in 30C room temperature. For other less optimized games or games that can hit VSync framerates most of the time, 1500MHz is a nice and stable overclock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
