<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5554</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kalisto should be billed from Chicago, not Mexico. You can be second generation Mexican American and still respect and admire lucha libre, I mean, just ask Kalisto.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not his fault the company has nothing for him. Right after the brand split they easily could've kept Ziggler in the main event tier but they quickly let him fall back down. They're just not that into him for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also makes no fucking sense at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writers absolutely share a lot of opinions with this sub and the IWC as a whole. But their job is basically just to pitch ideas to Vince every week and make the best out of whatever he decides he wants to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's seen Red live, it would be a crime for him not to make it to WWE someday. Incredible performer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I skip NXT frequently but has she had a promo on tv yet? Can't remember ever hearing her voice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll be saved by the fact that he's a big dude, a decent talker and has undeniable enthusiasm and belief in his gimmick. I see him doing really well actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one of them newfangled MacBook Pros with the touch bar this past Christmas. I'm now getting more into 3D graphics and find out Apple's GPU's are pretty dogshit. Thinking of selling it and building a desktop PC for half the price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked there briefly. I only saw Vince in the elevator lobby one evening when we were both leaving for the day, but I did bump into Triple H in the men's room. Vince I'm sure has his own bathroom. 

The office is really cool for any wrestling fan. TVs in the elevators and cafeteria playing wrestling 24/7. I was there before the WWE Network was a thing but I'd imagine it's all Holy Foley reruns these days. 

If you watch that old WWE Super Bowl commercial from the attitude era, that was all filmed in the office and it's pretty much the same today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Invasion angle completely poisoned WWE. As a kid I saw a show I love lose two of its biggest characters in The Rock and SCSA and get overrun with a bunch of WCW jabronis I didn't give a shit about. There was no reason to stay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though he literally never laughs or smiles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those frog jumps are something else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa I immediately want to know more about Thunder Rosa. Seems perfect for something different in WWE's women's division.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to this guy! I just bought a new MBP three months ago and now that I'm getting into Blender I'm realizing it's practically useless for rendering because of the Radeon card included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of people looking down on Uber drivers. It's just a part time job like any other, and you set your own hours. Seems pretty sweet to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why it's a secret.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White people need heroin money too you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how anyone can have coffee and OJ in the same sitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work culture in the US is really fucked up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm convinced if Socrates were alive today, he'd wear hoodies and the same raggedy jeans every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expect the pendulum to swing the other way in about a decade. I'm 27 currently (with no plans to have kids soon) but I can see myself having a very "Go to school and figure it out yourself." attitude towards my kids. That's how I was raised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just the 80s prep style coming back around. Nothing to be dismayed by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rambo series is known as one full of machine guns and bloodshed, but that's just the sequels. In the first film I believe only 3 people are killed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a funny joke a lot of people are taking too seriously to justify their Ryback hate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's was the kind of promo that makes you buy a Miz tshirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flair on another level in the ring? Ric Flair is Steve Austin's favorite wrestler of all time and even he has said "You've seen one Ric Flair match, you've seen them all."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Bryan would be in trouble at all for what he said. He defended the company and John Cena. Miz and Maryse are the ones that brought up a lot of shit Cena is probably not happy to see brought to light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way anyone on Talking Smack gets more than a few bullet points. There's way too much awkwardness for scripting of any kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid I always wondered why they had those carts at Wrestlemania. Why couldn't Andre just walk?

Answer: Andre could barely walk at all at this point in his life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think her character was kind of ruined long before this on the main roster. Pretty much when she won the championship after hardly any struggle to the top of the division. Bayley is the type of character that should have been jobbing or just barely losing for a full year at least. Kind of like they did with Sami Zayn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only people in 2007 could see this comment right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Miz and Maryse walk off the Talking Smack set like "Welp. We're definitely fired." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maryse is gonna get this show cancelled tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess D-Bry's contract expires in a year and a half? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know how Daniel keeps it together while Miz goes off like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Becky is the only one out there not stinking up the joint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mojo looks like he's about to cut me a deal on a brand new Hyundai Sonata. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of women enjoy face fucking from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck all y'all, I love Curt Hawkins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I live here. That's how I spotted the highway signs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A heel that doesn't back down from a challenge is called a babyface.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are they always driving in New Jersey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then we would all cheer him. What's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. My bad. This one's on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they do a tag match at WM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy man Vince thought the higher numbers made it seem old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS MAKES SO MUCH SENSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would Owens care about such a worthless title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Jericho having a jacket again. Nothing beats the vest and scarf combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the thing-uh: what the casual fans want and what smarks want don't have to be mutually exclusive. A good story is a good story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems decent. Good look. Why didn't he go anywhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If CM Punk couldn't beat Lesnar, tiny 185 lbs Finn Balor would be fucking silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want Samoa Joe to have a killer match with anybody at Wrestlemania. I know he has it in him but since his main roster debut he hasn't really had a solid one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really sucks ass every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing a really shitty red herring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foley deserves whatever he gets tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the Cesaro and Samoa Joe matches were really underwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm glad they *sort of* protected KO a tiny bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 seconds bell to bell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do they ring the bell before announcements? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I hear Goldberg's theme I imagine the main menu of a military FPS game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He never could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dana drove to Milwaukee for eight seconds of screen time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DQ finish. Baylee retains. Charlotte keeps her streak. Let's just get to the main event squash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that was the plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So who are these 2 fighting at Wrestlemania? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they change Braun's music? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately Hornswoggle was released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap can they drag this show out any more? Every segment is ten minutes longer than it needs to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I can't wait to see this Mike Lient guy debut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't want everyone to win every match.

We want Rusev to win every match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owens should never be in a suit. Looks like a guest at a wedding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Machka, young man, machka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the point of this? I hope this show turns around. We all know the end is going to suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Rusev still selling on the floor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cesaro with yet another terrible ill fitting outfit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope they push Jinder a little bit here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowd was pretty hot for a truly shitty match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd end up with a crushed orbital socket like 95 Undertaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably setting up for a title win at Wrestlemania </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in that WWE mobile game, do both Rollins and Ambrose have trunks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right I completely forgot about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you bring up Glenn Jacobs? Is he in the video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn USWA was like the WWE's RC Cola. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really is a great PPV. Several good matches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it could be great. He's gotta find his groove. He's only 22 so there's plenty of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zach Gowen

Amazing Red

Brad Maddox if he still cared about wrestling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that Maya Angelou's voice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not entitled to anyone's fucking attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're like a professional adorable person aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underrated match: Big Show vs Cody Rhodes tables match from Extreme Rules 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I think they're great. I'm a Billie Kay man but they're both hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's an okay wrestler, but she's excellent at her bitchy heel persona. She emotes well and delivers her lines well, which is more than can be said for half the roster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're never gonna get rid of shitty jokes and puns on Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very compassionate way to look at it. Good on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one: Locked his wife in the locker room backstage while he performed because he was insecure about the other guys looking at or talking to her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact you can have an awesome match with very few moves at all. Just watch nearly any Vince McMahon match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sara? Gold? Maybe bronze at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's not just hot, she's got an awesome physique. Eva Marie looks like a model. Mandy looks like a model who can deadlift 450.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mandy and Daria both show a lot of promise and I think both will go far (especially Mandy.) Though I think the idea of an "MMA fighter" going into a match and doing suplexes and roll ups is gonna be problematic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so. She's a fine athlete and a GREAT actress. Definitely an asset to the company in some way, even if it's not as an in ring performer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean Baron Corbin is doing it now. It just evolved over time but it's all metal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like both those guys, but I think booking them against each other is kind of dumb. When a guy leaves WWE, I want to see him work against my favorite indie talents, not another WWE guy. 

That said, I'm not a promoter so what do I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for trying at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're delusional. Fans care more about fucking James Ellsworth than Roman Reigns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clear consensus among all those comments is that Roman is a very talented guy who's been booked to his own detriment from the minute he broke away from the Shield. 

I.e. The same opinion most people on Reddit have of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always liked Swagger. They could've done more with him. His promos were fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why Shane needs a match at all, and to put him against AJ Styles is a huge waste of AJ Styles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I demand that Drew Gulak retrieve his medieval times robe at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really curious to see where that leaves Harper and Rowan now. Even though Harper broke away from Bray, it was mostly Randy's fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crews' pencil thin mustache is killing me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too get great enjoyment out of seeing Kalisto murdered every week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol gotta love Hawkins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever the plans were for Harper at wrestlemania, I hope they're being reconsidered after that sick performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow the commentators could care less that Shane was just murdered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early 30s I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very possible. I'm just going off what I remember from some Kamala interview.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, WWE didn't do that with Kamala, but I'm pretty sure Jerry Lawler did when he first hired him in Memphis. Kamala was like "but I'm not a wrestler!" And jerry was like "don't worry just go out there and growl and swat at me and we'll make a zillion dollars" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's also a live performance, and it's rude and classless to fuck it up and chant dumb shit during a serious scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was handled very well, but there's no denying he just wasn't very good his first few months. My point is that didn't stop WWE from calling him up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Seth's segment was great. He was pouring his heart out out there. Can you imagine being out with a knee injury for like 8 months, coming back and reinjuring the same knee? I felt so bad for him. Green Bay is a bunch of assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked her a lot in NXT. She's just in over her head on the main roster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WWE has a long history of putting giants on TV that don't know how to work and protecting them by hiding their weaknesses. From Zeus to Kamala to Giant Gonzales to Khali to Nathan Jones to a few dozen other guys we've long forgotten. Even Braun was a mess when he first debuted. They figured they could hide her weaknesses but with a female roster so thin, and women's wrestling having such a spotlight on it today, that's not as easy as it used to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a box. It's a little pager-type thing you wear on your person all day. They want to be able to measure all the media you consume throughout the day, in the car, at restaurants, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is petty, but I'm actually a Nielsen family and I mute RAW for Roman Reigns segments so the meter doesn't pick it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great psychology in that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left knee is a work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a flippy shit division. There's just as many ground and pound guys as flippy guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only people who like Raw being 3 hours are the USA Network execs and shareholders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
