<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish supermarkets replace sticky labels with laser marking: Food retailers aiming to cut plastic packaging by ditching stickers on fruits and vegetables, instead using hi-tech natural branding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 05:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish supermarkets replace sticky labels with laser marking: Food retailers aiming to cut plastic packaging by ditching stickers on fruits and vegetables, instead using hi-tech natural branding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 05:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julian Assange under pressure to hand himself in for extradition following Manning commutation: Last week Assange said that he would give up his sanctuary in the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, if Obama showed "clemency" to whistleblower Manning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parts of United States are heating faster than globe as a whole: A new study shows Northeast USA will reach the dangerous 2C warming threshold faster than most of the rest of the planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vladimir Putin calls creators of 'fake' Donald Trump dossier 'worse than prostitutes': Russian President claims international conspiracy working to 'delegitimise' the President-elect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile we've got [this](http://www.truth-out.org/news/item/39032-trump-s-suppression-of-climate-science-echoes-restrictions-under-stalin):

 Trump has appointed Scott Pruitt, a climate-change denier, to lead the US Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), while choosing another denier, former Texas Gov. Rick Perry to lead the US Department of Energy. Trump himself has labeled global warming a hoax created by the Chinese to damage the US economy, despite climate change being almost universally acknowledged by scientists.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China scraps construction of 85 planned coal power plants: Move comes as Chinese government says it will invest 2.5 trillion yuan into the renewable energy sector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human Rights Watch lists Trump as threat to human rights: "Donald Trumps election as US president after a campaign fomenting hatred and intolerance, and the rising influence of political parties in Europe that reject universal rights, have put the postwar human rights system at risk, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Executive Order 12333, often referred to as twelve triple-three, has attracted less debate than congressional wiretapping laws, but serves as authorization for the NSAs most massive surveillance programs  far more than the NSAs other programs combined. Under 12333, the NSA taps phone and internet backbones throughout the world, records the phone calls of entire countries, vacuums up traffic from Google and Yahoos data centers overseas, and more. 

... records the phone calls of entire countries. It's scary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior British politicians targeted by Kremlin for smear campaigns: Former minister Chris Bryant claims Russian agents compile blackmail dossiers on all high-profile ministers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With only days until Donald Trump takes office, the Obama announced new rules that will let the NSA share vast amounts of private data gathered without warrant, court orders or congressional authorization with 16 other agencies, including the FBI, DEA and DHS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British ex-spy behind Trump dossier seen as a cool operator: Christopher Steele is a well-regarded operative who wouldnt make up stories to satisfy his clients, according to diplomatic and intelligence experts who know him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With only days until Donald Trump takes office, the Obama announced new rules that will let the NSA share vast amounts of private data gathered without warrant, court orders or congressional authorization with 16 other agencies, including the FBI, DEA and DHS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With only days until Donald Trump takes office, the Obama announced new rules that will let the NSA share vast amounts of private data gathered without warrant, court orders or congressional authorization with 16 other agencies, including the FBI, DEA and DHS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia's religious authority says cinemas, song concerts harmful: The Grand Mufti Sheikh Abdulaziz Al al-Sheikh said cinemas and round-the-clock entertainment could open the door to "atheistic or rotten" foreign films and encourage the mixing of the sexes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....curiouser, since it isn't a word. 

Follow [this thread, perhaps?](https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/5nv73m/former_mi6_agent_christopher_steeles_frustration/dceovnn/). 

No offence intended ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A young woman has died after being diagnosed with cervical cancer  after she was previously refused a smear test for being too young </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog saves owners life by lying on him for nearly 24 hours in freezing conditions: 'I think animals can help and his dog really kept him alive and really helped him, he was very fortunate,' says doctor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This viewpoint that Britain, either its Government or people, favours a Trump presidency is bullshit.

PM May doesn't seem to think much about Steele although it hasn't exactly favour Trump, it's not supporting the Steele report either

http://www.bbc.co.uk/search?q=may+on+mi6 sa_f=search-product scope= </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Porn censorship laws and age checks breach human rights and threaten privacy, says UN official: 'said that amendments to the UKs Digital Economy Bill could violate international law on freedom of speech.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 10:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloudflare Finally Able To Reveal FBI Gag Order That Congress Told Cloudflare Couldn't Possibly Exist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alice in Wonderland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After almost a century of research, scientists capture rare ruby seadragons on video for the first time. And they are amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloudflare Finally Able To Reveal FBI Gag Order That Congress Told Cloudflare Couldn't Possibly Exist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mr Steele also decided to pass on information to both British and American intelligence officials after concluding that such material should not just be in the hands of political opponents of Mr Trump, who had hired his services, but was a matter of national security for both countries.

 However, say security sources, Mr Steele became increasingly frustrated that the FBI was failing to take action on the intelligence from others as well as him. He came to believe there was a cover-up, that a cabal within the Bureau blocked a thorough inquiry into Mr Trump, focusing instead on the investigation into Hillary Clintons emails. 

Its just get curiouser and curiouser - who hired Steele and why didn't British intelligence prompt their US counterpart to take action since its a 'matter of national security for both countries?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former MI6 agent Christopher Steele's frustration as FBI sat on Donald Trump Russia file for months: Steele was so concerned by revelations he worked without payment after Trump's election victory in November </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trans-Pacific Partnership is dead, according to a Donald Trump transition team policy advisor, while reaffirming that the incoming administration views China as perpetrating an economic war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia announces plan to permanently leave G8 group of industrialised nations after suspension for Crimea annexation: 'It is clear what this Group of Seven means without other major economies,' says Russian Prime Minister Dmitry Medvedev. 'Nothing' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson Won't Address What Exxon Knew About Climate Change: He refused to talk about Exxon Mobils funding of outside organizations in order to create doubt about climate science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While You Werent Looking, the FBI Acquired the Power to Spy on You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While You Werent Looking, the FBI Acquired the Power to Spy on You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia to decriminalise domestic violence to preserve 'tradition of parental authority': 'You dont want people to be imprisoned for two years and labelled a criminal for the rest of their lives for a slap' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top UK and European pharmaceuticals lose 11.6bn after Donald Trump press conference: $25bn was wiped off the value of the S P 500s top nine pharmaceutical companies in a matter of minutes on Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New evidence shows 'strong case' for ban on chemicals linked to bird and bee deaths: Scientists say the EU should consider extending a partial ban on the use of neonicotinoids amid evidence they are lethal to partridges and can stop house sparrows from flying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intelligence chiefs allege Russians have compromising personal information on Donald Trump: The claims allege the now-President-elect had been in contact with Russian intermediaries for five years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany's ugliest word of the year is "traitor of the people" - or Volksverraeter: The word is seen by many as having Nazi overtones and has been used recently by right-wing groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-thirds of all new HIV cases in Europe are being recorded in just one country  Russia: More than a million Russians now live with the virus and that number is expected to nearly double in the next decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese scientists believe they have established the identity of a "missing element" within the Earth's core. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czech government tells its citizens how to fight terrorists: Shoot them yourselves | The interior ministry is pushing a constitutional change that would let citizens use guns against terrorists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian government 'ready to negotiate on everything,' Assad says: President Bashar al-Assad indicates he is willing to consider the possibility of stepping down in free elections if rebels agree to restarting peace talks later this month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Cops Punish Suspected Hacker By Having Him Work With The Organization He Hacked To Patch Up Security Holes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2015, China set the world record for most solar power capacity installed in one year, adding enough solar panels to cover one and a half football pitches every hour. In 2016, the country smashed that record, doubling installations to three football pitches per hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2015, China set the world record for most solar power capacity installed in one year, adding enough solar panels to cover one and a half football pitches every hour. In 2016, the country smashed that record, doubling installations to three football pitches per hour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber has suffered another setback to its operational model in Europe after a Swiss insurance agency ruled that Uber drivers are employees, not freelance contractors as the company claims  meaning it must pay social security contributions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German police quash Breitbart story of mob setting fire to Dortmund church:'...rightwing website Breitbart claimed a mob chanting Allahu Akbar had set fire to a church in the city of Dortmund on New Years Eve. ' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warming seas are forcing fish to seek new waters: Rising sea temperatures are pushing shoals hundreds of miles from native grounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young Russian denies she aided election hackers: I never work with douchebags: White House claims Alisa Shevchenko was involved in hacking the US election but in an interview she says authorities misinterpreted facts or were fooled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four-day working week could be trialled in Italy: When Italy last cut down its working week it's believed to have created one million new jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sick seven-year-old boy died 'because parents prayed instead of calling 911': Parents said son had been ill for weeks but had not sought medical help because they had 'issues' with doctors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be fair to say that China is pissed with Trump?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Arrogant' US is just a 'shooting star in the ample sky of history,' says Chinese state media: Statement comes as Robert Lighthizer, who has called for a more aggressive approach to dealing with China, is appointed as Mr Trump's trade representative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One third of new medications offer no new benefits, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Christmas Day, Kevin Wesley posted a question on Facebook that you dont always expect from a pastor: What if the bible, is NOT the word of God? A day later, he made a video elaborating on that idea and effectively declaring himself an atheist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were extremely scornful, as if they were the masters of the world or we were worth nothing, Sofia recounted indignantly.

Are the cops there really that bad or is she just overreacting? The police would have been trained to handle such situations considering the various incidents of attacks   bombings in Turkey in 2016.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gospel Singer Who Said Gay People Are Perverts Who Will Die Will No Longer Appear on Ellen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK M62 shooting - Charts show difference between police shootings in the US and the UK: Just four people were shot dead by British police in 2016, compared with 957 in the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's smallest elephants killed for ivory in Borneo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finland becomes the first country in Europe to pay its unemployed citizens a basic monthly income, in a radical pilot project: Two thousand people will receive 560 euros every month for two years, without having to report whether they are seeking employment or how they are spending the money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials in Wisconsin removed information about climate change on a government website and replaced it with unfounded claims that the science behind global warming is still a matter of debate within days of Trumps election victory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook 'censors' naked statue of sea god Neptune: Facebook told art historian the image violates its guide lines because it "presents an image with content that is explicitly sexual". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Maher Pushes Back on Donald Trumps Supposed Atheism: His God Is Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Snowden says he is not worried](http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/12/13/snowden_not_worried_trump_deal_to_extradite/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mike Pompeo wants to execute Edward Snowden and firmly re-establish mass surveillance as the law of the land in a way that goes even further.

 In an op-ed at the Wall Street Journal in January, Pompeo wrote..., Congress should pass a law re-establishing collection of all metadata, and combining it with publicly available financial and lifestyle information into a comprehensive, searchable database.

 Combining of all ones metadata could be even more dangerous than what the government has already done (if its not doing this secretly already). Coordinating individuals metadata into government databases means virtually anything we dowhat we read, where we shop, who our doctor is, who we chat with online, who we call on the phone, who we datebecomes government info.

So he wants everything there is to know about us. WTF is he going to do with all these info?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps pick to head the CIA wants the government to spy on virtually everything we do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps pick to head the CIA wants the government to spy on virtually everything we do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps pick to head the CIA wants the government to spy on virtually everything we do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK a source of 'evil and misery' for the Middle East, says Iran's Supreme Leader: Ayatollah Ali Khamenei responds to Theresa May's recent comments on Iranian aggression at Gulf Co-operation Council summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlin Breitscheidplatz: 'Migrant' detained over lorry attack: The driver is an Afghan or Pakistani asylum seeker, according to security sources cited by DPA news agency. He reportedly arrived in Germany in February as a refugee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ridiculous German Court Ruling Means Linking Online Is Now A Liability </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Republics End </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK's biggest energy supplier faces boycott calls over climate change denier links: 'For a company that has claimed to be at the forefront of action on climate change, it is simply astounding that Centrica is donating money to climate deniers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Copenhagen makes fourth bid to legalise cannabis to help reduce gang warfare: Danish government unlikely to grant request for trial legalisation programme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte, who has unleashed a bloody war on drugs since taking office, is backpedalling after admitting that he once abused fentanyl, a powerful prescription opioid.

 Fools, I just made up that story and you believed it, Duterte said on Saturday, according to the Agence France-Presse.

The guy's a clown - who can believe what he says anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia lobbies US over law that allows 9/11 victims to sue the Kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T, Verizon Laugh At The FCC's Last-Minute Attempt To Crack Down On Zero Rating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Republican lawmakers in Utah are drafting legislation claiming abortion is reversible with medication - even though theres no solid scientific evidence behind the idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim cleric banned in Pakistan is preaching in UK mosques: It is feared that Syed Muzaffar Shah Qadri, who praised the murder of a politician, will incite hatred between Muslims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pharma Execs Arrested in Shockingly Organized Scheme to Overprescribe Notorious Opioid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Systems biggest asteroid is an ancient ocean world: NASA's Dawn spacecraft finds that Ceres is full of water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one wants to help Donald Trump build a registry of Muslims: Tech giants Microsoft and IBM have said they would refuse to help create a registry of Muslim Americans under Trump's presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Publishes Eight Secret FBI Requests: Google revealed in October it had been freed from a gag order preventing it from talking about a secret FBI request for customer data made in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Publishes Eight Secret FBI Requests: Google revealed in October it had been freed from a gag order preventing it from talking about a secret FBI request for customer data made in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Publishes Eight Secret FBI Requests: Google revealed in October it had been freed from a gag order preventing it from talking about a secret FBI request for customer data made in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 09:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DuPont to Pay $50 Million for Mercury Pollution, Largest Settlement in Virginia History: "[The settlement] ranks 8th in all of time of natural resource damage settlements across the country ... and that includes such big cases like Deep Water Horizon and Exxon Valdez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 09:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 08:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some sources reporting on the controversial new law: 

https://www.texastribune.org/2016/11/28/texas-moves-forward-rules-requiring-burial-or-crem/

http://www.bigstory.ap.org/article/dee4952b9123455a9ce42caf566489c5/texas-require-burial-or-cremation-aborted-fetuses

http://www.rawstory.com/2016/07/texas-republicans-want-aborted-fetal-tissue-taken-to-funeral-homes/

Advocacy group NARAL Pro-Choice Texas petitioned against the new law: 

http://www.dallasnews.com/news/texas-politics/2016/10/26/abortion-rights-advocates-submit-petition-texas-fetal-remains-rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon deforestation ticks tragically up: The rate of deforestation in the Amazon rainforest has increased again in 2016, for the fourth consecutive year - loss of rainforest this year has been the greatest since 2008. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge blocks a controversial Texas law requiring fetal remains be cremated or buried </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A federal judge blocks a controversial Texas law requiring fetal remains be cremated or buried. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK 'secretly selling arms to Saudi Arabia and elsewhere under opaque licencing system': Campaigners say licensing system designed for less sensitive trade deals is being abused </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Inspector Who Criticized Snowden for Not Using 'Official' Channels Found Guilty of Retaliating Against Whistleblower Who Did Just That </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who was wrongly imprisoned for 31 years gets $75 in compensation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia to 'inoculate' children against Westernisation, atheism and liberalism: They are listed as threats to ideological security, ahead of the danger from extremist groups including Isis and al-Qaeda and sectarianism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOAA Issues 'Jaw-Dropping' Assessment on 'Unprecedented' Arctic Warming: Latest Arctic Report Card finds that region's temperatures continue upward climb twice as fast as global temperature increase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOAA Issues 'Jaw-Dropping' Assessment on 'Unprecedented' Arctic Warming: Latest Arctic Report Card finds that region's temperatures continue upward climb twice as fast as global temperature increase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's richest man warns Trump - US jobs are at stake: Wanda's 20,000 employees will have "nothing to eat" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump advisors plan to strangle net neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US cancels major aid package to the Philippines over human rights concerns: '... there are 'significant concerns' about civil liberties under President Duterte' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists are frantically copying US climate data, fearing it might vanish under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 15:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new king of Thailand will pardon up to 150,000 prisoners in an unprecedented display of mercy, including some inmates jailed for insulting the royal family. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox Host Defends Putin: At Least Hes A Christian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump rejects science, claims nobody really knows if climate change is real: He is wrong. Climate change is real. Scientists know this to be a fact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump wipes $3.5bn off Lockheed Martin market value with single tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charity warns of FGM 'parties' taking place in England: 'The Black Health Initiative in Leeds says midwives from Africa are being flown into the country to carry out the illegal practice.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 11:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [12/13/16] Unarmed 73-year-old man with dementia shot dead by US police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 11:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump wipes $3.5bn off Lockheed Martin market value with single tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Activists Fight Back Against Exxon's Subpoenas: The oil giant, seemingly emboldened by a federal judge's ruling it can poke into a state AG's investigation, wants 350.org's records, too. The group is refusing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Becomes First State to Sue Monsanto Over PCBs, Accused of Knowing Its Toxicity for Decades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was told I couldnt even speak to my colleagues. All I had done was to nurse from my heart. How could it be harmful to tell someone about Jesus?

Because your trying to impose your beliefs onto others who don't wish to know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump will have wider spying powers than anything J. Edgar Hoover ever imagined </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nurse who gave a patient a bible she did not want and spoke about religion with patients has said she will fight her dismissal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The colossal African solar farm that could power Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boeing and Iran agree $16.8bn deal for 80 passenger planes: Firm says agreement will support some 100,000 US jobs, while Iranians will create another 8,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Government Gives $11,000 Back To College Student Three Years After The DEA Took It From Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Half of people "remember" events that never happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Half of people "remember" events that never happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Richard Burr of NC blocked foster care reform to protect profits for religious group homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenlands Vast Ice Sheet Is Way Less Stable Than We Thought, And Thats Bad News For The World: Two new studies reveal just how dynamic  and potentially vulnerable to climate change  it actually is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 14:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenlands Vast Ice Sheet Is Way Less Stable Than We Thought, And Thats Bad News For The World: Two new studies reveal just how dynamic  and potentially vulnerable to climate change  it actually is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 14:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rome to ban cars and scooters on Sunday as Italys cities fight smog: eco-Sunday will also see mopeds and motorcycles banned from city streets, with only vehicles deemed environmentally-friendly exempted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa and Stephen Hawking are working on a nano-starship that can travel 1/5th the speed of light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 05:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 04:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wouldn't it literally take centuries to do that though? really centuries.

Nope.

[SpaceX founder Elon Musk plans to get humans to Mars in six years]
(https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2016/sep/27/elon-musk-spacex-mars-colony) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa and Stephen Hawking are working on a nano-starship that can travel 1/5th the speed of light: 'If successful, the ship, called StarChip could reach Earths closest star system, Alpha Centauri, in 20 years.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte's Barbaric War on Drugs: Thousands Are Being 'Slaughtered Like Animals' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman who took selfie with neglected, skeletal horse prosecuted after being caught on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 07:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The CIA presentation fell short of a formal U.S. assessment by all 17 U.S. intelligence agencies, the Post said. A senior U.S. official said there remained minor disagreements among intelligence officials about the assessment because some questions are unanswered, it said.



So did the Russians interfered with the GE or didn't they, according to the CIA?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Collected Data From People Using Cell Phones On Planes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedens recycling is so revolutionary, the country has run out of rubbish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No apology will give me back my life: The man who served 43 years for a murder he didnt commit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No apology will give me back my life: The man who served 43 years for a murder he didnt commit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salvation Army: Anti-Gay Christian Church Not Worthy of Support | </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists slam Donald Trump's environment chief over climate denial: 'It's like disputing gravity' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists slam Donald Trump's environment chief over climate denial: 'It's like disputing gravity' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German court rules Muslim girls must take part in swimming lessons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German court rules Muslim girls must take part in swimming lessons: Constitutional judges say schoolgirl cannot be excused mixed classes on grounds of Islamic dress codes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groups Demand Arrest of 'War Mastermind' Kissinger at Nobel Peace Prize Forum: Nobel Peace Prize committee honors Kissinger a second time with speaking engagement at new forum on world peace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman who rescued Nigerian 'witch-child' beats Obama, Pope Francis to top list of world's most inspiring people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Softbank's Son Trying to Sell Trump on Sprint, T-Mobile Merger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malta becomes first country in Europe to ban 'gay cure' therapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese newspaper accuses 'inexperienced' Donald Trump of having tantrums </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Philippines: No country for poor men | Duterte won his presidency with a promise of a brutal crackdown on drugs. But six months and more than 4,000 deaths later, a troubling picture of the profile of those being targeted is emerging. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google to be powered 100% by renewable energy from 2017: Internet giant says renewable energy is increasingly lowest cost option and it will not rule out investing in nuclear power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Warns AT T, Verizon That Zero Rating is Anti-Competitive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading a post about shampoo/conditioner being a likely cause of this. Could be useful reading the comments:

https://www.reddit.com/r/SkincareAddiction/comments/5dae1y/acne_psa_if_you_are_having_trouble_with_back_neck/? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But he was only protecting himself, your honour!" /s

 Coe, who is 6ft 1in and weighs 16 and a half stone, admitted shoving the boy, who is half his size, but claimed he was acting in self-defence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man jailed for attacking boy over embrace with girl in London street: Michael Coe, an associate of hate preacher Anjem Choudary, sentenced to 28 months after knocking teenager unconscious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China says Trump clear about Taiwan, in touch with his team: Vice President-elect Mike Pence played down the telephone conversation, saying it was a "courtesy" call, not intended to show a shift in U.S. policy on China. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man jailed for attacking boy over embrace with girl in London street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela to reissue currency as value of its biggest banknote drops to 2p: The largest-denominated note is curently 100 Bolivars but a two-litre soft drink costs around 25 times that amount </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
