<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6310</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got to say, that just seemed like regular rage nothing crazy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, it wasn't. Herzog's voice is on a different spectrum of sound then the rest of the human race.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i guess for me, i would consider them more of an "always there" hazard. almost like the heat in the desert or the cold in the tundra. The helicopter is the only enemy that comes after you when its shot at. (Bears will come after you too, yes, but if shot from a mild distance they just stand there and take the hits.) Heli has a planned route it takes to go around "busy" areas on the map and attack people that meet its "get rekt requirements" ^^TM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah that must be where starcraft got the name for their primitive alien race "the zerg".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guys i think he's talking about the "PVE enemies" part not the "make enemies" part. Their is only one PVE enemy which is the helicopter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Characters in the story:  
Badass, FBI agent that knows about his legend but is undecided in whether its true or not, 3 well trained FBI Agents. 

***Badass hears helicopter approaching his cabin in the woods of west virginia.   
No address because obviously he's off the grid and has been for years.***  

*FBI agent: "Hello Badass"  
BA: "I'm Retired"  
FBI: you haven't even heard what i have to say  
BA: listen im 14 years old now *he scratches his glued on Halloween USA beard and stops chopping wood for a moment   "I've been retired ever since i killed those 3 guys in an alley in Brooklyn 10 months ago."    
FBI: i know but -  
BA: i said im retired! *starts to walk off   
FBI: *quietly "there are 3 more guys in that alley"  
BA: "im not doing it"  
FBI: "well then we're going to have to make you go."  
BA: "oh with those 3 well trained FBI agents? I took them out between lines 4 and 5."   
FBI: *looks back to see all 3 agents beaten with different bones in different parts of their body (honestly just mad lib which bones go where, shits brutal)      
FBI: so the legends are true...    
BA: *thinks for a second "fine i'll go, Im not becoming Batman though. F*CK that. I want a normal life.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly looks pretty bad compared to now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morty you're the best, I was able to read your post before the bots interference, so you're good. I'm glad you're saying the stress will be worth it because what I don't want to do is pay basically the same amount for a place I'm just renting and where I am it's really easy to do that. Yeah and it seems everything is either 20k too low and I don't want it or it's 20k too high and the house is perfect. So I agree with the price range difficulty. Thanks again for the numbers and the timeframe. In the next coming months when I finally do the deed I'll make sure to come back and let you know how it went!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow Morty! this is so much information Morty. But exactly what i was looking for! Im so nervous about buying my first house but having a general consensus of the numbers and a broad area of what i'll be paying. Seriously thanks for taking the time and getting me these numbers! if i get to the future Morty i'll make sure to make you proud Morty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is kinda weird because come march this is the exact kind of deal I want. Exact price of the house I'm looking for and you make the same amount I make. Are you future me? If so and if you don't mind could you delve a little bit deeper into how much everything ended up costing you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
