<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4342</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung Galaxy S8 preorders to start on April 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Silicon Shift That's Transforming How Tech Giants Make Phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got me excited for it. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Google is undermining MWC debutants simply by having the best mobile camera tech all to itself. Granted, the Pixels distribution and marketing still leave it as a niche device for now, but its acting essentially like an iPhone  dampening enthusiasm for the newest and shiniest Android phones by virtue of its superior technology.

I'm  all for having the best smartphone camera, but Google isn't undermining Android manufacturers by having unique camera software for its hardware. There is still plenty of enthusiasm surrounding new Android hardware releases. Not everyone is going to get the G6, but there's still a group of fans eager to get the phone. Then the even larger Galaxy fan base is enthusiastic for the upcoming S8/S8+. 

When it comes to the top tier flagships, you're going to get a good shooter no matter which option you go with. Would it be nice to have Google's processing on my non-Pixel phone? Yes, but that alone isn't going to sway my buying decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this has more to do with the behind the scenes processing of the camera than the actual layout of the app. So technically, the manufacturer could still use Google's camera software, but also be free to add in other options to the app. Manual controls are so useful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine a world where every Android phone has the Google Pixels camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google: We're hiking bug bounties because finding security flaws is getting tougher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Lenovo plans to introduce its own "AI-powered" service to devices later this.

 Lenovo's coming voice-based service will rely on a personal identifier attached to all users of its hardware, allowing it to work consistently across Lenovo phones, tablets, desktop and laptop computers, said Dery.

 Dery described this as a supplement to the assistants from Amazon and Google. While those two services mostly respond to queries and commands, Lenovo's will send notifications and alerts based on predictions about users' behavior and needs, according to the executive.

 "We don't like to call it an assistant because it's misleading in a way," he said. "This is something which is always aware, in the background, syncing for you."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Vies With Partners as Digital Helpers Crowd Barcelona </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In regards to the Galaxy S8:

 yield rates for Samsung's 10nm process technology have been low affecting production for its own Exynos 8895 and Qualcomm's Snapdragon 835 chips, the sources revealed. The unsatisfactory 10nm yield rates have already pushed back Samsung's schedule to launch the next-generation Galaxy S8 smartphone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it has been a while since I've seen someone talk about BBM. I'm sure some here still use it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait for the updates to drop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were removed for "rehosted content." As one of the rules, they prefer you post from the source link. This is a weird one since the source in this case were two separate links for the apps. I think an exception should've been made since the sources weren't actual articles, but I guess the rule is firm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New BBM Release Delivers Chat API, New Look and Feel, Better Analytics, Spam Reporting and More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beta sign up available for Gboard and Google Play Services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gboard](https://play.google.com/apps/testing/com.google.android.inputmethod.latin/join)

[Google Play Services](https://play.google.com/apps/testing/com.google.android.gms)

For those that haven't seen it yet since the other posts were removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android Studio 2.3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get more work done on Android: Exchange Tasks now available on Gmail app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Supreme Court: No, you cant hide public records on a private account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted in the post:

 Now, when you open the photo editor in Google Photos and select a look, well not only correct exposure and saturation, we'll also automatically correct the white balance in the image.

 Auto white balance in looks are rolling out this week on Android and web, and soon well bring it to iOS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six tips to make your photos pop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump pulls Obamas final FCC nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon explains big AWS outage, says employee error took servers offline, promises changes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Improvements to searching for special characters in programming languages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: [Official Google Post](https://blog.google/products/allo/smarter-sharing-chat-google-allo/)

The three noted changes:

 In an update to Allo for Android today, Google is placing a button to access the Assistant right in the little box where you type out a message. Previously, you had to type @google in order to call up the Assistant.

 Google is adding two other new features to Allo today. One is the ability to search for GIFs, which you can do by pulling up Allos emoji suggestion box and swiping all the way to the end of it.

 Allo is also getting some giant animated emoji today that spring to life when you enlarge them with the apps shout feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allo now makes it easier to bring Google Assistant into conversations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung wants its Exynos 9 chip in VR headsets, not just smartphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is UFS 2.0.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo says about 32 million accounts accessed using 'forged cookies' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC halts internet privacy requirements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC halts internet privacy requirements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear. [Others haven't been so lucky](http://www.apple.com/shop/reviews/MMX62AM/A/lightning-to-35-mm-headphone-jack-adapter) and I just want to avoid that from occurring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm basing it on what I've seen. [Plenty of people here](http://www.apple.com/shop/reviews/MMX62AM/A/lightning-to-35-mm-headphone-jack-adapter) have noted they're fragile. Keep in mind that I'm not saying everyone's adapter is going to break. I just want to avoid that possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google unveils playable ads for Android game developers and other tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For those that want to see](http://i.imgur.com/oAUONmb.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you can see why I said that. That said, the pair of Sennheisers I purchased years ago have survived all of that abuse and continue to work normally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't baby my headphones/earbuds. I cram them into my backpack, stuff them into my pocket, and occasionally throw them around. Also, reviews on Apple's site have people complaining about the adapter breaking after some time. It's not going to happen to everyone, especially those that just use them at home, but it can happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BGR finally puts out something worth clicking on. Looks good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do bundle it, but the adapter feels so cheap and flimsy. If I were to leave it attached to my headphones all the time, the adapter wouldn't last long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple does tend to start trends, but I think this is one that won't be widely adopted anytime soon. Plenty of people still rely on headphone jacks, and for those that don't, having a jack there isn't really a nuisance. On the Apple side, people just deal with it since it's an iPhone. Whereas some people shop for a phone that has certain features, such as water resistance or a fingerprint sensor, I have yet to see anyone saying not having a headphone jack is an important selling point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, Apple, the headphone jack isnt going anywhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Photos v2.10 prepares for photo archiving, includes syncing and improvements for RAW photos and other visual tweaks [APK Teardown + Download] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Screenshot of the channels it has](http://i.imgur.com/9h7boWP.png). Also includes regional sports networks and local TV stations.

 For $35 a month, subscribers get all four major networks - ABC, CBS, FOX, and NBC - and around 30 of the biggest cable channels. That price covers six accounts, so each member of the household can have a personalized account that offers recommendations tuned to their taste.

 Sadly, like many other streaming bundles, it has gaps. YouTube TV, as its called, will be missing channels from Viacom, including big names like Comedy Central and MTV. It also wont have programming from Turner Broadcasting, meaning you wont be able to get CNN, TBS, and TNT. AMC Networks, Discovery Communications, and A+E Networks are also missing as of the launch announcement.


Other tidbits mentioned by [The Next Web](https://thenextweb.com/apps/2017/02/28/google-announces-youtube-tv-service-rivals-cable/#.tnw_UUTRh8Pq):

 The service also includes a feature called Cloud DVR, which allows you to save an unlimited number of shows without worrying about the storage limits of a traditional DVR.

 The company also said it was focusing on providing a solid customer service experience, because cable services tend to suck at that. Youll be able to call, email, or chat with customer service right from the YouTube TV app.

 Speaking of the app, its divided into three sections: Library, Home, and Live. The Live section allows you to channel surf, even letting you swipe up and down to switch between channels instantly. To record a show, simply tap on the + icon.

 Meanwhile, the Library tab is meant to help you find your favorite shows as well as your recordings. It also provides show suggestions using machine learning based on your interests and a shows characteristics.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube launches its own streaming TV service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube launches its own streaming TV service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticking to the gaming topic, the following was also noted at the [Game Developers Conference](https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2017/02/welcome-to-google-developer-day-at-game.html):

 **More curation of high quality games through editorial pages**: One more way we'll highlight quality games is through new editorial pages on the Play store launching later this month. These pages allow our editors to hand-select games exemplifying optimal gaming experiences on Android. They allow users to explore different game styles and genres with editorial reviews on themes such as epic RPGs and top racing games.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Play now considers user engagement, not just downloads, in ranking games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home Assistants Like Amazon Echo Could Be a Boon for Assisted Living. Elliptic Labs says it can use the speakers and mics on smart home assistants to detect if youre there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When rivers caught fire and bald eagles were poisoned: why we need the Environmental Protection Agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New $10 Raspberry Pi Zero comes with Wi-Fi and Bluetooth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creepy IoT teddy bear leaks 2 million parents and kids voice messages. Publicly accessible database wasnt even protected by a password. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two noted additions:

 The first upcoming change is pretty simple, it's just a new button in the task bar that can be used to sort messages. The specifics about the available sorting options aren't available yet, but it's likely there will at least be options to sort by date and by sender name.

 The second item on the list is a bit more interesting. It looks like Inbox is going to offer to intelligently pick the "most important part of [a] message" to show in the brief line of text below the subject and sender in the email list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inbox v1.41 prepares to intelligently choose snippets from emails and allow sorting [APK Teardown] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still pretty much up in the air. If it was directly related to HP's patent, that would be an easy excuse to put out, but Sony hasn't done that. NextBit released the Robin with the fingerprint sensor and power button combo in the U.S. without problems. Mesa bringing up the U.S. carriers is still a bit vague. In the end, we still don't know much about the situation since the Sony exec danced around the question. As a result, people will continue to speculate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polymer additive could revolutionize plastics recycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The product was announced before, but now the price has been revealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingston's 2TB 'world's highest capacity USB flash drive' costs almost as much as a MacBook Pro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the video description:

**ALL-IN-ONE TILES**

1. [Quidgets](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.loveshack.edelman)

2. [Nougat Quick Settings](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=it.simonesestito.ntiles)

3. [Tiles](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rascarlo.quick.settings.tiles)

4. [Tile Extension for Nougat](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gunny.bunny.tilemedia)

5. [QuickTile]( https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.widgapp.quicktile)

6. [Custom Quick Settings](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.quinny898.app.customquicksettings)

**One-Tile-Only Apps**

1. [Ringer Modes](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cgollner.quicktiles)

2. [Quick Search Tile](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.loveshack.quicksearchbox)

3. [Explorage](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.frantzoe.explorage)

4. [Weather Quick Settings](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.florianisme.weatherquicktile)

5. [TallyTile](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=forinnovation.tallytile)

6. [Dice Quick Settings](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=kritrus.quickdice)

7. [Note Down Tile](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.chernowii.notedown) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 great quick settings tile apps for Android 7.0 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So here's the meat of the issue: based on some deal previously made relating specifically to the U.S., in order for Sony to sell phones in the country it cannot ship them with functioning fingerprint sensors.

 When pressed for specifics, Mesa acknowledged the rub with U.S. carriers in Sony's transition from selling carrier-backed phones to going entirely unlocked, eventually leading to this fingerprint situation in some way.

Gotta love our U.S. carriers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SanDisk Teams with Leading Manufacturers to Offer Consumers a Faster Mobile App Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oppos new camera lets you zoom in 5x further with no loss in quality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. LG allows for the order to be changed and it's pretty nice, especially for those that don't always prefer the stock way of doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sonys crazy projector that turns any surface into a touchscreen is going on sale this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working Samsung Galaxy S8 Leak - First Hands On Look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is also [this Google Drive link](https://drive.google.com/drive/u/0/folders/0B4PnH5TQXf06R1NwRm5vUF9vLU0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are all of the stock wallpapers from the LG G6 [Gallery] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharp vision: New glasses help the legally blind see </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dammit, why aren't you working](http://i.imgur.com/ghj6Anf.jpg)?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait till someone accidentally inserts it into a pencil sharpener  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protestors storm Samsung press conference building over Note 7 disposal issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung Galaxy S8 expected to come with AKG headphones, audio tuning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsungs new Galaxy Tab S3 comes with four speakers and a stylus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleting my post. AA doesn't deserve site visits for that dumb mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moto G5 and G5 Plus have metal designs and very affordable prices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motorola and Amazon will bake Alexa into Moto Mods and phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget DMCA takedownsRIAA wants ISPs to filter for pirated content </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because it's something you've never heard about before, please don't automatically assume it's a gimmick. Here's a recent [Forbes article](https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2017/02/24/how-the-ps4-xbox-one-and-even-the-apple-tv-could-soon-get-dolby-vision/#e1e1ed46647c) about bringing Dolby Vision to more devices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huawei Watch 2 comes in two versions, there's a Porsche Design model too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think the Internet Is Polarized? Just Look at the FCC These Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolby Laboratories and LG Electronics Announce First Smartphone to Support Dolby Vision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona Wildcats' My-King Johnson to make NCAA history as 1st openly gay football scholarship player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona Wildcats' My-King Johnson to make NCAA history as 1st openly gay football scholarship player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung's Latest Design Patents Cover Smartphones with Folding and Slide-Out Expansion Displays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I used to own a Moto Z Play and it performed as well as any other phone I've owned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the previous BlackBerry Priv, it runs Android. It'll launch running Android 7.1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The rewrite should be done soon](http://i.imgur.com/5QRu8gl.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a 3:2 aspect ratio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Searching for GK40 shows it's also the 2,800mAh battery used in the G4 Play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. Large battery, smallish display, and the SD 625 should translate into insane battery life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Colorado county is sending students to college on the $445,000 it made from legal weed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. However, on a recent CrackBerry podcast, the CEO of BlackBerry Mobile was a guest and really touted the camera. He's obviously going to speak positive about the phone, but I remember him saying that it's the best smartphone camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Syrian cinematographer has been barred from entering the United States to attend the Oscars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumor: Samsung could switch to a PowerVR GPU for the Exynos 9810 SoC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. I guess we'll find out later today, but I wonder if this is another situation like the Priv where AT T gets it first, followed by the other US carriers at some later point. Since it launched a few months after it was first released, that could be why BB never got around to listing VZW's Priv on their site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. For those that don't know, the BlackBerry you're used to hearing about is just handling the software. The hardware side of things (designing, building, marketing, etc.) is managed by BlackBerry Mobile, which is under TCL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The announcement is later today. Blackberry Mobile put the site up too early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Had a feeling the site went up too early. [Here are screenshots from the front page and the specs](http://imgur.com/a/ihwGG)

Some Specs:

* 4.5" Display: 1620 x 1080 IPS LCD (433 PPI)
* Qualcomm Snapdragon 625 Octa-Core 2.0 GHz w/ 64-bit Adreno 506 GPU
* 3505 mAh battery w/ QC 3.0
* 32GB Storage + microSD card support up to 2TB
* 3GB RAM
* 12MP auto-focus large pixel rear camera: Sony IMX 378 Sensor (same one in the Pixel)
* 8MP front camera with flash
* Android 7.1

Also: Judging by the network bands, the North American model won't support the US CDMA carriers. However, it has all the LTE bands for AT T and T-Mo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look up *LauncherPro Federico Carnales* on Google, you'll get some good info on the first page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security lapse exposed New York airport's critical servers for a year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [#NeverForget](http://i.imgur.com/VgHkJ9y.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cached webpage](http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:i6P8iTEiuywJ:df.olx.com.br/distrito-federal-e-regiao/celulares/moto-g-5-32gb-lancamento-308989052+ cd=1 hl=en ct=clnk gl=us). Someone in Brazil was selling a 32GB Moto G5, but the ad no longer exists.

[Imgur album](http://imgur.com/a/jIcIq) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How used cars became a security nightmare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Says Third-Party iPhone Screen Repairs No Longer Fully Void Your Warranty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman Pai rushes to block new privacy rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman Pai rushes to block new privacy rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISPs who dont want competition get good news from FCC chair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said they aren't working on it. It's just that most of the RCS articles written up to this point haven't been positive with regards to AT T, T-Mo, and VZW. However, it could very well be that they're quietly working behind the scenes to implement it and Sprint chose to be the main US carrier doing it publicly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can read. If you saw the first link in my reply to your comment, you'll see I linked to the GSMA page. Quit repeating the same stuff over and over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, [they're partners](http://www.gsma.com/network2020/universal-profile/), but they haven't done much yet to get behind the RCS push. The main US carrier that has been doing this is Sprint. [Here](http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20160222005526/en/Global-Operators-Google-GSMA-Align-Adoption-Rich), [here](https://9to5google.com/2017/02/01/nope-t-mobile-isnt-rolling-out-support-for-googles-rcs-offering-in-messenger/), and [here](https://thenextweb.com/apps/2017/02/24/how-google-is-trying-to-make-sms-sexy-again/#.tnw_wmKQaQ7B) you can see that AT T, T-Mo, and VZW are still not behind Google's RCS push. Being a partner for the Universal Profile is one thing, but actually working together to get widespread support for the standard is something different. Hopefully that changes soon after Google's re-branding for Android Messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad, but shouldn't surprise anyone. The quote below is pulled from [this Android Central article](http://www.androidcentral.com/what-rcs-and-why-it-important-android) back in December.

 Verizon supports RCS, but not officially in any way that the GSMA feels is compliant. That's not really surprising because this is Verizon we're talking about and they don't like to play nice with anyone until they have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android Cant Compete With iMessage. Google Is Changing That </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Math Behind Trumps Deportation Plan Makes No Sense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US general says ISIS are forcing children and disabled people into suicide cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Substratum introduces FloatUI: A Per-App Theming Solution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC lets billion-dollar ISPs hide fees and data caps, Democrat says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC votes to lift net neutrality transparency rules for smaller internet providers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile wants you to ignore last-place finish in nationwide network test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Lumia 1520**. I've never been a WP fan, but the hardware design always interested me, especially when the 1520 came out. However, I never bought it due to carrier compatibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trumps Attack on a California Railroad Should Trouble You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google to stop absorbing cost of Play Store refunds outside of 48 hours, will deduct funds from developer payouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone could just ship it to a parcel forwarding service, but I'm not sure how those types of things handle customs charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google is preparing to release a wireless 4K TV box, even as the Fiber service retrenches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the screenshots shown, and Rita stating she's using her Lebanon-based Google account, it seems that non-US users get the US prices, as long as you have a shipping address in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qualcomm Introduces Snapdragon 835 Virtual Reality Development Kit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature or Fluke] You can now purchase items on any other country's Google Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When computers learn to swear: Using machine learning for better online conversations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung Wins Two Design Patents for Distinctly Different Galaxy Styled Smartphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Google features a snippet from a "leading Internet Newspaper in Nigeria" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  4G LTE Capable 

Great to see that confirmed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gmail v7.2 Prepares to Add Support for S/MIME Enhanced Encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Play Store UI experiment appears, this time with separated store categories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could never do one phone per year. Last year alone I went through 11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. This deal is definitely better if you're already a T-Mo customer, or were looking to become one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Balls of Honor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huawei is releasing a 360-degree camera for its smartphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YMMV. I've seen some people say that the store price matched the online price, but that isn't always the case. Usually these deals are only online and a store doesn't have to match it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instagram Update: Share Up to 10 Photos and Videos in One Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're post-paid, you need to sign into your My Tmobile and you will get the option for device payment or one-time full charge of $360 (no $20 sim needed if you're an existing customer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smartphones with on-screen fingerprint scanning to debut this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG G6 Square </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [LG V20](https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phone/lg-v20)

[Galaxy S7 Edge](https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phone/samsung-galaxy-s7-edge?color=Bluecoral)

[Galaxy S7](https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phone/samsung-galaxy-s7?color=Goldplatinum)

**Bonus deal for V20 buyers**: LG has a promotion where you can get a free MiniBeam Projector by mail for purchasing the T-Mo V20. [Click here](http://www.lg.com/us/promotions/t-mobile). The purchase must be made by today (Feb. 22) to get this projector offer.

For current post-paid T-Mo customers looking to get either of these phones: You need to sign into your My Tmobile and you will get the option for device payment or one-time full charge of $360 (no $20 sim needed if you're an existing customer). For users who can't upgrade online or are still on JOD, call the 1800-Tmobile number to place your order. They will see the $360 price, but they will charge you a $20 upgrade fee (which they cannot remove).

For non T-Mo users, there doesn't seem to be a way to order the phone without a plan. You can cancel your plan afterwards and just pay off the device balance. If you want to avoid a credit check, you'll have to call T-Mobile. Lastly, if you're interested in using the phone on another carrier, T-Mo requires the line to be active for 40 days before you can unlock it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile device deals: Galaxy S7, Galaxy S7 Edge, or LG V20 on sale for $360 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some keypoints:

* The Snapdragon X20 LTE modem will use Samsungs latest 10nm LPE process and offer a few key enhancements over the X16 LTE modem integrated into the Snapdragon 835 SoC
* The X20 allows network operators to deploy gigabit LTE service with only 10MHz of licensed spectrum. This is vitally important in many crowded markets where 20MHz blocks are rare
* Exclusive DSDV feature: With DSDV the second SIM is no longer limited to 2G or 3G voice duties, because voice can be carried over LTE. It also allows the user to select either SIM for LTE data service.
* Like previous Qualcomm LTE modems, the Snapdragon X20 will be offered as a stand-alone product initially, but will likely be integrated into a high-end Snapdragon SoC next year.

it also boasts a peak theoretical bandwith of 1.2 Gbps DL, but I doubt any of us will be seeing that anytime soon.

Towards the end, there's also [this info pertaining to Snapdragon 835 antenna tech](http://i.imgur.com/bblSLf6.jpg). The QAT35xx parts can be used alongside the 835 and those work together to optimize signal quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qualcomm Announces Snapdragon X20 LTE Modem   New RF Front-End Modules For Mobile Devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if I'd use it, but the DeX dock sure sounds interesting. I'm sure some won't be fond of seeing touchwiz on a much larger monitor lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alleged Tab S3 system dump and photos confirm major Galaxy S8 features, including on-screen buttons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Multilingual Milestone: SwiftKey reaches support for 150 languages! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. In addition to sammobile deleting the article, it looks like the source of the info deleted the tweet. 

[The wayback machine has it saved](https://web.archive.org/web/20170217132557/https://www.sammobile.com/2017/02/17/galaxy-s8-and-galaxy-s8-plus-purported-color-options-and-pricing-revealed/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qualcomm First to Announce Support for Android Things OS on 4G LTE Processors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kernel source for Nougat on the Moto Z Play now available </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever a new phone comes out that catches my eye, as long as it's VZW compatible. To offset the cost, I usually sell my previous phone. I'm addicted to phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to get that one. My current red case is [this one by Evutec](http://imgur.com/a/PfbLt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can no longer replace the file. The option now is to continue downloading or cancel the download, if Chrome detects you previously downloaded the file. If you choose to download it again, it just adds a number to the end of the file name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're referring to the new, updated second part of the article, right? The first part is from back in 2015. I honestly haven't paid enough attention to when exactly I first saw it in Chrome. Either way, for stuff like this, I think AP should just create a new article, instead of bringing back older ones to update.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update: New behavior] Chrome Beta Now Asks If You Want To Replace Downloads Rather Than Clutter Your Device With Dupes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Black and red would make for a clean combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a rather interesting section on page 6 of the [manual](http://downloadcenter.samsung.com/content/UM/201702/20170216103134580/SM-T825_UM_EU_Nougat_Eng_D07_170209.pdf). Wireless charging is briefly mentioned. [Here's a screenshot of it](http://i.imgur.com/2PY4UCm.png). So wireless charging could be there, but just for certain models. However, it could also be Samsung just copying and pasting from smartphone manuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to stop by Verizon. Since the V10 uses a nano sim, you can use the one you already have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rumor] Apple Said to Debut 128GB iPhone SE and Red iPhone 7 and 7 Plus at March Event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Said to Debut New iPad Pro Lineup, 128GB iPhone SE, and Red iPhone 7 and 7 Plus at March Event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked Galaxy Tab S3 images hint at metal and glass build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those that don't know, the unlocked US model is compatible with both GSM and CDMA carriers. I've had no issues with mine on Verizon. Both the Silver   Titan colors are discounted to $499.99. 

Edit: Just noticed the title is off by 99 cents :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEAL: LG V20 (US996) Unlocked US Model on sale today for $499 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to a speculation by industry insiders, there could be two variants of the Exynos 9810 chipset: Exynos 9810V and Exynos 9810M. The Exynos 9810V could feature an eighteen-core Mali-G71 GPU while the Exynos 9810M could feature a 20-core Mali-G71 GPU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsungs next smartphone chipset could be named Exynos 9810 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AP for some reason cropped the front shot differently and didn't link to the original source. [Here's the full shot of the front](https://twitter.com/mmddj_china/status/833325110584963072), along with the other image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like those of us that regularly check for software OTAs within Settings. It's pointless to check regularly, but my OCD gets the better of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
