<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1922</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 16:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Random chance is not a thing or being. It didn't give you life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have proof that that tv show's pranks are all fake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 21:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are enjoying life. Who do you think made this world,  gave you life and the potential to do many things you desire?

Many people who are considered to be suffering believe in God themselves, and/or their suffering may only be temporary. And trials/tribulations often brings people closer to God anyway.  That's why i'm asking about how YOU specifically feel about yourself and what you believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you believe you are being tortured in this world? Are your depressed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If God hates you, why did He create you in the first place, and give you food, water, shelter, a computer and all sorts of things to enjoy in this world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you think that? We have so much sustenance, health, wealth in life including our very existence that none of us deserved to have. I would question why were we even given existence in this world in the first place and why we have so much potential to do good or evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for religion and spirituality.  There is a reason why we exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 05:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jonathan Brown description of Salafism: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PcxVXqHz-v0

You may want to check the video just posted a few topics ago: https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/3c95aj/good_watch_for_newcomers_to_the_subject_of/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 05:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a post just yesterday about ISIS and another Syrian army executing each other's fighters. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/3c5jnk/jihad_vs_jihad_another_syrian_muslim_army/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 20:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a controversial belief. A controversial belief of our time would be believing that Men are superior to Women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know very little about what is going on in Syria. There are many Muslim military groups there right now and plenty of confusion.  One of the videos posts "confessions" from ISIS fighters who claim they did not fight against the Syrian army while with ISIS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jihad vs Jihad: Another Syrian Muslim army captures and executes 18 ISIS fighters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 02:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Article](http://www.abc.net.au/news/2015-07-01/video-shows-syrian-rebel-group-executing-18-islamic-state-fight/6588158)

[Videos (NSFW)](http://leaksource.info/2015/07/01/jihad-vs-jihad-islamic-state-syrian-rebel-group-army-of-islam-release-videos-executing-each-others-fighters/)

The group referring to itself as "Army of Islam" is battling ISIS in Syria and has turned the tables on its enemies by capturing and slaughtering 18 IS soldiers on camera. Dressed in orange jumpsuits  attire usually worn by Islamic States victims  Army of Islam (Jaysh al-Islam) soldiers lead the shackled jihadis to their deaths. Islamic States captured soldiers are forced to kneel as a commander announces: Allah did not make a disease without appointing a remedy to it. The jihadis  dressed entirely in black  are then given something to drink before each of their faces are clearly shown in the 19 minute-long video. They are then shot in the back of the head at point blank range with shotguns.

"The most serious calamity for our jihad today is a group of people who grow at a time of division among Muslims. This group claimed to be the mother state and made Takfir [accused of apostasy] on other Muslims, shed their blood and looted their properties and dignities. They worsened the ordeal of Muslims by corrupting their religion and livelihood and killing the jihadi leaders who did their best to help our stricken nation. They wreaked havoc on our people in liberated areas and cut the supply route of jihadis. They left Tehran intact and instead they attacked our mosques. This is the penalty for what they have committed. We also call on their fellows to repent." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I didn't think he was referring to Sabians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What source says Pagan Arabs used to fast for the month of Ramadan?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this attack was of a "terrorist nature" but the other shooting a few days wasn't... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1400 years ago in Arabia, there were wild dogs that are nothing like the domesticated dogs we have here in North America/Europe today. So they weren't very fond of keeping dogs as pets in that time.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Arabia 1400 years ago, there were wild dogs that are nothing like the domesticated dogs here in North America/Europe today. So they weren't very fond of keeping dogs as pets in the past . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are free to believe in your wild theories. As for me, i'll stick with the facts. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, this conversation is getting stupid and i'm not going to even bother asking what you mean by "Islamism" or are referring to by islamists.

Like i said, any group fighting will want their own government or rule in the land. And you are assuming that these Muslims fighting will automatically be ISIS-like and oppressive towards others  and become worse than Assad. Not every Islamic government/ruler-ship/state has to be like ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wrong, their purpose is to get rid of the Alawite

Yes, that's what i meant by "tyranny". Were you in support of Bashar al-Assad's oppressive regime? Or are you going to ignore the crimes that he committed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 17:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, so when America fights and then helps establishing their own type of government/rule in the land that is favorable to their interests, that's not the same at all...

  for the purpose of creating the rule of islam, or an islamic government. 

I'm pretty sure their their initial purpose has to do with tyranny and ISIS being in the land so they would be countering that. So what if these Muslims also want their own type of rule in the land? That's to be expected by every group fighting in the area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be very difficult for someone born in an Ahmadi family to find out that his religion is wrong and then explain this to his family. We should try to be more understanding and patient with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on leaving Ahmadiyya to become a muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  militant islam.

Right, because they are Muslims who are fighting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shahid Kamal leaves Ahmadiyya group and becomes a Muslim. Here are some of his videos: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ahmadiyya Cult Exposed On Live Islamic TV](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9QFFsHGXcUI)

[Shahid Kamal Became Muslim from Ahmadi Qadiyani Mirzai - He Narrates his Reason of Conversion](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eVLn3Qc9VrY)

[Ahmadiyya  Exposed](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E-yRFudnT9A)

[Leaving Ahmadiyya For Islam - Rasheed Sarpong](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pW8hoW0-fMY)

[Ex-Qadiani Ahmadiyya Member Exposes The Cult](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Vqb5ZP3g3U index=10 list=PL648B35FFACE7EA0D)

[His website](http://thecult.info/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get this... What are your views? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 16:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are different people and not part of isis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 06:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's even a bigger stretch than before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Attorney Converts to Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 03:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to Islam (and more specifically 79:30) the earth is like an egg, which points to its geospherical shape.

I think that would be stretching it: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5D4ChAnqkxU

The Quran claiming the Earth to be flat is also a stretch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 23:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People complained that not enough Muslims are fighting ISIS, so well... here you go.  Now there are more Muslims fighting against ISIS.  Of course since these Muslims are fighting and they like Islam, they are automatically labeled as extremists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 03:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, what a confession. Someone doesn't like to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 06:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proof? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 05:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Content creators on YouTube rarely make that much money on ad revenue on one video. And one video uploaded on a Facebook page usually gets a much smaller number of views.  A crude estimate would be $10 for 7,000 views. So if a video uploaded to Facebook gets millions of views, then yes, that would appear to be worse. But then again, it's not just one person pirating a movie/song; it's thousands of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically it's okay to pirate off of someone as long as they are rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to interesting to see which side redditors will take on this issue. *"Nothing wrong with pirating movies or songs but in this case..."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 19:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were some comments like that, but they got downvoted pretty quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Attorney Converts to Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 19:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Converted to Islam | Reverted Queen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 03:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears (after reading your first topic) that you are overly attached to this girl to the point of worshiping her, and she probably recognizes this. Anytime you attach yourself to anything worldly like this, you are bound to be hurt sooner or later. 

*Through my attachments, I was dependent on my relationships to fulfill my needs. I allowed those relationships to define my happiness or my sadness, my fulfillment or my emptiness, my security, and even my self-worth. And so, like the vase placed where it will inevitably fall, through those dependencies I set myself up for disappointment. I set myself up to be broken.*

It's still possible that you could end up marrying this girl or end up with another girl, but you really need to work on yourself first before even thinking about her.  You accepted Islam, that's a start. You need to keep working on self-development and improving yourself first. Understand that the type of satisfaction you are seeking can only be momentarily  satiated with such a relationship. Think more about how a long term relationship would be with such a girl look like.

*We must also realize that nothing happens without a purpose. Nothing. Not even broken hearts. Not even pain. That broken heart and that pain are lessons and signs for us. They are warnings that something is wrong. They are warnings that we need to make a change. Just like the pain of being burned is what warns us to remove our hand from the fire, emotional pain warns us that we need to make an internal change. That we need to detach. Pain is a form of forced detachment.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 20:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only this but he pluralized the concept of dajjal and Messiah, saying that there are multiple dajjals and multiple messiashs. And he considered the Christian preachers of his time to be dajjals and that Jesus (pbuh) was buried in India. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 20:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should get a thorough understanding of mainstream Islam first and then work your way down to divisions and sects when you have full conviction of Islam being correct.  Ahmadiyyism shares a lot of same beliefs with mainstream Muslims but they add another prophet who interprets the Quran and hadith very differently. I have personally studied their religion and found many many problems with it that contradict mainstream Islam. I made one of my topics [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/1vltgo/some_questions_for_the_ahmadiyya_community/) questioning their prophet and was not able to get adequate responses from the ahmadi community.  I also had some of my topics deleted from their sub and my questions ignored.  I highly recommend watching [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E-yRFudnT9A) of a brother leaving the ahmadi group first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  all prophets die, 

 none are immortal 

 we need to eat food

I thought i made it clear before that i don't disagree with any of these statements. We believe Jesus (pbuh) ascended. But we aren't sure exactly what kind of state this is or what living in this state is like or whether or not he needs food in this particular state.  

If you think that this is not possible for Allah to do, just think about the **7 sleepers of the cave: Allah kept them alive for 300 years without having to eat food**.  

There is no explicit mention of Jesus's death.  explicit means: *stated clearly and in detail, leaving no room for confusion or doubt.*   We wouldn't be having this argument and you wouldn't have to explain what some ayat imply if there really was an explicit mention of his death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there an explicit statement needed for every prophet to say they have died for it to be proven? So do you have explicit Quranic statements for, say, Adam, Moses, Abraham, Isaac, Ismael....

The general rule is that people die within their lifespan. Jesus (pbuh) is an exception to this, which we only believe because prophet Muhammad (pbuh) told us about it and what he has to do against dajjal. 

 It's just taken as a given that someone who lived more than 200 years ago, let alone 2,000, is dead and it goes without saying.

Like i said, we don't know what kind of state he is in or how he is living in such a state.   Or are you having trouble believing how such a thing is possible for Allah? 


 In fact the burden on proof is on the Sunnis to show a single verse of the Quran which states he is still alive. 

Now you are confusing Ahmadi sources of reference for our sources of references. I  told you that we  have proof that Jesus (pbuh) is alive in our sources. Ahmadi's don't accept narrations which is funny because Mirza Ghulam Ahmad tried to make sense of several hadith in his writings but conveniently left the ones which contradicted his teachings. 



 I can show you many more which in my view prove he is dead 

Yes, you have shown me ayat which **you interpreted** somehow to mean that he died. But i have to yet to see one explicit ayah which makes such a claim.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  prophets are not immortal

True.

 all prophets die

True.

 prophets need to eat food 

Also true. Jesus (pbuh) needed food when he was on Earth and will need food again when he returns to Earth. The Quran doesn't mention what kind of state Jesus (pbuh) is right now, or if he still eats food in his current state.   Note that the 7 sleepers of the cave survived without food for 300 years so it's very possible that Jesus (pbuh) doesn't need food in his current state.

There is no explicit statement in the Quran that Jesus (pbuh) died. That is just your misinterpretation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 17:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  On Jesus - if the Quran pretty much explicitly states Jesus has passed away (as I believe the verses I quoted above demonstrate) then you will take a hadith over that?

Don't be dishonest with yourself, that's not an explicit statement at all. The ayah you brought up says that 'they ate food' which is true.    It wouldn't make sense to say that 'they are eating food', because Mary had already passed away and Jesus (pbuh) wasn't even on the surface of the Earth when the Quran was revealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we give this argument a rest. There are numerous hadiths which talk explicitly about the son of Mary (pbuh) returning to earth, which Ahmadi's reject.  Mirza Ghulam Ahmad was way off; he thought the Christian preachers and Europeon philosophers of his time were the dajjal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 16:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have also looked into Ahmadi's beliefs and found them to be very problematic. There are several ahmadi beliefs that they don't want you to know right away. For example, did you know that even Mirza Ghulam Ahmad said that any Muslim who rejects him is a disbeliever?   I highly recommend you watch this video of a brother with a similar journey as yourself: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E-yRFudnT9A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there is indeed some discrimination and unfair treatment to minorities that travel there to earn money.

So it's like every other country?  Seriously, every country has problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go through the seerah you will see that the sahaba struggled immensely fighting on the battlefield. Traveling for days, little food, little armor, few weapons, no medicine and being outnumbered by enemies; it was never an easy task. It makes sense that 'Jihad' is the term that can be used for fighting.

Is it just me or does anyone else get nearly the opposite feeling when seeing some clips of Muslim fighters today? It's like they want to end their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 03:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took a few courses, highly recommend it. 

Great teachers, students and the price is definitely worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every kid is different. Some kids will continuously act rebellious if they know that all you can do is talk to them or send them to their room. Sometimes physical discipline is necessary, obviously very light discipline.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see Muslims hating on Jews. I see some who hate Zionism and Israel however and that's about it. I also don't see any antisemitism on this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 21:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They have to get rid of it anyway to make room for fresh stuff and you always see kids and poor people grabbing free stale donuts and rolls.

That's a good idea. Why can't other stores do the same with unsold  or nearly expired food?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 21:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can he win when he is speaking out against banks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you need that much money for this app? Most of the work should just be about pinpointing different locations on a map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's also important how you address the problem, saying that "Arabs are racist" or "how come Arabs do this" can be seen as a racist generalization. It's easy for someone to address the problem within their own community, but when you're an outsider, you have to be careful and respectful when pointing out a problem of another group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As-salamu alaykum

 The reason I'm saying this is because some verses in the Quran can be taken out of context by Islamophobes and terrorists.

But you can do this with any book. All the verses Islamophobes use, you can debunk most of them right away just by reading the before and after verses. It's true though that the Quran doesn't mention all of the context; if it did, it would be a much longer book.  

The Quran is a brief speech in response to it's historical context (seerah) and at the same time it's a general guide for humanity. The Quran rarely mentions times, dates, places and even names so it's a general book that every community can relate to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably had to do with how you said it. I just checked some of your old posts on reddit, some of which can be seen as a bad generalization of a race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was another app which did something similar: 
http://ahliapp.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Message Yasir Qadhi about the part of his speech that bothered you, maybe he will readdress the issue better.  And it'll be a nice change from the death threats he has been receiving.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [News clip](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=koAsNXXeUk4)

[MONSTER Energy drinks are the work of SATAN](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bntfUA6TmLs)

[Previous interruption](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AYvukxUGgmg)

[She takes the mic in this one](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t4-C0aZ3V1Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monster energy drink lady strikes again: interrupting Adhan during Muslim day at Oklahoma state Capitol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yasir Qadhi on ISIS](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lezIO8yg2r4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Terminator movie series is a prequel to The Matrix movie series where machines have successfully taken over humanity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people in Saudi Arabia that do bad things. Let's not be racist and start generalizing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 18:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you found out that you've been lied to from your Christian upbringing doesn't make Islam wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 18:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video isn't arguing against evolution though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 04:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He plays a contemptible character. I think the show would prefer it if he lost because that would please the audience more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to learn about the religion i would suggest reading the Quran and a biography of Muhammad (pbuh).  (Links in the sidebar) If you want to know what the  Muslim world is like and what they believe, check out *Who Speaks For Islam?: What a Billion Muslims Really Think* by John Esposito. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Radio Host Chris Krok Calls U.S. and European Muslims Cockroaches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 18:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 16:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't base your judgement on a Muslim based on what some news article says about him.  The media can easily [manipulate](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X1puKmV_qOc) someone's character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this video was posted at r/videos](http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/2tagaj/eyeopening_video_on_how_the_media_only_shows_you/) 

In these type of clips shown on the news, the public normally gets to see only the edited final version of "those crazy Muslims".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to enrage a Muslim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 19:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 16:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you can say it, but it doesn't make sense. It doesn't make sense to believe someone is a messenger of God and at the same time failed to be a messenger of God.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 16:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That verse is saying that the Quran is protected and pure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 00:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X8CDvhM3arg), the satanic verses incident is based off a weak source that goes against stronger sources. Strange how some Muslims are willing to accept that incident as a fact but doubt the Quran's authenticity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's intellectual criticism.  There are Atheists who debate with Muslims all the time using the same type of rhetoric. Nothing wrong with this.  I'm speaking about insults which have no benefit except to incite hatred like drawing an offensive picture of a prophet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We know that the Koran has questionable content, retells and reinterprets Judeo-Christian stories, and has been altered or embellished by several scribes in different instances. Why can't we admit that we know this?

You can't make this statement **as a Muslim**. It doesn't make sense for you to believe that the Quran was altered **as a Muslim**. You can however question it all you want **as a non-Muslim** and Muslims will debate with you about it academically. 

 If we can't question, examine, or pick apart our holy book, how can we call ourselves scholars?

Unlike other religions, Muslim scholars don't debate whether or not the  Quran is accurate or authentic; it's part of the faith. Muslim scholars will however discuss and examine the interpretation of the ayat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 22:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you say you're a Muslim. If you believe the Quran is God's words, then you cannot say that the Quran is wrong or question whether it is really God's words; that would make your testimony of Islam a lie.  There are of course things you can question. For example if God says to give charity, then you can question the amount of money to give or what groups should receive it. But it doesn't make sense for you to deny or question God's command of giving charity as a Muslim.  

And of course non-Muslims are allowed to criticize Islam. We do it on this sub all the time and we have Muslim groups who discuss with non-Muslims, answer their questions and debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 21:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference between intellectual criticism to refute an idea or belief and insults/mockery which is used often to incite hate upon a person or group. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ym3Znb0wb7s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Actually, free speech is kind of important in that whole "western liberal civilization" concept.

Well apparently, a good portion of France's population don't seem to look at it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, that's your opinion.  I'm just pointing out that there are people who will disagree with that opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. I don't think people are aware of how bad it's getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This topic is to raise awareness. I think you're trying to hard to assume what my attention is for making this topic. I'm not looking for an apology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alternate news source on Moroccan man killed in France](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/moroccan-man-in-france-killed-at-home-in-front-of-wife-by-intruder-shouting-about-islam-9985072.html)

[Infograph of 50 Anti-Muslim incidents all over France in one week.](http://tellmamauk.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/antimuslim-attacks-charlie-hebdo-II-final-resize.jpg)  Most of the incidents are regarding vandalism, hate speech and discrimination, while some of them are more serious and more hostility is expected to come.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French-Moroccan Man Victim Of Retaliation Murder As Backlash Sweeps Europe. Surge of anti-Muslim incidents continues since Charlie Hebdo massacre last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free speech without any limitations is not some kind of absolute rule that all of humanity is obligated to accept. People can disagree with it.  

I think a lot of people would also disprove of racist, sexist, homophobic and antisemitic cartoons/jokes coming from a magazine publishing company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This topic is highlighting the rise of Anti-Muslim attacks. It's not to seek an apology from France's population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted. The link you gave is something that happened 2 years ago. The infograph above gives details of each incident below it  and i gave another link which can explain further of each event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has nothing to do with the shooting. Believe it or not, many people don't like images intended to insult or mock a specific group of people. There are those who also disprove of racist, sexist, homophobic and antisemitic cartoons/jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is asking France to apologize for these crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not being called a pedophile is not really much of an accomplishment...

Helped Lady carry groceries.  Did not get called a rapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is islamophobic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the incidents are regarding vandalism, hate speech and discrimination, while some of them are more serious.  Thanks to [tellmamauk.org](http://tellmamauk.org/) for the picture.  You can also visit http://frise.islamophobie.net/ for more information on the incidents (translate the page to English). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 50 Anti-Muslim incidents all over France in one week. More hostility expected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 04:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did i say it was equivalent?  

You should try reading the article before commenting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 20:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Kuffar" means disbeliever.   It can be offensive if you find disbelieving in Islam to be offensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More than 21 shooting incidents nears mosques in France in the last few days.](http://www.france24.com/en/20150112-more-50-anti-muslim-incidents-french-attacks-group/?aef_campaign_date=2015-01-12 aef_campaign_ref=partage_aef ns_campaign=reseaux_sociaux ns_linkname=editorial ns_mchannel=social ns_source=twitter) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 19:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  Private employers have the right to penalize those who make remarks that are racist, sexist, homophobic, antisemitic, anti-Islamic, etc. Countries also have the right to limit the type of hate speech or insults that can be said in public. People need to stop acting as if complete freedom of speech is a God-given right or an absolute standard that all of humanity needs to accept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 22:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  your speech creates an unhealthy working environment, private employers have the right not to let you work for them anymore. This isn't oppressive. This is logical business practice.

EXACTLY. Private employers, like those in a magazine publishing company, have the right to penalize those who make racist, sexist, homophobic, antisemitic or anti-Islam remarks. Similarly, countries also have the right to decide whether or not to penalize those who publicly make these remarks hence passing laws such as Gayssot law.

You can't seem to grasp the fact that other countries might disagree with you regarding the limits to freedom of speech and it is their right to have their own laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You don't get to tell other people what they can and cannot say. Period.

Actually most countries have limitations on what you can and cannot say. [Even America has limits to freedom of expression.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_free_speech_exceptions)  You can even lose your job quite easily for saying something sexist, racist, homophobic, antisemitic, etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 18:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insulting and mocking someone's faith is the opposite of tolerance... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 18:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Here in the US we have a constitutional right to free speech and your belief is completely contrary to that right.

I live in America and i respect the rules here.  If you go to a country, you should abide by their rules. 

If you move to Turkey and they have certain restrictions on free speech, then you should respect their rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 18:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is the problem, folks. This right here. People like /u/REDPILL  simply do not value the freedom of speech. 

You do realize that France has similar laws towards Jews right? Research the The Gayssot Law. IN fact, a satirist in the exact same newspaper was fired and put on trial for an anti-Semitic article that he had written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 18:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you know, Islamic states are more restrictive regarding freedom of expression. Different Islamic states throughout history have had different rules and laws towards how to deal with people who publicly mock Islam. There are certain fatwas that call for the death penalty for such cases, but these fatwas aren't absolute. 

I can't say that i understand the fatwa op is talking about or why the author of that fatwa calls for death in retaliation for such an offense, but i personally do believe that there should be restrictions regarding mockery towards religions (not including intellectual criticism of a religion).  I understand that you will disagree, but that is what i believe. 

edit: And before you start critisizing me for wanting limitations on Freedom of speech, please do realize that France ALREADY has these restrictions towards Judaism. In fact, a satirist in the exact same newspaper was fired, and then put on trial for an anti-Semitic article that he had written. [proof](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/europe/france/4351672/French-cartoonist-Sine-on-trial-on-charges-of-anti-Semitism-over-Sarkozy-jibe.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 17:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are you being serious when you defend the killing of the innocent by saying "it's only valid in an Islamic state" or are you just pulling my leg?

Did you ignore what i said? I am NOT defending the killing of the innocent.  I am saying that the article op linked to does not justify this attack. OP's claims that the link instructs the killers to what they did is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 17:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from r/islam. It's a very BIG stretch. **No one on /r/islam said that the shootings were a good thing.**  You will find several condemnations on that sub.  The link that op is referring to is relying on historical fatwas occurring **within an Islamic state**.  Last time i checked, France is not an Islamic state so his proof that Muslims support the killing is invalid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that Kevin O'Leary's character on Shark Tank is one that worships money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
