<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6752</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By installing the Shazam app? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually eager to charge it. I'm running a battery test. Got them on Tuesday at 10:37AM (EST)it was at 100% and 72hrs later the little shit is still alive. I never disconnected it from my phone or Watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/ofcoursethatsathing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature] Not sure which Beta introduced this, but 10.3 now tells you when your W1 headphones are connected to your Apple Watch or not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to resign the app via Cydia Impactor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filter Notifications in what way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still can't see it. 

Can you please put more big red arrows around it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  not the lesbian militia.

I will be stealing this. Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, for those worried, log will still kill princess.

In what scenario?

1-) Killing a barrel and hitting the princess all in one log?

2-) Killing a princess that's standing right in front of the king </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't so hard to check. We are talking about the balance changes coming 3/13. What video will that be? 

The video for the balance changes coming on 7/6/2089? 

Fucking people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/oXKK3BA.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't, but OP is doing an unofficial one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because it is used in most decks, it needs to be nerfed? Is like saying the Fireball needs a nerf because it is found in most decks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New LG 5K UltraFine Display models work properly near wireless access points including routers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He watermarked the art, but at the bottom so is easily "crop-able" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But as a tech support or just a general support?

I've had good experiences with them, but I can't say anything about the tech support they have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you got the wrong Acapella buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that makes sense. I got it confused so that's why I asked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you mean that the phone isn't letting you quick reply to messages from the screen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By what you say, my guess is that you aren't a developer.

Everyone can use a graphing calc, is easy to use, but realistically speaking, how many people that use the stock calculator need a graphic function? 

As a dev, I won't waste my time developing something and mantaining it if 99% of my users won't use it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Tops 'Tech Support Showdown' List for Third Consecutive Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... well played. 2 years waiting for this moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But we can't see the banner with Narwhal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video is down :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Prime example that peaceful protests work and that these types of protests do have power to influence.

I wonder who will be next... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that was for me. 

I mean, she reads the headphone's name, so mines are is to my_name's Beats Solo ^3.

If I drop the Erick on settings she only says Beats Solo ^3

Edit: See how she says that my headphones are now named Reddit: http://i.imgur.com/WXpbPpk.png  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know, I mean that you wrote np.www.reddit.com instead of www.np.reddit.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   by this post

You might want to move the "np" after the www. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't... Isn't that what I said? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airmail, Instagram (for post notifications, hit or miss though),   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works with the Apple Watch and Solo 3 too: http://i.imgur.com/W0voB5V.png  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked with the 6 and it works. Check your settings. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since iOS 10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in 2014, U2 decided to give all iTunes members a free copy of their album. 

So they had the glorious idea of telling Apple to send the album to every member and if you had some settings on, the album will be downloaded on the device automatically. 

At the end, [U2 apologized](http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/15/tech/web/u2-bono-free-itunes/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By any chance, you took a screenshot of the headphones at the lower price? They are back at $219 now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were downvoted because you were wrong. Not because we are sensitive. 

Now, I feel like you are the sensitive one here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sensitive in what way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does Nudekeys have to do with this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. Is that B7 is not for the iPhone 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is not. Is a red case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Remember the U2 iTunes album.

Oh God... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard of US Customs regulations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, that didn't take long. 

90%+ still good tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What. The. Fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL:DR:

* Allow users to import video and images into Sharefactory from an USB

* Clone Clip feature. This addition allows you to easily duplicate any clip being used in your project and retain all of the existing filters, stickers, text as well as the clip duration. 

*  2.50 update allows you to select up to 16 video clips or screenshots from your Capture Gallery and launch directly into Sharefactory for editing.


Other features in this update include:

* Added over 30 textures you can use to personalize your text as well as the ability to freely scale your text

* New Infomercial Sharefactory Theme

*New Photo Mode collages with support for up to 16 images

* New Photo Mode Templates
* New stickers

* Contextual Help has now been added throughout Sharefactory

*Updates to the UI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharefactory Update 2.50: New Features Detailed, Out Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you saying it like that Stewie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means your friend is connected to their PSN and they have the Playstation app open on their phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To help satiate your thirst for carnage and gear up for Tuesday, Warstock is slashing the SecuroServ prices on Special Vehicles. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my Voltic 2 weeks ago too. I should have waited :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had mine do that. Clean it and it will be good to go. The dust is covering the ventilation windows of the system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted a transcript: https://www.reddit.com/r/gtaonline/comments/5yfiub/cunning_stunts_special_vehicle_circuit_coming_to/depjrvc/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cunning Stunts: Special Vehicle Circuit Coming March 14 - Rockstar Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those at work/school:
Next week, a different breed of high-flying vehicular competition hits GTA Online with 20 new Stunt Races custom built for the Rocket Voltic, Ruiner 2000   Blazer Aqua in Cunning Stunts: Special Vehicle Circuit. Designed with each of these vehicles' unique characteristics and abilities in mind, this collection of Stunt Races comes to GTA Online on Tuesday, March 14. Also on Tuesday, Legendary Motorsport adds the classically-styled Progen GP1 to its formidable roster of supercars.

And to gear up for next week's Special Vehicle Races, we've also got a flight of new GTA Online bonuses kicking in this weekend and running through Monday, March 13th (on top of ongoing specials including Double GTA$   RP Stunt Races). Aspiring kingpins can claim their own high-rise for 25% off Executive Offices and Office Garages before taking advantage of CEO bonuses all weekend long. To help satiate your thirst for carnage and gear up for Tuesday, Warstock is slashing the SecuroServ prices on Special Vehicles. Special Vehicle Missions will also dish out Double GTA$   RP throughout the weekend, allowing you to earn big while getting acclimated with the Special Vehicle of your choosing. Bodyguards and Associates are also getting a Double GTA$ salary bump this weekend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those at work/school:

Next week, a different breed of high-flying vehicular competition hits GTA Online with 20 new Stunt Races custom built for the Rocket Voltic, Ruiner 2000   Blazer Aqua in Cunning Stunts: Special Vehicle Circuit. Designed with each of these vehicles' unique characteristics and abilities in mind, this collection of Stunt Races comes to GTA Online on Tuesday, March 14. Also on Tuesday, Legendary Motorsport adds the classically-styled Progen GP1 to its formidable roster of supercars. 

And to gear up for next week's Special Vehicle Races, we've also got a flight of new GTA Online bonuses kicking in this weekend and running through Monday, March 13th (on top of ongoing specials including Double GTA$   RP Stunt Races). Aspiring kingpins can claim their own high-rise for 25% off Executive Offices and Office Garages before taking advantage of CEO bonuses all weekend long. To help satiate your thirst for carnage and gear up for Tuesday, Warstock is slashing the SecuroServ prices on Special Vehicles. Special Vehicle Missions will also dish out Double GTA$   RP throughout the weekend, allowing you to earn big while getting acclimated with the Special Vehicle of your choosing. Bodyguards and Associates are also getting a Double GTA$ salary bump this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cunning Stunts: Special Vehicle circuit coming to GTAO on March 14th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cunning Stunts Special Vehicles circuit coming on March 14th! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD are at the Jewish children's museum at 792 eastern parkway in Brooklyn investigating a called in bomb threat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone fill me in on what's happening? I'm out of the loop here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See this: https://support.us.playstation.com/scea_searchresults?lang=en_US selStr=ws-37397-9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your IP was blocked. You live in a dorm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The PS Messages app got updated on iOS and Android </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changelog: 

- You can now reply to messages directly from notifications. (Android only. This isn't on the iOS changelog)

- You can now respond with a quick reply when you receive a party invitation.

- A mobile icon is now displayed to indicate Friends who use PlayStation App or PlayStation Messages but are not currently online.

- Cover images are now displayed on player detail screens.

- You can now rotate the images you attach.

- You can now check the status of PlayStation Network services by going to [Settings]  [View Status of PSN Services].

- You can now check whether the app has been updated to the latest version by going to [Settings] - [About PS Messages] (This is only present on iOS per changelogs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might need an [August doorknob](http://august.com/products/august-smart-lock/) + a camera compatible with Homekit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Store whole games and play from them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply it is to compare build size across all devices. If you don't care, scroll past them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ColorWare](http://www.colorware.com/p-709-dualshock-4-2016.aspx)

They have a good warranry (and you can buy extra warranty too), good prices and top-notch work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you are into competitive and online games, but if you ever need a solo time, get Infamous Second Son. The game is fun to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sorry :( Required trophy count is 3800 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another alternative (if you want) to the one posted is the one I am in. FollowTheLight. We are constantly trying to push forward and we have never missed a 10/10 CC. We are in the Top 200 of the US, and we kick the 50th person in the clan to open space for new people to join. 

The chat is pretty chill, you say what you want to say, the way you want to. We don't eat, we aren't kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By now the Earth should be empty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Combat MG for every use. AP for cars, Heavy Sniper for Sniping, Homing Launcher for Rocket needs, sticky bombs for surprise attacks.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut?

  "Bluetooth connection issues in a watch OS beta led to bricked devices that had to be repaired at an Apple Store"

These watches weren't repaired. You know how you plug in your iPhone and restore the iOS? Same thing Apple does with the watch. Reason they tell you to send it to them is because the special cable is not available for sale. 

 You let folks with devices that they can afford to lose data from try betas first before you rush in and get all sad when your phone can't hold signal anymore or the mic stops working.

But these folks asked for a beta program to ensure their apps are working before a public release, and Apple gave it to them. Also, think about if the signal or mic bugs you mentioned are released to the public, wouldn't it create chaos? Isn't it better to let people who *volunteer* to test a new iOS version report the bugs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Rockstar just ignore my emails

Of course. They said all bans are final and you can't appeal them. Why bother responding to an email saying the same thing all over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? That doesn't change the fact that people like Chrome Cars. 

I personally don't but why hate/question on other's choices?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for once, I'm glad I am playing on console. I'm glad I didn't buy the game for PC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal Preference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top comment, not top post. Bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the app for PC/Mac, and log in to your PSN ID and connect. No need for PS+

If you are away from your system, connect the PS4 via USB cable or use this fi you want wireless: http://www.bestbuy.com/site/sony-dualshock4-usb-wireless-adapter/5589800.p?skuId=5589800 ref=212 loc=1 ksid=9916f2a9-fdc2-495e-aa13-f782fc5775a4 ksprof_id=15 ksaffcode=pg129308 ksdevice=c lsft=ref:212,loc:2


Ideally you will want another burner account connected to another PSN to remote play if you are using a computer and you are at home close to the PS4. Why? Remote Play in computers acts as a remote that you can't do much with, so if you want to use your remote, that's connected to the PS4 and not to the computer, you will have to do this. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will. Apple has their own MacOS restore file that's not available to the public that includes these apps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person doesn't like the game it automatically becomes garbage for them and everyone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both the of you guys update from the same version/beta?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I reproduce it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had *what* years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I noticed tho, I didn't have to setup my iCloud again (re-authentication) after the update finished  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.3 Beta 5 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iosreleases/status/839536195772252160

462.2mb on 7+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is probably on indeed.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you do it in the toilet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A CUH-700 series game means a game optimized for the PS4 **Pro**

Here is a list I found: https://www.google.com/amp/www.psu.com/amp/32125/ps4-pro-boost-mode-games-compatibility-list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course is not. Do you see a mountain here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the option is enabled then yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Heres a look at some additional features heading to your system soon.

Meaning that these are features they said "We will tell you soon" when they announced the update. The original list is not there to show the new ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try rebuilding the database to see if that helps. 

If it doesn't, try uninstalling the game and installing again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited for this. I have seen myself multiple times wanting to talk to people when my PS is in another room when playing on my computer. 

I know I can connect headphones to the DS4 but is nice to have the option of using the computer's mic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully someone can chime in who remembers 100% what happens, but if the full release has a new build number (higher than the beta) then you get the update to a full release. If build #s remain the same, then the latest beta becomes the full release and you will be good to go
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 4.50 update out tomorrow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I can go downstairs to the mezzanine of the station and tell the cashier in there so they can tell the right people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snapchat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Is a Rocket League joke. They essentially disable your chat if you keep sending messages. In this case, Savage, Brutal, and Both were 3 separate messages, I "disabled" the chat.](https://www.google.com/amp/s/amp.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/3xxyte/where_does_chat_disabled_for_x_seconds_come_from/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a Black Matte with a red pearlescent? How did you achieve it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chat disabled for 3 seconds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The phone is not even 6 months old... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what?

 Apple didn't know this was stolen until you told them

OP never told them. OP wanted to have his Pencil serviced, and Apple knew already. The store reported it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is unnatural for me to shoot with a keyboard and mouse \\\_()\_/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hate Lava Hound (2)/Ballon/Lightning and Mega Minion/Rage.

I still can't find a good deck to counter it. 

Basically anything I try is futile because of the Lightning. Minion Horde is somewhat helpful, but the Balloon buff makes it so that the bomb it drops kill them. 

Any suggestions? Lava Hound/Balloon users, what do you hate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subway Info Display in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a pretty cool ad I saw in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about it. We understood you. 

But when you are talking about multiple *things*, we usually put the "s" in the last place. (See thing/things) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep saying this and people bash me for it, no. Once you learn the Touchbar, you will not look down to change a setting or use a shortcut.

Like you, I tried the TB in a shop and didn't like it, but I had my order in, so I was planning to return it but that changed. 

I'd say, give it a go. There is a 50/50 chance you will like it \\\_()\_/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but that means there is an app waking up and doing things to my phone, constantly tracking me and etc. 

Android is good and all, but 1st party  3rd party. No matter the way you see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you killed them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. Upon further research, they just joked around with the blog post but it was never a thing in the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it Lester's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes: https://clashroyale.com/blog/release-notes/new-balance-live-4-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong, but after the 22GB threshold, the data speed if reduced if and only if the tower you are connected to is congested. You are de-prioritized. 

You will still have LTE as it is unlimited, so you will never run out
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just by using it, from 1-10, how fluid is the OS? (Performance)

Did it lag or made a hiccup while in use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this means OP deleted his/her account  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I know I am coming across as a dick to my country

Compatriota!

You aren't dick, you are just saying the truth. I always thank my family for bringing me to the States and not leaving me there. I'm almost finishing college, but imagine if I were to be living there... No thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's this spoiler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I'm close to hitting the buy button even though I don't need the phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dominican Republic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS Vue: Watch Multiple Channels at Once with Multi-view, Out Today on PS4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TRADE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a PC (or if you visit Reddit.com desktop version) just below the sidebar you will see a list of mods in a box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://download.cnet.com/RecBoot/3000-18553_4-77428313.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you finish thinking about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] An update for Polus has been submitted to BigBoss with iOS 10 compatibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] HMX updated to version 1.0.4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now through 3/5, FF XV is 40% in the PS Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know this is a long shot, but can any T-Mo employees in NYC help me out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to purchase an iPhone 7+ Matte Black (32 or 128GBs), however I am looking for a device made between weeks 46-50 of 2016. 

Is it possible for any NYC Retail worker to check inventory to see if they have a device that's old enough?

You can see when the device was made with this website: http://sndeep.info/en

If you don't wish to use that website, you can also use this guide: https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/5kllys/tutorial_confirmed_serial_number_sequence_to_buy/?utm_content=title utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage

I will greatly appreciate it and I can give you a reward for your effort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playstation congratulates Nintendo on the release of the Nintendo Switch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple quietly re-launching iPhone 6 in a gold 32 GB model, available at select Asian carriers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 132 apps on Google Play were infected with malware, from the wrong OS... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo discloses yet another data breach, its third in the last 6 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature] iOS 10.3 brings in a new diagnostic tool/app that's activated from a cold boot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steps to get in:

Turn off phone and have a powered lightning cable ready

Hold the power button and the Volume Up while plugging phone in on anything iPhone 7


On the iPhone 7, it is Up and Down + Power buttons. 


Let me see if I can look up a tutorial in YT, if there isn't one, I will make a quick video

Source: https://twitter.com/stroughtonsmith/status/836544547614248960 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MKBHD - Dear Apple (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HRgtHE9_3KU feature=youtu.be


TLDW:

* Please, Matte Black everything. Mouses, headphones, computer, Mac Pro, iMac, Keyboard, everything Apple

* Please, USB-C all the things

* "Please, refresh the Mac Pro. Is sad to use a 4 years machine for work and is sad that the price is the same as launch"

* Please bring Wireless Charger in the next iPhone
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] AWS outages are causing Bigboss to not work now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google now notifying general and academic recipients of I/O 2017 tickets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple updates system status site for reporting iCloud service issues, now emphasizes last known outage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MOD AMA] I would not like to be mod. Ask me anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bug that prevented some users from taking a screenshot in the Siri UI, in the 10.3 beta, has been fixed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read about the bug here: http://reddit.com/r/SiriFail/comments/5vsvmr/it_has_come_to_an_end/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] The bug that prevented us from taking a screenshot in the Siri UI has been fixed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] iOS 10.3 B4 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Upcoming] TVOS 10.1 JB coming soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @lenovoUS: "Captivating Design. Unlimited Performance. #newmotog5 #LenovoMWC" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] I've been hearing a lot of conflicting info, is it possible to downgrade an iPhone 6S on 10.2.1 (or 10.3) using the 10.2 blobs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to update because my phone has problems with the display. They asked me to restore via chat before coming to the store.

After the repair is done, is it possible to downgrade to 10.2 using the blobs and Prometheus (or futurerestore), or this only applies to the 5S and iPad Air? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the arena, Gang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple cut ties with server vendor after potential security issues were found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Netflix++ now has background playback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I wrote down the number to call. It was. 1-800 something something. Let me look for it" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] BioProtect updated to version 2.1-99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ColorWare now carries Airpods (custom order)! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] BatteryLife updated with iOS 10 compatibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] 0ptimo removes every tweak of iMokhles from Big Boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
