<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4242</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that'll work
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stickin in my throat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rotflmao, you made my day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a stalker? Have you received other gifts?  Do you have any pagan friends who would send you a gift?  (I'm being serious, lol, I would look up rune symbols, pagan symbols...these do seem familiar, but I can't place any of them right off the top) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you remember/recognize any of the actors?  Even a first name?
(this has become a challenge) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **nice**... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> defiance of gravity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there an apocalypse theme to the movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Beach ? Probably not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> micro-management? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mad max....the original (idk if its been remade, the sequel was) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old?  If it is from the eighties, it could be a Pretenders song, and now I can't remember the name of said song. lol I come back if I remember the name. 
Brass in Pocket https://youtu.be/-7Hy7uAb_eU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does have body parts in jars, maybe a heart...it may not be the flick you're talking about, but it is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love mine, it's my second favorite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once, while very angry, I had been holding a glass of water that I had finished.  I sat the glass onto the counter behind me, and returned to yelling at my friend.  The statement was punctuated by the glass exploding.  The look on my friends face told me that it hadn't fallen to the ground nor had I bumped it.  It just exploded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bogeyman?  I may be miles off... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!  Glad to have you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fringe? Wayward Pines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was it w/ Mickey Rourke, Angel Heart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> skim off the top row, wipe my prints off, run away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only just learned of that sub, crackin'! 
r/confusedboners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sayin'....and these two were barely hitting puberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Wendigo' was an old nickname of mine...I always wondered if he knew the origins of such a tag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what...I have no idea what/where/why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gotta be staged (incredibly well, mind you), the setting is too well lit and the photography too professional.  But yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, there have been 3, I suspect...the main person I have experience with is now deceased.  Her life was a very troubled one.  The individual that is the obsessed fan, I have no idea, it's now been 12 years ago.  It is still something of a mystery, one that will always intrigue me.  (There is no nutshell in which to fit this, there was not a name for what people now call catfishing).  So, it is not urgent, just a point of interest.  I'm glad to have validation that I'm right, though.  I think she came too close to the 'object' of her affection, and when he didn't recognize the connection she felt, something splintered. There is so much more than just that, if you want to hear about it in more detail, I'm glad to share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wherever it was that I found this, I do remember it was tagged as being 'old Disney'..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! I feel successful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indoors? At an abandoned auditorium or theatre? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  What a strange compliment (I'm taking it as one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt that she was panicking....which caused more panic...some days I'd have joined in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't laugh this hard this early omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they have a subreddit for that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's friendly about mother in laws or old lady hands? Ewww get 'em off me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh that is fucked UP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that makes me feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it seems this one has been here before...oops... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an small expanse of woods in my back yard, a creek  that empties into the nearby river.  By the river, what as kids we called "The Clay Pits".  A brick factory that exploded at the turn of the twentieth century.  
Its the noises after dark that are stark and frightening.  Unidentified animals crying, mating, screaming?  I think one sound to be a screech owl...or screech owls feeding their young...idk, I'll get back to you on that.  
But the dark offers your imagination room to move in whatever direction it wants.
edit: NOT a screech owl, identifying this sound is going to take some time lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orphans found under a desk after a forest fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dead marionette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking upward in Hong Kong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you wouldn't think so, just last night at the grocers the girl ringing me accidentally hit the button that stated I had given her exact change....she owed me $1.66......had to have help.  Bless her heart, she was almost 30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would call it 'The Voice on the Wind', and when they talk to you, they say little but loud.  When you listen, you'll be left with a void and a question mark.  Because whatever is was it told you not to do, you didn't....if the voices on the wind tell you not to do something, and you choose to ignore them, you won't have to wait long at all.  You'll know why immediately.  When you listen, you may never know.  And that is okay.  Not knowing sometimes is better than the knowledge of precognitive advice ignored.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I did NOT steal a Red Bull </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming this was in the seventies? Ish?  I'm not being supportive of your mother, I'm not doggin' on her either.  Nobody talked about these things then, to each other, the public, to doctors? Certainly not to your children, and not to a boy's father.  I don't think they knew any better.  No one had told them they didn't have to feel shame. (I'm talking about the parent here, much less the child) I'm sorry such an experience fell into your life, but you seem to have a good head on your shoulders about it.  Right on.  Changing how you handle your children is everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Des Moines, IA, se side bottoms, Harriet and 15th...by the river bank, idk, within a football fields worth of walking along a trail that runs alongside the riverbank.  The stairs connected the woods (built upon an old landfill covered over w/ sod long enough ago that there are fully grown woods over) to the riverbank below.   The path, called 'The Highway' by locals, called 'Glass Cemetery' by others, because after a rain, broken glass from the landfill underneath sparkles to the top.  The Beach is jagged with broken glass shards, some huge. 
Is that what you meant?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was incredulous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I was a redditor, I had somehow come across the SaR stories, the staircases in the woods...that's about when I actually joined reddit.  It was within a few months of that, so about August of last year was my first hike into the woods after reading about stairs in woods.  I had made no mention of this to anyone.  I made no mention of it when I saw the staircase, it was along the river bank....it was about twenty feet or so between the waters edge and the woods we were walking through. 
 Its not that it was so deserted, it wasn't.  A lot of homeless folks converge in the area, and it is a fair fishing location.  Someone had hand-carved out of the earth, a perfect stairwell.  I've never before (nor since) seen a staircase in the woods.  
We walked about a mile in, and there were other oddities that day, but I had made a mental note that I wanted to closer inspect those stairs on our way back out.  I couldn't find them again.  So, I should post this over in the Glitch section too, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can make plans to do that, I've wanted to do that since, because there are other oddities to photograph there as well.  You see, I looked for it on the return path that very day and couldn't find it again (doubles! glitches, 2fer) but I think it was because there were numerous distractions that day...the location, one of Des Moines' 'glass graveyards', old sodded over landfills from yesteryear, and after a rain, broken glass shards from years and years ago shimmer up from the underneath.  And, in '93, we suffered a 1,000 year flood on this river.  There  is a rusted out truck, wrapped around a tree, far far above the river bank, in the woods.  It is incredibly weird and creepy.  And the dirt stairs were perfect.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That house was haunted in more than one way.  That was just one way in which it spoke to me, I guess you could say.  It was a glitch in the house memory, switching back and forth from what it used to be and what it is in the present.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read and so enjoyed those!  I didn't even think of that, I was referring to https://www.reddit.com/r/Glitch_in_the_Matrix/comments/5zyd2n/staircase_disappears_and_reappears/
funny thing, tho....the last 'nature hike' I went on I saw a staircase, in the woods, along the river bank.  It was hand scooped/carved out of earth, and connected the beach and the woods.  I had never seen a staircase of any kind in any woods.  First time after reading that, poof!  I didn't have a damn camera with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed.  Teaching them how to count change is another thing that is going to fall to the wayside as well, all transactions moving to plastic such as they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly.  Raised the question to him once about what in him was broken in that he wanted me (after a particularly vulgar string of insults). Truth be told, motherf@cker was lucky as many times as I had wanted to beforehand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that does raise other possibilities to the meaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this post belongs in r/Glitch_in_the_Matrix/
No one broke into your house and did that to your cube trays.  Unless they are gaslighting you.  (I'm being serious, not a smart ass) (maybe a fraction of smart ass, but I can't help that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had an experience of someone who is an erotomaniac being obsessed with me as well as their desired person; in the end it turns out the person was suffering from D.I.D. as well.  I have looked for and waited for over a decade to see any professional mentions of erotomania occurring within D.I.D. Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cursive in school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard that schools are no longer teaching cursive to students.  I guess I can understand why, but really? Is this a good idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the article, thank you!  In the fourth yes/no spread, I do 3 piles of 13 cards in each (potentially), stopping the count in each pile if an Ace shows, upright or otherwise.  An upright Ace, a good yes, reversed, a bad yes (yes, you have cancer, for ex.) 
I have also found that when counting that many cards you are almost certain to pull at least one Ace, so I find it a little flawed.  Just thought I'd share. I love your posts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you wrote the article, I'm just figuring out.  Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article! Thank you for sharing it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was happening, for me, I had been affixing images onto guys of whom I thought them to be.  Not who they were, but whom I thought them to be. Once I was able to get past that, nothing like that has happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental/emotional abuse.  Big time.  After that shit gets flying, how could I possibly still want someone?  It always flabbergasted me that he thought sex should still be happening, despite all the horrible things he regularly said to me.  Kind of a contradiction there, pal.  You shouldn't want to fuck someone that you feel that way about.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept my married name because it was my sons name as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happened to me, twice, both times I had been smoking really good weed and it was as I had taken a big hit that choked me, so I had a reason for passing out like that.  That doesn't happen for no reason, so you should see a cardiologist or someone of that ilk. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> speaking of staircases.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the early nineties, a bunch of us in our early twenties shared an old Victorian house, one that had been renovated into apartments after a fire had destroyed the original floor plan upstairs.  The owners did not have a copy of the original abstract, so there was no way to know exactly what was where to begin with.
I had one of the apartments upstairs, there were two staircases to choose from.  The back one was a servants passage and quite narrow, and mostly as it was in the past, pre-fire.  The main stairs in the front opened up at the top like most old ones do.  When in approach to begin descent, my feet wanted to start stepping down two-three full feet before the stairs began.  And in reverse, on the way up, my feet would want to continue to climbing.  I think the 'house' had memory (?) of where that original staircase, because I swear every time I used the stairs I would experience this weird vertigo-thing.  Not to mention when my roommates were drunk, more than one took massive tumbles down those stairs, probably starting/stopping inaccurately.  Does this make sense?  Did I explain what I'm talking about well enough?  And does this count as a 'glitch'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe by going downstairs you would have prompted the non-event into having occurred...does that make any sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's about the year this happened, or close anyway. It would technically be the guy behind me at fault, but he had even less a pot to piss in than I.  None of us had licenses, well, I assume due to their age and lack of knowledge of any English, the kids in the Lexus not only lacked a driver license but green cards as well...they were in the most pinch of us all.  They were so pissed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ewwww, scary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have the gut feeling that it is a single individual with an unhealthy obsession for someone named Amie...or Amie in a narcissist who needs more seats than everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> once I used 'float', I swear by it.  W/ gouache or acrylic, either dipping the brush in water or just putting drops of float in the paint, I swear by it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It'll never get to Iowa...:( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( Dammit anyway.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are definitely loved, then respected, in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try experimenting with different brushes, and mediums, like float, and turn a fan brush to 'up and down' instead of flat across, like drawing lines, but with a fan brush???  I've never tried hair, but I think fan brushes and maybe paint float </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually like the last pic, the way it came out?  Accidental, perhaps, but I like whatever it is that happened.  (I'm fairly new too, just for the last year been playing with oils, gouache, tempera....mixing them up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't need to be sure of a direction...i just let it play out through the brush and paint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Captain Howdy"... I only know the reference from 'The Excorcist'; others have added a movie I've never seen, Strangeland maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, and people and cars and houses in urban/suburban areas are not good subjects either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> narcissist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my ex of 12 years made me laugh every day.  Literally, even through the bad shit. He was emotionally abusive. He made me laugh tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably panicky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I turned 30, my best friend decided to throw an impulsive last minute keg-type party (we had done this a few months before for another friend and it turned out fine), but we didn't think about the fact that it was a Tuesday night.  Not one person showed.  I was horrified; I don't even drink alcohol.  I didn't care one way or another.  Then, that.  Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> horribly....he hates me ... he hates a lot of people ... but, very emotionally abusive relationship.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it took me a few seconds to catch up...nice call
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine did shit like that too!!  I called it 'throwing a pity party'...she died a few years back, but from cancer.  Lots of suicide attempts, dating back to before I was born.  Alcoholic, too. I think she intentionally killed one of my cats, too, about sixth grade.  I asked her where Loretta was, first she told me she drove her out to the country and let her go.  Even at 12, I knew she hadn't driven 45 minutes with a yowling feline.  I called her on it, and she amended her statement to having drowned her in a sink.  At that point, I just wondered why she would even say anything like that to her kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My browser doesn't show me anything when I click on the link.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spray?  a damned fine job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you demonstrated water brilliantly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry to hear that, the piece is awesome....and I love that you are able to put beauty within the tragedy; what else is there to do with it? btw, you say your mother burned it down, I hope accidentally....I guess you'd have made mention of it if it were arson.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [3092x1804] 1856 US Map, published in the Des Moines Register, March 11, 1956 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  That is intense, I'm sorry that it is through such destruction such inspiration happened?  Did I say that right?  I've experienced fire as well, but I only lost 1/3 of my home.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm leaving that alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks a little more....obsessed...than a group of teens being ornery.  That is one obsessed adult being...stalky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
