<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8985</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me put that another way... it's not an objectively defined behavior separate from "Fidgeting" or "Facial expression" obviously. I'm not doubting that as with any group of tics, behaviors and expressions, many people would have them in common. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They may hope to gather more data on you, push notifications, add microtransactions, etc. It can also be the result of a manager or VP or C-level thunder*cough* having a "bright idea" as often as not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good, short video from a US municipality which answers all of your questions: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q20-DBAmm2E

This is definitely one of those things that's easier to just see than read about and imagine. 

If you want more detail, or don't like videos... https://www.quora.com/How-does-land-surveying-work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We" don't, and the only person who could answer this question, is you. Sorry, but it's not a universal thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally any day of the week, in any year, "North Korea repeats nuclear threats" would be no less true, or newsworthy.

Stop feeding the distraction machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear, you've cast the magical spell that summons "libertarians" from the corners of Reddit to complain that Monsanto and Bayer are just horribly misunderstood. By the same token, expect the usual anti-GMO crazies to crop up, and it can all end when someone brings up Zyclon-B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically brutal "justice" from the UK on this issue... the US takes a similarly pathetic stance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a slow news day, and speculating about Armageddon is a favorite pastime of media the world over. Note the word, "Could" which is oh-so-vague, verging on meaningless. 

I could take a shit out of an open window, and you could eat a live rat, but *would* we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Wipes away tears* 

It's so sad, I mean... everyone else has to pay taxes on profits, but you're right, poor Apple and their quarter trillion USD in cash!

*Sniffle* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Because they have no clue what to do with it, other than sit on it; this is what terminal stagnation in a company with *tons* of momentum and a massive installed userbase looks like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/LkcIVUmf1qoUM/200.gif

https://alltogetherscattered.files.wordpress.com/2014/05/literally.gif

https://m.popkey.co/a529a9/DYgrr.gif
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THAAD Missile Defense System Initially Capable in South Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skirmishes start as Venezuelan leader's foes, backers rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if you believed your own lines, but... that answers that. 

At least you're in on the joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Active cooling of the walls, but also plasma sent through the diverter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy to process and handle too... nothing exotic or unknown about water, and it's easy to process for disposal at the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me old fashioned, but I'm still more worried about being shot, bombed, poisoned, infected with something nasty like anthrax, or nuked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not unlike Reddit; if you go through someone's comment history and report everything that touches or crosses the line, most people will at least have some comments deleted; many would be banned from a given sub or the site as a whole. 

If there was a meter maid for every parking space, ready with a ticket the *second* the meter ticked over, or someone to check who bought or smoked pot over the last hundred years. Most people wouldn't stand up to the level of scrutiny a state can bring to bear, including the people bringing the scrutiny. 

The law is *intended* to address issues which naturally rise to the surface, but it can just as easily be a weapon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The woman with a strange second sight | The article is talking about something known: 'Blindsight', and not a new a sense. [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blindsight] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also incredibly useful if you have a flat, or you can deploy from the rear to compensate for heavy loads. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Warrrggglllaaaarrrrggllhhaargggglle!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Which other religions cut off women's clits and forces them completely cover their whole body?

The clit thing isn't religious, it's cultural, and if you want to see women covering themselves... look at ultra-orthodox Jews, or go find a catholic Nun. 

Anything else? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Scholarships that they give out are from trusts set up specifically to give them. The school does not have access to the money at all unless they give them out as scholarships.

Soooo much ^This. If you don't restrict a gift, the uni will spend however they see fit... usually on some glitzy shit, or by sinking it into their endowment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your actual point?

Made two days ago, feel free to review at your leisure. Me? I'm over this. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything you need to know about people in general, and Reddit in particular: 

Substantive issues regarding Merkel's KSA visit? 76

"OMGZ Merkel didn't wear no headscarf!" /r/all FP.

http://i.imgur.com/sPwgpLj.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're stone age religions that murder apostates and believe if you don't covert to their religion your punishment is death

Yeah, most religions are like that, or were, or are in some parts of the world. Grow up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only guess that either camouflage isn't a factor (i.e. that if you're close enough to see eggs, things have already gone awry) or that its camo against a non-mammalian visual spectrum. 

Edit: http://wild.enature.com/blog/why-do-bird-eggs-vary-in-shape-and-color </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Swedish are major hypocrites.

Oh good, I was worried that you might not end on a sweeping generalization about a whole nation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reuters article for another perspective on the same thing: http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-budget-idUSKBN17X0YF?il=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could run near the the speed of light (ignore The Flash's superluminal activities) a bullet would be the least of your worries. The air would be detonating against you like nuclear bombs, and you'd build up a catastrophic shockwave of gamma radiation ahead of you. 

IRL The Flash would be a WMD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Kill The Trucks!!!!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't find a game of musical chairs with organs and antiviral medications a bit strange? I would suggest that you need to re-calibrate your "oddity sensor" if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I can smell... EVERYTHING!!!!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he did notice issues, he could also probably snag an in-line booster fan too, but I agree with you, that sounds reasonable without any assistance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one really wants to free them at this point; even if their state peacefully collapsed today it would cost China and the RoK a fortune to integrate millions of impoverished, chronically malnourished, largely uneducated, and ideologically indoctrinated people. It used to be a given that the RoK wanted "Reunification" however the reality now is that the people with family ties are old or dying, and they have a *lot* to lose with little to gain. People in the RoK don't spend most of their time worrying about the DPRK. 

So... who knows, but most of the current brand of international politics around the DPRK is devoted to never having to really answer that question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more "ask sci-fi" than ask science. That said, if you want to just WAG it, I suppose you could expect a series of sensory inputs, feelings, impressions, and probably a lot more, but who could know?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Panama Canal *is* the connection; without the series of locks and so on, it would just fill in over time I'd guess. Remember, it was an artificially created feature, and requires maintenance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As is so often the case in life and medicine... \\\_()\_/

Seriously though, this is a pretty strange case, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just incidentally, while it's a rare thing, occasionally radioactive material finds its way into the world; if you ever see a piece of "pretty glowing blue" metal... don't touch it.

See: Goiania incident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this analysis using US national survey data collected in 1991-1992, 2001-2002, and 2012-2013 from 118 497 participants, the risk for cannabis use and cannabis use disorders increased at a significantly greater rate in states that passed medical marijuana laws than in states that did not.

This is not even wrong... A meta-analysis that ignores the last 4 years of massive change and newly available research? 

It would be funny, but under this administration it's just sad.

"We knew we couldn't make it illegal to be either against the war or black, but by getting the public to associate the hippies with marijuana and blacks with heroin, and then criminalizing both heavily, we could disrupt those communities. We could arrest their leaders. raid their homes, break up their meetings, and vilify them night after night on the evening news. Did we know we were lying about the drugs? Of course we did. -John Ehrlichman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SOCIOECONOMIC STATUS AND ADVERSE BIRTH OUTCOMES: A POPULATION-BASED CANADIAN SAMPLE

Why change the title?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten patients at Penn Medicine have been cured of the Hepatitis C virus (HCV) following lifesaving kidney transplants from deceased donors who were infected with the disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not really. Look at the Swedish cabinet *in Iran.*

...A totally different country? A Persian rather than Arab one? Shia rather than Sunni?

Practically the same... *rolleyes* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone who doesn't want their homelands to be filled with muslim scum is a neo-nazi.

Case in point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect that this is one of those situations where a huge majority of civilian casualties occurred before intervention began; IS didn't exactly take it slow or easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The neo-nazi's and other vermin post this stuff habitually; it fits their silly narrative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any statement beginning with the phrase, *Theresa May Refuses To Accept Government Responsible For...* is inevitably going to be true. More broadly you could probably remove the word "Government" without substantially altering the truth of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No we don't, crazy grandpa... no we don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you actually familiar with the stories I was referencing? I don't think you are... all are or were *scams*. (Edit: Well the moon thing was an offhand comment taken out of context) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I think they're suggesting that we have secret space-based DEW weapons that somehow nobody has noticed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The He-3 mine was an offhand comment, and the male contraceptive was also bullshit.

Want to guess what *this* announcement turns out to be in a week or two? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in your fantasy world, everyone is magically hyper-competent? That must be nice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, when it comes to rocketry, people do tend to learn from failure... I'm less amused by this than some of my fellow Redditors it seems. That they keep testing and improving things like range and payload, over periods of years, rather than individual successes and failures... that's the issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the male contraceptive and the $4 smartphone!

*lol*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's amazing! They can drive them on their Lunar He-3 mines and call home from their $4 smartphones.

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be unable to open the hatch; the pressure difference would be horrendous, and you'd have nowhere near the strength to open anything against it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it helpful to listen to Jeremy Hardy's views on May at times like this... very cathartic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of Yazidis enslaved by IS in Iraq now free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree with that, and it's no less impressive (maybe more so) for being made with stone tools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good, someone who actually knows what they're talking about! Ok, that all makes sense, thanks for the details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong, but when discussing the general technological (rather than social) level of a civilization, the material used for tools is *very* useful. The nature of hunting, of warfare, agriculture, etc...all change *radically* when metal becomes the primary working material. 

I'm not trying to diminish the accomplishments of the Aztecs, Mayans, Olmec, etc... I'm just pointing out the truth which fundamentally got them all killed; they didn't have much metal, or the knowledge of how to use it. In some cases that meant that a city-state might actually exceed its local capacity to feed its people; at some point you need metal tools to support huge numbers of people efficiently in a small region. Tilling with wooden plows is *much* harder than even a small additional metal front to the blade, and that's just agriculture. 

Then you have the problem of warfare; there wasn't much to be done with people covered in metal, with guns and blades, on horseback showed up. It's true that those invaders got some lucky breaks, but even without that it wasn't going to end well for the natives for a number of reasons.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping in mind that the late *bronze* age collapse occurred *thousands* of years ago... I think it's not totally unreasonable to be amazed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You raise the whole egg's temp a lot, for a very short time, in the shell; most "raw" eggs used in US restaurants are that kind of egg. You can also use them to make 100% safe cookie dough for kids and the elderly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^...Are ^you ^in ^my ^house, ^mister? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh... what a good boy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... they most assuredly will; they'll get a giant settlement, and an NDA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water, toy, lap... life is good for a sleepy puppy. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/DiYooih.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOI link is broken, no mention of peak output, pulse length... basically they're touting the fact that multiple beams can be made to converge? 

...This sub... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no known significance to the order in which you consume alcoholic beverages, although I've heard speculation that maybe ultimately those rhymes are meant to be a *guide*. I.E. if you take some shots to get somewhat lit, then switch to beer to maintain you could do well. By contrast, if you start off with some beer, then get the bright idea to take shots... maybe you wake up in the gutter.

It's not the order or the liquor, it's maybe more of an indication of behavioral patterns?

Or it's bullshit... probably bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I'm going to be testifying at your trial, aren't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What technology did they have which you feel is uncharacteristic for a stone-age society?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...First of all let me just congratulate you for genuinely catching off guard... that's not something that happens to me every day online. Ok yes... wow... honestly I have no idea. I'm not sure if anyone has done a uh... a nutritional analysis of human eggs. I would of course point out (what I suspect you know) that they are *very* small; in essence you'd need quite a few women's lifetime output for an... omelette. 

That said, I'm pretty sure (based on what I know about the human ovum) that it would lack the key properties of chicken eggs. Human eggs don't have albumin, a "yolk", lecithin, or anything you expect from eggs in the culinary sense. The human egg doesn't carry its own food with it it; that's provided by the uterine lining and placenta. Really, when we eat eggs, we're not *mostly* eating the little fleck of genetic info, but the large "food store" for growing the baby outside of the mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking or eating it usually. Seriously though, there isn't a great objective measure of something as nebulous as "creativity" and cannabis is poorly studied anyway. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense, in that those are real words and the mean things. It could even mean something in that you would probably expect that a sci-fi super genius would need a more efficient brain. Given that our brain is stuck in our skull, there are limits to how you can make it go 'vroom', and increasing the connectivity between the hemispheres would probably be part of it.

That said, no, those things alone are things you'd expect to result in psychosis and death, but then... Star Trek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They exist because you think they are quaint and should be preserved for tourism and science. 

You really don't know even as much about me as you might glean from my posting history...

Should you be allowed to live in the jungle and enslave and abduct women and convert them to your religion and culture? No. Send in the main line battle tanks and herd them into reeducation facilities.

Whether you're trying to be edgy, genuinely that young/ideological, or just trolling... *yawn*. That shit was old when AOL was new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how it's misleading; they used stone tools, not metal. Those civilizations are arguably best known today for their stone buildings, and their stone/glass weapons. Again, "Stone-Age" is not a value judgement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Is that the "forbidden" island; with the people who pretty much kill all-comers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find videos of any group being violent; that's actually what "cherry picking" is. Learn what words mean before you abuse them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Again, IIRC, they were still pretty devastated, but one of them managed to rig a warp drive that got the attention of the Vulcans. 

Again, it's been years since I've watched Trek, I could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooh... that's pretty straightforward, but you're not going to love it...

Fluorescence: 
http://www.etymonline.com/index.php?term=phosphorus allowed_in_frame=0

Phosphorescent = Phosphorous + -escent
http://www.etymonline.com/index.php?term=phosphorus allowed_in_frame=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gymnastics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know about that... very very cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How great is RES? I'm going to toss you into my ignore list, and you can explain to whoever will listen about whatever you like.

http://imgur.com/uqzMcpj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be a special variant of Hinchliffe's Rule for TDM. 

TDM: *Question?*
Answer: Always No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just report and move on; no doubt this article is going to get slammed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/68bhl5/just_a_girl_and_her_raven_on_the_subway/dgxctyk/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phosphorescence is a type of photoluminescence related to fluorescence. Unlike fluorescence, phosphorescent material does not immediately re-emit the radiation it absorbs. The slower time scales of the re-emission are associated with "forbidden" energy state transitions in quantum mechanics.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phosphorescence

From the page you quoted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the time the native populations would have seen even a measurable start to recovery the Europeans were all over the place.

Yes... and the active ingredient there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my gentle Jesus... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...And seriously, how awesome are Ravens? 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lrYPm6DD44M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Above all, most of us do what feels good, and believe what we want to believe. "Feels good" and "Want to believe" tend to be a cocktail of regional, social, and genetic factors, the deeper and more related to our success and a species, the more prevalent.

As you say... the feedback loop of hunting-acquiring is at our behavioral core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thousands? No. Hundreds? Sure. Mind you, far from a pattern of slow recovery, something very different occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: you can search YouTube and find many regular people who live in various countries in Europe who have uploaded videos 

...You can search YouTube and find videos about absolutely fucking *everything*... you might want to branch out beyond anecdote before forming such poisonous convictions. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The French hopefully recall the last time fascists had their way in France.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, I totally grant you that I was overthinking this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, that's one of the more interesting aspects of human history IMO; the role of surface metals like native copper. If you want to get even more extreme, Eskimos (not sure which tribe, so using the broad term) generally had no metal at all... except for the occasional iron-rich meteorite, which was seen as incredibly valuable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing interesting, just someone who followed me from another sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...And why didn't those populations recover over time, and life simply return to normal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/nlx0n said: 
Hey retard, did you figure out the difference between england and rome

Drink less during the day. 

Your deleted reply:
http://i.imgur.com/WDpm2Gl.png

To: http://imgur.com/HkcOjcA

Still don't see where you went wrong?

Hint...

Me: If you go back to ~1400 BC then you have the height of the Bronze Age... so... that would be a more realistic marker.

You: You mean a bunch of illiterate savages making human sacrifices?

Me: Illiterate?
*Checks written record going back to Sumer and Akkad*

You: "What the hell does that have to do with England?" 

...having already forgotten what had been said just a sentence or two earlier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but the point of hawala is that it explicitly isn't a bank, or a banking system; it's a way to transfer debits and credits via p2p cash transfers or gifts in kind. If you want to do the things a bank does, at some point you *do* sort of a need a bank; if all you need is a way to transfer the concept of debt and credit, hawala works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC all of that happened after WWIII wiped most things out, so maybe there wasn't as much of a banking system as you'd think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 99.9999% positive that there must be some deep, dark Rule 34 of this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally, I gather the nerve to look under the bed.

*Oh goddamn it Frank, stop humming under there!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, some ravens really *can* imitate human speech; that's one way to kill off an old Poe fan I guess, train a raven! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to go an impressively long way down the comment chain before people start to take this in any way seriously... not bad Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who tries to sell you on a "Good guys vs. Bad guys" narrative for that region has an agenda, or an agenda has them. That's not to completely equivocate, but it's certainly more complicated than X vs Y. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always fascinated by this style of argument; by that logic a war is made through a roughly even exchange of casualties, rather than a legal/moral cause, issues of provocation, politics, etc. 

It's the sort of viewpoint that the phrase, "Gross oversimplification" was invented to describe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously am starting to think that as a whole, we don't know how to decipher information we receive anymore, and this thread is a prime example of many people reading the article, comments, or discussion and drawing literally every conclusion from the unknown as possible. I mean look at each comment chain and see the conclusions everyone is making based on info and theories. There is almost no consensus over who is even right which I think is a deliberate act.


This is *not* an accident.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wcy8uLjRHPM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illiterate? 

*Checks written record going back to Sumer and Akkad*

P.S. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roman_conquest_of_Britain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, Antarctica is more remote than Mars?

I never said that, calm down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yes, but just a few hundred years before that the Romans had invaded. The careful selection of 1500 years AD as a point of reference suggests that you know that fact too. If you go back to ~1400 BC then you have the height of the Bronze Age... so... that would be a more realistic marker. 

Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically, and I swear I'm not just trying to be a dick here, but can't you be sure that you'll *never* get a good answer to this question? Serious people with real ideas on the topic are never going to casually share them, never mind broadcast them on Reddit. In essence, however you phrase the question the result is bound to be a list of things which could at best be lucky guesses amidst the noise of other guesses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only take responsibility for what *I* say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask the same question, but now instead of "Other planets" or someplace insanely remote and devoid of resources like a polar region... how about the oceans? On, in, under, *DEEP* under... while they all have challenges, said challenges really pale next to a Mars colony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but it will always be with the caveat, "...Relative to..." and by the same token, "Stationary *relative to...*"

For the rest, all the way back to the last scattering surface: 
https://astrosociety.org/edu/publications/tnl/71/howfast.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For "observer" just read "perturbation of the system" and then don't worry about the how.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can know about something, and not have ready access to it... hence poverty. The degree to which isolated tribes "choose" when few members have access to much in the way of money, education, or opportunities beyond a favela, etc... is a bit disingenuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
