<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 17:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really surprised this isn't a bigger story here on this website

I've been monitoring several Trump Internet forums, and I have NEVER seen them more discouraged and despairing that they are right now today

They REALLY believed Julian was going to come through with something that would "put Hillary in jail". Probably because he said that exact same thing.

With the mounting negative news stories about Trump, this was their last best hope And now it's been dashed. Seriously, these people are in full meltdown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the problem is that combat induced PTSD is very likely not a "mental illness", rather it is legitimately a deterioration of the physical brain due to being in the proximity of bomb blasts

being close to a bomb blast, even if you suffer absolutely no physical injuries, begins a long slow process of literally turning your brain to mush. During this process you literally lose your mind, and right now there's absolutely nothing we can do about it.

No amount of medication, or counseling, or group therapy can counteract your brain literally disintegrating. It's called "brown dust"  in the brain

And what's more is nobody wants to talk about it

http://www.nytimes.com/2016/06/12/magazine/what-if-ptsd-is-more-physical-than-psychological.html

And

http://boingboing.net/2016/08/08/study-confirms-a-physical-corr.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 00:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the thing that's confusing to me is this

By your own admission you look like a boy, you dress like a boy, you sound like a boy, you act like a boy, and you date girls. And now you can't believe that somebody mistook you for a boy?

Don't get me wrong, dress and act any way you please. Totally fine with that. But I think you should stop being quite so nave. When you act and look like ________ (fill in blank) and then somebody in fact assumes you are that very thing That's completely normal. That's how the human brain works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also raise the fifth in an Answer to the civil complaint,

if Trump gets elected I'll be raising many fifths, trust me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trixie's should be shut down for the egregious offense of it's hideously orange paint job!

I mean it's a crime against good taste and basic human dignity

EDITS: down vvotes? How dare you people! Uncouth troglodytes with no sense of style. Every one of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anthony boardgame (or however you spell his last name) hates HATES truffle oil!

LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay fine take the "disturbed" out of it.

She still said he acts like a child who can't keep his mouth shut. And she has no problem with that

Will guess what? I do have a problem with that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a liberal and I have a strong belief in God. I can believe in God and believe in science at the same time, no problem. This is not an atheist/theist issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh FFS!

yes it's kind of funny But it's also maddeningly tragic.

People keep saying that us liberals are "condescending" towards Trump supporters, and we should try to be more understanding of where they're coming from.

But when these people keep saying and believing patently provably stupid things What am I supposed to think?

she is saying "Donald Trump acts like a emotionally disturbed child and that does not bother me"

I'm supposed to pretend that's not a fantastically stupid thing to believe and say? I'm condescending because I look at that and think "for the love of Thor! These dumb people scare the shit out of me!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're giving these people the benefit of the doubt

In reality these people love war. They love the thought of murdering lots of people in large numbers. Especially brown people, especially Muslim brown people.

If they had a chance to press a button and nuke Tehran, they would. In a heartbeat. And then they would slap themselves on the back in congratulations.

they are bloodthirsty, and scary. And Trump knows EXACTLY what he's doing by riling them up with warmongering braggadocious rhetoric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tick? Awesome!

I Love Dick? Meh

I tried watching and I couldn't get through the pilot. It's slow moving in the characters are just completely and totally uninteresting to me. The scene where she finally sees Dick and is completely enraptured by him just felt so phony and dumb

Also the main character lady is constantly hysterical and annoying

I will not be watching it at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice!

That one--view from the capital--you can see the building that Teddy wedgers is in today looks about the same as it did then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why were the stone rings at the ancient site of gobekli tepe built, then buried, then another ring built on top of that, then that ring subsequently buried? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, gobekli tepe is so far the most ancient evidence of an advanced civilization we have ever found

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/G%C3%B6bekli_Tepe

One of the prominent features of the site are large stone circles, with carvings of animals like serpents and lions on them. But for some weird reason these circles were regularly buried and then built back on top of.

Why?


http://ngm.nationalgeographic.com/2011/06/gobekli-tepe/mann-text

For reasons yet unknown, the rings at Gbekli Tepe seem to have regularly lost their power, or at least their charm. Every few decades people buried the pillars and put up new stonesa second, smaller ring, inside the first. Sometimes, later, they installed a third. Then the whole assemblage would be filled in with debris, and an entirely new circle created nearby. The site may have been built, filled in, and built again for centuries.

Bewilderingly, the people at Gbekli Tepe got steadily worse at temple building. The earliest rings are the biggest and most sophisticated, technically and artistically. As time went by, the pillars became smaller, simpler, and were mounted with less and less care. Finally the effort seems to have petered out altogether by 8200 B.C. Gbekli Tepe was all fall and no rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is the deal with wiggies anyway?

Is a bar? Is it a restaurant? How does it stay in business considering I rarely see cars in the parking lot?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick's (on State Street)

Ugh. Nasty moldy carpeting that at least 25 years old. Thrift store paintings on the wall from goodwill circa 1983.

I ate there three times. Two of those times I was served spoiled disgusting nasty food. never again.

I honestly have no idea how it's still in business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reaching out to black communities?

LOL

That is really hysterical you think that is happening. You are delusional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and Vladimir Putin are not "allies"

They are power mongering fascist narcissistic spirit brothers cut from the same cloth

Big difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary is a neocon

That's just a fact. She is a warmongering neocon.

Trump on the other hand is unhinged deranged racist narcissist hatemongering question Mark.

So Pick your poison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when Bush was elected and I predicted he would start a (disastrous) war based simply on the fact that his vice president was one of the largest military contractors in the world. And most of his advisers were former defense contractor workers

People told me I was crazy. Turns out I wasn't.

We will see. Talk to me three or four years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it may actually be more humane

Airstrikes destroy infrastructure which causes years long even decades long decay disease and death

we invaded Iraq over a decade ago and some of those areas are still in total and complete utter ruins, with people suffering just terribly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh well

I mean were destroying modern civilization with carbon emissions anyway, why not just do it quickly with nuclear fallout?

then again,Global warming is nothing but a Chinese conspiracy Maybe nuclear fallout is just a Chinese conspiracy too? Who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right.

Why would trump start shit with his own personal fascist corrupt murderous role model? That would not make sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> morally speaking killing 1000 innocent civilians with one type of weapon or killing 1000 innocent civilians with another type of weapon Is the same thing!

how is one any morally different than the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes absolutely true!

They are murderous depraved bloodthirsty human beings with no compunction whatsoever of killing people that disagree with them.

And we treat them like there some kind of hilarious joke. Honestly, I'm telling you right now Trump will most likely become president and it will NOT be funny. At all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Godspeed Terry

You gave us a lot to laugh about. Thank you

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary enjoys destroying central governments with absolutely no plan how to replace them leaving the country a chaotic nightmarish mess all while declaring victory. See: Libya.

But she has shown no inclination to use nuclear weapons, unlike Trump who has literally said that he would do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shrug

Bush Cheney started a campaign of lies in order to start a war that eventually killed 500,000 people. That war helped destabilize the entire region of the planet and is a major contributing factor to the immigrant crisis right now roiling the EU

oh right it also cost a few trillion dollars

and many people were perfectly willing to vote for Bush's brother for president.

Most people in America have no qualms killing people by the hundreds of thousands or even by the millions. It just doesn't bother them

what's the difference between killing 500,000 people in conventional war Or a couple million with a nuclear bomb? Same damn thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because once America starts "tactically nuking" that lets the door open to Russia "tactically nuking"

And then China will get in on the game of "tactically nuking" because after all was going to stop them?

That Pakistan will get in on the game of "tactically nuking"!

fun times! What could possibly go wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you even paying attention?

How can you not understand this?

These people FANTASIZE and MENTALLY MASTURBATE to the idea of using nuclear bombs on the people we currently dislike. This is an awesome idea to them!

There are literally no downsides. Remember, Muslims are essentially evil. They worship Satan and are going to hell anyway so why not send them their little bit sooner? 

You've never heard of these type of people say "let's turn Tehran into a glass parking lot!"? You think they're joking? They are not. They are serious.

My question to you is How the fuck could you be confused about this?

Bush Cheney enacted a psychopathic campaign of lies in order to start a war that killed 500,000 innocent men women and children and enriched Cheney's bank account. Most of these people have no problem with that war

That's how morally bankrupt they are. 

wake up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey are you Mr. robot fan?

I'm very excited about the season finale tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes the propaganda is working perfectly with you.

You are a fully functioning automaton citizen of this great country. Thinking exactly the thoughts we want you to think. Carry on my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the only way my government will stop killing people in third world countries by the hundreds of thousands is if I stop using the Internet?

Somehow your reasoning escapes me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A person is criticizing his country's foreign policy  I must tell him to leave the country! How dare he use critical thinking and ethical considerations!"

This is what is going on in your brain. Sadly it is entirely predictable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right! Good point!

When they kill people is because they are murderous horrible people

When we kill people (by the hundreds of thousands!) It simply because we need to protect ourselves. It's completely reasonable and natural thing to do!

Thank you for setting me straight on this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see

I had no idea that was even an option! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what you're trying to say here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you aware that 500,000 people died as a result of the US war in Iraq? A war that was started on the back of lies and deceit

500,000 people. We are responsible for their deaths

Look at what we did in Libya. We destroyed a government and left an entire country in shambles with absolutely no plan on how to replace the government, which created chaos.  That's an atrocity.

We are just as bad as they are we just don't want to admit it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you I will try that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because the powers that be always need a group they can focus the public's hatred on

This is Orwell 101. Create a group, tell everybody in the country they are the source of all evil in the world, focus all their hatred on that group, blame everything on them

Every country in the world does this.

In America it was the blacks, that it was the Communists, then it was Al Qaeda, now it's IS

When IS disintegrates, there will be another group were all supposed to hate. it's how the military-industrial complex propaganda machine operates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to say that they are not ONLY religious wars would be correct

To claim that religion has no part in these wars is ludicrous. Muslims are currently the most hated subgroup of people in America.

Look at the countries we going to war aagainst in the last 20 or 30 years. They are 1) oil producers 2) Muslim

Both of those  playing major role in all of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a craigslist alert service that actually works? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a flipper, but I'm in the market for something that might appear for sale on my local craigslist once every six or seven months. Maybe longer.

I used a service that promised to email you if "specific item x" appeared in your local craigslist. I realized later that it didn't really work very well

Is there one of these services that actually work that you can recommend me?

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not too late to join up and go kill Muslims in Iraq, or Muslims in Afghanistan, or Muslims in Libya, or Muslims in Syria (if you are special forces)

oh wait my bad. We are pretending like those are not religious wars (to some extent). Carry on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LA air was some of the worst air in the world in the 1970s and 80s

Then the big evil government showed up with big evil REGULATIONS and forced these poor innocent companies and agencies to clean up their act and the air got infinitely better

I'm just glad Ayn Rand wasn't alive to witness this horrible tragedy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it has nothing to do with better content

It has everything to do with guests. And ratings. The big-time guests will all flock to the Tonight Show/fallon because it's prime network real estate.

Look at the guests Conan gets. They are second and third tier guests </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Harvard educated physician Michael Crichton, Creator of ER   author of Jurassic Park, was a climate change denier; accused climatologists of "fomenting false fear To raise money"; and wrote a book about climate terrorists that influenced Pres. George W. Bush </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, and Conan has been ostracized to cable Siberia

Meanwhile the host who enthusiastically licks ass has a prime time slot in all of the biggest guests in the world

Leno was the same way. Ass kisser.

Old-school Letterman and Conan were the only late-night guests who refused to kiss ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 15:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you're telling me bicyclist was recklessly careening around town, no hands on the handlebars, without regard for his personal safety or the personal safety of anyone else?

Well I never! I simply can't believe such a thing would happen! This whole thing is clearly fabricated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madison planning commission may shut down Barriques (on Park Street) coffee roasting operation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a really great movie with Willem Dafoe about the hunt for the Tasmanian Tiger

It's fictional, but still totally worth watching if you are a Willem Dafoe fan. Which I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Harvard educated physician Michael Crichton, Creator of ER   author of Jurassic Park, was a climate change denier; accused scientists of "fomenting false fear To raise money"; and wrote a book about climate terrorists that influenced Pres. George W. Bush </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sad to hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow

so do these dead trees created fire hazard and is that something you're concerned about?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Holocaust and Christopher Columbus were literally 500 years apart

I'm talking about events that happened very very close together by the same governments and the same people oftentimes in those governments

There is simply no comparison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah! Yes of course Mistake.

Our bad.

are you aware that virtually EVERYTHING the United States government said about that "mistake" in the first two months was absolutely proven to be lies?

Literally everything the Pentagon asserted about that incident was later proved to be completely wrong.

http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/war_stories/2014/07/the_vincennes_downing_of_iran_air_flight_655_the_united_states_tried_to.html

they lied about where the plane was, they lied about the distress signal the plane was sending out, they lied about the plane quickly descending, and most of all they lied about the fact that the US ship was in Iranian waters when he shot that plane down. But hey, if you want to continue to believe liars and the lying lies that they lie Go ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nowhere in his comment does he address it

My point is simple. When other countries shootdown civilian airliners its grounds to destroy the government

When WE shootdown other people's civilian airliners Well Stuff happens I guess.

We always think our shit doesn't stink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh no! Shooting down a civilian jetliner? That's horrible.

you mean like when the US shot down Iranian civilian jetliner flight 655? Like that?

Yes I agree it's terrible. But why is it only terrible when other countries do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my problem with blaming too much of this on Obama is that it's a mentality of "Bush Cheney created an absolutely ENORMOUS and TRAGIC mess for no reason And Barack Obama didn't clean it up! What a terrible president!"

Like I said, my own personal belief is that a three state solution is the ONLY solution in Iraq. I don't believe there's an international political will to make that happen.

So really What are you going to do? Leave massive amounts of troops in Iraq for the rest of all eternity? I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> surely you jest

In the aftermath of the initial invasion of Iraq, chaos ensued and government buildings and museums and national archives etc. were raided and destroyed

There was only one ministry that was protected by US troops-the oil ministry.

There was absolutely no winning strategy in Iraq, at least not in a unified Iraq. The ONLY winning strategy is to separate the Sunnis and Shiites, as well as the Kurds. Three separate states. Anything else is going to be more terrorism and chaos.

Unless of course you let a strongman rule the country with an iron fist, that would definitely work. Somebody like you know Saddam Hussein  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually France was probably the largest driving force behind the tragically stupid decision to remove Qadhafi with absolutely no plan in place to replace him

But yes, Obama and Hillary are also to blame. Then again the Republicans did the same thing in Iraq on a much larger scale. This is not a Democrat/Republican thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does that even mean?

Western powers destroyed a government with ABSOLUTELY NO plan in place to replace the government. This caused a power vacuum. This gave rise to chaos and IS terrorism which was as predictable as the rising sun

Barack Obama himself even admitted that lack of planning for post Qadhafi Libya was the biggest mistake of his presidency

https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/apr/12/barack-obama-says-libya-was-worst-mistake-of-his-presidency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An in-depth look at how Libya is doing several years after Western military powers destroy the government of Col. Qaddafi

Cities descending into chaos, widespread lack of medical services, terrorist attacks antigovernment with two different capitals neither of which is officially recognized by the UN.

Many feel that life was better under the dictator Qaddafi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Qadhafi Libya is a mess. A fractured government, IS terrorist attacks, desperate lack of medical services, entire cities in ruins. life under Gadhafi was much better than it is now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice guys was fantastic!

Pretty sure it's out on DVD now, 100% worth watching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived a lot of places in this country

Guess what? That's pretty much true everywhere you go

Local politics are very much controlled by a loud, ENGAGED, vocal minority.

that's just how it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Nearly every recreational drug studied has been shown to be bad for brain cells except one: marijuana. Cannabinoids have been shown to stimulate neurogenesis - the production of new neurons from stem cells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 16:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can you recommend me a good tree trimming service? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need some trees trimmed

Can you recommend me a good service? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ himself only gave one account of the judgment. And that was in the parable of the sheep and the goats.

The upshot of that parable is that if you are kind to other people, if you help other people when they are in need, if you go out of your way to provide assistance for those who need it, if you are NOT a completely narcissistic self absorbed douche bag Then you are going to heaven. It's that simple.

Yes I know a lot of  Christians disagree with me. I don't care. Jesus Christ himself said your fate after this lifetime is based on how you treat your fellow man, and it is NOT based on your belief system.

Your wife sounds like an absolutely wonderful human being. Unlike other people on this board, I am 100% convinced your wife is in heaven waiting for you and you will be reunited with her when you die. That's how I see it.

My condolences, I certainly hope you find comfort

Matthew 25

31 When the Son of Man comes in his glory, and all the angels with him, he will sit on his glorious throne. 32 All the nations will be gathered before him, and he will separate the people one from another as a shepherd separates the sheep from the goats. 33 He will put the sheep on his right and the goats on his left.

34 Then the King will say to those on his right, Come, you who are blessed by my Father; take your inheritance, the kingdom prepared for you since the creation of the world. 35 For I was hungry and you gave me something to eat, I was thirsty and you gave me something to drink, I was a stranger and you invited me in, 36 I needed clothes and you clothed me, I was sick and you looked after me, I was in prison and you came to visit me.

37 Then the righteous will answer him, Lord, when did we see you hungry and feed you, or thirsty and give you something to drink? 38 When did we see you a stranger and invite you in, or needing clothes and clothe you? 39 When did we see you sick or in prison and go to visit you?

40 The King will reply, Truly I tell you, whatever you did for one of the least of these brothers and sisters of mine, you did for me.

41 Then he will say to those on his left, Depart from me, you who are cursed, into the eternal fire prepared for the devil and his angels. 42 For I was hungry and you gave me nothing to eat, I was thirsty and you gave me nothing to drink, 43 I was a stranger and you did not invite me in, I needed clothes and you did not clothe me, I was sick and in prison and you did not look after me.

44 They also will answer, Lord, when did we see you hungry or thirsty or a stranger or needing clothes or sick or in prison, and did not help you?

45 He will reply, Truly I tell you, whatever you did not do for one of the least of these, you did not do for me.

46 Then they will go away to eternal punishment, but the righteous to eternal life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you.

Right now they've got $7 chocolate bar display right at the register

I mean it's kind of a joke. How many seven dollar chocolate bars are they really selling to us North Siders? they don't seem to get it that this is not an expensive wealthy neighborhood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right, but what I'm saying is that from what I heard business is at the level that they thought it would be. I'm not claiming they are profitable at this moment.

"Meeting benchmarks" simply means that they had a projection for how much business they should be doing at this point, it doesn't indicate anything about being profitable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumor: Willy St. North is meeting sales benchmarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> according to my supersecret insider source, Willy St., North is currently meeting its sales benchmarks

And they haven't even had their grand opening yet

Also, how long does it take to make a freaking sign? They've been working on that stupid sign outfront for like a month now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 01:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting

Can you tell me what else is in that article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I mean stuff leaks out. Stuff leaks out of every single organization on earth.

Just because stuff leaks out doesn't mean it's not a classy organization </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay great, so that's how he is on a radio show

Now imagine how he is in the locker room. Now imagine how he is at a players barbecue after he's had about six or eight beers in him.

After a while that kind of shit gets old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha!

if anyone out there honestly thinks that Ted Thompson is sitting around his office going "oh my! What will people think if we cut player X? To counteract the potential negative PR I will have my people plant false stories in the press to make us look a little better! Yes definitely!" Well then you are hilariously misinformed

I legitimately think TT is high functioning Asperger's. That's not a joke. Not only does he not care what other people feel, I'm not sure he understands feelings at all. He literally just doesn't care what anybody thinks about anything. He is entirely 100% focused on his job and doing it. PR campaigns just aren't in his nature.

This is the cold-blooded mother Fucker who said no to Brett Favre when the fan base was clamoring for him, and then traded him away. Just doesn't care.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so Does Randall suck now all of a sudden?

What the hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remember when our sub wanted to cut Adams about 10 minutes ago?

 LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let's get real people. She's done.

Toast. She is not coming back from this. People ALREADY didn't like her. then the email scandal. And now this?

people are not going to vote for a person whose health seems to be completely collapsing. It's not going to happen.

Get used to the term "Pres. Donald Trump"

Get used to feeling like you live in a country full of the stupidest people in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she is fucked

People ALREADY didn't like her. Then we got the email thing, now we got the medical thing.

She is screwed. She's going to lose this election and were going to be absolutely humiliated on the world stage by electing Donald freaking trump

I'm telling you right now she's going to lose this election. She will not win.

Good Lord have mercy on my country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh boy oh boy oh boy

spriggs WILL be good At some point in the future

Right now he's very weak and will get manhandled. Good grief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This agent Smith, Mike, let me tell you his ability to phase shift in out of various players bodies is really incredible. One of the best I've ever seen.

kids got a real future in this league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not buying it!

Elliott asked the dark army what phase 2 was. They (and I include white rose in this I pretty sure) were confused because phase 2 was Elliott's idea

White Rose would not be confused if he/she understood about Elliott split personalities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they get some of my tax money. So I don't have a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But I've never seen any of these critics explain what, in February or March of 2011, would have happened if the US had stood by and had encouraged our European allies to similarly avoid intervention. What, exactly, do these critics think would have happened? They need to answer the question, "What if we had done nothing?"

oh give me a break with this shit!

Saudi Arabia has been BOMBING Yemen for the last few weeks. Killing women and children and other innocent civilians. NOBODY in America or Europe has made a stink about it. Nobody.

You know why? Because they are our allies. So it's okay.

But when somebody we don't like does the exact same thing that is all of a sudden we start hyperventilating "OMG! We have to do something about this! Won't somebody think of the chiiiiiiiiiildren!" 

we don't care about children dying. We don't care about innocent civilians dying. We just care about the global sociopolitical chess game and how to get an upper hand in it.

Let's stop deluding ourselves about what we really care about

if you really want to know "What if we had done nothing?", Well then look at Yemen because we are doing nothing.

Re:

https://www.google.com/search?q=Saudi+Arabia+bombing+Yemeni ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8#q=Saudi+Arabia+bombing+Yemen+civilians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well anytime you come up with a plan to end homelessness in Madison we're all waiting.

 We all want to hear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah that sounds fine. Sounds great.

the problem is that a lot of these programs designed to help homeless people are very corrupt. A lot of money goes into them Very little comes out the other hand where the homeless people actually are

Lutheran social services is TERRIBLE when it comes to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton's vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny thing about all of that

EVERY SINGLE one of those criticisms could be laid at the feet of the Saudi Arabian government also.

Every single one of them.

In fact the Saudi Arabian government is guilty of all of those And much worse! And yet they are our good buddies. Our best friends! I mean sure that implicated in 9/11 But who cares!

The whole thing is a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the difference is that Bradford has both legs attached Pretty sure trainers are still looking for Teddy's leg in the bushes on the side of the playing field </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they could have been part of a 7982 country coalition

What they did there was still wrong.

In the aftermath is that Libya is the number one Isis recruiting ground in all of Africa 

It's a disaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the bills are pretty injury devastated

I wouldn't worry too much about them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is. The fact that there were other people involved is not the point.

Obama authorized the bombing of a sovereign foreign country. That eventually led to chaos and a fertile recruiting ground for Isys.

It's inexcusable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not laying this all on Obama!

but what you people are not realizing is that the CIA was hard at work in Libya right from the get-go. Well before 2011. this is what the CIA has been doing in country after country after country for the last 60 years, and it almost ALWAYS ends disastrously. Nearly always.

They did in Iran in the 1950s when they overthrew democratically elected government and set the stage for Islamic radicals to take over that country, they did it in Cambodia where they supported Pol Pot who turned out to be one of the worst people in the history of the universe. they did it in Chile in the 1970s when they assassinated Salvador allende and threw their support behind general Pinochet who just happened to prove himself to be one of the worst people in human history.

I could go on


Learn your history

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Col. Qaddafi

Col. Qaddafi

Col. Qaddafi

That's how my spellcheck spells it. So yes, my arguments here are probably incorrect because my spellcheck spells Col. Qaddafi like Col. Qaddafi

Finally I've been defeated by somebody with a crushingly logical argument against me. I concede defeat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's ridiculous.

I've done nothing but post legitimate reliable solid sources and make honest arguments

What I get in return is down voted, people mocking me, people responding with ZERO actual arguments, and nobody bringing a single solitary link or source to the conversation

People are really brainwashed in this country, even the ones who think they aren't because they don't watch Fox news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hhahahahahaha!!!!!


So funny. None of you jokers have yet to actually come up with a reason why I'm wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude! Come on!

Don't be so nave!

The CIA was hard at work pulling together various factions, doing its normal nasty dirty work, stirring up a "homegrown" rebellion that eventually exploded.

Come on man, they've been doing this shit 50  60 years or so now. It's the same thing every time. It's glaringly obvious and the whole world knows it's happening even if we don't want to admit it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no NATO didn't start

The CIA did.

http://www.globalresearch.ca/benghazi-the-cia-and-the-war-in-libya/5386266 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and?

it was still a giant mistake. Libya today is the number one recruiting ground for Isis in all of Africa. We took a bad situation and made it worse. Just like in Iraq. Just like in Syria. We have a habit of doing that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yes I love this!

The US sends military and humanitarian aid to rebels, the US bombs Libya, this creates chaos and disorder, and when the government tries to reestablish order tthey are instantly accused of being war criminals.

Absolutely hilarious!

500,000 innocent Iraqi women and children and civilians were killed because America invaded a country based on lies and greed. And we're sitting in judgment of Col. Qaddafi because a couple hundred people died when he tried to reestablish control over his country after American bombing?

Give me a break

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Casualties_of_the_Iraq_War </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how about one of you actually bring up an actual argument on why I'm wrong here

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was a rebellion Because the US was backing the rebellion by bombing the capital!

Get your facts straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes they were, learn your history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right, in part thanks to us!

we established diplomatic relations with the rebels, gave them humanitarian aid, and we even bombed the government for them

So yes there was a Civil War And we were the main instigators of that damn thing!

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_involvement_in_the_2011_Libyan_Civil_War </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have no idea who he was or what he did in that country. He took it over when it was a complete shit hole, and turned it around

Literacy rates skyrocketed, poverty rates plummeted, universal healthcare, college education expanded, cholera and other diseases were nearly wiped out etc. etc.

He did great things for the country. Stop buying into American propaganda BS about everything

 EDIT: I love how people keep down voting my comments about Libya, but not one single one of you people have brought up a fact or an actual argument on how I'm wrong. You just down vote.

Hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what Obama did in Libya is inexcusable. It's an atrocity.

He destroyed a perfectly stable government, honestly one of the best governments in the entire area of the world, and replaced it with chaos and disorder that is now one of Isis' prime recruiting grounds.

It was a foreign-policy disaster all the way around.

for those down voting me, this is from Col. Qaddafi's Wikipedia page

Supporters praised Gaddafi's administration for the creation of an almost classless society through domestic reform.[351] They stress the regime's achievements in combating homelessness and ensuring access to food and safe drinking water. Highlighting that under Gaddafi, all Libyans enjoyed free education to a university level, they point to the dramatic rise in literacy rates after the 1969 revolution.[351] Supporters have also applauded achievements in medical care, praising the universal free healthcare provided under the Gaddafist administration, with diseases like cholera and typhoid being contained and life expectancy raised.[351] Biographers Blundy and Lycett believed that under the first decade of Gaddafi's leadership, life for most Libyans "undoubtedly changed for the better" as material conditions and wealth drastically improved

From 1969 to 1973, the RCC introduced social welfare programs funded with oil money, which led to house-building projects and improved healthcare and education.[75] In doing so, they greatly expanded the public sector, providing employment for thousands.[75]

Compulsory education was expanded from 6 to 9 years old, while adult literacy programs and free university education were implemented; Beida University was founded, while Tripoli University and Benghazi University were expanded.[76] These early social programs proved popular within Libya.[77] 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've had a lot of wars of my own"

This of course is referencing some of the most hard-fought, raging, high casualty, twitter wars in history. He has received three virtual twitter purple hearts, along with a virtual twitter Congressional medal of honor.

He is one of this country's greatest bravest twitter warriors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Soglin proposes record highs in capital spending, authorized borrowing for 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was anybody else really impressed by UDFA offensive lineman Lucas Patrick in the preseason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is now on the practice squad. I watched him in the preseason and he seemed to be doing really well, especially for an undrafted free agent.

 There's virtually nothing on him out there on the web.

Did anybody else notice him? What were your thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big dig for legendary Nazi gold train in Poland a bust, explorers say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 00:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Investigation confirms long-held claims of widespread sexual abuse at elite Rhode Island prep school. Should be of interest to those looking into pedophilia abuses by those in power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's long been many conspiracy theories regarding pedophilia abuses and coverups by those in high levels of government, both in America and Europe and several other countries.

Interesting case here which revealed at least 61 former students from the 70s and 80s testifying regarding widespread sexual abuse of students at a prep school for the elite and rich in Rhode Island.

https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2016/09/01/stgeorges/4so7ElWQwjTsnDkv5eI3NJ/story.html

After a months-long investigation of sexual abuse at St. Georges School, a report released Thursday described the elite Rhode Island prep school in the 1970s and 80s as a cauldron of sexual exploitation of students.

Sixty-one alumni gave investigators first-hand accounts of the abuse they say they suffered, with 51 saying the abusers were faculty or staff and an additional 10 reporting abuse by classmates. Two staff members abused at least one student every year they worked at St. Georges.

The picture that emerges from this investigation is profoundly disturbing, wrote attorney Martin F. Murphy in a preface to the 390-page report. Murphy, a partner at the Boston firm Foley Hoag, was appointed in January by St. Georges and the victims group SGS for Healing to investigate sex abuse at the school in Middletown, R.I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Trump trails Clinton by two points </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick takes on 2 new Amazon shows: "The Tick" - Great! "I love Dick" - Meh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 17:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Tick**

in a world where superheroes are real, a young man is recruited by a superhero called the tick to defeat a nefarious mysterious bad guy. 

Problem: this young man has been diagnosed with mental illness. Is the tick real? Is the tick simply a product of his mental illness?

Well acted, well written, both dramatic and humorous, very involving. The young man's back story is wonderful and perfectly told. I will definitely be watching each new episode as they come out

**I love Dick**

A man and his wife moved to the small town of Marfa Texas because the man has scored a prestigious writing residency offered by a guy named Dick. When his wife meets Dick she's instantly infatuated with him. Dick is played by Kevin Bacon.

slow-moving, uninvolving, and really just not a lot going on. I didn't really care about the main characters, and the wife is hysterical, needy, and annoying. I lasted three quarters of the way through the first episode, got bored, and turn it off, I will not be watching anymore episodes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pamela Hupp case just got even more bizarre. She's being charged with first-degree murder and an attempt to frame Russ Faria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for those who don't know Pamela  hupp, she is one of the most coldly calculating despicable people I've ever run across. And the worst part of it is that her main enablers and unwitting accomplices were her local police department.

Here is the background on her

https://www.reddit.com/r/UnresolvedMysteries/comments/42b2l1/anybody_watch_dateline_last_night_i_swear_to_god/

TLDR: Russ Faria's wife is found murdered. Pamela was the last person to see her alive, and his wife recently changed her will to make Pamela the sole beneficiary.

Pamela pointed the finger at Ross, and the police ignored the mountain of evidence against Pamela and instead try to railroad this poor man for his own wife's murder which he was CLEARLY innocent of. A real tragedy, the kind of case that makes you want to punch the prosecutor in the face.

Anyway she's been recently arrested for first-degree murder.

http://www.nbcnews.com/dateline/prosecutor-charges-pam-hupp-1st-degree-murder-alleges-attempt-frame-n636841



Pam Hupp has been charged with first-degree murder and armed criminal action in the August 16 shooting death of Louis Gumpenberger, 33, a man she told police was burglarizing her O'Fallon, Missouri home when she killed him. The charges were announced Tuesday at a press conference with the O'Fallon Police Department and Prosecuting Attorney Tim Lohmar.
Dateline NBC

Hupp had been the state's key witness in the case against Russ Faria, who was convicted in 2013 of murdering his wife in 2011. Hupp was the last known person to see Betsy Faria alive before she was stabbed to death in her home in late December 2011. Four days before the murder, Hupp had become the beneficiary of a $150,000 life insurance policy that Betsy owned. It was a change that no other friend or family member knew about. Hupp uncorroborated allegations about Russ, who became the only suspect in the case. 

[Snip]

 But the prosecutor said there appears to be a connection between the Faria case and the charges Hupp now faces.

According to police, Hupp called 911 at 12:08 p.m. on August 16, to report an active break-in at her home. While on the phone, she told 911 that she had shot the intruder. Gumpenberger was pronounced dead at the scene. He was later identified by his fingerprints, as he had no identification on his person. However, $900 and a note were found in Gumpenberger's pant pockets. According to the probable cause statement, included with the charging document against Hupp, the note "appeared to be instructions for Gumpenberger to kidnap Hupp, get Russ's money from Hupp at her bank, and kill Hupp in order to collect the rest of the $10,000." The name Faria was also on the note, authorities said. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a non-injectable way to take BPC-157? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is the only way to take BPC-157 right now to injected?

Is there a non-injectable option of this peptide?

Thank you.

Also, if anybody has a source for BPC-157 you feel very comfortable about let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> huge tree on Capitol lawn just fell over for no reason. darn near killed somebody. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 04:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anybody else see that?

A very large tree on the capital lawn just crashed down onto the sidewalk randomly.

Almost killed a passerby. I don't think anybody was actually hurt, although there was an ambulance over there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Printer won't print, shows off-line. It's definitely not off-line. Googled it, follow directions, does not work. and told to "configure port", get error message saying "operation is not supported" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay so my printer won't print. Shows it is off-line.

Googled it, follow directions in the video below. Told to go to "ports" setting, then hit "reconfigure port"

When I do that I get error message saying "operation is not supported"


Now what?

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ououPOBThwc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explorers in Poland began digging Tuesday for a legendary Nazi train said to be laden with treasure and armaments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 14:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is a long-standing legend that a Nazi train chock-full of gold disappeared into the Polish countryside near the end of World War II. Nobody knows if there is any truth to the legend or not.

-----------------------------------------------------------------

http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2016/08/16/world/europe/ap-eu-poland-nazi-train.html

Search Resumes for Nazi Gold Train That Might Not Even Exist

By THE ASSOCIATED PRESSAUG. 16, 2016, 7:39 A.M. E.D.T.

WARSAW, Poland  Explorers in Poland began digging Tuesday for a legendary Nazi train said to be laden with treasure and armaments.

They're not dissuaded by decades of fruitless searches, a scientific determination that no train is there and warnings by historians that such a train might have never even existed.

The search in southwestern Poland attests to the power of a local legend claiming a Nazi "gold train" disappeared in a mountain tunnel as the Germans escaped the advancing Soviet army at the end of World War II. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who watched the Bears play tonight? What did you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what was your impression? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are in the Golden age of TV dramas. We are also in the Golden age of whiny bitchy nitpicky viewers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy crap I just can't stand it anymore!

I'm telling you right now there has NEVER been more quality TV shows to watch than there is right here right now. Never. I'm almost 50 years old. Let me tell you growing up we had three, maybe four options of things to watch on any given night and they were usually cheesy and stupid and dumb. 

Some stupid sitcom, or some horrible soap opera like Dallas, or a different god-awful sitcom, or some fantastically cheesy cop drama, or whatever. Lots and lots and lots of crap

Today? Incredible choices! One great show after another after another. Better call Saul, preacher, orphan black, banshee, Mr. robot, game of thrones, stranger things, etc. etc. so many great shows out there!

And yet what I see time after time are both critics and casual fans whining and bitching and moaning and complaining and nitpicking about all of these great shows.

"Well you know preacher started out good, then by the third episode it wasn't so great, but then one quarter of the way through the fourth episode started getting good again, but then 5/8 through the fourth episode I got to tell you it's that started dragging for me and I just don't think that it just didn't quite have the quality of the first 3/5 of the episode and bla bla bla bla......"

Good grief people! If I could take you whiny bitches and transport you back to the 80s and force you to watch primetime TV you would come back weeping and whaling, clutching my clothes, your entire world shaken to its core, promising never again to complain about TV quality today.

And Mr. Robot is still great! Second season is fantastic I love it and everybody who's whining and bitching about how it's too slow or whatever can kiss my ass!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parabiosis (Young blood therapy) looks VERY promising. We are about 1015 years away from a legitimate viable rejuvenation therapy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> parabiosis is using young blood to rejuvenate older organisms. Of all of the longevity therapies I've researched this one seems to have the most promise, as well as the most realistic actual science going on.

Studies done on mice and rats showed that when plasma is taken from young mice and injected into older mice, the older mice experienced a 400% increase in new neuron growth in the hippocampus area of the brain. These results were published in the journal nature

http://www.nature.com/nm/journal/v20/n6/full/nm.3569.html

buoyed by results like these, the first human trial of young blood therapy is underway by a company called ambrosia. 

https://www.technologyreview.com/s/602080/the-next-health-fad-blood-transfusions-from-young-people/

Ambrosia is planning on giving 600 patients four rounds of weekly blood infusions coming from 16- to 25-year-olds. Ambrosia founder Jesse Karmazin, who went to Stanford Medical School, said in an e-mail that he was inundated with interview requests and unable to speak today.

The pay-to-play nature of Ambrosias trial has draw criticism from some researchers, according to Science, and is reminiscent of recent news highlighting the surge in unproven stem-cell clinics that require their patients to pay for clinical trials that may never see data published. The Ambrosia clinical trial lists over 100 blood biomarkers it plans to measure before and one month after the transfusions, but David Glass, executive director of aging research at Novartis, says that because the trial has no placebo control group, it will be impossible to decipher any benefits from it.

More info on that here

http://www.vanityfair.com/news/2016/08/peter-thiel-wants-to-inject-himself-with-young-peoples-blood

but realistically the best hope is not simply injecting Young blood into older people, but rather it's the proteins in the young blood.

This researcher here notes there are 700 proteins in blood. Several of those proteins have the ability to program the body to literally rejuvenate itself. Once those proteins identified they can then be filtered out and administered to older patients. This process is probably going to take 10 to 20 years.

https://www.theguardian.com/science/2015/aug/04/can-we-reverse-ageing-process-young-blood-older-people

Wagers picked out one factor, known as GDF11, as a rejuvenating protein in young blood. In Villedas most recent paper, published in July 2015, he found a second factor, B2M, which peaks in the blood of old mice, as it does in old humans: when injected into young mice, B2M impairs their memories.

The studies all point in one direction. Among the hundreds of substances found in blood are proteins that keep tissues youthful, and proteins that make them more aged. Wyss-Coray has a hypothesis: when we are born, our blood is awash with proteins that help our tissues grow and heal. In adulthood, the levels of these proteins plummet. The tissues that secrete them might produce less because they get old and wear out, or the levels might be suppressed by an active genetic programme. Either way, as these pro-youthful proteins vanish from the blood, tissues around the body start to deteriorate. The body responds by releasing pro-inflammatory proteins, which build up in the blood, causing chronic inflammation that damages cells and accelerates ageing.

Alkahests ultimate goal  to identify the key proteins in plasma that rejuvenate or age human tissues and then manufacture a product that uses them  could take 10 to 15 years. In the near term, the company has another strategy. Earlier this year, the Spanish blood products firm, Grifols, pledged $37.5m for a 45% stake in Alkahest. With another $12.5m, the company will bankroll more research in exchange for rights to Alkahests first products. Over the next two years, Alkahest will take human plasma and divide it into fractions that are rich in different proteins. Each fraction will then be tested in mice to see if they boost brain function. Any that do will be swiftly introduced into human trials and developed into the first generation of products.


Ted talk on the subject

https://www.ted.com/talks/tony_wyss_coray_how_young_blood_might_help_reverse_aging_yes_really?language=en

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billionaire Peter Thiel, and others, think old bodies could be rejuvenated by injecting young blood. Are they crazy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short disagreement about Donald Trump ended at an East Side sports bar when the Trump supporter showed he had a gun tucked in his waistband. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump, Sen. Joseph McCarthy's red scare, and the mysterious briefcase that help determine the 1980 US presidential election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] Project Berenstein? LOL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 06:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh that's pretty funny!

For those who don't know there's a running Internet controversy/Conspiracy about how the children's book Berenstein Bears somehow mysteriously change to the Berenstain Bears later on

this has convinced people there is somehow parallel universes or something

Re:

http://www.vice.com/read/the-berensteain-bears-conspiracy-theory-that-has-convinced-the-internet-there-are-parallel-universes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy gets four years for a long series of burglaries and break-ins, including holding a 90-year-old lady at gunpoint, and assaulting another homeowner. Really? Four years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 15:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> generally speaking I think we have too many people in prison in this country. Many of them for petty offenses.

But holy shit! This guy went on a multi-year break in and burglary spree which included holding a 19-year-old lady at gunpoint and also physically assaulting another homeowner. Judge notes that he had lots of positive support in his life and still did this

four years? That's it? That seems crazy to me

http://host.madison.com/wsj/news/local/crime-and-courts/madison-man-gets-years-prison-for-residential-burglary-spree/article_ef02f691-30eb-5458-96cc-acd7cbabdb58.html

A Madison man was sentenced Monday to four years in prison for a long series of residential break-ins that happened mostly on Madisons West Side in late 2014 and early 2015, including one in which a 90-year-old woman was held at gunpoint.

Dane County Circuit Judge David Flanagan told Jamal A. Scott, 22, that even if Scott could round up all of the stolen valuables and items that had sentimental value and return them to their owners, he couldnt change the enduring feeling of victimization that those people feel.

Some couldnt return to live in their homes again, Flanagan said, while others have said they still dont feel safe in them.

Flanagan also said that given the amount of positive support that Scott has had in his life, from family, clergy and community mentors, he couldnt understand how Scotts burglary spree continued unabated.

But it ended on April 3, 2015. That day, Scott and Jeffrey D. Harrison, 21, broke into the home of a 90-year-old woman. For a half-hour, Flanagan said, Scott rummaged through the womans home, looking for valuables, while Harrison held a gun toward her head in her bedroom.

There had been some dispute over which man held the gun, but the womans description of that man made it more likely that it was Harrison, who was much thinner than Scott. Flanagan said it didnt matter to him.

On some level, it must have bothered you to see a 90-year-old woman afraid in her bed, Flanagan said. But it didnt. You went out and did it again.

That day, Scott and Harrison broke into another home, where Harrison got into a struggle with the homeowner and was arrested. Scott fled but was arrested later.

Harrison was sentenced on July 1 to 8 years in prison.

Deputy District Attorney Matthew Moeser said he didnt believe Scott truly accepted responsibility for what he did, because he said he was high on Xanax at the time and didnt remember the crimes. He asked for a 14-year prison sentence. Scott insisted in court that he accepts responsibility, and that what he did was wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally saw "Mulholland Drive" (David Lynch). Many (including Roger Ebert) consider it bizarre and ultimately inexplicable. I found it rather straightforward. What? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> many consider David Lynch's Mulholland Drive to be completely mysterious and utterly inexplicable. This includes Roger Ebert who said

http://www.rogerebert.com/rogers-journal/lost-on-mulholland-drive
In short: "Mulholland Drive" resists, defies and finally defeats logical explanation. It is impossible to produce a consistent precis of the film that accounts for everything. And there is an admirable reason for this: Like a dream, it does not have to make sense.

personally I found it pretty straightforward.

There is a scene when Diane (Naomi Watts) is at dinner at the director's house. She is talking to the director's mother about her life. She explains that she's from a small town in Canada, moved to Hollywood, had a rich aunt who died and left her money, she tried to break into the movies, she really really wanted the lead part in a specific movie but instead went to Camilla.

After that Camilla helped her get smaller parts in various movies but ultimately she didn't have a lot of success.

In my opinion all of that is true. None of that is a dream. All of that happened in real life.

The other thing that happened in real life is that Diane and Camilla started a torrid sex affair. For Diane it was true love. For Camilla it was nothing but a good time. In fact Camilla took delight in flaunting her other relationships in Diane's face including her relationship with the director. This happens when her and the director here sitting in the car and the director demands the set to be cleared but Camilla insists Diane can stay. Camilla then begins making out with the director in front of Diane.

When Camilla and the director announced their engagement at the dinner, Diane has reached a breaking point. her career has failed, her aunt is dead, the only person she cares about treats her cruelly, and possibly she is a junkie. I'm unclear on that however.

So she hires a hitman to kill Camilla. The hitman shows her a blue key and says the blue key will show up at a specific place when the deed is done.

Again All of this happens in the real world.

Back in her apartment, Diane sees the blue key sitting on the table. She knows the deed is done.

Even though the movie is not edited this way, CHRONOLOGICALLY speaking this is when the first scene of the movie takes place with Camilla riding in the car and the men in the car attempting to kill her. THIS SCENE is a DREAM.

this is Diane's flight from reality, and the way in which she imagines she can be reunited with her true love Camilla who she has in the real world just had killed.

in the dream world Diane is named Betty. Everything in the dream world is reversed for her.

In the real world Diane is a failed actress. In the dream world Betty's aunt is not just rich, she is incredibly well-connected and these well-connected people pull strings to make sure that Betty becomes successful actress.

The entire sequence with Betty arriving in LA, encountering the two weird old people, moving into her hands apartment, encountering a amnesia stricken Camilla, the director being forced to cast Betty in the role, the cowboy, investigating Camilla's real identity etc. All of that is a dream.

Again in the real world Betty wants to be Camilla. In the dream world Camilla wants to be Betty and goes so far as to make up her face and get a way to look like Betty/Diane.

Ultimately the dream ends/collapses, and Diane kills herself. 

Again, I think the movie is pretty straightforward. I don't really see how it's "utterly inexplicable" like some people think.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legendary crooner Roy Orbison famously had a 3 (4?) Octave vocal range. How unusual is that and what singers have had a similar range? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ball lightning is a bizarre phenomenon, and can Even float through walls. Scientists have struggled to explain it. Now a new theory says it's the result of lightning accelerating electrons to near light speed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ball lightning has fascinated researchers for decades, although many scientists have insisted is nothing but an urban myth.

These balls of light, resembling plasma spheres, appear during thunderstorms and can slowly move through the landscape and even go through walls.

Wikipedia actually does a great job of explaining it. Below that part of an article which describes the latest theory on how ball lightning is formed 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ball_lightning

Ball lightning is an unexplained atmospheric electrical phenomenon. The term refers to reports of luminous, spherical objects which vary from pea-sized to several meters in diameter. Though usually associated with thunderstorms, it lasts considerably longer than the split-second flash of a lightning bolt. Many early reports say that the ball eventually explodes, sometimes with fatal consequences, leaving behind the odor of sulfur.[1][2]

Until the 1960s, most scientists argued that ball lightning was not a real phenomenon but an urban myth, despite numerous reports from throughout the world.[3] Laboratory experiments can produce effects that are visually similar to reports of ball lightning, but how these relate to the natural phenomenon remains unclear.

Scientists have proposed many hypotheses about ball lightning over the centuries. Scientific data on natural ball lightning are scarce, owing to its infrequency and unpredictability. The presumption of its existence depends on reported public sightings, and has therefore produced somewhat inconsistent findings. Due to inconsistencies and to the lack of reliable data, the true nature of ball lightning remains unknown.[4] The first ever optical spectrum of what appears to have been a ball-lightning event was published in January 2014 and included a video at high frame-rate.

---------------------------------------------------------------





http://www.skyvalleychronicle.com/BREAKING-NEWS/NEW-THEORY-EXPLAINING-RARE-PHENOMENON-OF-BALL-LIGHTNING-MAY-ACCOUNT-FOR-SOME-UFO-SIGHTINGS-2533765

(INTERNATIONAL) -- A new theory about how the rare phenomena of "ball lightning" forms, and the strange propetrties of movement and transformation it displays after formation, may account for some or many UFO sightings.

[snip]

Wu believes his theory has solved the question of how ball lightning forms, and why it exhibits some very unusual properties such as the ability to float through walls or to suddenly appear inside the cabin of a jetliner.

The theory states that ball lightning is formed when lightning strikes generate a "plasma bubble". The bubble is formed this way: as a "regular" lightning bolt reaches the ground, it accelerates electrons rapidly - close to the speed of light - and that causes them in turn to release intense microwave radiation which then "charges the air," resulting in a "spherical plasma bubble" that then traps the radiation for a period of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Did anybody notice the color of the phone in the last scene and how it relates to the matrix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 04:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elliott is holding a bright red phone. Very unusual color for a phone to be. Not to mention it's an old school handset phone.

Old school handset phones remind me of the matrix.

notice how the phone call is Elliott reconnecting back into the virtual world, the real world so speak.

Anyway the red phone reminds me of the choice Neo has to make between the red pill and the blue pill. I think that scene is Elliott choosing the red pill

The red pill and its opposite, the blue pill, are popular culture symbols representing the choice between embracing the sometimes painful truth of reality (red pill) and the blissful ignorance of illusion (blue pill).

The terms, popularized in science fiction culture, are derived from the 1999 film The Matrix. In the film, the main character Neo is offered the choice between a red pill and a blue pill. The blue pill would allow him to remain in the fabricated reality of the Matrix, therefore living the "ignorance of illusion", while the red pill would lead to his escape from the Matrix and into the real world, therefore living the "truth of reality" even though it is a harsher, more difficult life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Testimony in documents allege Joe Paterno knew of child abuse in 1976 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> finally saw "Gone Girl" after rave reviews. Sorry, but the ending was absurd and make no sense whatsoever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so with all of that build up, with that psycho bitch framing her husband for murder Suddenly she shows up with a story about being kidnapped and raped by a completely different dude.

well that dude just so happenned to be rich, he had cameras all over his house, I'm sure he had GPS in his car etc. etc.

In other words all of his actions during the time he was allegedly abducting her could have very easily been tracked. Where exactly was he when she claimed she was being kidnapped and raped by him? I'm talking about that period of time Time when she was staying in that resort when she first disappeared.

The feds didn't track his GPS? They didn't look at the cameras at his lake house? 

I'm sorry just made no sense really whatsoever. I couldn't buy it. It completely ruined my suspension of disbelief.

I'm really surprised more people are bitching about this

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Doyle Square approved:250-room hotel for Monona Terrace, retail and commercial space, 354 apartments and more than 1,000 parking spots just south of the state Capitol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor gets a phone call from his alternate universe father. Freaky stuff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the Phoenicians (Carthaginians) practice institutionalized, regular (100+ per year) ritual human sacrifice of infants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I just watched this short documentary called "blood on the altar" on Amazon. (Free to watch right now if you have Amazon prime)

https://www.amazon.com/dp/B015XFDSDC/ref=atv_hm_hom_2_c_s9obwan_2_3?_encoding=UTF8 pf_rd_i=home pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_p=2524047002 pf_rd_r=V72V73M7BNJHBRJM6814 pf_rd_s=center-4 pf_rd_t=12401

so apparently several ancient Roman and Greek historians claimed that the Phoenicians, more specifically the Carthaginians, practiced institutionalized ritual infant sacrifice.

But many modern historians dismiss these claims as nothing but war propaganda.

In the video they interview 2 Harvard professors who claim that new archaeological evidence shows these sacrifices most likely did happen.

However, they also interviewed in Italian professor who was very very adamant that no human sacrifices ever occurred in the Phoenician culture and it's all just bad propaganda

So what's the deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> help! I'm looking for a good fish sandwich in the State Street/downtown area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a perfectly good fish sandwich in the downtown State Street area. Doesn't have to be phenomenal, acceptable is fine.

Here's my experience so far

Buck   badger: served a perfectly fine fish sandwich with fries. Discontinued.

Nicks: served me a fish sandwich that was rancid. I repeat, it was RANCID!

Hawks: they've got a salmon burger. It's got an overwhelming fishy taste. It's obviously a generic frozen salmon patty. Not interested

Where else can I get a fish sandwich? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a 400 ft. house for sale here in Madison. There are houses with bedrooms bigger than this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 08:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This scientists identified the two genes responsible for tree growth. By manipulating these genes we could have trees that grow crazy fast, and crazy big </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy claims that at 4 yo he saw how his whole life would unfold and that he would live to be 128 yo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an NDE junkie. I've read literally thousands of NDE accounts. This one was just posted last week I have to say it's quite fascinating.

This is NOT me. Everything I know about it is at that link. There's a bit more at the link but not much more




-----------------------------------------------------------------------



http://www.nderf.org/NDERF/NDE_Experiences/bobby_r_nde.htm



 I was 4 years old.  As I recall it was in the summer or fall. I had been having difficulty breathing and in the evening I was taken to the emergency room by my mother and father. This wasn't unusual; I averaged a trip to the hospital at least once every two weeks. On one occasion I distinctly remember listening to a doctor advising my parents to stop caring for me and to let me die, telling that I was not worth taking care of due to the extremeness of my asthma and would be dead by the time I was age 9.

Anyway, I was laying on an examination table, my parents were to the left of me. The door to the room was closed and I was in extreme pain. Every breath felt like burning razors were tearing through my lungs and throat. I don't remember the moment, I stopped breathing; only, all of the pain stopped and I found myself in a vast place.

The air, if you could call it that, was filled with an unearthly white light. The place seemed to expand for all eternity.  I do remember a being of light, God, standing near me. It was looming over me like a great tower of strength, yet radiating only warmth and love. Its first words sent a shock through me, 'Bobby, I'm sorry for the pain this meeting will cause you. When I created the Universe, I put rules and limitations in place. Every time you come here, it changes you, because this is your second time here.  You will remember more than you're supposed to, and it will cause you more pain than you know. You will suffer as no one in your family ever has, and I can't change that.' As those words were spoken, if that's what you could call them, I caught glimpses of my life and felt pride, love, joy, and sadness, all pouring into me. Each images was of me, but from the standpoint of a being standing with me or looking on.

I remember the conversation going on for an eternity, but in reality it only lasted a minute or two at the most. I remember a white light that seemed to pulsate and understanding that it was some kind of extension of God.  It stored the moments of every moment and life.  It allowed a mortal to experience them. If I was to label this, I would call it the Book of Fate, that contains all that has, is, and will be.

Somehow I felt the light from that device and God merge to become one with me. I saw my life, all 128 years of it. I saw my mother die, and me being unable to do anything about it as I had moved away. I saw my sister struggling with depression and worse due to a rape she experienced in her mid 20's. I saw my father die a few years after my mother. I saw a home I'd built for my family, in a place halfway across the country,.  This home was far away from my home.  I also experienced the final moments of my mortal life. I was in a bed, I don't know where, my children and grandchildren were there with me. I remember thinking, 'It's finally done.' I remember feeling a horrible wave of sadness rip through me as I thought of my daughter who had died before me, and then I remember thinking of my wife. (Keep in mind I was 4 years old while experiencing the life experiences of an 128 year old man)  I remembered the night we were married, the room was dimly lit and she was standing in front of me getting undressed. I remember seeing a strand of gray in her hair and then looking back on that moment, realizing how in that moment I had been reborn and everything was worth it. Then I realized I'd be able to see her and my daughter again, and gave into death for the final time.

That wasn't the end though, I was shown the consequences of my life, thousands of people that I'd interacted with and felt what they felt about me, saw their life and how I had impacted them. Next I saw the consequences of my life and the influence of my actions. I saw people reading my books, teaching lessons to children that I had taught them.

I remember waking up confused and trying to deal with everything. For a long time afterwards I struggled to deal with what I saw, every time my mom got sick, I wondered if it was time for her to die. I tried to always be strong, and in time eventually came to blame myself for my mother's oncoming death and sister's oncoming rape. I couldn't deal with the things I had experienced and it took nearly 29 years after this before I could begin to stop blaming myself and accept that I had nothing to do with those things.

At the time of this writing, my sister was raped years ago, she got pregnant and then had a miscarriage. My mom had Alzheimer and stage 7 dementia, and is not expected to last another year. She entered the final stage about the same time I signed up with Teach For America and ended up half way across the country. My father is preparing for my mother's death and working on finding his final home, before it's his turn to die. As for me, I've been teaching for 14 years and have worked with nearly 10,000 children. I've also begun to write a book and the occasional article. I now live halfway across the country and have begun to consider dating.

(Further down the page as an answer to a question he posts this)

 I saw what humanity becomes, and my part in helping that to occur. All I'll say is that we don't go extinct, kill ourselves, or destroy ourselves. It still terrifies and feels me with joy, love and contentment. As a species, we're not remotely ready for that knowledge and I'll take it to my grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a beautiful Japanese blood maple in my yard. Friend told me it's "worth a lot of money." Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 02:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a really nice Japanese blood maple in my front yard. Maybe 18 or 20 feet tall, 15 feet wide. Beautiful deep red/maroon color. Very healthy.

A friend of mine insists this is "worth a lot of money" and I could sell it to somebody.

He doesn't know what he's talking about does he? Can you just sell a tree that is growing in your yard?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am trying to conceptualize the new Jerusalem as explained in Revelation 22. Can you help me out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 15:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the angel showed me the river of the water of life, as clear as crystal, flowing from the throne of God and of the Lamb 2 down the middle of the great street of the city. On each side of the river stood the tree of life, bearing twelve crops of fruit, yielding its fruit every month. And the leaves of the tree are for the healing of the nations. 

Okay so the text says "the tree of life" (singular) stood on "each side" of the river. 

Does that mean a single tree was growing up above the River somehow roots on either side? Like the tree straddled the River?

or maybe in this context "the tree of life" could be thought of as a species of tree. And there could be many trees of life all of the same variety growing all over the new Jerusalem.

Also, I'm not a literalist. I fully understand that interpreting the book of the Revelation is challenging and I don't think anybody has an absolute solid 100% correct answer.

I would just like to hear what other people say about this, as I think it's fun to think about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to James Madison Park beach Memorial weekend: it was utterly, completely, and thoroughly disgusting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the water by the beach was completely revolting. Seaweed, algae, dead fish, garbage, various unidentifiable detritus, etc. etc.

When the waves broke on the beach the water had a sludge like consistency, and was a puke brownish greenish color

some kids actually went out to swim in it, until their mom found an enormous dead fish floating next to them

We have a freaking limnology department right here in the city.

It's actually an embarrassment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traditional Mexican burritos consist of tortilla, meat, and maybe some onion/peppers. So who invented the American "everything but the kitchen sink" style burritos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to Mexico and order a burrito, you get a tortilla with meat and maybe some onions and/or peppers inside. That's it. Rice and beans are ALWAYS served on the side. No salsa, no cheese, inside the burrito etc.

but if you go to just about any American Mexican restaurant and order a burrito you get a tortilla shell with meat, rice, beans, salsa, cilantro, cheese, three different salsas, sour cream, guacamole, leg of lamb, glass of sherry, an Allen wrench, a basketball autographed by Darrell "chocolate thunder" Dawkins etc. etc.

So who invented the "everything and the kitchen sink" style of American burritos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prediction: Rachel saves all of the clones from being killed by you know who </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I predict Evie will attempt to kill all of the clones. She will start first with Sarah and her crew, and then try to kill all of the rest of them

Rachel is the key here. She is the only clone to know what Evie is up to. Even though Sarah put her in a wheelchair, she is still going to figure a way out to alert the rest of the clones that Evie is trying to kill them and basically save their asses, possibly with Ferdinand's assistance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of course we hate Evie Cho, but isn't she basically correct when it comes to the issue of clones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 15:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evie wanted to kill clone program once and for all.

Isn't that a good thing? These clone experiments have produced nothing but agony and misery. Not to mention you are experimenting on human beings without their consent. It's Nazi level experimentation at some point, regardless of all of the ideological BS they throw around.

I mean of course we hate her, but isn't she right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a welder/fabricator in the downtown/Northside/near East area. Google is not helping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 21:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google has several welders/fabricators listed on the north side and near Eastside all of which either don't answer their phone number or the phone number has been disconnected.

I called badger welding supplies and they recommended Mike's prop shop. But that guys all booked up and seems overwhelmed

Recommendations?

also regarding Sector 67- are there people there you can hire to do stuff? Or is it strictly DIY?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idea: Convert part of Central Park into a miniature urban forest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 16:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the new Central Park is an awesome park but it's rather bland, and very much underutilized

My idea is to turn maybe one third of it into a miniature urban forest. This would be the part on the far end opposite the skate park (near Brearley Street).

You would plant trees, but with enough space in between the trees to walk and/or sit and/or have a picnic. The idea would be that as the trees mature eventually the canopies of the trees would all merge together.

 Perhaps have one  small clearing within the miniature forest, perfect for a picnic. All of the walking paths currently there would remain untouched.

What do you think?

https://www.google.com/maps/place/Central+Park,+202+S+Ingersoll+St,+Madison,+WI+53703/@43.083072,-89.3696883,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x8806537106dffa67:0x23da204f4358c43d!8m2!3d43.0831395!4d-89.3672942 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who will deliver burritos to the North Side besides burrito drive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there any other restaurant that will deliver burritos to the Northside besides burrito drive?

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About 40% of my neighbors tree overhangs into my yard, dropping leaves into my gutters and branches onto my roof constantly. Options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> neighbor has this HUMONGOUS and I'm talking giant, maple tree.

It's constantly dropping crap into my yard. In the springtime it's those little whirly birds as well as the left over bud thingies, and of course in autumn its leaves. My gutters constantly getting clogged from this crap. Sometimes it drops small branches onto my roof

what are my options?

If the tree gets trimmed do I have to pay for it? Seems unfair considering it's completely his </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really right-wing America? Your top two choices are a reality show freak fest and a megalomaniacal self-admitted religious fascist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 00:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this really the best that a party that represents 50% of America roughly can do for a general election?

 a reality show freak fest, five ring circus of a sideshow trump.

or a megalomaniacal religious fascist that belongs to a extremist Christian sect that believes the apocalypse is really and truly right around the corner. And that the apocalypse would be the harbinger of the second coming of Jesus, so in many ways it's kind of a good thing.

Like the dude is in an actual doomsday cult! 

And this is the best you Republicans can come up with? I'm not complaining about the REPUBLICAN PLATFORM! Believe whatever you want to believe. But the ***character and the nature*** of these people you nominate I find utterly abhorent.

I have to believe that 50% of America  can do a little better than this!

Come on people!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Acme up 23% after early rave reviews of its new tunnel system. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 19:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acme Corporation is up 23% after rave early reviews of its just introduced virtual tunneling system technology. I've been looking at this stock for a while and am attempted to jump in now.

What are your thoughts here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Amyloid plaque is probably NOT the cause of Alzheimer's, current very convincing research shows iron deposits in the brain are almost certainly the number one suspect. Amyloid plaque is found in the brains of Alzheimer's patients, and people with no memory problems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edge of Tomorrow (Tom Cruise): 1. Actually pretty good movie! 2. Can somebody explain the ending? maybe I'm dumb but there's something that doesn't make sense to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 23:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> first of all this was a better movie than I thought it would be. Totally worth seeing!

Secondly the ending was a bit confusing to me, and perhaps I just missed something really obvious? I don't know. Feel free to point out if I am being an idiot

Two things about the ending

1. So these mimics are incredibly intelligent, with insane reaction speeds, and even seem to be able to affect time and space.

But when Tom Cruise drops a bunch of hand grenades on the Omega, it eats it up like it's a delicious snack. How stupid is that? Why doesn't it realize they are hand grenades and don't eat that?

2. At the very end Tom cruise goes back to being a major, and everybody acts very deferential to him. In this timeline is he considered a hero of the war? If so how could that be? 
I mean in the final timeline of the movie, was it known that Tom Cruise was the man who killed the chief mimic thingy and therefore won the war?

I guess I don't understand how we go from the scene where he kills the thing, is killed himself, the bad ass full metal chick is also killed, but suddenly he wakes up in the current timeline with the war being over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royster Corners Project: Millions spent removing contaminated dirt, which was replaced with More contaminated dirt! At least a $400,000 mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 17:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pierces/Willy Street co-op Update: Crater filled parking lot is latest snag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 00:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's the latest on Pierce's grocery closing and the possibility of Willy Street opening up a third shop there

First of all Willy Street is THE ONLY interested party in that location at the moment.. There are no other suitors.

Secondly, the owner of that complex is notoriously cheap. Has been an issue for years. Will do anything he can to get out of upgrading and/or fixing glaring problems.

So Willy Street co-op made a demand that they will not rent that space unless the owner resurfaces the parking lot. Given that it currently looks like Falluja circa 2005 it's a completely reasonable demand.

so owner of the complex has been trying to get some kind of financial help from the city and/or a cheap loan or what have you to fix the parking lot.

So basically everything is still up in the air. Pierce's will be closed within the month either way regardless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How about a enormous parking ramp above John Nolan with a beautiful 6 acre park on top that pays for itself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you click on the link the guys got all kinds of great ideas for making Madison economically vibrant as well as really accessible and beautiful.

 Now in his 80s, Peters still dreams of a much different Downtown and Isthmus. In November, I wrote about Peters plan to build a parking ramp above John Nolen Drive with a beautiful six acre park on top. The park would be paid with real estate impact fees. The city would borrow $12.5 million for the ramp, but Peters and his associates would pay it back by renting out the parking spaces at $140 a month. The cost to the taxpayer would be zero.

http://host.madison.com/wsj/opinion/column/mitch-henck-kenton-peters-offers-real-vision-for-downtown/article_c30da433-38e9-5ba8-b797-ca6dcc50336b.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Willy Street co-op set up a special email for feedback regarding opening up a store at the current pierces location. If you care it's important! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 19:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Willy Street co-op set up a special email for feedback regarding opening up a new location where pierces is off of Sherman Avenue.

a big part of their decision to open up a store there is from feedback from current and/or potential customers. So if you care, please send an email, even if it's only one or two sentences long. Every email is being read and all the feedback is being compiled.

Thirdstore@WillyStreet.coop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day six: skin is excreting crazy amounts of oil . (X-post from r/fasting) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 18:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on day six of a fast. Mostly water, but I have been sipping on a little Gatorade here and there. No food.

Feel great. Energetic, alert, sleeping less etc.

One crazy thing is the amount of oil that is exuding from my skin. Mostly on the face and my scalp. In fact it's almost all the face and the head

Last night I took a shower scrub down my head and face really well, and then hit it with some isopropyl alcohol to dry it out

This morning my face feels like somebody slathered coconut oil all over it

Anybody else experienced anything like this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
