<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1105</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 05:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still available?

P.S. Would you be willing to do 75%? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Hart first place was 28k and and second was 22k. Third was far behind at 9k. First placer ALWAYS scores around that high in solo raid. Scopely needs to make more prestige levels just for this person lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good places to eat at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! It'll be my first time visiting Bangkok for five days in October and I'm a huge foodie. What are some places you can recommend? I know street food is huge there so I'll definitely try them out. If there are some in particular that are especially good please let me know!

P.S. I've got a huge sweet tooth too so dessert place suggestions are more than welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a coincidence! Me too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for responding! I'm actually from the Philippines so I'm familiar with bibingka! :) it's definitely one of my favorite delicacies!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely! The 5* tokens are so hard to come by. Hopefully the positive feedback on the Telltale tokens will encourage Scopely to do more of these. I certainly would benefit from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I was referring to the Telltale tokens, saying that it could really help players who don't spend real money to build their teams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a salted egg dessert recipe they can share? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 11:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I've been wanting to come up with a salted egg dessert recipe for a while now, something unique and different. I know there's a lot of salted egg buns and croissants popping out and wish to make something else. Ideas I've thought of are salted egg ice cream and salted egg donuts, so if anyone has some foolproof recipes I can use I will be so thankful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just scanned the QR code and added you!

P.S. Are you Filipino by any chance (I know some people with the same surname)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Scopely decides to make more events like this. Could really use f2p players build their teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well both of those are pretty decent 5*s! I'm still trying to farm the tokens now but I'm barely getting them. Gonna keep my fingers crossed for another good 5*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are the other 5*s you got? I wanted a Blue Kenny or Ben! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 10:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! He's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 09:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! It's me again. Hope you don't mind. We got his blood test results back and his total CK is at 801 U/L and apparently the normal range is at 30-170. ESR is at 20mm/hr. What does this entail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11th. We've done better. More importantly, I only got 5k Telltake tokens! Soooooo frustrated! :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. The best I got was 5* Clem. And I've done almost 20 single pulls. Maybe I should have done 10s too. Congrats!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 08:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! I could use a human shield Lee *hint hint Scopely* Fingers crossed we get the most out of the Telltale token crates!

We have a lot of newer members this time around and it sucks because they don't listen to directives. They're more concerned with scoring points and getting mvp than taking towers and totally ignore us when we call them out and send them private messages. One long-time member even went rogue and started repairing when we clearly said no repairs then ignored us completely lmao. It's been painful, really.

How do you have enough space for all the members? Our leader turned down another merge with a new faction composed of 10 members all in the top 100. He refuses to let go of people and just take 20 to satisfy the merge. Loyalty is a big thing in my faction but sometimes I wish we were stricter. We've been far too lax with our members. I totally would have gone with the merge. Sadly I'm not as happy as I was before when I first joined. When I started out I was low-leveled and super active and seeing all the higher ups made me try harder. Now it seems I'm the one who tries the hardest and is the most active it sucks. I've considered switching factions but it's all just too much of a hassle :/

P.S. Best of luck in war! I hope you kick your opponents' butts!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade #1 completed with /u/grimmz77

PayPal for iTunes
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM sent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently reading **The Rose and the Dagger** by Renee Ahdieh. I'm more than halfway through and it seems I liked the first book much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 04:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright. I'll try to experiment. I wish I had a good strong character. I really don't have anything decent against fast characters. How are you doing this war? I'm just happy to place above 15th for telltale tokens. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 04:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you consider PayPal at $40? Let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Now I'm kinda gearing towards aiming for 2nd place for the raid refills :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] $30 PayPal [W] $40 iTunes (US) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new here so no rep to show as of now. I'm willing to go first though. 

Wouldn't mind trading with different people in parts so long as I get to at least $40. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 04:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your consideration. Appreciate it! Let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not certain as I'm not from the US, sorry. I just have a US account to be able to download apps that aren't available in my country yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple store gift cards are exclusively for the Apple store, sadly. I can't use it for other purposes like iTunes/App store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 17:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/subject1105 GCX Rep Profile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Redditor since March 11, 2016
* If you have been linked to this page, please make sure that you're on the real /r/GCXRep, and the user who linked you was indeed me, and not someone with a similar username trying to impersonate me. Note that just because you're reading this doesn't mean a scammer didn't include this note in their fake profile to trick you into a false sense of security. Double check, and don't get tricked or scammed! 
* Second profile :https://www.reddit.com/r/GCXRep/comments/5r5r26/usubject1105_gcx_rep_profile/?st=j2crsqf6 sh=4565afb3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 03:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I got her too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got Molly, 2 Chucks, and enough 4* weapon tokens to get me an Olivia and a Chad. Don't give up! You still have 6 days to get what you want! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! I would love a Kenny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me 8 pulls to get my 5* fast Clem. Now I'm at my 14th and have mostly gotten trainers and recruit/weapon tokens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood. My dad still has some x-ray and blood test results to wait for and we'll go back to his doctor then. Thank you for taking the time to answer my questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for responding! Yes, this is the MRI of my father who is 55 years old. I feel like I understood your explanation, but just to be sure, there is nothing to worry about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. If only I hadn't been asked to clean I would've landed top 5 for sure. I got 5,000 tokens from the single open though. I got 300 5* tokens from it. I also got 4* Fast Clem today. Will Clem be a good defense leader for my team? 4* Jesus, Abe, and Andrea and a 5* Lori?

Or I could use 4* Clem too? I also got a 4* Molly so I have enough for a full fast time. I wanna integrate my 5* blue Lori and red Abe though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the meaning of this MRI result? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 11:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mild diffuse parenchymal volume loss. The degree of ventriculomegaly is somewhat disproportionately more prominent in relation to the degree of peripheral parenchymal volume loss. This is of uncertain etiology, but is suspected to be due to disproportionate degree of central parenchymal volume loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 11:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What region are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very rare though. Fingers crossed for more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/u7NpCTo

Hart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 09:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UGHHHH I had enough refills to place 3rd to 5th but I was at my internship and the executive chef was in a bad mood and asked us to clean the chillers and freezers when we weren't doing anything (and I was raiding)!!! So I didn't have enough time and just landed at 6th!! I am so pissed :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! You're always so lucky! :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep at it! I got 5* fast Clem on my 8th pull so it really takes time for some. I'm probably at my 14th pull now and nothing else good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 11:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 08:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to place high too but I'm not sure if I will have enough refills for it. Right now I'm just trying to sit at the top 10 and then go all out tomorrow if I think I have a shot at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 06:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. They were so much easier to get during the first day, and then Scopely patched the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 06:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eep I wouldn't want a Vernon either... Some comments above state that you can get more than just one. I've lurked the Scopely forums and saw one person post a screenshot of their pull. They pulled 3 at once and got a Lily and another 5* recruit (I forgot who lol). Here's hoping we have better luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want them both too! Plus Blue Kenny and Human Shield Lee. I was thinking of using Clem for my defense team actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on your blue Kenny! Really wanna pull him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they patched it yesterday and the tokens dropped less. Fingers crossed we get an even better 5*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know there's a chance for more than just one epic. Wishing you better luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
