<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5027</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up until he gets uber religious it is phenomenal. Brilliant soul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where to go now though. Where do the aggressive perfectionists flock that's healthy at all? Where do the manic personalities go if not to some other hellish industries. 
Part of me wants to agree with you. But while I watch my friends age into menial positions in bland cubicles and I get to enjoy my music loud and my daily inspirations in action it's hard to look at it so black and white. You had many good years, some will have none of that, menial dedication, no pressure, no satisfaction. I'm not sure I can agree with you so easily even as I age and question my career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good toilet paper
Nice bed sheets
Quality food

Everybody gonna eat, poop, and sleep eventually. I also recommend an air filtration unit but depends on where you live I reckon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this subreddit has some of the worst comment sections I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree, the random butt plug would be far more startling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here for this also, stayed for the shart comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have to agree. A few of you sound like real company men, and no one is asking you for moral guidance here, the guy wants a fat ass TV. Pass on your advice and shut it.  Also OP check for floor model changeovers. Eventually a newer model will replace a display product and the display can be purchased at drastically reduced prices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The presidential position </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem a cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough but I think their current state will be their future as well haha either that or my mom is going to give me one for Christmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah yeah.... That's it see, second edition, hot off the press I swear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. No majesty involved, big box warehouse store worth multi millions with a bunch of underpaid unconcerned millennials stocking shelves and shrugging as I buy my milk and cookies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best lpt I've read in a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irony for sale, twenty two bucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or when you run out of mega men in Sonic's final fantasy, totes brahski </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost. Have you no shame madam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest edition to my gaming den! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *snaps fingers sassily* Oh no you didddnttt. 

Yes. Yes you are correct. My bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current favorite is toaster. Let's trade for a week, report back here, insultors awayyyyy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're ten pounds of shit in a five pound bag.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's how you pretend to be involved and knowledgeable on subject matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8500 too many views. That was the worst song I've heard in a long time. And a time-lapse video is just really not interesting in this context for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must be talking to hear his own voice (so to speak). As much of Reddit is alas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the fact that every major authority including its builders call it a "nuclear-powered ballistic missile submarine" means it's not a nuclear sub? Huh, imagine that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Granted but it went back up in price by double. Even if it was just a sale, sorry to hear you think seventy dollar controllers are a good idea bub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can they remake this movie for the eighth time with all Black characters with disabilities please. It's only fair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha really now. Again. Somebody living under a rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freeze his shoes in a cambro of water. Removed the shoe Ice block and put it on his station for his arrival. Then punch em in the mouth and do a shot of whiskey together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the morning crew wishes you well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *you're </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let the boss relax yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've got nothing, hurry up and do it if you're gonna do it bitch" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Lord have you people no sense of humor or chef life? Lighten the fuck up losers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a cooper sunny platitude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, It's fifteen years ago.  That's not nostalgia. Maybe for a twenty year old but they're still snot nosed children for the most part if you ask me. I don't speak to anyone under twenty five without a baby voice and tickling their belly. Works great at parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog city, with Ace Heart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Yes I do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Don't trump this up kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is estimation. Call and ask for a reading before you pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody post the video where he gets knocked the fuck out in one punch like a bitch for running his mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morton's kosher salt baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a war lad. An all out war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just wanted to show the other side of the rare great potoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legit, punch a server because his steak was too meaty.  There was an altercation that led up to the punch but it was all over, no shit, steak was too meaty. Made the papers here years back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember eating a fucking legend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have to agree. While initially mutations will exist you have to keep in mind Chernobyl happened very recently compared to the timeframe given for fallout lore. Don't get me wrong there are issues to critique, but on this topic it's very unlikely first generation mutations survive, let alone procreate. They are much more likely (like Chernobyls) to die, young, and tragically if we're being honest.

The fev of course makes more sense, but I think ghoulification is a huge stretch, and might merit your specific concern on mutations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you haven't saved in insomnia new game plus will put you next to the beds save point in insomnia, that's what happened to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an Earthbound on my local Kijiji for 200 bucks I'll check if it's still there if you're interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you having a seizure? Do you need assistance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll build my own fallout, with blackjack, and hookers, in fact, forget the fallout! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The formula of Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha a fine point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Include a receipt for these posts dbags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm pretty sure his name was meant to be Malaka. Username checks out in that case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up and take my upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the developer notes saying it has to do with a minimum distance in between each habitat required so in multiplayer games people can't just build in your immediate space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mistake my downvote as butt hurt so much as your joke is old and dated to the point of no repair, like your mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you supposed to taste the fucking meat?? Somebody needs to remember good food is better than good gimmicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this over a week ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can die with people if you want but I'll be happier to keep living thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Quit and stop wasting everyone's time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorgeous
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are actually "that terrible". If you need to describe food as not "that" bad, fuck off and have some standards. And it's false economy. A mind set like yours is that which allows this shit to continue.

 It's substantially cheaper pound for pound in the long run to make your own mashed potatoes.  People are paying for a night out and shelling out their hard earned money for food they expect something of. If you'll proudly march the box of mash out to the table and ask them for their money I might consider this less than total bullshit. But no. I won't. Your opinion is not "that" awful but it is definitely awful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This does not seem wise. Take the fucking car back yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 best comment in thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his suggestion was you'll know fascism when you see it. And they are not subject to a fascist state comparatively </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause we ain't bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask Reddit's with more comments than upvotes. Come on people, if you like it then like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trogdor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're rational. I like your style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely disagree. There's a significant amount of repetition but I don't see why they wouldn't throw it in for the sake of users who do want it. Doesn't seem like a hard ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially seasonal reasonable seasoning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone talking terrorist shit and I'm just glad to see two gay lovers openly showing they can't grow a beard, but they're still gonna subject is to the pubic hair they've glued to their face.
And the guy on the left, even if you were a failed abortion that face still looks good to your Loverboy, congratulations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fuck those guys. You safe. Add honestly it's illegal to punch those kids in the mouth too but I'd be alright with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? The new half life isn't out yet??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand to a degree. But I feel that knowing it's fiction doesn't stop you from starting the game all together? Knowing they never existed doesn't stop you from investing into the story. As with all fiction you just suspend belief from time to time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 09:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loving the slight Orange tint to her face, really helps her elbow frame her tattered hole ridden soul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your time and wait for deals. You really don't need much that bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answering this question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One where families are in seperate rooms with glass walls between them. They are fed through a slotted hole similar to prison, and given a curtain around both shower and toilet. But overall it is very open and very visible to the adjacent family. Each family has two parents and two children. They can not hear the family in the next room but they can not avoid seeing them for long.
After two weeks the youngest child of each family is rotated to the next adjacent room, all moving down the line to a new family. At first it's an experiment to see how others treat strangers welcomed into their family knowing they are being judged similarly to those who have their youngest child.
Within four weeks though, you stop feeding the families... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick Google search brings up dozens of models of this style of "axe" or guitbox, bass or stringamajig. My friend had a similar bass that was white years before the show ever emerged. It's possible it's a nod, hard to tell tell because these styled guitars have been famously played since the seventies.  Generally it's a one sided axe, brought into prominence by KISS but double sided axes are available and commonplace. I'm not a fan. But I'm a huge fan of regular Show. 
Mordecai and Rigby we will miss you. Hamboning saved my life. Hmmm hmmm hmmm hmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nine vulvae in a shoebox.

Who wants to start a band? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cat chew envelope Mike blow any mother villianaires </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that woman doesn't look too old to abort herself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presuming I don't know the year because I just woke up like normal ... I'd Google the same thing I google every morning, phat ass HD porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dental plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not even. Just normal or whatever the top difficulty is, I shouldn't say hard since I don't think any final fantasy had a hard mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ifrit was a real fight though. That was a good time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude fuck off, that's your opinion. And we both know the wire was way better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "cats meow" in the background. 10/10 would recommend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A valid thought. But I went in at recommended level on hard and while it was a challenge to get to ardyn, he himself was a literal joke. The end scene where you have to push the QuickTime o was just as difficult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> **SPOILERS** Let's talk about that final fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there was a lot that kept me from loving this to the point I've loved other Final Fantasy's but by the end I was fully drawn into the story, the gameplay, and even the characters (despite not watching the movies). But, and this may not get me any friends here, I have to say, the last Battle required zero skill and felt ridiculously "on rails". I legitimately can't recall fighting an easier boss... perhaps in my entire life? The creatures outside the Citadel were significantly more difficult and the threat of dying was at least real. I know I'm not the only one who noticed this so what does everyone think of having such an "on rails" end boss?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking tell us OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The unibrow in the back though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it? You're lucky they don't withhold your last pay depending on the laws in your area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn Spanish asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're not. No organization like that would hide success </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that woman in the picture eating them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Challenging??? It's an on rails walk through </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And also, eat Snickers. It's greaaaattt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know they do and is the best you got, triggered? Are you as just spouting whatever Justin Beiber does? Not that there's anything wrong with your choice of life just try to pull the dick out of your mouth before you go running it cupcake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ffxv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick it to the man. And play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about how it's clearly In new Jersey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't you just the kind of person who should have ended up crusted into your dad's belly button rather than ever meeting that egg. But thanks for coming along and proving people still deserve a punch in the mouth now and then lil Missy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo, get off the stage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha you're alright </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't recall asking for bigger games, or better graphics. In fact I'm sure a lot of people could easily point to the indie game movement exploding as evidence that you are speaking out of your ass kind madam. And also I don't make my bed, so let's all sit back and enjoy a refreshing Gatorade. Gatorade, it's there when you need it. *Stare at camera, wink sophisticated like* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little statue, maybe a plastic bobblehead if we're lucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very easily I would imagine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally more than a hug. Give em the ol military grade reach around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate, hunger, bzzzrrr whirrr *--* can not compute rest of sentiment *--* bzz whirr boing *--* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The greatness of a nation can be judged by the way itsanimalsare treated." - Gandhi-
Interesting fact about this quote, he said it while playing a sick Metallica solo and boot stomping kittens, the more you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha this made me laugh. I like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
