<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3600</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 16:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It requires quiet and concentration, plus a strong belief that it will work.

You'll need any pretty little satchet or bag, finely woven to keep from shedding the ingredients, daffodil stems or petals, lavender, star anise, and sage, plus black salt. If you can't acquire any of these items, you can substitute them for an herb you like more. It's always been more about willpower than ingredients, anyway. (My favorite way to make black salt is with finely ground sea salt and incense ash. It will be more brown/gray in color, but it smells wonderful, and is the same.)

With the items before you, imagine yourself inside a large white circle, with all evil things and bad thoughts burning away. Place your gatherings in your satchet and pray or ask for safety and protection. When done, close the bag, and imagine your white circle dissipating into your protection satchet. It will glow in your mind.

Carry the bundle with you to repel negative energy. Squeeze for an extra boost of power.

*I hate that I have to say this, but this little bundle is for energy and bad spirits, not bullets, knives, or bad decisions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Grandmother and Dead Cousin Dave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day Sallys husband came home, we were comforting her over having lost him to a work accident.

Itd been a long day. Wake, funeral, catering for the family gathering after we laid Dave to rest, meal prepping for Sal so she could sleep, eat, and mourn as was proper, and then cleaning up. We were on the last step when there came a knock at the door.

Id learned my lesson some years before, so I let someone else answer it, and continued drying the dishes my mom handed me. It was mindless work, and it helped lessen the sad thought of losing Dave, the first of Sallys husbands Id actually liked.

Aunt Brenda patted Sals arm, and went to the door. Brenda screamed when she saw whod knocked. I nearly dropped the plate I held, when I turned to look.

Dave stood on the doormat, smiling. Seem to have lost my keys. He glanced around Brenda and saw me at the sink. Hey Jo! The whole family here? Whats the occasion? As he turned his gaze to me, the right side of his head came into view, or rather what was left of it. The skull, right above the temple, had caved in, a rather nasty result of letting an I-beam fall onto it.

Brenda fainted, and my grandmother stepped right over her and out of the house, pulling Dave with her and shutting the door.

I dried my hands on my apron, double checking the pockets for the little herb packet wed made last week of daffodils stems, clover leaves, black salt, and sage, a handy aid against possession, and bad thoughts. Before stepping outside, I grabbed the regular salt from above the stove. 

No one else in the house moved, except Sal, who tried to ask what was going on, since she couldnt see the door from the couch. I pointed at her as I left, and my mom went to distract her.

Outside, Dave argued with my grandmother, who remained calm. You cant tell the dead that theyre dead straight out. You have to coax them into the realization, or the shock can cause a nasty haunting.

Why Cousin Dave still hung around around was quite a mystery, but he seemed more upset that no one had been there to pick him up from the ER.

I waited for days outside that hospital, Maggie! Where the hell was Sally? I thought for sure someone at work would tell her to come get me!

Do you remember why you were at the hospital, Dave? my grandmother asked gently.

Work accident, knocked my noggin good, but the doc patched me up quick, and then I waited for a long ass time shooting the breeze, thinking surely my wife would turn up, but she couldnt be bothered. I walked all the way home and Im out of smokes!

You walked forty-three miles from the hospital? my grandmother questioned him.

Mustve, since Im here, and couldnt catch a ride with my thumb out for nothing.

Dave, what happened at work? What knocked you in the head?

You can read it in the workmans comp report Im gonna file on Monday. Right now, I wanna speak to my wife. He turned to the house and my grandmother caught his arm.

Dave, hon, wait. Her voice hitched a bit, losing its calm. Sally is really upset over the accident. I think if you can explain it to me, maybe shell feel better, and be happy to see you. She stalled him.

I stepped closer, and he looked at me. For a moment, there was a strange feral look on his face, not human, but he came back quickly. I tried to ignore the gaping bloody hole in his head, but squished brain matter and a fragmented skull are tough to look away from.

Look, ifn I tell ya what happened, will ya give me a smoke and let me see Sal?

I snatched a pack of lights from the stoop, left by some mourner earlier. Tell us first, and then Ill hand em over. I waggled the pack, and his eyes lit up.

Deal. I was walking the factory, headed to lunch, when I heard a snap and looked up. I-beam chain had broken from the lead and the whole thing was coming down. I dodged and knocked my head on the conveyor. Rode in an ambulance to the hospital, got checked out, walked home. Smoke? He put his hand out.

You dodged? my grandmother prodded.

He paused, thinking. Yeah, I mean, the beam was falling, and I moved...wait. His brow creased. Wait His outstretched hand rose to his jaw, fingers feeling along his skin to his temple. His nails plunged into his head and dug deep into the viscera. I...I...I...wait.

I felt sick, stomach revolting at the disgusting sight of seeing a man touch his own brain. I dropped the smokes on the patio, and tried not to heave.

Daves mood changed as he went through the stages of grief. It was so clear on his face. But he bypassed acceptance and returned to anger. Shit.

Back up, my grandmother ordered, grabbing my arm and dragging me off the concrete into the grassy yard. 

Daves face grew darker and darker as he looked at the fallen smokes. His fingers dropped from his head wound, dragging blood and brain bits down his face and work shirt. He began to shake, hands twitching, as realization of his death took hold.

Then he laughed suddenly. Am I dead?

My grandmother nodded.

Well, shit. He cursed, raced to the door, kicking it in with supernatural force. SALLY! he roared.

Well, shit, my grandmother echoed. You wanna handle it, or should I?

Hes all yours, I said, hands up.

She sighed. Next time its your turn. 

Rolling back her sleeves, she marched into the house. People had started screaming at the sight of dead cousin Dave. Sally was the loudest, with her OH SHITS and WHAT THE HELL KINDA JOKE IS THIS. There was a scuffling noise over the shrieking, a few plates broke, and then my grandmother was back, dragging Dave by his shirt. She tossed him straight into the dirt. His smushed brain matter sloshed about in his head, and I was suddenly very glad shed taken this one.

He growled in the dirt, eyes dull and animalistic. Whatever part of his brain remained intact had gone feral.

A feral ghost becomes a ghoul if left unattended. Capable of nothing but destruction and terror, dead cousin Dave didnt deserve that fate. Hed start by eating Sally, and anyone else that got in the way, and possibly rampaging along the neighbors farms and woods before the souls hed consumed twisted him into some boogeyman that rednecks hunted on Big-Foot documentaries. Hed eat them, too.

I handed my grandmother the salt from my apron and she it chucked it at him. It bounced off his chest, spilling everywhere. His body fizzled, smoke drifting up, and he came back suddenly, focusing. Salt, the almighty cleanser.

Now, Maggie, listen, he protested. I deserve to see Sally

My grandmother ignored him, as she muttered under her breath, and stretched out her arm to me. I stepped over and took her hand. Together, we worked to send Mr. David Michael Willis to a better place.

Sally hit the threshold of the kitchen door then. Seeing her smoking husband covered in copious amounts of salt stopped her. Oh, that explains it, she said. Dont worry, honey. Im getting a helluva settlement from your work. Ill be fine! You be good, ya hear? She waved farewell to her husband sadly and retreated back inside, probably for the vodka shed stashed in the pantry earlier.

Theres no door, no lightshow, for a spirit that doesnt want to leave. It becomes a feat of willpower to push them across to the other realm. At some point, they generally realize its for the best, and complete the journey on their own.

Not dead cousin Dave. He dug his hands into the grass, and fought us every inch of the way. At some point, I considered kicking him in the head, just to break his grip on the ground.

Finally, after long moments of wishing him gone, his legs faded, dissolving away. He gave up hope then, knowing hed lost, and looked at us. Sorry for the trouble. Tell Sally I love her.

I nodded, and the wind kicked up. Dave fell in on himself, before he vanished. The breeze blew the salt across the yard.

Well, that was a struggle, I muttered, taking a deep breath.

My grandmother clapped her hands together. Touching him was like holding a live wire.

Howd you do that anyway? Ghosts arent solid.

Lots of practice, she replied.

 Together, we stepped back into the house and over Brenda, still on the floor. The kitchen door closed, dead cousin Dave found peace, and I found that I didnt hate the taste of vodka.

Years later, we laugh at the story, but his sloshing brain pan still makes me queasy. I have no wish to ever see it again.

[Heres to you, Cousin Dave. Dont come back.](http://fb.com/subject3600writing)




[Story 1: My Grandmother Was a Witch] (https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/55o192/my_grandmother_was_a_witch)   
[Story 2: My Grandmother and the Rabbit Man](https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/55uaj9/my_grandmother_and_the_rabbit_man)   
[Story 3: Things My Grandmother Taught Me](https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/560k6z/things_my_grandmother_taught_me)
[Story 4: My Grandmother Isn't in This One](https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/566swv/my_grandmother_isnt_in_this_one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
