<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In another universe, two bartenders walk into a chemist. The first one says "I'll have some H20". The second one says "I'll have some H20, too". The chemist looks really confused and asks "Why don't you just ask for water?" to which the bartenders say "NOW YOU KNOW HOW WE FEEL!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smith being Smith.

Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things I Can't Believe You've Done

\#1: This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those comments on the Borg, yet not a single one about HAL 9000?

[Ummm...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O0TQbRNmYus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 13:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, for CRYING OUT LOUD!

And EX-222 was going to be my first planet name, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodshirt - Blowing Dirt [Alternative Rock] A New Zealand one-take-video wonder from 5 years before OK Go's "Here It Goes Again" hit the scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 05:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #HailAshman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 14:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Namekian - Tallest and heaviest


Lv. 95


HP - 54


Ki - 54


Stamina - 54


Basic Attacks - 60


Strike Supers - 0


Ki Supers - 60


Supers: Gravity Impact, God of Destruction's Anger, Big Bang Attack, and Maximum Charge


Ultimates: Giant Storm and Sphere of Destruction


Clothes: Full New Hide Battle Costume set


Accessory: Tagoma's Scouter


Z-Soul: Bwa ha ha... Thanks for the energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 04:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reckon it'll be the other way around. Ivan Ooze will be used to sweep Azalea Gym and Dwandelyn will fall prey to Whitney.

Not her Miltank, though. Oh, no; my money's on her Clefairy's Metronome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 01:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low-quality rendition of popular 80's movie montage song? Check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 03:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of Kubrick in these comments. I love it.

Here's my entry: [Kong on the bomb](https://cdn.thingiverse.com/renders/57/82/8a/92/f7/bye-bye-major-kong_preview_featured.jpg) from "Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb" (1963)

EDIT: inb4 "It was released in 1964." I know. But it was made and was going to be released in 1963. That's how I roll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was an alcoholic for seven years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today marks my eighth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 05:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. I did the whole thing in capitals so that people wouldn't miss it.

The case sensitive translation of the code is **Vault 16 Radio Beacon** which will give you the correct sequence upon encoding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do us a favour and tell Vault 16 to keep to themselves. We've got enough trouble to deal with on the surface as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **THE STRING OF RANDOM LETTERS, NUMBERS AND SYMBOLS IN THE TITLE IS A PHRASE IN BASE 64.**

**THE PHRASE READS "VAULT 16 RADIO BEACON".** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Query: if it was proven that consciousness does not possess physical dimension of its own, how would being able to visualise multi-dimensional objects and scenes in a non-dimensional space be explained?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 12:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, I'm not saying this video isn't a completely astonishing, well-edited nostalgia trip.

All I'm saying is that when Disney and anything Daft Punk collide, I expect some TRON Legacy to appear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 08:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a big, fun, well-written movie.

One problem: how the hell did the Franklin, an old Federation ship, barely able to hold a candle to the systems of the Enterprise, manage to navigate the massive debris field of the nebula without being destroyed?

9/10, could definitely watch the theatrical release again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 02:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You can't poison a poison."

Give it a few months, boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah, like THAT will ever happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current population of the Earth is about 7.438 billion people


If all of the planets in NMS were divided among 7.438 billion people, each person would get a little over 2.48 billion planets each.


If 1 person discovered 1 planet per second of all the planets assigned to them, it would take nearly 79 years for that person to discover them all.


**And to think there are people worried that No Mans Sky will die out in the near future.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a few random factoids for you:

If every planet in No Man's Sky was sequentially named using the letters of the alphabet (A, AB, BA, ABC, ACB, BCA, BAC, CAB, CBA, etc.), you would need every combination of A through to T plus roughly 31.343798694713145830399% of all combinations of A through to U to name all of the planets with a unique combination without repetition of sequence or double letters.

Additionally, the average human genome (the genetic material of an organism), when visually sequenced, is roughly 3.2 billion letters long. If every planet in NMS was assigned one of the four specific letters that are used in genome sequencing (A, G, C, T), there would be enough letters to sequence the genomes of over 5.75 billion people, or roughly the population of Earth in 1996. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 10:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the closest thing to my real name Smith has ever said.

I'll let you figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Character customisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 10:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dislike the LACK of evolution of Tauros to Bouffalant and Luvdisc to Alomomola. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 07:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me the Sinnoh badges are musical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a mouse, but a dagger.

You're drinking embalming fluid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with a bang, but a 'click'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 12:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refulgence?

Could've gone with Insvatic instead, as this fusion is clearly Thu-Fi-Zer from the manga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 12:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there, CE3K reference. I was wondering how far down I had to go to find you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 14:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butterscotch schnapps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 07:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except it's not canon, and the beginning of the [article for the game on Wookiepedia](http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Star_Wars:_The_Force_Awakens) clearly states that, not to mention that no material added to flesh out a story in any Lego game has ever been considered canon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Theory] Kylo Ren is the best pilot in the galaxy...and he knows it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 03:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets look at the facts.


His grandfather, Anakin Skywalker, was considered one of the greatest pilots around. He was the only human podracer due to being Force-sensitive, blew up a Trade Federation battleship at a young age and displayed his talent for flying through a war zone to save Chancellor Palpatine only to safely crash-land a half-destroyed dreadnought onto Coruscant. As Kylo is a Vader fanatic, theres a chance that, in order to be greater than Vader, he would continuously hone his flying skills.


His uncle, Luke Skywalker, also became somewhat of a prestigious pilot after he helped destroy the first Death Star. He avoided cannon fire, TIE Fighters and even his own father to, without guidance equipment but by way of the Force, launch the photon torpedoes at exactly the right time into the vent that caused the chain reaction to blow it up. Sure, he got shot down during the Battle of Hoth, but he displayed aptitude on a speeder bike during the Battle of Endor. Luke probably told him the story about the first Death Star which may or may not have given him the drive to try and do something just as prestigious as his mentor.


Then you have his father, the legendary smuggler and celebrated pilot Han Solo, Corellian captain of the Millennium Falcon. Corellians are known for being reckless and daring alongside being considered fantastic pilots, and theres a saying that Corellians have rocket fuel for blood. No doubt Han would have trained Kylo back when he was still Ben Solo to assist in flying the Falcon at a young age.


**Kylo Ren is a half-Corellian, Force-sensitive human with great pilots in his lineage, was most likely taught by Han Solo to fly, possesses a drive to be better than his grandfather and his mentor AND there seems to be a hint of both respect and mocking when he interrogates Poe Dameron and says I had no idea we had the best pilot in the Resistance on board as though hes really saying Youre a good pilot, but not as good as me.**


*Please, God; give us a dogfight between Poe and Kylo in the upcoming episodes.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One spreadsheet in Microsoft Excel 2016 has 17,179,869,184 total cells.


If you were to use Microsoft Excel 2016 to compile a database of the names of every planet in No Man's Sky with one name per cell, you would need exactly 1,073,741,824 complete spreadsheets to list them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 13:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lud-e-coli </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 11:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, considering that Trott IS comfortable with anything and everything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 13:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm...Red Dead Rivalry? Red Dead Resistance?  Red Dead Reclamation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 06:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the butt plug asks "I have to deal with THIS shit too?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 05:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there existed a Pokemon world where most, if not all Pokemon exhibited power and behaved in the same way as their Pokedex entries state, would that world be able to maintain a balanced ecosystem in which people can live in comfortably, or would the world be too chaotic for a human presence to sustain themselves in?


EDIT: Think about THIS one, /u/supjace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 05:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're unique

As no-one in their right mind

Would do the same.....DAMN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any of the Babylon Club scenes in Scarface (1983). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this statement, albeit it in a small capacity.

Yes, I can understand that the high volume of these types of par-for-the-course jokes can be a bit much for the relevant audience, but it is up to said audience to speak up as to whether or not they believe that the trio should cut back on these jokes.

Such feedback might be achieved through their Twitter accounts, here on the Hat Films and Yogscast Reddits, in the comments of the offending videos and meeting them face-to-face at conventions.

The fact is that, until a noticeable amount of people complain about the jokes the trio make, there's a good chance that they'll keep going with those jokes.

And that's all I have to say on the matter. Good day, one and all.

~~Also, I may or may not be excited to see the end of Hat Films culminate into one big dick joke as they've said in the past.~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 03:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now that you know, I hope you can understand why I chose the word "indomitable". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 13:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 7/8-with-interspersed-7/4 kind of guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 09:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might I refer you to the first letter of each line to determine the subject of this poem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 07:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 90% sure Matt is Kylo Ren. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 06:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, to make up for the lack of Flute distribution, they decided to release Arceus as an event Pokemon for the available Gen IV games instead.

These days, if you see an Arceus in online battles come out of a PokeBall that's not a Cherish Ball, there's a high chance it's hacked, but legitimate different PokeBall Arceus do exist, but it's hard to know which ones are the genuine articles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 06:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Steven's Shiny Beldum (later Metagross)

2) PokeBall Pattern Vivillon

3) Shiny Giratina

4) Team Plasma Deoxys

5) 2014 Supersize Pumpkaboo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn right I'm excited!

Once they get it over and done with, we'll get the next Tintin movie! WOOOOOOOOO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, uh...wow. This evocative verse hits hard. I know...I FEEL every line as a knife in my heart, as knives I deserve, as knives I have no right to protest against.

It may be a chapter of my life I'm glad is closed now, but I hope she's doing well for herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once read a limerick online

I thought it was truly sublime

Jim sounds like a prick

I hope death comes quick

For the man who'll be no friend of mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last of the True Ghost Ships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 04:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring me a vision of black on white

Adrift on unyielding, endless wastes,

Yearning to end under rainbow light,

Clamped fast by natures frosty brace.

Here it rests, an aboveground tomb,

Indomitable seafaring history;

Many dream to make fantasy bloom

On board this unassuming mystery.


 nbsp;
 nbsp;
 nbsp;

https://www.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/4r4omu/jim_a_limerick/d4ydueg?context=3

https://www.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/4r51as/for_your_ghost_wherever_she_may_be/d4ydy0d?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 09:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The grim punctuation to a career in unmasking charlatans and mediums. I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 09:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right; Houdini turned debunker in his later years and died in 1926 in Michigan. He might not have been in New York, but there could be a throwaway line in the movie like "We have to do something about Weisz. He's getting too close." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think THIS person will show up in Fantastic Beasts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 09:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's look at the facts.

Where is Fantastic Beasts set? **New York.**

When is Fantastic Beasts set? **1926.**

New York, 1926. When you think of famous people in that area at that time, most especially when you think about people being called and considered wizards and doing things that the general public think are extraordinary or downright impossible, who do you think of?

The biggest name that comes to mind is none other than **NIKOLA TESLA.** A man considered a wizard with the incredible energy of electricity who was living in New York in 1926, Tesla would be a prime candidate for showing up in Fantastic Beasts. We could see him included in any conceivable way, from a simple nameplate on a door in the MACUSA to seeing the elderly Tesla (he turned 70 in July, 1926) battling it out with one of the escaped creatures from Newt's case.

Now, I could have also said Thomas Edison here as well; aside from the obvious title of "The Wizard Of Menlo Park", there is a chance he would have been in New York in 1926, but a full appearance might not be likely as he was known to frequent Florida in the mid-1920's. To that extent, there could also be a door with a nameplate that says "Thomas A. Edison" on it; there could even be a small scene showing a door with both Edison and Tesla's names on it, ironically subverting the famous War of Currents between them.

**What do you think? Could there be a nod to Tesla or Edison in Fantastic Beasts? Might they show up in the sequels? Who else famous was known to be in New York in 1926? Leave your thoughts below.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's Ross when you need him?

[Oh, wait...](https://www.reddit.com/r/Hatfilms/comments/4pa97v/ive_been_collecting_the_links_to_the_stream/d4jt1dx?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Pokemon is the most forgotten about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's over 730 Pokemon in the Pokemon world, so it's inevitable that a number of Pokemon are going to take a seat on the bench...and maybe never get off of it.

I'm talking about Pokemon you've probably forgotten exist. I'm talking about the Pokemon that, when you hear their name, you're like "Oh, right! Completely forgot that was totally a thing!"


So which Pokemon do you always forget about for one reason or another? For me, it has to be **Maractus** because there's barely any exposure on it. Seriously; when's the last time you saw a Maractus in the Pokemon world that wasn't the one you caught and stored in your PC for collection and completion purposes?

**Which Pokemon do YOU forget exists?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried the Vintage Database. It was the first thing I did. Nothing matched this particular model. I think a watchmaker will be the go, but I thought Reddit might be a good shot first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking to have it work again and I'm not looking to sell it either. I just want to know any information about it; I like learning about small things like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Identify - Omega] Found while moving house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 12:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I moved house earlier this month and came across this watch while going through an old chest of drawers. It was a present from my Dad to my Mum on her 21st Birthday back in 1979.

Here is a front and back view of the watch:  http://imgur.com/m5GnYVw 

The writing on the face says "OMEGA - DE VILLE - QUARTZ - SWISS MADE" (sorry about the quality) and the inscription on the back reads "To Rita, Happy 21st, Love Todd 8.10.79"

So it's a late 70's Omega De Ville and that's about all I know. I don't know much about watches and my searching efforts on the internet turned up nothing conclusive.

Any information regarding the specifics about this watch would be much appreciated. Cheers in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you'll just have to look out for my question next week.

In the meantime, why not stew over the question I asked [last month](https://www.reddit.com/r/pokemon/comments/4lpffw/weekly_questions_thread_30_may_2016/d3rddhs?context=3) ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BIGGER. And less specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bigger. Think globally, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, nothing like that. It'll be a big question to think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait until you see what I ask next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #MakeTheLightfoilCanon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone else cheered and gasped.

I was the only one who, like a roaring bull, stood up and angrily yelled "GARBAGE?!? HOW DARE YOU, YOU BITCH?!?"

I didn't care that half of the audience turned and looked at me in shock. I couldn't have cared less about any young children in the cinema.

NO-ONE calls the Millennium Falcon garbage and gets away with it when I'm in the room, thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 11:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can a Slowpoke that has had its tail removed still evolve into a Slowbro? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yes; the infamous "Onion Fairy" Tumblr image </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...damn it. I promised myself I wouldn't cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 06:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Type: Dark

Number in Region: 5th

Leader: Mannox

Gender: Male

Age: Late 30's

Title: "The Monk Who Lives In Shadow"

Number of Pokemon: 3

Pokemon 1: Umbreon Lvl 47

Pokemon 2: Weavile Lvl 47

Pokemon 3: Houndoom (Mega Capable) Lvl 50

Badge: Eclipse Badge

TM Gift: TM97 Dark Pulse
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Pokemon do you always lead with? What's its story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just curious to know the stories and love behind your most used Pokemon. In case you're a bit confused, here's my story.

I've been a fan of Pokemon since the early 2000's. My friend loaned me his Game Boy Color and Pokemon Silver and the rest is history.

Anyway, I didn't actually own a Pokemon game of my own until Pokemon Pearl was released in 2007. I started the game and got my starter and went out into the new world.

The first Pokemon I come across? A simple Starly. I catch it and name him 'Soarateryx' (From 'soar' as it's a bird Pokemon, a corruption of the word 'sora' which translates to 'sky' and 'archeopteryx' as it was MY first bird Pokemon ). It quickly became a staple of my team, and I trained it...maybe not as best as I could, but I trained it in a way that felt right (I'm an exhibitionist, not a competitor).

Fast forward to now. Every chance I've had to transfer Soarateryx over, I've done so. In the 9 years since that first encounter, he's seen 6 regions across 15 games (counting different versions) and has ALWAYS been the Pokemon I lead with. Pokemon Amie was a godsend, as it allowed me to bond with him at an unprecedented level. I will never not have him in my party as we've been through so, so much together and he will be my companion until the day I die...or until my game gets corrupted.

Anyway, that's my story in a nutshell. **What's yours?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Declasse Sabre Turbo - Sure, it's not the best muscle car around, but it's a pleasant reminder of my Vice City days.

Coil Voltic - Fast, quiet and grippy. Good little all-purpose car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
