<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2866</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't hit my kids or let anyone else hit them as punishment, and I won't let my kids be around my stepfather. These are my two hard and fast rules.

My mom, who turned out to be a great grandmother (even though she wasn't a great mom), does abide by my rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having kids is very, very scary, because children are dependent on you for everything. Also, I try to model good, emotional responses (feeling angry is ok, punching walls is not ok, being sad is ok, being so sad you can't get out of bed is concerning, being happy is ok, faking happy is not ok). It's also a really personal choice, and it's ok if you don't feel up to having kids. Take care of **you**, first and foremost. 

I manage one day at a time. My biggest concern is that my kids will inherit my predisposition for depression. I know that their upbringing is very different than my own, so there is a big component of nuture that they will have that I did not (I was abused from age 9 by my stepfather, and my mother sided with him). I also want to state that my husband is pretty awesome, and is very helpful in my day-to-day interactions. 

I will fully admit, after my second son was born, I was hit with post-partum issues. I couldn't stop thinking about my kids dying, and I honestly thought that my family would be better if I just died because I was just a crap mother who couldn't keep it together. I even had a suicide plan, and notes for my husband and kids, and every day I had to force myself to call my therapist first before I would go through with my suicide plan. It was a hard six months. That was probably the lowest I've ever felt as a mom.

I think that my upbringing has helped me become a better parent. I try to emotionally give my kids what I didn't have growing up, and listen to their words. I still feel like a crap mom at times, but I think all parents feel like that. Parenting never comes with a manual. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
