<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His father worked hard to build that monopoly. They made him shit on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What year did it come out? who was in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a sad ending though, even if there was two of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't have legs. Clarification: was there anyone in the movie with two working legs that she met and she did not sleep with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never read the book. But from the movie that was my read. She never snapped, she always was this frazy bitch, who's cool as long as she's getting what she wants or until she's done with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me have a taste :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "mad wool" is that a euphemism for poon? first time I heard it referred that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 07:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You my friend, need to read the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh I thought you built Narwhal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not seeing your app in the App Store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 17:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why no one just tries to take Kim out. 

If it feels like the situation is hopeless since you lose if you escape (your family hauled to the camps) and you lose if you don't (you get executed) then it looks like the next best thing is to take out the person that is the cause of your miseries... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 06:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great then. Next time I hurt someone badly, I'll tell the judge not too worry since I already forgave myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 05:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll start chatting with my nephews and nieces about mortality and other mind exercises that could help them later just like your uncle did. Kudos to him, he comes across as someone generous from the way you told the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The accent plus the DENNIS System is a winning formula. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you switch accent while she was going down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of it was, and part of it was not. Germany was fucked over after WWI - which never ended, merely paused. Japan had imperial ambitions (which was true for most advanced nations in those era) - none of which is evil by itself, but the means were. Or at least ruthless (it had to be)

Saying the US went to war to stomp out evil is simplistic at best. You could even say that statement is egotistical. 

It went to war to protect itself and its interest which include its allies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 19:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By not asking for total surrender, they would have offered it themselves. By being forced, there would've been resentment and shame. In the end it seemed like 2 was enough and there was some fundamental change in their society after the war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 19:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Some wars you have to fight. 

Marking them as evil simplifies motivations to black and white and fail to solve or reduce the chances of the same things from happening again.

Breaking their appetite for wars does not mean they won't go for it again. Just that they'd think long and hard before they do, and hopefully their populace raise questions whether it would be just for them to go into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 18:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved most/all of SK's earlier books (anything before the 90's)

Try reading any of these after: Christine, FireStarter, and Cujo. Just like you described Pet Sematary, the horror in these books aren't in the supernatural and is centered around the personalities and emotions of the characters in the stories.

The last and most recent SK book I read was Dr. Sleep - here it seems/reads like he's back to old form. I finished it in 5 days and while not exactly a "can't put down", I couldn't stay away from it for too long.

The main character is dealing with alcoholism and the destruction and pain it causes; I could've skipped reading the "horror" parts and it would've still been a good read. 

This book feels like it's autobiographical, and felt all the more sincere.

EDIT: Added 3 more paragraphs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 would've been better. Should've just dropped one a day until Japan's high-command itself reached out and offered unconditional surrender.

Those 2 bombs were not enough punishment for the amount of destruction and misery that Japan dealt out to the Pacific nations.

As such, 2 was merciful and measured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't Evil that the US was trying to rid of, it was Japan and Germany's taste for wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Tell me if you do :-)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is keto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch that. Jimmy Olsen getting two in the head. Perry and Lois too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the rub, I can't remember. :-( 

They were bundled in two other short story collections by King. Both story features the never aging butler from the Club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 19:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty old for 32. She's got some miles on her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those poor sweet goats... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 03:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you can argue that our knowledge of gravitation, calculus, the laws of motion would not be where it is today if it weren't for the plague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 23:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm still waiting for The Breathing Method - which was the best in the four.

Incidentally there were at least two other short stories from King that was told in the same Club where we hear about the The Breathing Method. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 23:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Drumpf/Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 23:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately your assessment is the more likely outcome. Criminal enterprises are very Darwinian; those you catch are just the "weakest" and those you don't, improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't crappy design! this is loads of fucking awesomeness when I was a kid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The first few were good, but eventually it devolved into rich people licking each other's ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 15:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you'll get there. Time passes no matter what, so if you want to learn and be good at anything, just put in the hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 06:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy on top is choking the guy on bottom. The bottom guy's arm is trapped at that point and can't effectively apply a choke anymore (wrong angle)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just trolling. 
I got you :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy at the bottom was twitching/spasming. He was out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long winded, but yeah, dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. It's a repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 06:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friend's mom's still got it. I'd tap it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean break down your body? Getting sick? grossly fat or skinny?, etc.?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 07:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. A match between opponents with only a slight difference in skill level will most likely be won by the heavier fighter. 

Gender also matter (favoring the male gender) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that you're not smart. Just may be being willfully wrong - but I am curious, is it more stylish these days (again) to selectively use bad grammar?

I know it was a decade or so ago: "aks"instead of "ask"; excessive use of "like", etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your insecurity is showing. Tuck it in bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 17:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "had to *have* been" - "had to *of* been" just doesn't make sense. Sorry it bugs me, but is purposely being grammatically wrong the hip/cool thing now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mashed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 23:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best is when you've caught them fresh. Vinegar "cooks" them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/7PAOz09hEPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 23:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. they're small enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 23:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh sea food! lookup jumping shrimp delicacy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yeah! A drop of spiced soy sauce makes it even better.
Same with with little shrimps: drop them in vinegar, let them jump around a bit (maybe in pain, maybe not - but fuck it they taste good!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems fair to me. I might even force the little tickets to lick it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can tell, just by the looks of it, that she takes it up the ass regularly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 05:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You motherfucker. My weed high hit me just as I was reading your post - my gut hurt from laughing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 10:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a member of Mensa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 05:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God! Everyone of you guys can't be that fucking dumb! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 01:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a troll subreddit? 

You guys can't be serious about wanting to even give Donald Trump a chance to become the President of the United States...

And if this a troll subreddit, hey good one. But it's like playing with fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 00:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good though. Would love to French it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 18:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That last pic. Your pussy lips look plumper than usual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 17:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't start shit, you don't get shit.

Japan's neighbors hate their guts to this day. After WWII, it seems like Japan got more help than the countries they raped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get a better offer, leave. They'll call you if they want to keep you. But even then you should not stay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Plus at 3.5 year mark, it's time to start shaking things up if you're not seeing any significant progress in pay or position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd you let her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you male or female? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 05:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Weird Science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very apt way to describe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 20:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her pussy looks loose AF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 01:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And crazies too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DM me. Maybe I could take over your rent... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 10:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it looks like for Earth-like planets to be a successful host to complex life-forms, it's not enough that it is conducive to life, but also that it must have a neighbor or neighbors similar to Jupiter (to stave off extinction from occasional asteroid or comet hits) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how was it measured? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 23:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ichi The Killer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 23:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was just sad though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 23:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depressing as fuck. But interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 23:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. 

The original version. Fuckkkkkkkked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look like Filipinos, so adjusting for that, they might be in their early 20's... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 08:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this nerdy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the same issue. 

Are you in the US? because this seems to be a US phenomenon/culture, to talk over everyone else in a conversation, everyone pushing they're own topic and not picking up anyone's thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not autism. You let these things slide, soon the English language will read like pidgin. 

The machine used to write these comments could do a lot of cool shit: from launching spaceships to correcting spelling and help with grammar. Use it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least you acknowledge when you're wrong. Unlike most people who gets corrected in Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a very stark and morbid view point. I think I'll pick up this book finally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 09:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was this from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Serious] Does she get paid to do these shoots? What is the shoot for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 18:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah people forget that. Compared to his fights, 5 second, 1st round KOs cease to be so impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus H. - you gotta fail in despair against an opponent like Ali. Barely moving and you almost always just miss by less than inch no matter how fast or hard you throw your punches. 

Here it looks like he could just decide to end the fight because he got bored. And equally so extend it, just so it looks like he worked for his paycheck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice dodge. Yet honest.
But it's fucking retarded that it's even an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 07:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switch to weed. An indica edible is great if you just want to get a deeper sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 05:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meh, kinda expected it. Most of Reddit confuse popular with correct.

fistbump my letardic bro :-)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before picture was better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 19:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many books in the series? Would you recommend reading all of them? I know his son started wrote at least one, so I think that those I would skip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 19:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting because "amok" also means the same in Tagalog, but almost everyone thinks it's English.

A joke based on this word:

Q: What's the English word for "amok"
A: "osquito"

Explanation: "lamok" is the Tagalog word for "mosquito"

Edit: additionally, the word "juramentado" is used in place. Almost everyone thinks it's Tagalog, but is likely Spanish (at least in origin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 18:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know she wasn't wearing much by the end, but did they both take off their underwear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 19:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wether you agree with the results or not, it's another question... how about that man with the stunning red hat?! stand up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not so bad. He can chalk it up as paid schooling. He should be able to get a substantial bump in pay once he jumps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 22:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to move. 

They might counter but the salary jump from moving to a new job can be hard to match, the only plus with staying is you know the people you work with and presumably you like the people you work with. 

In my experience (20+ years) it's almost always better to move. If you're good with your current employer, you now have them as a valuable node in your professional network (at the very least)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
