<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 22:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think that sort of response will work with the sort of people being described here? They may simply say "Your mother must have had a good reason. Honor your mother!" Don't presume that a religious person will yield to this type of societal reasonableness. 

I wish I had a better solution to offer here, but I would be remiss if I didn't point out the risk of this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 08:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/_cr_WimU4oA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 08:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've seen this type of game played before, but I've never seen it done in a useful way like this fellow does it. It really forces you to think about what your position and solid mixed play strategy on every single hand since you can't just mechanically evaluate the hand against a mental bank. I found it a bit challenging to keep up with his line of reasoning at first, but by the end I found it compelling. Of course, I wouldn't subject myself to that limitation at a 200nl table. At lower stakes, though, it could be a good training exercise. 

Now if he could just never drink from that bottle again on camera, i'd be happy. I'm afraid to catch another of his videos for fear of a repeat on that chugging, splashing noise. :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...there are some places where you're the person who wrote the only book on the topic. Or, in other cases, you're the person who wrote the most popular textbook. Granted, the appearance is not good when you assign your own text. I'd never do it, though I'd never write a textbook. Still, in some cases it's appropriate to assign a self-authored text for class. 

I had an Econ prof as an undergrad who write his own book and used it to teach a course. Only charged us copy costs. It was a terrible book, but luckily he was a solid teacher. So that can happen too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 15:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't, but that was a pretty epic one to read! Sued for playing blame the old employee? That's crazy!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equality FTW!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a great post in one of the IT subreddits where the manager fired the best employee over some minor infraction because the manager didn't realize the employee's relative skill level. After the firing, it became apparent that the fired employee was doing the work of multiple people and things subsequently fell apart. 

I wish I could find it...I just spent a half hour trying to find it but failed. Anybody recognize the post from my description? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That particular book had it coming the whole time...good work, OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 07:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right. I just watched it in slow motion on the NHK feed and it looks like that face slap before the loud slap connects directly with the eye socket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 05:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it look like an eye gouge to you? I've watched the replay a few times and it looked more like a slap than an eye gouge. 

Either way, I hope Chiyootori recovers quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 02:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aoiyama will, I hope, improve on the last basho and go 9-6.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 01:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was simply fantastic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're pretty hilarious! I feel like you should consider marketing...you really can turn a phrase! Thanks for the story and best wishes to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 03:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many situations life will present you which can be approached in a variety of ways. An assignment like this, for example, can be treated as an opportunity for deep introspection or written off as a waste of time (or something in between). Neither is necessarily right or wrong, but each has implications for your personal development...that is, if you accept that every situation presents an opportunity for growth. Expending effort in one situation means you might not have effort to expend somewhere else. Thus, there is clearly some opportunity cost to your decisions. 

At the end of the day, what we take from our activities will inevitably be a function of what we put into that activity. It's always your decision, therefore, as to how much effort or thought you will expend on any specific activity. In my opinion, your asking the question as to how to approach this assignment is a really good sign. 

I know this isn't an answer to your specific question, but I hope you find it to be an applicable bit of life advice which will help you make these decisions for yourself in a more thoughtful way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, Reddit directs me to read something that I can never unread. The earnestness of the guy in that post is unreal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's important to say that it's fine even if you are able to take in the kids but choose not to do so. Having children should be a deliberate choice. You are doing them a favor by not taking them in if you don't really want to have them in your life. 

Being child free is a legitimate and perfectly fine choice on its own. Set aside any guilt you may feel knowing that by not taking them in under duress, you're giving these kids an opportunity to find homes with families that will give them the love and support they need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a professor, I'd like to give my two cents and tell you not to pursue this. There are one of two possibilities here that are most probable. 

1. He is a professor and looks at you like a student.  This means that you probably look like a child to him. I don't mean that he thinks your childish. Rather, I look out at my class and the students physically look like high school kids to me. Even the "attractive" ones are not attractive to me because it seems almost like pedophilia to be checking them out. He meets your eyes because he's actively looking around the room for eyes to meet. That's how he can tell if the class (aka the children) understand what he's saying. Everything you think your seeing with respect to your connection, therefore, is, at best, paternalistic and, at worst, nonexistent. 

2. He's a creep and is actively trying to lure you in with his gaze. Any professor who would seek to hook up with a student (and I know some who have) is doing so with the full knowledge that they are the strong party in the relationship. Students are the limpy gazelle of the classroom savannah and the professor is the proud lion, hunting his prey. He's attracted to you, therefore, as a conquest and not as a person. 

The most logical scenario is 1 based on your comments. If you seek him out, you're more than likely to embarrass yourself. Frankly, I'd report a student who made a pass at me. It may not be illegal or against the rules for you to do so, but you may end up in the Dean's office nonetheless. 

So, for your sake and for his, stop now and proceed no further with this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been stories about Ted and his degenerate gambling habits for a long time. He personally told a story about winning a tournament and then quickly setting up a huge craps game where he lost most of those winnings. I couldn't find the article where I read that, but here is a 2+2 thread where they reference the article and describe his huge deals losses. 

http://archives2.twoplustwo.com/showflat.php?Cat=0 Number=3772620 page=0 fpart=all vc=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Victory at last!!!  I've never understood why we put antibacterials in hand soap outside sterile environments like hospital surgeries. This will hopefully help slow the rise of antibacterial resistance while also encouraging people to be more attentive to their cleanliness. People are lulled into a false sense of security by these soaps, something which will change (hopefully) now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they persist, your university should have an HR department you can talk to. By harassing you like this, they are creating (potentially) a hostile work environment. Don't be shy about dealing with these busy bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're technically correct here regarding he church and its view of the baptism. This doesn't mean, however, that OP shouldn't take every step to report the behavior of the Priest. Archdiocese bureaucrats rarely appreciate illicit behavior even if they can justify it on a technicality. Speaking up may help some other family down the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely this! In addition, you should report the priest who performed this baptism to the Archdiocese. Doing baptisms of children without the consent of their parents is explicitly against the rules. Even if your mother lied and said she is the legal guardian, the priest should have check that and verified it. This is the kind of behavior that gives Christians, not just Catholics, a bad name. 

Of course, initiating that action would also allow you to confirm if your husband authorized things. That information is important as well. I'm not sure what I would do if he authorized the baptism, but clearly you aren't overreacting here. 

Edit: So...I looked this up and was surprised that it is apparently no longer possible to formally defect from the Catholic Church. They apparently removed this act from the legal code of the Church in 2009. I'm incensed at reading that because it now seems there isn't anything that can be done, short of legal action (which is absolutely something I would suggest you consider depending on your means), to remove yourself from the roster of the Catholic Church.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song still makes me cry after all these years. For a child watching this movie for the first time this song represented everything I always suspected life could be but which my parents didn't appreciate. Willy Wonka made it ok to hope and dream for the future. I may not have seen him do any recent work but I'll be sad that the possibility of him doing it no longer exists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a large guy, I've certainly run into chasers (as they are called in the gay community) before. There's a big difference between a chaser and someone who simply likes larger people. What your boyfriend seems to be describing isn't really a fat fetishist. He's not placing the focus on your weight in your relationship or your sex life. If the concern is that he won't continue to find you sexy, I think you know that won't happen based solely on how he's reacted to this revelation. I could tell you some stories...weird ones. :-/

The real issue here is that in revealing his preferences, he has left you feeling insecure. By telling you how his "ideal" woman looks, he's left you to compare yourself to an ideal. Up until now, you have been able to assume you are his ideal looking woman. Now you know you haven't been until recently and that you will be moving away from his ideal as you drop weight. I don't really think this is a matter of trust...after all, he was forthright when asked even if he wasn't forthcoming. What kind of asshole says "I'd like your body better if it were different?" I think it's unfair of you to expect that he would have shared this information about his preferences since they are essentially non-actionable. He could ask you to wear a corset or slap him around a bit. He can't ask you to put on weight...that's just not done. So now when it comes time to be with your boyfriend, you're left with this underlying insecurity regarding your looks and his interest in them. That's not really a great start to sexy times. 

My partner loves me. I'm quite sure I'm not his ideal type. His exes have all been smaller than me. We both look at conventionally hot guys when rarely we talk about such things. If he were to explicitly confirm those suspicions, however, it would be devastating. If he were to say that I'm actually his ideal looking guy, I'd probably be even more self-conscious since I'd feel pressure to maintain this look when I'd rather lose pounds. It's a no-win situation all around when someone says stupid stuff like that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL the virgin birth was actually a miscast "Fetus Deletus" spell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did an undergraduate degree in the arts and have a business-related PhD. My decision to pursue the humanities undergraduate was actually a last-minute change. Prior to that, I had thought to get an undergraduate degree in the same field as my PhD. I figured, however, that your "dreams" can more easily be pursued in your youth. After working in the field of my degree for several years, however, i decided to switch back to my original plan and pursue the business degree. 

My main suggestion would be to have a plan. My pursuit of a PhD took 10 years from the point to when i identified it as the desired outcome to when I graduated. I researched what the degree entailed and read articles in the field to ensure that I was willing to do the research and that my interests were represented in the literature. I picked schools to apply to that supported that research. I went back to school for a master's degree, but not before taking a few undergraduate classes to make sure that I really wanted to go through with studying that field for an extended period of time. Once in the master's program, I told all my professors my plan and was able to get some good guidance on pursuing the degree. It was a very intentional process and I took steps to make sure that I was fully invested the whole way. 

Getting a PhD is a long and trying process. If you don't love what you're doing, you are going to have a hard time being persistent enough to finish. Good luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 20:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like Bill Belichick...give away nothing with your words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my first thought on reading this post. I've shared an office with Chinese colleagues and have been driven to near madness by the slurping, open mouth chewing, and mid-swallow talking of these same colleagues. Personally, loud eating is an absolute deal breaker for me. I hope you can work it out, OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Thanks to science! Clemontic Gear On!!

Seriously, though...the new CPA exam is going to be very interesting. I like the focus on critical thinking and I (like most people) think it's going to really change the mix of who passes and fails the exam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a Wigglytuff...

Congratulations either way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See...this is the trouble with people lumping all social justice activities together. Feminists and members of the Black Lives Matter movement can and do have legitimate grievances regarding the treatment of certain groups in our society. This is not the same as some random undergraduate whining because they have to consider other viewpoints that aren't their own.

The behavior you're describing here (your own behavior) seems to me to be the hallmarks of a manager or, by extension, a company that doesn't care about people who are different from them. You might like to have a workplace where you're free to tell off-color jokes, for example, or insult and yell at each other without repercussions. 

If that's what you are (and I strongly suspect that to be the case), that's certainly a choice you can make. It's to your detriment that you're unwilling to entertain the merits of people with different positions from yours, from my perspective. You don't have to share my perspective, however, and that's also a choice you can make. 

Don't hop on your high horse here and try to pretend that what you're doing is some noble defense of free speech, however, or standing up for traditional values. Recognize it as exclusionary and own that. 

tl;dr: You're an asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also true. Some job fields in academia are miserable, mostly in the humanities. Even if they aren't miserable, they might not be good (i.e. Some STEM fields).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is correct. Professional degrees are often paid for because they pay off in the back end in the form of a job. I paid for my business masters and didn't think twice about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frigging Armenia...stick us with the Kardashians and then don't accept out homosexuals? Ridiculous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly didn't read the linked article, or any related article for that matter. That's ok, though. Believe whatever you need to to keep on sleeping easily at night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he made his chance a good one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what I mean. People are essentially being tossed in prison, forced to work without pay, given meager rations, and ignored by society. And for what? Smoking a joint? Lots of people on Reddit are guilty of this sort of transgression. Not me, of course, because I'm too stupid to operate a bong (true story). Regardless, it's a miserable plight and we are all here making jokes about it. "Hurf durf, don't drop the soap while you're in the shower trying to forget how you're starving and thinking over how society will never let you forget you've been in prison."

It's a national disgrace and we should treat it as such! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fascinated, yet not surprised, with how few comments focuses on the horror that is the US prison system. We feed them so poorly that they're literally trading soup for work in order to get enough calories? The reference in the article to particularly poor conditions in private prisons is no surprise either, yet so few people here pick up on that issue either.  Seriously, is this Dickensian England we're talking about or the 21st century USA?!? It's not like we fill our prisons with the worst of the worst people, either. With all the racism inherent within our policing and judicial system, we all need to be concerned with this type of problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tell people that I'm going to haunt a medical school after I die and that my skeleton be hanging in some classroom like in a cartoon. They always think I'm joking, but with a full-body anatomical donation I'm hopeful there's a non-zero chance of one of those things happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd better, eh, "knot" mention that again...

- The Goat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd check with /r/legaladvice, personally. If that partner is interfering with you getting a job by telling them something false, it could open them up to liability. Even if you don't want to sue them (you don't, probably) you could put some fear in the guy by calling up EY and telling them that you have a potential cause of action. 

Maybe it's not worth the trouble, of course. I'm just vindictive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just picturing the dust clearing on a Pokemon battle and the doctor's eyes replaces with spinning disks. Nice work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that this subreddit is sufficiently cynical and condescending to young people that this is somehow the top comment. This young woman is thoughtful enough to seek out help when she needs it and to provide an update on how things went after taking our advice. What does she get from you in return? Saltiness. 

If you're going to condescend, at least have the decency to do so in a substantive way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you're focused on your own details being leaked (for good reason), there may be some HIPPA issues with this girl improperly accessing someone's files for non-medical reasons. She didn't work in her case, thus had no medical reason to access the information. I had a friend of a friend who was fired from a job because he improperly accessed his own child's medical records rather than wait for the consultation. This stuff is serious for sure!


What wouldn't she do to satisfy her curiosity?!? Report her and help give her the boot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 07:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to take so long in replying...the term begins next week and I've been swamped. 

I think your case may be one where a DBA makes sense. Of course, you'll want to pick one with a strong placement record and which meets your needs for residency (i.e. Low residency program so you can continue to work). Clearly the money is an issue for you such that even a stipend plus loans isn't going to allow you to focus on a traditional PhD. That's a perfectly good reason to choose a DBA over a PhD. The local schools you reference are likely ones that are more teaching focused...they'd probably be glad to have a DBA on the faculty. Check the credentials of people at those schools for comparison of you want to be sure. You can ask PM me specific schools for some input on what they are probably looking for in a job candidate so you don't out your location publicly. 

With that said, it isn't clear to me how you'd overcome the main difference between the degrees - the research experience. A PhD program puts you in touch with other research active people and a mentor, or multiple mentors, who guide your progress. You are forced to read piles of papers and become an expert in your chosen area. You immerse yourself in the research work and finish your degree with a dissertation befitting that commitment. I just don't see how you could find that sort of mentor after the fact at the type of schools that would hire you with a DBA. Faculty at those schools teach a full load of classes and often aren't all that research active in the first place. They won't have time to guide your research progress in the same way a PhD program is equipped to do. 

This need not be an obstacle to your pursuing a DBA, however. If your main goal is to teach, a DBA from a reputable program with a strong placement record could be enough to get you there. Research doesn't have to be a huge part of your career. Getting the DBA is basically a choice to focus on teaching after you finish...and that's a fine choice. If, however, you want to focus on research after finishing your doctorate (also a fine choice), the DBA simply isn't enough to reach that goal. 

I hope this helps. Feel free to ask more questions as they come up, either here or by PM. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her putting you in the position of lying to keep her out of trouble is what's putting the strain on your relationship. Do you really want friends like that? What if she stole your stuff instead of shoplifting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The assertion that the government uses sophisticated fraud detection methods makes me feel better about all this. That and the knowledge that this article is reporting gross adjustments. 

I'm left wondering, however, how well the auditor can ascertain whether or not the Army is following its own accounting procedures. The use of estimates is all part of the game, as we all know. It shouldn't be any surprise, therefore, that adjustments are later made in order to reconcile estimates to actually. An auditor should be able to figure out (1) whether the estimates were made according to relevant standards and company policy, and (2) whether those estimates are reasonable. The fact that the financial statements are disclaimed the way they are suggests that they can't even figure out if they've followed their own policies. If the auditor could determine the Army followed its own policies, they'd only have to assess the policies in order to answer the second question. Even if they only have internal auditors and didn't subject themselves to external scrutiny up until now, those internal auditors should be able to answer those questions as well. It sounds like they may have a manpower issue rather than a systems issue from what I'm reading. 

Of course, I may be misinterpreting all that...I was never an auditor and only did reporting work on the management side. Please correct me if I'm mistaken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discussion fodder for the first day of classes FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 04:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus penalties and interest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like it is impacting his obligations based on what you say here, at least to some extent. If "forever" is hours, he's kind of leaving you all hungry while he's off playing games. If it's 15 minutes, perhaps it's not so big a deal.

One of the signs of addiction is that it interferes with your life in one of several ways. So long as he's still getting his work done, making time for his friends and family, and maintaining his usual life routine, it's probably an acceptable level of playing. If he's withdrawing, avoiding work to play games, and basically excluding everything but the game, it's probably a problem. Here is some info on video game addiction for you to read for your own information:

http://www.psychguides.com/guides/video-game-addiction-symptoms-causes-and-effects/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the trouble with a lot of data I've found. I was hoping someone might know of some magical data set with individual-level compensation data that isn't self-reported, but it doesn't seem that's the case. Thanks for the suggestion!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your reply! The industry-level data could be helpful so I'll take a look at the Quandl website to see what they have.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your reply. I should have specified that I was looking more for individual-level data (anonymous) but I appreciate the information you provided. I may be able to do something with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 00:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I caught a 36 CP Rhydon. :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reminded of that time I went to Denny's at 3 AM and the waitress said "Our menu has no trans fats." I replied "I'm at a Denny's at 3 AM...clearly I have no concern for my health."

Tl;dr: Grammar doesn't matter when you're talking about pillow soaking!

Edit: Fats do not ride trains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 05:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been at least one case in the new about this recently. Here is a link:

http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2016/05/iphone-fingerprint-search-warrant/480861/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck me...I just looked it up. I can never unsee that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, her husband and his mom may have a great relationship and he still might not want her to live with them. My mom and I get song very well and have a close relationship. Not "momma's boy" close, but we talk regularly and sometimes take a vacation together. I would only have her move in with me, or vice versa, if we had self ate living spaces like in a multi-family unit. I certainly wouldn't want her to be the primary caregiver for my kids. I still see glimmers of the passive-aggression that I've dealt with my whole life and don't want that for my kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite hours of prayer and wishing well visits, I haven't seen so much as a hint of gay activity while watching the Olympics. Believe me, I've been watching with eagle eyes! 

They couldn't get two divers to make out a bit for the fans? What a crock!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point is that if you're robbing people, you probably have other needs that outpace the desire to see the Olympics. Food, for instance...or shelter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 05:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, at least a little bit. Not a pleasant realization. :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot that could be said on this topic, but I'm a bit pressed for time so let me offer a few salient points for you to consider in making your choice. 

1. Training Depth and Breadth - A traditional PhD program in business takes 4-5 years to complete. Those extra years are used mainly used to further your development as a researcher. You're completely focused on your studies as a PhD student since most business programs offer you a stipend, so you learn the nuances of academic writing and digesting research papers. More importantly, you learn to think about research. A 3- year program simply cannot offer you the same depth of experience in thinking about research. Having read some of the dissertations from graduates of this sort of DBA and having worked with such graduates, their work tends to be compulsory and surface rather than making deep contributions to their fields. 

This isn't necessarily bad. Most business fields have outlets for practice-oriented work which this type of DBA can prepare you to do. It won't likely be enough to get you tenure, however, at anything other than a relatively low-ranked program. More importantly, the training you receive won't really set you up to stay up to date with the research in your area. It's hard to digest research papers without a complete knowledge of statistics and research methods. 

(Note: The Kennesaw program at least has the benefit of employing Joe Hair, a noted expert in multivariate statistics and the author of an influential textbook.)

2. Employment Prospects - you mentioned all the people employed out of the program you referenced. A review of their student cohorts, however, reveal a number of people without jobs from recent cohorts. This suggests (notice I say suggests rather than proves...I can't prove this despite having some first-hand knowledge of what I'm saying) the marketplace may have gotten some signal about the quality of their graduates based on earlier graduates. A DBA such as the one you're referencing is viewed askance by the academics who would be hiring you for a tenure-track position. At my school, we wouldn't even consider you for a teaching-only clinical position with that degree. This is mainly because of...

3. Lack of Teaching Training - PhD programs in business generally offer assistantships. Even if it's only a single class, that assistantship gets you some practical experience at dealing with students and teaching. You might run your own class or simply assist a professor with their class, but the experience is invaluable in preparing you for a job in which you'll have to teach. DBA programs like the one you reference don't generally offer this training. 

4. Money - You don't generally pay for a business PhD. You generally pay for a DBA. The loans you would take for a DBA could be taken as cash and, when combined with a PhD stipend, could be used to support you for a PhD of living off the stipend isn't feasible based on your living situation. 

There are my two cents. Good luck to you as you think more about this important choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/datasets to see if anyone has an idea of whew to obtain such a data set. I do not know of one, unfortunately. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
