<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you absolutely can't park right on top of stop signs, that's illegal in basically every state.  FWIW, this site says MD prohibits parking within 30 feet of a stop sign:

http://law.justia.com/codes/maryland/2010/transportation/title-21/subtitle-10/21-1003


I'm fine w/ just enforcing the rule for parking too close to a stop sign.  Also, giving tickets to people that actually park in a crosswalk should be enforced and would help.  And finally, if cars are allowed to park right up to the corner, a mirror across the street to help drivers see oncoming traffic really wouldn't hurt now would it?  It gets really hairy when a something like a delivery truck or a moving truck parks right up to the corner and completely obstructs your view nearly 100%.  I mean I've learned a lot of tricks when normal cars park such as looking across the street at the cars for a reflection in their paint, but it doesn't always work if a larger vehicle is blocking your view.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 06:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something under the bed prob in his CD case of hacked files.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 06:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet she's still alive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whiskey. And a damn good bottle of it too.  If you don't have a bottle too you just haven't been in academia long enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is going to happen?  Nothing.  The university will always find a way to keep you a lowly paid serf.  Oh, so we're supposed to be treated as salaried employees now with OT or whatever?  OK, students will get paid $40-50k 'salary'.  Now tuition will no longer be 100% free and will cost PhD students $20k per year.  Ta-da!!! You end up making $30k like you did before.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good lord, shit is getting worse in science.  I made $58k + bonuses + 401 + health with a BS in science way, way back in 2006 in industry.  $40k is horrible.  Below that is catastrophic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youtube is your friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do I complain to about parking too close to intersections and stop signs? Diving is ridiculously treacherous in CV in the morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All throughout CV you might have a T or cross intersection where traffic on the cross street is extremely heavy.  The street you're driving on might have a stop sign at the intersection.  Cars now are routinely, and I mean almost everyday 365, park right on top of the stop signs or right until the edge of the corner of the intersections, making it virtually impossible to see if it is safe or not to drive through the intersection without either A.) driving into the cross walk to see or B.) flooring it when you think it is 'safe', but often time it can be close.  If you can't visualize what I'm talking about, here's a crappy pic:

http://imgur.com/a/rybnm


I mean I know it is already illegal to park right next to or on top of the stop sign, which no one enforces around here.  But it looks like there was already a discussion over the idea that in fact is indeed illegal to park within 30 feet of an intersection:

https://www.reddit.com/r/baltimore/comments/1n0y9u/no_parking_within_30_feet_of_intersection/

Probably for safety reasons--it's literally impossible to see oncoming traffic when people park right on the corners.  Who do I talk to in order to get meter maids to enforce the laws?  I mean is it quite ridiculous how people park in CV--right on top of the stop sign and even on top of the ped x walks. all over night too.  If they don't want to enforce the laws, can I at least ask for mirrors to be placed on a pole at intersections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NIKE. Literally bought a new pair for my trip to Brazil.  Put them on for what was supposed to be an easy hike.  75% of the way through 85% of the sole come detached from the shoe because of cheap ass glue.  The shoe had literally never been worn before.  It wasn't hardcore hiking either.  You don't know how miserable it is having to trek back 4+ miles up hills, over rocks, etc with a fucking shoe that has almost an entire 'floppy' sole.  Fuck Nike.  Never again after that fiasco  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't this shit on the front page.  Absolutely atrocious and outrageous behavior.  They should be fined 20x that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 22:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we please get Scott Adkins to be batman?  Would have sick Batman martial arts moves that are legit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how those comedians who make rape, 9/11, and retard jokes are reacting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a style of pistol squats.   Pistol squats even without weight are fucking diabolical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What blows my mind:

Preschool gradeschool teacher: need teaching degree/certifications/training

Middle School/High School:  need master's degree/teaching degree/certifiations/real world experience for training

College: Throw a grad student in there to the wolves who might have never even tutored before to teach a class of 300 students who are paying $50k a year for education.  The more money you pay the less qualified teachers you get! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC researcher here.  The problem is that when you are diagnosed with PC it is already too late.  No one has really figured out a way to reliably detect precancerous lesions that end up leading to PC but which are very survivable if caught.  

Be honest, would you want your family to spend $150,000 to increase your life span by a few . months?  Sure, there was one or two survivors out past one year and even 3 years, but the sample size is so small it might not even be statistically significant.  PC is 95-98% lethal, yet what if that survivor is just part of that 2-5% anyway that ends up living?  I'll reserve judgement until a larger trial happens.  We have a much much much less successful time with immuno therapy against solid tumors.  I mean we are seeing success in lung and skin cancer , and quite robust success w blood cancers, but different kinds of cancers pose different problems with their abilities to shut down the immune system, tissue access, etc etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost World

SLC Punk

Ghost Dog

Poolhall Junkies

Narc

Gattaca

Rushmore


Hearts and Minds

Bubba Ho Tep

Blue Velvet

Red Rock West

Go



Damn, now that I think about it, the 90s were a great decade for movies.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who remembers the opening scene for Narc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 03:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time you open the refrigerator I'm going in for a look.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 15:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run the AC everyday.  Your bill should not be that high.  The highest I ever pay is $150 for gas + electric during the summer. Keep annoying them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know my buddies use Bumble (I think that's what it is?).  The girl is the one that responds, so it is a lot less creepy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 14:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not always true.  My bro got extremely sick while traveling in India.  His ass would not stop leaking even while he was asleep.  He literally couldn't sleep on the hotel beds and had to sleep on the floor wrapped in a towel so that he didn't soak shit into the bed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 07:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, another quirky thing--Asian Taste is a take out Chinese shop on the avenue by day, but at night they have a lot of good punk and hardcore shows, there's really nothing quite like it. Then if you get lucky it might be comedy night over at Zissimos. Just walk over and go upstairs.   It's free.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 07:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koco's Pub.  Get a real and giant crab cake.  It's what Baltimore is famous for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 06:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza:. Johnny Rads, Gil's, Pasticcio

Chinese: none really, there is a dearth in Baltimore.  Chopstix is OK, but take the ride out to Rockville. Start w/A J


Bars: Of Love and Regret, Snug and Evil, Bar liquorice, Secret Bar, Cardinal Tavern, De Klein Duivel, iBar,  Wet City, 1157, Peabody Heights


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 06:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ibar:. Always have $1 natty bohs 4-7 and best wings in the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 20:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda like Roman Polanski?  But film buffs continue to praise him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicholas Cage from Adaptation to Face/Off.  Probably some whack ass shit had to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a federal holiday until Grover Cleveland signed the order after the Pullman Strike. Yes, multiple labor days existed, but the nation didn't recognize it until after Pullman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 15:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ju-on the original Japanese version of short movies.  Pretty creepy.  It takes a little getting used to, but the girl on the staircase scene is burned into my brain for forever.   

Would Funny Games count as horror?  That movie fucked me up good.   

Pure garbage with some gory scenes : Xtro

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 02:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why soccer players do this crap.  They should just suspend every player automatically for 2 games if they do it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife is from a foreign country.  She never leashed her dog back where she's from, ever.  It would follow you for blocks and block in a city when you took it for a walk, would wait outside of shops/stores when you went in and then when you told him to 'go home' he'd walk himself home.  He knew exactly how to cross the street full of busy cars, knew exactly where to go, and never got lost.  Did it that way for years.  He never got hit once.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 00:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weirdest, diviest, most 'hidden'/least talked about, and neighborhood bars I can think of:

Venice Tavern

Snug and Evil Tavern

Mount Royal Tavern

1919

Secret Bar (I dunno if this place still exists 'cause I haven't been there in a while but this is google st view:http://imgur.com/a/GyfcO)

Butts and Betty's Tavern (super duper baltimore)

Spirits Tavern

Muir's Tavern (one Baltimore's Oldest family run businesses)

Knotty Pine

Bar Liquorice

1157 Bar and Kitchen (Gem of a place for good food)


Weird as crap store: Bazaar in Hampden.  They even have a painting by John Wayne Gacy for sale.  








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that we have Labor Day as a result culminating from The Pullman Strike. During The Pullman Strike the US government sent the US military and federal marshalls to break it up, they subsequently opened fire on citizens and killed over 30 people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 23:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KMFDM - WWIII [Industrial] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 23:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most epic run on sentences I've ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of these.  Many are terrible.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> different molecule.  not in epipens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, growing up in the 80s and 90s, I remember the typical grade school lunch for a ton of kids:  Wonder Bread with Oscar Myer Bologna or PB w/ Fluff, Fruit By the Foot or Gushers, Handi Snack Cheese and Crackers, and Ecto Cooler.  Kids today eat so, so, sooooo much better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 07:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because, if you read the article, there's all sorts of 3rd parties involved in the supply chain, which, ironically, Baum actually praised Bresch for talking about.  You can absolutely do what humans always did in the 40s, 50s, and 60s before autoinjectors existed and simply use a syringe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 07:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
The point about insulin pens is that they're highly reliable , the technology/design is already known, they're very rapid,  and they work in quite a similar manner as epipens.  Even adrenaclick exists as a generic alternative to epipens.  Where there's a will there's a way.  Autoinjecting technology isn't a barrier.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 06:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, auto injectors have been around since the 80s, and millions of diabetics use many different brands of pen needles everyday.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More from Baum in another article:

"I like to practice ethical capitalism. It's good business to be empathetic towards customers. It makes financial sense in the long run to behave like this," Baum said.

Baum and others argue that unreasonable prescription drug price increases have helped fuel a precipitous rise in American health care costs.

"This is unsustainable," he said.

That's why Imprimis is planning to go beyond Daraprim and offer compounded alternatives to other "absurdly-priced" drugs.

"We're going to show with clean hands how we can make a huge difference for the health care economy," Baum said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 02:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back then they were a pretty good hardcore punk band.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 23:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NHL 94  wayne gretzky injury scene is literally a documentary of my friends and I back in the day https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z3vHbOilhpc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I don't need to make $19 million a year," Baum said, referring to the big pay package Bresch took home last year.

"Tonight when I go home I'm going to eat a nice piece of fish and the fish I eat isn't any better or worse than what she is going to eat."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Baum, CEO of Imprimis pharmceuticals who previously came out with a $1 alternative to Martin Shkreli's AIDS drug after 5000% price hike, is now going to take on mylan and is plotting to offer a $100 epipen alternative. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you haven't been around this sub for a long time have you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orioles have one of the highest TV ratings out of the entire MLB.  That means the Os have a huge fanbase outside of the city.  Why would people in the suburbs come in to the city and spend money when all people do in the city is bitch about people in the suburbs and are openly hostile to them?  Plus parking and traffic suck balls.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ether literally evaporates almost instantly at room temperature with a lot of surface area.  I have a hard time believe 100 mL is a huge problem after  many minutes when poured down the sink. It is probably all vapor by now.  Just flush the sink with lots of water.  Taking apart the drain etc. seems excessive.  Just don't do it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that because of the ease and relatively extreme secrecy you can open a shell corporation in Delaware, 'companies' routinely make 6 figure donations to Super PACs nearly ever election cycle. DE's corporation laws also help launder money for major criminals all over the world, such as El Chappo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the entirety of grad school when working with undergrads. Somehow someway undergrads will always find a way to epically fuck up. Shit, one time some undergrads broke the laws of physical chemistry and set the inside chamber of a cryomill on fire.  Of you don't know what that is, basically it is a pulverizer for tissue samples that crushes biospecimens under liquid nitrogen.  How the fuck do you set something on fire with an atmosphere of nitrogen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe it is already that old.  I still remember leaving the theater and thinking goddamn, not only was that the best Bond movie in a long time, this was the best damn movie in general that I've seen in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew how fun it'd be shooting people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, that's not the end though. If you don't buy more expensive insulin and go buy it at Walmart some people's insurance companies will claim they aren't buying insulin.  The  insurance company will then stop covering glucose strips, glucose monitoring supplies and supplies for pumps.  That's how perverse our system is--you have to pay more or else you'll be fucked for other reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm OK.  This is a good achievement, but I had a prof who earned his PhD in economics from Princeton at the age of 15.  Were talking hardcore econometrics and stochastic modeling shit too. This will absolutely sound douche, but I have no idea why people found calc so hard.  Breezed right through that shit up to functional analysis.  Some people are just wired for it.  I can barely color inside the lines though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At some point the government is going to have to take over the production of some of the most important medicines with their own GMP facilities so that they can sell medicines to citizens as a non-profit before the entire system goes bankrupt. We wasting millions, if not billions of tax payer money for no reason on technologies and medicines that have been around for 100 years.  Shit, it'll give people jobs and it'll significantly cut down on costs.  We already did it with penecillin 70 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, at this point it might be actually cheaper for the government to step in, build GMO facilities, and start manufacturing its own essential medicines for citizens. It's an insane waste of tax payer dollars to massively overpay for medicines that are over 100 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what's super infuriating ?  Can you guess how much the scientists who discovered insulin sold their insanely valuable patent for?  Go ahead, guess. 









They sold it for $1 to their university because they wanted it for the betterment of mankind and not for profit. 100 years later we are now massively overpaying for a technology that has had no real innovation put into it for nearly a century.  How infuriating is it to know insulin was released to the world with altruistic intentions by its discoverers, yet some greedy entities who put almost 0 work into it have fattened offitike parasites while millions of people can no longer afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've paid ~$300-500 for about 25 pipettes to be calibrated or tested.  Who ever is doing it for you is ripping you off, big time.  A good tech would not calibrate pipettes that don't need to be calibrated, and not charge you calibrating fees for just weighing water.  If you're stuck w/ the company, why not spend 30 minutes testing the pipettes yourself by weighing water, and then only hand over the pipettes that need to be calibrated to help cut down on cost?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one for the wife, and one for myself.  6 gb data.  verizon.  that's with a organizational discount too.  yes, it's expensive.  i've debated moving after this contract.  it used to be $80 a little while ago (5-6 years ago), Verizon has gone insane.  


Still, $170/12 months = $14 per mo.  That's $4-5 per month per person for a family, as the article implies.  Who doesn't have $4-5 per month for each family member for clean water?  Meanwhile people pay for cell phones, buy too many clothes, throw away food, drive cars they can't really afford, go out to eat too much, etc. etc.  $5 extra per month per person?  OUTRAGEOUS!  Did people already forget how much of a clusterfuck of traffic all of those water main breaks over the last 3 years caused from decaying infrastructure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huuuuuuuuuuuuuuge, and my team is completely out of the playoffs.  at least i traded Rondon (closer) for moncada in a keeper league.  something to look forward to while my team is in the gutter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, i forgot to put *more* after the $170.  Still, I pay $1680 for a phone per year.  That's over $1000 more than for clean water.  What's cable, $100 per mo. (I dunno, I don't own a TV)?  That's $1200 a year just to watch crappy TV.  Still almost double than what you pay for clean water to live.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A *family* expects to pay $170 *per year* for fucking water.  Whoop dee doo.  I fucking pay $140 per month just for some stupid ass cell phones; I think water, and having access to clean water, is more important.  If they need it to fix up infrastructure who cares?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, it's a bunch of bullshit  inflated over the years by lore surrounding probably Boston's most beloved baseball player of all time.  There absolutely 0 chance Williams hit with more power than say the likes of a modern guy like Giancarlo Stanton. Have you ever seen the size of Staton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be a long season for Cowboys fans.  Romo need to retire before he can't even shit on a toilet in 3 years and completely untested rookies almost never pan out, in their first seasons at least.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens every year.  Classes haven't started yet, but they'll start to simmer down by Oct.  This weekend will be BAD though.  Expect hundreds and hundreds of kids evvvvvvvvvvvvverywhere on Fri./Sat.  Tons of them in the street and yelling until 4 AM.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reyes to remain in rotation with Leake on DL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard people say good things about the mac 'n cheese at the Cardinal Tavern. Haven't been there yet myself.  It's probably OK to bring a kid there earlier in the evening I'd imagine.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it illegal?  Dumb and boneheaded? Absolutely.  Worse than doing favors for China or Saudi Arabia for money? Absolutely not.  What's more disturbing is the lack of privacy.  Boyfriends can get arrested for publicly posting nudie photos of their exes that were sexted to them, yet Weiner's mistresses can probably make hundreds of thousands leaking texts to tabloids.  He's a horn dog with a sex problem, no doubt, but I couldnt care less.


PS, not even a Trump fanboy either, voted Dem my whole life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 14:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares?  Millions of people sext.  Name something illegal Weiner has done.  I'd rather have Weiner in office than a phony liar that does favors for foreign interests for money like Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made the front page? This shit is everywhere here..   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but it isn't exciting or anything.  

http://imgur.com/a/Upnlp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can't, it's an email sent to DE state employees, FWIW.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heads up from DSP-new scam Occurring in DE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks-
 
     We are starting to have a rash of complaints in which a motorist stops to pick up a purse laying on the side of a sparsely travelled road.  Our suspects then jump out of brush or a cornfield and rob the victim (usually a female).  If you see a purse laying on the shoulder or in the roadway, please do not stop.  Note the location and call 911 so we can go pick up the purse and check the area.  Please feel free to forward to friends and family.
     Take care.
 
John
 
John W. Shoemaker
Delaware State Police </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If everyone does STEM then it won't be lucrative anymore and then art will become lucrative when all but a few people abandon it.  It's all about supply and demand  This shit constantly ebbs and flows, you just have to be in a field before the title wave comes.  Art can pay a shit ton of money provided you learn something useful.  For example, if you combine your art skills with digital work, programming, and web page design, you can make a nice career for yourself.  My bro is a freelance digital designer in NYC; he's the artist of the family.  He makes his own hours.  Works for whoever he wants to.  Takes months off at a time to travel the world if he wants.  He can pull in over 6 figures if he wants to.  You need to find marketable skills and a niche.  Degrees alone are worthless.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 14:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everyone, very useful info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 14:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop.  The STEM shortage is such a myth.  There are no jobs for anyone outside of crappy permatemp gigs and lab technician jobs that pay $32k a year for doing horribly monotonous work.  OK, yes, not all STEM is created equally, STEM really should just be TE.  S and M pay garbage, M is worthless without other training such as in finance, economics, programming, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I thought Millennials were supposed to be environmentally conscious.  Using billions of plastic bottles is a massive waste.  Liquid soaps also have a shit ton more chemical additives, which I though Millennials were scared of, seeing as we're die hards for things like organic foods.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know this is a possibility, but if there's any recommendations of where just to start that'd be helpful. I'm just a student, and I absolutely hate being spammed non-stop by sales reps. The more I can cut down on that the better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations for the most robust chromatography-MS system for metabolomics/proteomics/glycomics analysis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The PI and a few others would like to get together and write a major large instrument grant for a MS system that can do all of the above types of analysis (if possible).  I've been asked to do some research in order to help write this grant.  I'm not an analytical chemist by trade, but have extensive experience with chromatography (not MS though).  Are there any recommendations on what kinds of MS systems to couple to a chromatographic system?  I'm assuming we should be looking for liquid chromatography (not GC, etc?--I dunno, I don't normally do this kind of work and only analyze small molecules).  Should we be looking for MS^n capabilities with ion traps?  It's sort of like a chicken an egg thing--we can't attract experts in proteomics/metabolomics until we have the instrumentation, but we can't get the instrumentation until we have the experts.  But any manufacturers, setups, and types of MS recommendations for routine metabolomics/proteomics/glycomics analysis would be extremely helpful.  Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This place is going to make such a killing.  Finally, a walk to pharmacy in CV.  I think there's also a new Rite Aid that opened up across from the 711 on 28th street too in the new apartments.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've been doing construction on I95 from New Castle down to Xtiana/Newark since the time I was in high school, and they're still not done.  That's been since 1998.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rocket fuel wings at Rocket to Venus are pretty spicy.  I mean we aren't talking Man v Food challenge level or anything though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 20:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except this random redditor has worked in the pharmaceutical industry as a professional biomedical scientist.  You don't have to take my word for it, fine, this is the exact protocol for schools in CA:

http://www.sde.ct.gov/sde/lib/sde/pdf/deps/student/health/steps_in_the_emergency_use_of_an_epinephrine_autoinjector.pdf

9.Take the victim's vital signs (if trained to do so) and record them. Duplicate the emergency card for the paramedics. **When paramedics arrive** tell them the time EpiPen was administered and the dose administered. If EpiPen has not been disposed of in a sharp's container, give the expended EpiPen to the paramedics.

10.If symptoms continue and paramedics do not arrive, use a new EpiPen and re-inject 15 to 20 minutes after initial injection. Continue to monitor the victim's airway and breathing.

11.**Follow-up medical care should be obtained at the emergency room or from the victim's physician**. A second delayed reaction may occur up to 6 hours after the initial anaphylaxis.


because I'm sure CEOs like Shrkelli aren't trying to portray their strategies as nothing but just...sorry, but Epipens absolutely don't entirely prevent the need for hospital visits/ambulance rides at all.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epipens often require multiple dosing and are designed to buy you 10-20 minutes before more emergency response can reach you. Many people still have to go to the hospital anyway and require ambulance rides.  Epipens don't prevent that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.medpluspro.com/owen-mumford-autojectr-2-injection-aid-device.html?gclid=CNGOkMyI4s4CFQpehgodQCUFxg

All you have to do is literally ask your doctor for $10 worth of epinephrine.  Mylan can easily be put out of business if people spend a bit more effort.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  If you can't handle using a syringe on yourself you can use generic, reusable autoinjectors.  Diabetics use pen needles alllllll the time:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GHVtiJ9xd6A

That shit is sold at walmart.  And reusable autoinjectors can easily be bought:

https://www.maxiaids.com/autojector-ii-for-easy-injection?gclid=CPP69OqG4s4CFYpbhgodxCIDqg

That's what's infuriating about Mylan--they literally haven't innovated anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, everyone does know you don't need Epipens right?  You can fucking buy epinepherine for less than $10 with a physician's prescription and a syringe.  You just have to practice using a needle.  You're literally paying $590 for convenience.  Put those assholes out of business and use syringes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shit is absolutely infuriating.  These 'companies' literally aren't innovating anything.  They're just buying up 20 year old tech that saves lives and hike the price.  Why bother innovating anything if it is so easy to become a millionaire at the expense of others?  The worst part is that a shit ton of tech behind EpiPens at some point was probably a result of publicly funded research.  Thanks Skrelli.  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of anything similar, but much more economical, to this Maurizio Baldassari knit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be Oliver peoples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I mention

-all the people who drive around with high beams on at night who are blinding everyone.  It happens multiple times nearly 100% of the time I have to drive at night around Baltimore

-the absolutely bizzare and brazen red light runners, and no I don't mean people trying to beat a light *turning* red. I mean all of the douche bags around here that sit at a solid light that has been red for like 10 seconds who then decide basically 'fuck this' and blow through the light

-all of the double parked cars, especially in Mt. Vernon during rush hour.  Just because you put on your hazards doesn't mean you can park wherever you want and cause a massive traffic jam.

-people who feel the need to drive 65 mph on 28 and 29th streets.  People who feel the need to drive 85 mph on I 83.  Dude, calm down before you kill people

-all the people around here who give  0 fucks and turn right on red at intersections that clearly say NO TURN ON RED.

-people who go 2 mph on the on ramp to 83 from 29th.  Pick up speed, going slow and trying to merge makes it more dangerous.

-the shit ton of people around here who do the opposite of driving with high beams on and simply drive around with no lights on at night.

-the people behind you  who honk  and cuss at you for not running pedestrians over when you have to yield when making a right turn . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget, it was FRANCE too that dragged the US into Vietnam.  That was shit they started.  You think bahn mis on French bread existed before the 20th century? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samuel Parker Clothier--anyone ever shop there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found this place the other day, although it wasn't open.  There were a lot of really nice things in there from what I could tell; does anyone happen to know what price range we're talking about?  I mean I see $$$$ on Yelp, but are we talking like Ralph Lauren purple label prices?  I mean I know the stuff doesn't look cheap and it's Rolland Park and all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said, and I exactly quote, ' video about how you can't turn left at a stop light'.  A.) like you pointed out, you are absolutely allowed to make a left on red from a one way to another one way in nearly every state with a few exception, so the all encompassing claim that you can't turn left at a stop light is wrong.  B.) it doesn't even have to be from a one way to another one way either, for example here's WA driving code:

http://app.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=46.61.055

*Vehicle operators facing a steady circular red signal alone shall stop at a clearly marked stop line, but if none, before entering the crosswalk on the near side of the intersection or, if none, then before entering the intersection control area and shall remain standing until an indication to proceed is shown. However, the vehicle operators facing a steady circular red signal may, after stopping proceed to make a right turn from a one-way or two-way street into a two-way street or into a one-way street carrying traffic in the direction of the right turn; or a left turn from a one-way or two-way street into a one-way street carrying traffic in the direction of the left turn; unless a sign posted by competent authority prohibits such movement.*

In other words, you can make left turns on red no matter what type of road you're on as long as the left you're making is onto a one way road.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 21:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can turn left at stop lights, depending on context. Actually what really sucks are suburban drivers who don't know shit about driving in a city who make it take longer to get where you're going.  Making left turns on red is perfectly legal on many city streets.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 14:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maple syrup smelling urine is absolutely a condition:

https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/000373.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Esmail could take a crap on your TV screen yet the fanboys would eat it up and still vehemently claim.this is the best shit that has ever graced the boob tube.  This season is a goddamn mess beyond belief.  It took 3-4 episodes for Angela to help hack the FBI, and what'd we get? 0 mention of the dark army and some background phone call crap about bearanstain that got blown off after 3 minutes.  A shit ton of FBI agents were literally murdered on Chinese soil and all we have is well time to move on Dom. It took 4-5 episodes to establish e coins were taking over and 6 episodes to reveal what we all suspected--that Elliot is in jail.or in a mental institution.  And worse yet, 8 EPs in and 0 Tyrell, we don't know what Elliott did w the gun, and we still don't know really any Tyrrells wife killed the valet who saw his car after 5/9.  Speaking of which, has Tyrrells wife been around the last 2-3 EPs?  No?  Just more example of bad script writing.

Literally the most incompressible, most disjoint season 2 ever. I like Mr. Robot, don't get me wrong, but it isn't the best show ever.   I get it, fanboys get off on all of the Easter eggs and tech junkie service jobs, but you still have to write a good and coherent drama to captivate the viewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shiiiiiitttt I remember seeing this *in theaters*  as like a 9 or 10 year old, and during this scene the kids weren't crying, it was all the moms and dads who took their kids to see this movie who were cracking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 00:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People forget, we have shit like the neutron bomb in our arsenal, tactical nukes that can control nuclear fall out, and God knows what kind of bio and chemical weapons.  The world has also never seen our cyber WMDs, the NYT wrote a report on Nitro Zeus, a cyber WMD that could have ended Iran without ever even needing to drop a single bomb.  If N. Korea ever even tried to send a rocket to the US it would cease to exist.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our brothers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat will not stop licking lacquered wooden furniture all around the house. Is this harmful, why is he doing it, and can it be stopped? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk chocolate has disgusted me ever since childhood.  Guess I'm just a contrarian. 80%+  chocolate ftw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously thinking about moving to Singapore w/ their $70k GDP per capita and some of the world's best education.  I bet they don't give homework, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlimited moves completely ruins half the game of fantasy baseball.  What's the point of pitching then if you can stream 200 extra innings per week?  No one cares about ERA and WHIP with counting stats on the line.  Absolutely cap moves, we set it at 4 and the league dramatically improved.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoehn's bakery:  best doughnuts ever, but they also make peach cake, blueberry cake, and smearcase that you won't find practically anywhere else.  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically what I imagined it would look like if the aliens from Independence Day started hovering over Baltimore and were prepping for attack:

http://imgur.com/a/FjS8x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a guy in Maryland that does this and has a whole youtube video catalog for you people that love abandoned/rundown building porn:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mEN498DRDpY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive work.  Keep it up.  Love the happy hr section on your page too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL, that although interest compounds on a retirement savings account like a 401(k) so do the fees, and that just a 1% fee can eat away 28% of your returns over the long run. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 02:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HA!!!!!!

You're asking college students to talk adult responsibilities for themselves.  Fat chance.  I had to TA a large undergraduate class, and you would not believe how many students had so much trouble submitting homework on time, understanding the grading to know what the consequences were, or even when some things were even due.  Everything was in the syllabus.....and the best part is that the students get to rip your a good one at the end of the year on course evaluations when they blow chunks and get a bad grade.  It's always someone else's fault for their bad grades, of course.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jackie Chan vs. Benny the Jet Urquidez from Meals on Wheels (one of the best ever): 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H6eC-BAsVdQ

Several scenes from Warrior with Tom Hardy:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dldz_AytSRU

Final fight with Michael Jai White from Blood and Bone (excellent):

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I1wi5Mw6kZI


Scott Adkins also has a shit ton of beautifully choreographed, non-CGI action scenes like this (he should have been Batman too):

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PkCfPjeux5o



You can't make action scenes 'realistic' outside of war films or boxing movies.  One punch to the face will knock a person out a huge percentage of the time, thus a truly 'realistic' fight scene would be quite boring for a movie.  




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to get rid of the concept of insurance all together.  Getting rid of the middleman would be a massive step towards controlling health care costs.  Americans pay absolutely insane prices for health care all just so they can have the luxury of being told by their providers 'No', 'not allowed', 'not covered', or 'not in our network'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, OK.  Still not sure I follow.  The mirror is 200 inches.  Did you even look at the photo of the final product?  200 feet is way off, you think it is the size of 2/3 of a football field?  There are no typos anywhere.  Yes, the mirror is literally 16 feet, 8 inches= 200". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure:

http://www.nytimes.com/2007/08/28/science/28crop.html?_r=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just increase the surface area of the xylem (basically just find a bigger branch) and run more than one filtration.  The advantage is removal of chemicals/small molecules/ and even some viruses.  And we're just talking about a gravity drip, maybe you can rig a device where you can apply pressure with a plunger of some sort.  The only part that needs to be replaced would be adding a branch every once in a while.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is in the paper.  They did 4 liters / day using only a 1cm^2 xylem..which is enough to meet the demands for a single person per day.  From the paper as well:

*This is comparable to chlorination and biosand filtration, which have the highest production rates of prevalent point-of-use water treatment methods, and far exceeds typical production rates for solar disinfection*  

Also, it is possible for wood xylem, in theory, to filter out even viruses.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 07:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MIT already has this beat:

http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0089934


All you need is fresh wood xylem cut from a  tree and not only will it reject 99.9% bacteria, it can remove even some chemical contamination as well.   Why spend all the engineering effort when nature has already done it for you with a gravity drip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 06:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From our local, albeit organic food focused, store.  Maybe a higher end farmers' market or city with a big market might have them right now for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 06:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From MD, but apparently they're from CA and the west coast.  They're one of the earliest apples, so right now in August is the time to buy. They won't be around for much longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 06:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crunchy, more like granny smith flesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, not sure I follow?

http://archives-dc.library.caltech.edu/islandora/object/ct1%3A4509 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly how they made ruby red grapefruit, disease resistant cocoa, and some types of barley for Scotch, peanuts, cotton, peppermint, sunflowers, bananas, and sorghum--they hit the plants with radiation in order to create mutants and looked at and selected the desirable products.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid brosef </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple A mazing!  The flesh is firm.  The taste is a little tart (in a pleasant way) with a berry type flavor.  Very aromatic and flavorful.  A bit expensive but absolutely worth every penny.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A delicious pink pearl apple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 21:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, a TIL inside of a TIL.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the 200" mirror produced by Corning for the Palomar Observatory at Caltech took 10 months to anneal properly. Also, grinding and figuring of the final product for the telescope removed 4.5 tons of glass off the surface to get the correct shape, and it took over 6 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 18:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to make a cut off for this list to get rid of garbage joke entries.  Max: $40-45k, Min:$10-15k.  That would cover 95% of stipends that don't have some special awards attached to it. Post-doc salaries don't count, seeing as this is supposed to be for Phd students.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relatives always bring back craft bourbon.  It's hard to find anything other than JD abroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private investigators, what's the scariest or most disturbing case you've ever worked on in your career? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever lose a job and while you were unemployed had to pay insane COBRA fees, pay for an emergency visit to the doc when your child gets sick, and then your car breaks down, a car that you need to get to job interviews?  Yeah, it's called life and it happens to a lot of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
