<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp Germany you're our last hope. Be the country for everyone else to look up to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah Hitler really had blind support from a mass of people. Trump only has the willfully ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's ridiculous. Wheeler literally lobbies for a coal industry. This is the simplest case of "follow the money" I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah maybe in this case specifically but you might notice that Trump isn't only receiving slack about his policies from Liberals. Many conservatives are holding him accountable for the crap that hes proposing as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's not how it working. These bans are being struck down because there is no basis behind them. There has never been an attack on the US by any nation on his ban list. The only reason he can give for implementing this ban is to keep Muslims out which goes against the constitutional basis of freedom of religion. 

Now if he switched this ban to cover strictly SA there would be no reason for a court to block this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember everybody Watergate took two years to come to conclusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... Is this referring to our current president who is threatening North Korea / China? Cause that's the only thing that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This presidency is bringing Conservatives and Liberals together on more topics than you would think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is the absolute LAST person i would want dealing with the North Korea issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you get citizenship then you have to pay taxes.... without it there's no way to pay taxes...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dudeeeee you're getting old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But where are the live chickens and the steaks? This plan doesn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To maintain some type of quality. Without regulations and testing how would you know if your local sunglass company was using a toxic type of plastic for their new $2 sunglasses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying there's very little regulation on all of those things and in each case you end up with a monopoly. When there's very little regulation companies can cut corners to lower their price and easily end up with a monopoly on a certain demographic. 

When regulations are introduced yes it makes it harder for smaller companies to enter a market but it also makes it harder for larger companies to corner a market thus more competition. 

Take cars for an example. Market is extremely heavily regulated up to the point on where emissions tests are required every year in some states. While its extremely difficult to enter the car manufacturing market there are plenty of competitors because as long as your product can pass quality tests it can be sold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISPs, Meat industry, standardized testing, Textbooks, Sunglasses, satellite radio, and I guess Ill throw in Utility complanies and phone companies but their elasticity can be argued.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's rarely the case. Regulations when used correctly are basic standards that a company has to keep up with. Having theses basic standards leads to competition because companies have to see who can offer these standards while providing the cheapest product. Yes its harder for small businesses to thrive but if a small business has a demonstrable competitive edge they will thrive.

When you eliminate regulation you end up with something like the current cable service provider industry. They have almost no regulation and a very elastic demand yet they are able to provide crappy service and stay in business because they are fundamentally corrupt. They've managed to eliminate competition by making deals with each other and buying out every small company that tries to emerge in the market. More often than not, when you eliminate regulation you eliminate competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media but it honestly makes sense. The GOP has only managed to procure enough money for 1 mile of the proposed wall so far. This seems like the easiest way for them to procure funds. This wall has been estimated at 12-15 billion dollars which is honestly on the low end with hopes that nothing goes wrong. Then after its done you have a yearly upkeep on it. The wall will have a huge impact on our economy.

I'm not sure Trump is so libertarian. Hes libertarian in the terms of less govt involvement and regulation which isn't always a good thing. Without regulation whose to stop companies from gouging the consumer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont really understand libertarianism. You can be a right wing libertarian and believe these cuts arnt far enough. Or you can be a left wing libertarian and believe that they are taking away your freedom of access to such systems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because a lot of Trump supporters believe anything the guy says without any evidence. Its very frustrating to argue with someone who has no evidence for their own remarks but then requires a litany of evidence for yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read the specifics.... where do you see these sectors growing? Only thing I saw growing was defense, homeland security, and veteran affairs (Which i agree upon) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you dont work for minimum wage..... Most jobs that illegals are taking are minimum wage jobs that without illegal low priced labor would of already been automated. I really don't see illegal immigrants breaking into skilled labor markets. And govt assistance programs are usually very strict programs where you would need to fill out a litany of forms requiring proof of citizenship to even apply. The place that illegal immigrants do feed off of are our healthcare system and public schools but those channels are hard to block and our govt seems to not want to fix the system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True but these are some of the few agencies left to help the little man and Trumps trying to cut em out in one swoop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they are not separate issues the money from these budget cuts is going to be used for the building of the wall.

I mean the community who benefit the most from these goverment programs that he is cutting are the lower income community: Agricultral dep (food subsidies), Commerce dept(govt funded state university education), Education dept(cutting from public schools to give to charter and private which are much more expensive to attend), Health and human services(fed funded drug rehab), housing and urban development (everything they do!), labor dept (job centers). A large majority of the population who use govt funded programs come from lower income families. That's who hes cutting from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had nothing to do with the hacks. All they did was spread propaganda till Trump was elected. They found no useful information in those emails. If they had they would of run with what they had and put HRC in a court room. They preyed on the middle of the countries insecurities along with our need for over protective security to promote xenophobia and get Trump elected. If it wasn't emails they would of found some other nonsense to harass her with and she just didn't have a strong back standing populace to count on.

Yes the she was the head of the state department and she shouldn't of circumvented the system for a sake of convenience but she was using a server that was arguably as secure as the state departments just not as often monitored. I mean really this system was set up by secret service for the president! It's not like she was using AOL... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really think a wall is worth cutting subsidies to most of the lower income community? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
