<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject757</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. I'm Mulan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, first paragraph "violation of U.S. immigration law". The law doesn't give a shit what gender you want to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a Russian spy had leaked them, how American would they be then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swamps everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You started with words and then just slipped into REEEE.. Can you pick on issue to discuss as part of a conspiracy or do you just need to go back to /politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've thought about things sometimes too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The joke is that the bureaucracy doesn't stop money laundering. It generates mountains of data that no one ever looks at and pads a substantial amount to the price of goods and services throughout the economy to further grow the Government and continue the cycle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with this theory is that I can't give enough credit to the cabal to have made such a strong fake towards Hilldawg when they wanted DJT all along. The theory looks worse in the light of which candidate was clearly controllable, controlled and who was doing the controlling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good, it's the daily /r_Conspiracy [Russiaroo](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5ubflg/this_sub_is_full_of_idiots_from_rt_d_and_its/)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count sheep until you fall back asleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't heard of these assaults, but the assaults in Cologne and my personal experience in 15 years of regular travel to France and Germany, there's no reason to make things up. Paris in particular has turned into an unfortunate shithole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be the reference. That guy also has no shot and if I know that, JA knows that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the club.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feb. 19th was referenced. You can hold out a sliver until then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early start today. [Here is yesterday's R_Conspiracy RussiaRoo if anyone needs topic ideas](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5ubflg/this_sub_is_full_of_idiots_from_rt_d_and_its/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's conflating and trivializing multiple complex situations. This has nothing to do with wiretaps; it has to do with the handling of said data. I praise wikileaks, I praise the Flynn leak, I think it would be the penultimate to have the call publicly released and let everyone make up their own minds. That being said...

The 3rd separate issue conflated is the White House being infested with subversive treasonists that need to be rooted out and prosecuted. You signed the paper, you passed many men with guns on your way into work, you know the deal. If you're going to leak, don't be surprised when you get frogmarched out for participating in the attempted overthrow of the democratically elected President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equating the term "Chris Cuomo" to journalists like using the n-word.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see a source for that beyond the dude that "thinks he saw Trump on the plane once but didn't talk to him". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way that I can see. Thousands of telling details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no coincidences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banned in the USSR...er..USA... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. why not? Seems like a harmless bunch of jokers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope man, hope, people gotta have something in these chaotic, dark days... 

I hear they are building gulags in Utah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, wait until he moves the embassy and then the real bloodbath begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is he a patsy for? 

Furthermore, I was promised he was a racist and I'm lacking promised legislation. He should at least nominate the Civil Rights Act for abolishment to show some backbone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda late, I was starting to wonder who would make the daily post. Thanks for stepping up! 

[R_Conspiracy RussiaRoo](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5ufkq3/so_we_all_agree_a_republican_can_never_be_a_part/)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, not an OCR friendly font. Good example for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda how I see it also. I was hoping that the FBI and Bannon could team up though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they pushed her out because she was concerned about Flynn back in January. 

Then why not push her out in January instead of waiting for a completely legitimate reason to get rid of her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a truly unique time in American history. The number of people that have seen the man behind the curtain in recently is historic. It's this sort of mass awareness that leads to revolutions and political change like we are seeing now.

I think Nixon was the last time it became public spy vs. spy and then operated as usual with small hiccups (Iran Contra, Lewinsky, Iraqx2, etc..) for the past nearly 40 years and now it appears that it's time for a change. That's as far back as my visibility goes first hand.

In my opinion, people are logical coming to some obvious conclusions for the first time in their lives. They are realizing that wars aren't being fought for freedom or justice and they are just rats in a wheel with very little chance of ever getting off. They are realizing that reality doesn't have to be what those in power tell you it is. Every single person on this earth is just a bag of meat. No bag of meat is quite like another but they are all stuck in basically the same fridge. There are always some number of bags of meat that tell the other bags of meat how they need to live their meaty little lives.

Eventually you reach an age where you are comfortable with your belief system and the moral justification that you maintain to support that. After that happens, when you hear bags of meat telling others how to live, it is plainly obvious that they are just as clueless as you've ever been. They don't have any secret knowledge nor do they prioritize the things that you value the same...e.g., they don't value your kid in the same way you do, and by definition nearly every person is going to live their life with different and competing priorities. You might come to realize that the bags of meat telling others how to live are often the ones that require the most assistance coming to terms with reality.

From there folks started to seek out and find their own truth. Instead of reading a biased article, they scan it for the source, read it themselves and make up their own minds...or as is often the case, realize there is no source. Then people start to see patterns. They see the same words in their headlines "chaos", "dark times ahead", they see bags of meat on TV claiming that they know best and finally this rings out like the warning alarm that so many others still miss.

Then the journey begins; constantly seeking truth, looking for the real story while your own foundation of knowledge grows deeper and more secure ultimately leading to a better society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Narp](http://i.imgur.com/M8NdLga.png)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joseph Clancy Resigns As Secret Service Director...power is shifting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good. I'll bring beer and a pasta side! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CTR Celebration thread!! We beat the idiots, we win!

^(What do we win?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> | She is Chaste.

I smell a conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Introduces an interesting question, without tying it to any leak or incident but "could the White House be bugged"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/offbeat wants their article back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But have you examined the evidence yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many youtubers committing pizzacide today... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sally Yates...gee..where have I heard that name before.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flair would be great. I request at least 19 pieces please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I guess it's exactly like this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great visual. Just need one of those fancy reddit drawers to make it real. 

Should include Jr. and Sr. and maybe Jeb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A section on a website called 4chan where people post things. Similar to this but not really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's both. 

 * It's clear there is a coordinated attack from shills.
 * He brought it on himself and they smelled blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^(That's the joke) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dexter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's going to be a good number of mini-youtube careers that will either take a big hit and be discredited moving forward...or not...and even then, I predict one more full week before the critical mass has turned on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If pizzagate arrests do happen, my ejaculate will properly 'gum' up the works of anything that could even to pretend to oppose it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. There's no shortage of Waste, Fraud and Abuse to go around and I'll upvote this shit every time I see it. There are trillions of unanswered dollars and millions of bad guys living good lives because everyone's too afraid to fucking hurt someone's feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K, Maurice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, huh, 'girlfriend'...sure...I know where the real conspiracy is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really use a cursive font? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should look into Mr. Douglas Perry. I guess he's a touch typist as he doesn't appear to remove his head from Hillary's ass long enough to see a keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your opinion is not a conspiracy. Just normal people shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mofos are all running short on wolf calls...I'll give it a week, two max and everyone's going to turn on these guys. 


Per Trump himself, "eventually you need to deliver the goods". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the conspiracy is that why out of the thousands of existing pipelines in the US that this one is special? Who's funding the protest movement and who stands to lose money? Latest I've heard is something about Warren Buffet having control of the railroad routes so that might be one place to start looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A senior National Security Agency official 

Literally not a source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's literally not new. Same with PG posts where they just keep rereading the same 4chan LARP like it's news. 

I would hope someone in this sub would be able to read an article with a critical eye and figure the parts that are being said because they are based on something vs. the parts the author is just making up or talking about trying to paint a setting but have nothing to do with the topic he claims to he writing about. Articles like this lack substance and are seething with hate and the intention is clear...to some but not all it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring something new. It's the same source that it's always been and now they are just referencing themselves in a sourcing circle jerk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN and Wash Po as sources. I'm convinced! [Clearly couldn't be an agenda there](http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2017-02-11/amazon-discloses-iranian-transactions-may-have-violated-us-sanctions-warns-it-may-be). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then stop playing hide and seek with JA and hide the sausage with obtuse clues.

They bring this on themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that this sub is a combination of contributions from the subscribers. I have not heard of Mill Gill. Perhaps you should post something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm impressed. He held off for 5 paragraphs before bringing up Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would find equating the term "Chris Cuomo" to journalists like using the n-word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: literally fucking "sources". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or we can drop them in with the cannibals just like recently happened in Venezuela. 

They make sure they are properly handled...at barely  medium rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah. It's pretty backwards to say "wow, those good thing those guys were safe and comfortable while being paid to not do their job". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But divided up so that everyone can only be around people their own age to make it extra frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck did you find that title? Oppositeville?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizzagate 'defendant' appears... would have been a more accurate title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the effort, however, mirroring so many posts in this sub, ain't noting till there's something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Exciting story today"...talks about story 6 days old... getting tired of youtube people based upon reading things that people should have already read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew of Alexa, knew of Bezos but hadn't mixed the two. Toss in the CIA and now we've got a stew going! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird...I was just thinking that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I come here quickly to make the first comment that comes to my mind and I find it's the most unoriginal comment in the thread made hours ago and noticed by hundreds. I'm just a dot in a bell curve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Obvious choice for a woke generation: TrumpCoins. 

More Neal Stephenson than Douglas Adams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump Bucks...could be out of a Douglas Adams book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep hanging onto that high ground. It may be all you have soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too shall assume the position of sneering at those that believe in something after researching it. It's the best of both worlds. I reap the benefits if everyone's correct while getting the satisfaction of being a smug asshole in the meantime. PG8'ers are suckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for more /r/politics bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump this, Trump that, stop treating /r/conspiracy like your /r/politics shitting ground please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary lost.

There's still time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Written by a Brit that thinks [the Kremlin rigged the election](http://www.cnn.com/2016/11/02/opinions/kremlin-trying-to-rig-election-nimmo-opinion/index.html) with an org with [shady corporate funding](http://thehill.com/policy/defense/282047-atlantic-council-releases-foreign-donor-list-for-hagel):

 "One problem with the Atlantic Council letter is that it omits individual contributors, which were specifically requested," the aide said.

"We have no idea if funds came through individuals from foreign nations that could create conflicts of interest," the GOP aide said. "He doesnt have a right to keep such potential conflicts hidden." 

Let's dig into "Atlantic Council" a bit more...see if there might be a pattern here...

Members include anti-Israel pieces like [A Middle East Agenda for Hillary Clinton](http://www.atlanticcouncil.org/blogs/menasource/a-middle-east-agenda-for-hillary-clinton).

And keep looking...Ahh, here we are, ["Thank You, George!"](http://www.atlanticcouncil.org/blogs/ukrainealert/thank-you-george)...bet you can guess who "George" is on the first try...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude in a wheelchair.

Someone sitting on a bench.

Dude a with a big eye and mouth sitting on a white ball.

Seal balancing a ball.

Cream coming from a dispenser.

Snakes eating eggs. 

There's a poop joke in there somewhere.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the premise but we don't need a new post every time someone else rereads the 4chan post on youtube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting mediamatters is a bold move Cotton; let's see how it pays off.

Meanwhile, hard hitting journalism about some angry dudes tweets. 

He's is probably pissed AJ stopped talking about PG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which part? 

"presented with exactly two choices: pro-Israel, anti-Muslim and pro-Muslim, anti-semitic."?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pro-Trump. [Here's mine](http://i.imgur.com/RuzzPL0.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikileaks recently tweeted a 9/11 reference which created some chatter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing there are countries still willing to allocate public money to killing babies in other countries.

I wouldn't know what to think of the world otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens to us all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I promise they don't care. 

Someone might pretend to care, but it doesn't matter as no one is going to get paid any less because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's your source](http://archive.is/dyLv3). All the youtubers are just reading this to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this is going to be well received...just a theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably right. People are just delusional. Idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for doing this. Great thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and me both. This one is a classic. I think about it from time to time and weigh current technology against the problem.

It probably wouldn't be too unreasonable to dig down that far now for some eccentric rich person. 

Then again...we'll have Geraldo's vault too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you really have to pick?

Right now, yup, you really have to pick. I was really angry about this for awhile but I've gotten over it a bit now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhh, stop pointing at the propagandists. They'll ban you from something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I could be wrong, but I don't recall Gonzales, Ashcroft, or Reno being called racist/sexist.

Cool, but that doesn't invalidate my point.

 It's not apples to apples. The transition team didn't have their shit together at all with the disclosures required by the ethics committee.

Fake news. Forms were in within hours. That is clearly not was is causing the delay as Dems publically and dramatically drag every possible window to the max the law allows; again not because it will make a difference, but only to appear as a literal impedance to the progress of anyone that wants it.

 Trumps ideas and some of the people he's choosing to enact them are fairly radical compared to the mainstream politics of the past (that's what got him elected), so of course there's going to be a lot of resistance. I actually think it's healthy. Why have hearings at all if they're just going to get a rubber stamp?

They disagree with administration by definition. We get it. They literally don't have the votes to stop it, so, yep, might as well rubber stamp since we literally can't do anything else except whine at a cost of literally millions of dollars per day in lost productivity. 

 I'll re-phrase. Do you think it's possible that there are pro-trump factions flooding these communities with the idea that sessions alone can bring us justice here, to increase public support for his nomination getting passed?

"These communities" are being flooded by bots and propaganda from both sides...and it doesn't matter. We aren't voting and we aren't making the laws. We're just addicted to trying to shape and control the smallest sliver of the world that we might be able to control...our information bubble.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I believe you're right that the left would fight any pick, but they will fight especially hard against a pick that appears to fit the "racism" narrative. I don't want to get into the "republicans are right democrats are wrong" type of discourse.

Every choice would have fit a racism or sexism angle. Few folks are accused of racism or sexual assault until they run against Democrats. See Trump, Huckabee, Thomas, etc...old tricks are old.


 Republicans were equally as oppositional, and I'd say more so, with the backing of tea party conservatives , when Obama came into office. Both parties put forward "deals" (aka legislation) that intentionally include provisions and riders that are unpalatable to the other side. That way they can say, "see? they can't agree to anything we propose!" 

You can say that, but the simple truth is that the Democrats have turned this into the longest cabinet approval process in history. Literally every single cabinet had been approved by the President's fouth week.


 What do you think makes him the best man in Trump's eyes? This is the heart of my question. 

Trump has stated this.

 And a follow up: do you believe it's plausible that the "Sessions is the key" narrative is just a little too politically convenient? I'm not here to bicker, I'm asking genuinely.

I'm not sure what this means.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Who are the "good guys" 

People that would have approached him and told him to chill as he was going to screw up an active op.

 and what do you mean something big

An active op.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told you it was a clue. Are you stating that Amnesty International is pro-Israel or misrepresented somehow?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
