<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 01:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hnnngggg Back To Baghdad was so fun when I was a kid. Does it still hold up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 01:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Road to Wrestlemania, if you're into that. I kind of replace football with UFC, WWE and NASCAR. I don't watch other sports until the playoffs. Mostly because the Red Wings aren't televised a lot where I live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 18:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hunter, Bishop, is a very calm young man. He wants to do what is right but sometimes his own goals get in the way. He gave up on doing the right thing after the death of his lover. A wanderer, Bishop traveled the world in search of a purpose. He was a bodyguard for a nobleman and also a mercenary for quite some time, some would say he was a natural. After a job gone wrong that resulted in the death of a child, a price was placed on his head. The hunter became the hunted. He fled the region and eventually made his way to Yharnam where he knew that nobody would be looking for him. Shortly after his arrival he went to a popular clinic in Yharnam hoping that the stories he heard about the blood were true. After waking up with a newfound power and purpose, Bishop is at peace doing the one thing he knows best...hunting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I'm not the only one. But I thought that Claiborne was gonna be the next great corner. I thought he was gonna be top five by now. 

He is in my Madden franchise. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 17:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I had no idea the 49er defenses were that good. Which one do you think was the best? 14.2 PPG is pretty amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 16:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I fantasize about what could have been had Dallas actually drafted him. 

I have to change my pants now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 17:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a Metal Gear Solid themed team. 

The weapons specialist: The Boss

The stealth specialist: Solid Snake

The juggernaut/tank/heavy: Colonel Volgin 

The getaway driver/pilot: EVA

The tactical specialist: Big Boss

Replacing Healer with a second heavy: Vamp

The long range marksman: The End 

The logistics specialist: Ocelot

The hacker: Otacon

The cannon fodder: Sunny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 04:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I guess it did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 02:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chip cuts Navarro Bowman for looming better in a sweater vest than him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 21:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But again, it is hindsight. Like you said I probably would have bought it anyway, but I like to think that I wouldn't. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly if I had waited and seen the gameplay and how much the new dialogue system simplified the role playing aspects I would have borrowed it from a friend instead. It's what I did for Dark Souls 2 (which to me was disappointing). Again this is all hindsight talking, but if I had just seen the intro quest with the minutemen and starting off with power armor I would have been wary of purchasing it. It was at that point while playing that I was already losing interest. FO4 seemed (for lack of a better word) casualized. I think now I know how Elder Scrolls fans felt between Morrowing-Oblivion-Skyrim with how simple they had made everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 17:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buying it? Most likely. I've been grinding through Bloodborne to prepare for DS3 and I'm excited to play a new FromSoft game. 

Preordering it? Not a chance. I hadn't preordered a game since Colonial Marines until Fallout 4 came out and that was a mistake. I thought,"Fallout is one of my favorite game series ever, there's no way this preorder won't be worth it." It wasn't. I played through it once and haven't touched it since. Did I get my money's worth? I guess so. But I don't want to get burned again. I won't even risk it for DS3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 22:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most large dogs can kill a human.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 18:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe team success had something to do with it. Either way that is strange and is one of the reasons why pro bowl bids are starting to become worthless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 18:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna say the top one. Which is ridiculous. It seems to me that pro bowls are popularity contests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 18:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They meant a lot more before everyone and their mother became alternates. All Pros are still significant though, and Welker has Edelman beat on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 16:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 01:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily Melo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 09:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 22:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't help that he repeated himself like 3 times. Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 18:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephen A "Now I tell ya skip, 'Famous' Jameis Winston is mah brother! But he's on a slippery slope being just like my other brother Jamarcus Russell if he don't step his game up!"

Skip "Did you just say something about MY Buccaneers!?" 

You can replace Jameis with any other QB and the Buccaneers with any other team and it'll work. Jesus Christ this show is more cookie cutter than a cookie cutter shark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first NFL game I ever saw in person. It was fucking amazing. I remember the disbelief when they iced the first kick. My dad and my uncles were upset as all hell. Then he made the second kick and it felt like we cheered for years. I'll always love Nick Folk for that moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 00:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a HUGE Alien and Predator fan so my scores might be higher than most, I'm going to rank them by movie individually. But here we go:

Alien: A-
Aliens: A+
Alien 3: B-
Alien Resurrection: C

Overall: A

Predator: B+
Predator 2: B
Predators: B

Overall: B

I like the Predator flicks as action/popcorn/bro flicks. I enjoyed Predators more than most people I know, but I'm a sucker for these two franchises. Aliens is probably one of the best scifi movies ever made and Alien is a classic horror film. Alien 3 was a return to the roots of having just one Alien and while Resurrection was definitely the weakest of the series it has its moments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching Pro Wrestling since I was a kid. I got burned and quit watching WWE when Edge retired and got back into it when Daniel Bryan won the title. I'd say it is definitely still that popular if not more popular thanks to YouTube, WWE Network and the newly formed NXT.

Recently I started watching Lucha Underground and it's some of the best wrestling I've ever seen.

I personally love wrestling because it takes me back to when I was a kid. And I have fun hanging out with my bros, having a couple beers and watching some guys beat each other up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, I can't imagine a lot of the pundits would vote for him after the "...so I don't get fined." stunt he pulled last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I understand that. I guess it's a good thing that I'm not a voter :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the offseason and I'm not patient lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see the data but I would rather have Megatron than about 25 of those guys. You can't honestly think that Joey Galloway and Donald Driver are better than him right? Muhammad and Roddy White? Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point, but for the sake of the post let's just assume he is due to all the reports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd put Megatron in my top 25 at least. Who would you take ahead of him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 16:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anyone currently in the league that you WOULD consider HoF worthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Beast Mode and Megatron retiring, where do they rank all time for their respective positions? Also, where would you rank other players that will be retiring in the next year or so on the all time list? (eg Fitzy, Boldin, Smitty etc) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 15:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of want to start the offseason with some discussion on the veterans of the league. I'm sure the retiring of Lynch and Johson caught everyone off guard. Where do you guys have them on the all time list and would you consider either of them to be hall of famers? Feel free to include other players near the end of their careers as well. 

I personally think that Megatron should be in the hall. He holds the record for most yards in a season, game and was the most dominant receiver in the league for most of his career. 

I'm unsure about Lynch. If I could put him in I would simply just for having the greatest run by a player in NFL history, along with some of his accolades, but I can understand why some people wouldn't. 

I realize we had the Case for Canton series within the past year but there may have been some players that you feel should have been discussed that weren't. 

So, what do you guys think? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 20:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go friend. 

https://youtu.be/UuIjbNkBDAw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 20:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eli Manning. I love that mouth breathing playoff destroyer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 07:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/JaguarGator9 I seriously love everything you post and appreciate all the work you put into everything. This one was a really good read. Thanks man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 06:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's Gretzky and IMO it's not even close. 

Is there an argument for Roger Federer? I hear his a lot. I'm more of a Djoker guy myself but I think the top two ever are Agassi and Federer and you can make an argument for either. 

And in my personal opinion KAJ is the GOAT over MJ, but that's just me. MJ has the titles and the media presence, but I feel like Kareem is better. But he also played in a less competitive era maybe? Idk, I'm not a huge basketball guy. 

What about NASCAR? The only two I can think of are Richard Petty and Dale Sr. Maybe Jimmy Johnson as well. 

What do you guys think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 13:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a blowout. IIRC there was an American football World Cup type thing that happened in the last year and the players for the American team were like D2/D3 college guys and they steam rolled everyone. Those are guys that probably WONT EVEN MAKE IT TO THE NFL! Using the 2015 All Pro team the US stomps everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 12:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha what is this bot for?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 12:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R1) Where exactly in the Mojave? If it's down south near Goodsrpings and Primm I can see it doing some damage due to the gangers and the civilians there. But once you go up north near McCarran and the Strip it'll be a bit tougher. And if the Deathclaw and alien fight once and it isn't over quickly I can see one of the two retreating. I'd like to imagine a Xeno-Deathclaw hybrid :o

R2) Hmm. I think it's pretty even. I'd give it 6/10 to the queen just because of her tail. If she can get a lethal strike with a tail she's got it. Death claws are smart but their usual method of attack is charging forward. 

R3) same a above 6/10 queen. 

BR) oh shit. I'd love to watch these unfold. I think replacing the Deathclaws with Xenos would be pretty devastating. The ultimate death bringing creature along with the creatures it could impregnate (Yao-Guai, super mutants, Nightcrawlers) would devastate both the east and west coast. I can see the Xenos being a bigger threat because of that and the fact they reproduce on a larger scale IMO 

As far as the Deathclaw goes in the alien universe:

Alien: I give it to the Deathclaw 8/10 times. IIRC the only weapon on board of the Nostromo is a flamethrower. That isn't gonna be enough. Their only hope is getting it out of the airlock, but I feel like it'll kill everyone before they can react. Or if you want to be specific, the Nostromo wins 10/10 times by leaving when they realize that Kane got eviscerated by a giant lizard. :p

Aliens: The way Hudson says,"Just another bug hunt." During the debriefing leads me to believe that the colonial marines are used to killing creatures. I think they were shaken up in aliens because they were stealthy. If you've ever played the fallout games you'd know that deathclaws aren't very stealthy. I feel like they'd be able to kill all of them with minimal to moderate casualties. They got tactical smart missiles, phase-plasma pulse rifles, RPGs, they got sonic electronic ball breakers! They got nukes, they got knives, sharp sticks... 8/10 Colonial Marines

Alien 3: They're fucked. The Deathclaw won't stop after each kill, it'll just keep killing. 9/10 DC

Alien Resurrection: This one is tricky. The aliens don't really become a factor until the break out, and they only break out because of the acid blood. Deathclaws don't have acid blood. The have razor sharp claws, but I don't think that the corporation would put them in cages that they can slash their way out of. If they can't get out of the cages it's 10/10 Resurrection. If they can I give the deathclaws a decent chance. 7/10. Only because they won't be as unified as the aliens and aren't as tactically adept. 

AvP: Predators stomp. Deathclaws are a much easier target to hit. 

AvP Requiem: US military stomps, I don't even think they'd have to glass the city of it were deathclaws. Plus having an elite predator hunt a bunch down helps too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 12:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually ship Craig and Tweek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 18:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember to never touch OxyCodone. I stay in college. I save my money. I spend more time with my Grandfather. I go out more because now I know that the people that I didn't think we're my friends actually were so I have no excuse to stay home and get high all the time anymore. I smile more. Granted, it's only been two years, but a lot happens in two years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 16:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear. I'm gonna start a new run once I get the two DLCs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 15:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! :) Hope it's stayed away since then!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 15:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game was my GOTY for 2015. I really enjoyed the story even though that was a complaint I was reading about online. The combat was fun and micromanaging equipment is my shit, experimenting to find the best load out for each member of the party and then experimenting to use the best tactics and learning how to fight certain mobs, man I had a blast with this game. 

The only complaint I have is that the bosses weren't very challenging, specifically the final boss. It was disappointing that the dungeons leading up to most of the bosses were more difficult than the bosses themselves. 

I recommend this game to anybody looking for a new RPG to pump time into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 13:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 11:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitch Hedberg. IIRC it's from his CD "Mitch All Together."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's gonna get strong with all the quarter pounders he'll be lifting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 06:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we factor in stats with this? I enjoy the "holy" Greatsword of Artorias with 40/40/40/40, if I recall correctly the only weapon that beats it in AR is Grant with 40 STR and 40 FTH. I think with everything 99 Grant has the highest AR. But if you mean DPS it may be the PGS with like you said the bleed plus the high attack speed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 23:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are...other websites?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely Yoren and Oberyn for me. I also really liked Marsi. At least Yoren had the most badass death in the series. 

"I always hated crossbows...take too long to reload!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 02:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as Super Bowls that I've seen live. Hmm. 


Probably the Saints v Colts Super Bowl. It had:

1) Brees finally getting a ring
2) The ballsiest way to start the second half of a super bowl
3) My neighbor and his son (an Indy and a NO fan) were arguing the whole game at our SB party

Close second is last years but that's just because I have a hard on for Brady and the Pats. The interception to seal it is my favorite SB moment ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 11:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that my council was in a perfect world, not when everyone is vying for the throne.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit! I didn't even THINK of Sam as Grand Maester. Damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 13:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh I really like Davos as Hand of the King. I never thought about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ALL SPOILERS] If there is any character that you could put on the Iron Throne who would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 12:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that I'm probably posting too much but to be quite honest my only friend that watches this show is my father and I like discussing with people on this subreddit a lot more.

In all honesty I'd pick Aemon Targaryan to be the king. I feel like if he was on the throne rather than the Mad King Robert's Rebellion never would have happened. Unfortunately that means that a lot of the characters that we love probably wouldn't exist. 

Aemon is kind, wise and very observant. I think he would have been a great fit. 

Another character that I would like to see on the throne is Stannis Baratheon. He seems like he would be the best at Protecting the Realm. He understands the threat of the White Walkers and doesn't take any bullshit from anybody. 

Who would you guys like to see on the Iron Throne?

EDIT: I'm going all in on Stannis, considering that some characters probably wouldn't exist within the timeline of Aemon being the king.

You can also include the small council if you would like. My dream small council (implying that it is a time of peace and there wouldn't be any families trying to usurp the throne) would consist of:

Hand of the King: I'd probably go with Davos, as /u/rayluaza pointed out, Davos is intelligent and also has a commoner's perspective.

Master of War: I'd have to go with Tywin Lannister. The Lannister army is one of the best in the 7 kingdoms and he has been at the helm for over 30 years.

Master of Coin: Petyr Baelish. A self made man. Even though the crown was in debt while he was master of coin I feel like he would do a decent job, I wouldn't know who else could be Master of Coin, maybe Tyrion?

Master of Whisperers: Gotta go with Varys. He has little birds all around the known world and always knows what is going on. He's the man

Master of Laws: Ned Stark. Honorable, wise and just. "He who passes the sentence swings the sword." I couldn't think of anyone better. 

Master of Ships: Balon Greyjoy. Assuming that he would be willing. Being the Lord of the Iron Islands I would think that he would have plenty of knowhow considering Naval warfare.

Lord Commander of the Kingsguard: Gotta go with Ser Barristan. Well respected and has won the most single combats in history.

Grand Maester: Pycelle. Even though he's plenty sleazy, he serves the crown justly. Just as he had been doing before the show started.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I completely forgot about this post and was going through my history and found this. Thank you so much good sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 04:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would've been cool if he was friendlier to Dany but the closer and closer they got to Westeros the more he started to try and get rid of her. I didn't like him but I enjoyed him, kind of like Joffrey. I wish he lasted until at least season 2 just to see more of his side of the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS ALL] If there is one dead character that you could bring back to life who would it be and why? Book and/or TV show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 03:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would bring back Ser Barristan Selmy. I feel like show watchers got the short end of the stick for Ser Barristan because if I recall correctly he's still alive in the books. I was incredibly happy when he joined Dany and I feel like he didn't get to do much of anything. His death hit me hard as well, it seemed cruel that he gets killed by a bunch of nobles with daggers. I want to see more of his badassery and I feel that he could have been one of the best advisors for Dany. 

I know I picked a character from the show but feel free to pick someone from the books as well. I'm excited to see everyone else's opinion on the matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 03:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Was it Beric that said "Every time I come back I lose a piece of who I was" or something along those lines? Hopefully that doesn't happen to Jon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 03:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link! I'll definitely be checking that out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. I forgot about that. I miss Ned :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't mind the Boltons. I know they betrayed the Starks and flay people and such, but there's just something about them I like. Roose is intimidating as hell and Ramsay is unpredictable as hell. I enjoy every second that they're on the screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive me for my ignorance but when you say one of the children Ned was trying to save do you mean Joffrey? What exactly do you mean by that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 02:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that with everything Sansa has gone through she'll be either extremely relieved to see him or extremely hesitant. I'm hoping she's relieved, but due to how her life has been since Ned was executed I will understand if she is nervous to be too relieved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ALL SPOILERS] Neat little connection I made earlier during a rewatch. Also, discussion concerning character comparisons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 12:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know about what happened to Theon and his transformation into Reek. His motivation for making his rash decisions were to finally earn the acceptance of his father. He wanted to live the Ironborn way by taking what he wanted, unfortunately it backfired.

Here we come to Ramsay Snow. While his father was fighting in the War of the Five Kings and presiding over Harrenhal, Ramsay was toying with Theon and eventually turned him into Reek. Eventually Ramsay earned the favor of his father and earned the name Bolton. 

What I find interesting is the contrast between the two men. We have Theon, the rightful heir to the Iron Islands and throughout his interactions with Ramsay he becomes completely disowned by his father (some would say he already was but I think at this point there is no going back as the only one in his family that cares for him is Yara) while Ramsay finally becomes appreciated by Lord Bolton. 

It just seems funny that they travel down the same path (trying to make their father proud). One succeeds and another fails. I'm not sure if that was on purpose or not but I've watched the whole series multiple times and finally noticed. 

On that note. Are there any other comparisons or contrasts between two characters that you might have noticed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 14:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO BUT THEY GOT TWO COLOREDS IN THE FOREGROUND </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the Pats would give him an honorary Super Bowl ring? I'm pretty sure the Colts did that with Edge. I think it'd be pretty cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 04:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably. I don't really know how any of it works. It does get annoying to because it doesn't warn you until you're out of data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 01:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had Madden exceed that a few times. Especially with how many franchises I play and each franchise has about one or two auto save files with it. Plus all of my rosters and extras.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 09:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! This is perfect! Thank you so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 11:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think he has the potential to be a primary target for Mariota going forward? Or is the jury still out on that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting a new play through. Anyone have any weird but useful builds that you would recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 11:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I've been playing Dark Souls since the beginning. It completely consumed my life from my sophomore year of high school up until my freshman year of college and after a six month hiatus I'm picking it back up to play through it one more time. Are there any fun unconventional builds that you guys have tried out that you would recommend? I've done a fair amount of playthroughs but they usually ended up being DEX builds just with different weapons each time. I really just want to try something new, anyone wanna help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi all! I didn't follow the Titans as much as I usually do this season (Cowboys fan but my Grandfather had been a fan since the days of the Oilers) how did Dorial Green-Beckham perform this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 11:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stats only tell so much of the story. He was my favorite rookie WR coming into this season. I'm a big fan off tall physical guys and he fit the picture perfectly. I didn't hear much about him on Reddit or ESPN this year so I figured I'd come here. 

Also if these types of posts aren't allowed and has to be removed I understand.

Thanks in advance! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 10:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my quarterback. :')  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 10:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tough to pick just one. 

I LOVE Brady. Fitzgerald and Boldin are also some of my favs. Watching those two in Arizona was a match made in heaven. Antonio Brown is phenomenal as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 10:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can also have Greg Hardy fight a drop bear. 

I got $50 on the drop bear as long as Hardy isn't allowed to bring a bed of assault rifles. Hell, even if he is allowed a bed of assault rifles I still got $20 on the drop bear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 10:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same thing but I think I read somewhere that the pro bowl gets better ratings than some playoff games for other sports. I could be wrong though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey all! Looking for a midrange gaming laptop, details inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 07:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **LAPTOP QUESTIONNAIRE**

* Country of purchase: USA

* Budget range: $700-$1000

* Purpose (netbook, ultraportable, mainstream, gaming, desktop replacement, etc.): Portalble gaming

* Screen size preference: 13" is what I'm used to. I wouldn't have a problem with going up to 17" though. 

* OS preference (Windows/Mac/Linux): Windows

* Gaming requirements (list example games and desired fps/settings): I play CSGO, Diablo, Fallout (3,NV and 4), Skyrim, Witcher 3. I also want to use this to emulate too mostly consoles PS2 and earlier. 

* Other performance requirements (video editing, CAD, etc.): nothing else really. I'd like if to have a built in mike though. 

* Portability requirements (constantly carried, frequently moved, mostly stationary, etc.): the size or weight isn't too important. It's going to be transported every other day. At least once a week. 

* Brand preferences and reasons (already owned accessories, familiarity, business compatibility): no bias here. Any brand works for me. 

* Any particular style that you like (examples are great): again, as long as it works. 

**Which of the following qualities would you prefer? (Choose one or two)**

* Long battery life -vs- Low weight -vs- High performance: performance over everything. 

* Build quality -vs- Low price: low price

**List any critical features:**

I think I already mentioned but a built in cam/Mike are almost a must have. 

**Which features would you pay a premium for?** (eg. high resolution screen, great keyboard/touchpad/audio, low noise/heat): high res screen definitely. 

If I didn't post this correctly just let me know. Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 20:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he leak those pictures on one of those EX girlfriend sites? There are so many of those out there! Which one!? Which one did you post them on!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. That's like a Madden game lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn! Brady went off that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on guys don't downvote him. It could have easily been autocorrect.

I didn't get to see that game (I was still a toddler) what was the reaction like from the media during and after the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recency bias aside that's one of my favorite super bowls I've ever watched. We had a super bowl party at my house and I was one of the few people that bet on Seattle to win. Ended up with about $40 at the end of the night. And sorry about last weekend :( I was pulling for you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured this would be the top if not one of the top answers but it still blows my mind thinking about it. Poor Marino. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn! That Bills team must have gotten far huh?

(I'm so sorry /u/98_Vikes hurt me and I had to take it out on somebody, I secretly like the Bills) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just the shit-icing on the shit-cake for Marinos career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! I have no memory of football from then (I was only 7) but that's insane. Were the Jets favored in that game or was that game out of nowhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( y u do dis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I feel like a dick because I never replied. Sorry man! And yeah, even though I believe that, I feel like its up to the lore/canon of The Last of Us universe. We really don't know how large the Fireflies actually are. We know that they're prevalent enough to cause pseudo-terrorist attacks in Boston, and there are pendants EVERYWHERE throughout the game. I feel like if the Fireflies are large enough to have a presence in most (if not all) quarantine zones and have a few more outposts other than the one in Utah (or wherever it is in the end of the game, hadn't had my coffee yet lol) I feel like they'd be able to get a lot accomplished. But considering that Marlene requests two freelancers (Joel and Tess) to transport Ellie it's easy to assume that isn't the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In your opinion, what was the most one sided playoff game in NFL history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it's the week before the Championship week and it's going by PAINSTAKINGLY SLOW I'd like to drum up some discussion on what the community thinks is the most unfair/one-sided playoff game ever. Whether defined by margin of victory or talent between the two teams, I want to see what everyones opinions are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 12:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every parent ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 20:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude they have that already. Ever heard of NFL Play60? /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 10:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you meant. And yeah, getting points nearly every time you cross the 50 would be a ridiculous advantage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 10:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Id like to see the Pats win because Brady is my favorite non Cowboy of all time. Seeing him win is the next best thing to seeing Dallas win. 

2b) It would be amazing to see Palmer and Fitzy and even CJ2k finally get rings. And Arizona too. 

2c) Carolina would be nice because Cam is the man. Along with Allen, Davis, JStew, Peanut Olsen and Allen, I'd be really happy seeing them get a ring. 

3) ISIS

4) Denver. I don't like Manning. I don't like how he's invincible. Any criticism of Manning is met with backlash. I'm bitter about Ware going to a contender. And my ex is a Denver fan. So fuck 'em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 10:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy Vegas through me for a loop. Holy shit hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 20:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Shouldn't Be Here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 08:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 07:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can make more than one seasonal character right? This is my first time playing a season before and I'm worried that I'll be stuck with a character I don't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think many people other than Central Mew Yorkers will know what I'm talking about. But I was going to school at the community college right next door to a juvenile detention center where a kid broke out. My friends and I were walking through the cross country trail smoking and we heard sirens go off and dogs barking (you can literally see the detention center from the trail, there's a barbed wire fence separating the jail yard from the trail) and we started freaking the fuck out. We put all of our weed away and started walking further away from the jail and my residence hall. About five minutes later I get a call from my uncle (higher up at the college) who was freaking out making sure I was alright. We go back to the residence hall about 15 minutes later to find out the kid tried to rob one of my other friends of his phone and my friend beat the dogs hit out of him. The kid ended up fleeing into downtown Syracuse and got caught a day or so later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks. How do you like 16? Should I finally replace 15? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I really enjoyed 8 and 9, they weren't the best seasons but they were still pretty good. Better than most shows IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 06:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DLC is definitely worth getting. My favorite character was definitely Joel. I feel like the contrast between him and Tommy represents the contrast between my brother and I. We always disagree and do things our own way but there's always one thing that we come together on. And as far as keeping Ellie with the Fireflies I have to disagree. I think even if they did manage to find a cure it would be a lost cause because of how messed up the world is already. If you want you can join us over at 
/r/thelastofus for more in depth discussion! 

Almost forgot. As far as praise goes, this game definitely deserved all of it. The only thing I didn't like too much was the combat but even then it had its moments. Near perfect game IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bahamut Zero from FFVII. 

Nuke it from orbit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaaaaat. I really enjoyed seasons 8 and 9. What didn't you like about them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 00:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We hate it too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
