<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3775</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He checked his staff as airline luggage and the airline misdirected it. Killing time, waiting for the magic to come back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fifth ranked source of "immigrants" is Puerto Rico. Somebody needs to tell the authors PR is US Territory. Not a state, but everyone born there is a US Citizen, issued a US passport, able to freely travel anywhere in the US without any administrative restrictions, just like any other US Citizen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So would be helpful to have a level headed Turk give a reasoned argument why the Turkish government cares so much. The events which some call a genocide and the Turks argue wasn't one occurred when the country that is now Turkey called itself The Ottoman Empire. That country was dismembered into parts of Syria, Iraq, Romainia, Macedonia Palestine Lebanon, Greece, Cyprus, Georgia and Armenia during and at the end of WW I. The country Turkey was formed by a revolutionary government from the remaining rump territory of the empire.  It can easily be disavowed as the acts of an overthrown government of a now nonexistant country. Why should modern day Turkey care? By protesting so much, it gives very much the perception that Turks today have something to hide. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 15:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Professional bear tickler kids, don't try this at home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fawn has rows of tiny nose spots, mirroring the ones on its back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 03:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what the person interviewed claimed. They said the 9 second delay before the actual answer they gave was deceptive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't watch but the article indicated the thing the activist complained about was a 9 second gap in question and answer. No change in activist's words, no clipping of their words, just a pause. I would like someone who's pissed off about it to explain exactly how that changes the message. It seems more like the activist is more interested in claiming a deception than actually complaining about a specific manipulation. Make enough smoke and true believers will rally to fight a fire, even if there really isn't one there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? You've got the wrong bald man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The linked site is incredibly deceptive with the imagery provided for Ankor Thom in Cambodia (requires 30M sea level rise before innundated). Easter Island, pictured on their site, not identified on their map of threatened sites. The island surrounded by rocky cliffs with the majority of the sites not affected until 10M or more sea level rise.   

There are sites that will be affected much sooner, like Venice but they've identified the most iconic sites and claimed they're all threatened. This article is sensationalist bollocks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 15:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, putting a 9 second gap between the question and the activists answer is lying how?  What specifically did this gap do to create deception? Were there subliminal images flashed on the screen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 01:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admiral Akbar's wife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 22:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess maybe depending on your definition of transitioning, this might or might not be true.  Individuals seeking to have the sex change surgery have to live as the opposite gender for multiple years before a physician can perform the surgery. During that time they take hormones, live, dress and interact socially as their identified gender; and while in that state, are considered to trans. I know this only from a transgender display in Trinidad Colorado which is apparently a sex change capital in the USA. Caitlin Jenner for example is considered trans, yet has not completed the full monty so to speak, and recently has expressed doubts as to whether they will go through with it, perhaps even going back to being a man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 21:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't we all, don't we all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 17:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A recent news story cited a european country changing its medical regulations to declassify transgenderism as a form of mental illness. In your AMA title your use of the word "treat", appears to imply that it is considered a disease condition. Can you comment on the implications of classifying transgenderism as a disease both from a social ostracism perspective but also from the perspective of insurance compensation. Would declassifying it as a mental illness change medical coverage rules that compensate for the services you provide? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 16:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different subreddits have different cultural biases. Most of the default subs have a "progressive/liberal" bent but there are tribes of gun fondlers, and "sure cops should be able to kill anyone who looks at them funny" trolls lurking in a few, r/news in particular.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except in some cultures in doesn't mean ok. It means, nice asshole, lets fuck it. Ok, I partially made that up. I only know in cultural sensitivity training for the middle east and asia, westerners are warned against using it as a gesture, indicating it has obscene connotations referring to anal sex   

--EDIT--  
Hmm, accumulating some downvotes here, but no comments countering. If you have reason to disagree (e.g., I'm from the middle east and this is SO not true.), I'd love to hear it. Was definitely part of cultural training. If the company giving that training was full of shit (so to speak), would love to know what this gesture actually means in your culture, and whether or not people actually use it. 

--EDIT2 ---  
Here's a [site](http://matadornetwork.com/abroad/5-common-american-gestures-that-might-insult-the-locals/) --see #5 -- claiming the "OK" gesture means "you're a faggot" in Turkey and Venezuela.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting feature in the early documentation for the LHC data collection system struck me: the detectors produce data far faster than any networking and storage system can capture. The designs included a component that examined events from the detectors for "interestingness" and discarded a larger part of the data from the detectors before it was ever stored. Does that feature still exist in the LHC data collection system? If so, how are "interesting events" determined? Are those parameters changed for different runs of the LHC? What were the criteria used for the data included your data release? How do you know new physics hasn't been thrown out with the discarded data?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 04:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention several publicized gang rapes in India involved police officers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what I'm looking at on that data page
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - Raspberry flavoring is made from the secretions of a beaver's anal gland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wild horses on the coastal islands of the east coast of the US will stomp your coolers and knock down your tents to get food  

Black bears will break into cars, breaking the windows if they can see a cooler inside. 

Raccoons/trash pandas will aggressively approach and go through your stuff, baring their teeth and hissing if approached or hit with shit you throw at them. Raccoons also carry rabies so its never a good idea to fuck with one. Skunks will also come into camp and go through your shit while you're sitting a few feet away at the fire. Any threatening moves and they will turn around to shoot their chemical warfare weapons at you

Out west marmots will substitute for the trash pandas, although there are raccoons and other small vermin too. Skunks and cougars and griz, oh my!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 14:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do we know AKABoondock isn't just another one of those sock puppets and the karmathief/spammer is just getting extra clicks by "catching himself in the act?". Feeling very Keanu today ;-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty cool looking. The ground illumination makes it appear as if this is CGI. Can you say where and what direction your camera views were? I can never pick out any constellations in these kind of shots and would like to compare your pics to a star chart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As falls Wichita, so falls ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same Sheriff David Clarke who helped cover up deputy's drunk driving accident and malicious prosecution of [accident victim?](  http://fox6now.com/2014/07/07/fox6-investigation-prompts-a-lawsuit-crash-victim-filing-federal-suit-against-sheriff-clarke-others/). He's a real paragon of integrity. Maybe the motorist could have saved herself if she'd been armed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 03:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, where exactly are you sending your canned human flesh Mr China? I suppose you think it's funny to imply Africa when it is actually... Mexico! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially the one with the lemon garlic marinade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China: No, we are not sending cans of human flesh to Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except when the birds are murdering cassowaries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Brit, I was hoping you could tell me. Mainly my exposure to them was in the movie Clockwork Orange, but my brit friends have referenced their teens heading out to the milk bar. Also saw one in the Sydney Opera House ferry terminal some years back. I assume it is commonwealth culture thing - head down to the bar for nice creamy glass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I predict this research will win the 2016  Ig Noble award for biology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a [source](http://www.bxscience.edu/ourpages/auto/2009/4/5/34767803/Pre-Columbian%20population.pdf) with high and low estimates graphed for different regions. The "north of the Rio Grande" (US and Canada) estimates range from 3.8M to 12.2M. I've seen other documents estimating the Mississippian cultures of the Gulf Coast, Mississippi and Ohio river vally region population of 7 million pre-contact. By the time the spanish explorers were first coming through the region, they'd been decimated by plagues, with estimated population reduction of 90%. The ~~Wikipedia entry~~ *Redditor /u/400-rabbits*  indicates the current consensus estimate is 100M for all of the Americas, with the majority of that in Central and South America, but still room for a significant population in North America *in [post](https://www.reddit.np/r/AskHistorians/comments/2sx6h9/whats_the_current_scholarly_consensus_of/cnueklc) to /r/askhistorians about a year ago*

---EDIT--- 
Correct a misattributed statement in post   
(sorry - looked at too many sources too fast)  

--- EDIT2 --- 
link to old reddit post cause a bot to remove post. I guess I don't understand how to use a permalink to another post in a posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At what point in British evolution did milk bars appear in the historical record?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spanx For Men

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do everything you can to stop fossil fuel extraction and burning. It's not the "Carbon Footprint" that is killing the planet. It is the fossil carbon footprint. Second biggest contribution to sequestered carbon being released into the atmosphere is concrete production. Not quite sure what to say about that except it is one quarter of the total fossil carbon release.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot, plankton making calcium is how oceans are scrubbing CO2 from the atmosphere and interring it in the earth's crust on million year time scales. Think we have  global warming problem now? Wait until half the CO2 produced by anthropamophic processes each year stops simply disappearing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 23:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dozens of years younger, in dog years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of our uses the "just for men" dyes to color his beard so he doesn't look like an old dog. Thought about how my dog has gone so grey around the muzzle and decided "just for dogs" hair dye would sell like hotcakes to both dog owners and men who fancied themselves as horndogs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back King Zog!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but notice this same information has been posted multiple times to reddit, yet there is nary a post about the same era soviet nuclear targets in the USA, Canada and all the European NATO countries. It almost seems as someone is trying to paint the US as this horrible threat to Europe, especially those countries who were formerly dominated by the Russians; while ignoring the historical context of Russian missiles pointing the other way. Now who would want to undermine European opinion of the USA? Could it be ... I don't know.... [**PUTIN!**](https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/the-danger-of-russian-disinformation/2016/05/06/b31d9718-12d5-11e6-8967-7ac733c56f12_story.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen multiple people EDIT a hyper popular post RIP inbox. I don't get it. On my account
1) All recent replies get cleared when I open the inbox, not just the ones I read
2) I don't use my reddit inbox for anything real, just a way of seeing responses to posts, which you can see in the reddit thread anyway. 

Who cares if you miss one or a few hundred when you open the inbox but don't read them all?

So, what is the RIP comment about? Does it crash your browser when there are a few hundred or thousand responses when you open it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 14:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody have any backstory on the name? Was Lou a wave hog, stealing the good rides out of turn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure USS Parche was the submarine that went into the Sea of Oskosk and had divers get out at 900 ft depth to attach taps to the soviet military cables run across the sea bottom. The dive suits were some special technology still classified that allowed them to free swim at incredible depths  

---EDIT---   
Google Operation Ivy Bells. You can learn about what the USS Parche got up to in the late 70's and early 80's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genomics has branched out into a lot of fairly different, distinct areas including whole genome analysis of individuals within a species, populations of individuals across a species and comparison of one species to another. There is also the study of active vs deactivated genes in different tissues and with different disease states. For example in recent years, they've been studying the genes active in different types of cancer. In medicine today cancer is treated on the basis of what tissue it originated in. When cancer has metastasized to other tissues of the body, it retains the genetics that it had in the tissue where it arose. Recent work has demonstrated that cancers of several different origin tissues are related and have common elements, but other cancers are so different they should probably be classified as completely different diseases. Finally, and more to the point, the genetics are only a small part of the picture. Genes encode RNA which encodes and makes proteins but some RNA turns around activates other genes, or suppresses the activity of already active genes. Proteins interact with each other. Some of them bind with DNA to promote or suppress its expression. To say the study of genomics has slowed isn't accurate, but what has happened is that it has been realized is the operation of the machinery of the cell is far more complicated than anyone ever imagined. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ashokan Farewell](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7TSm3GpQNoE), AKA the Ken Burns Civil War Song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be a lot more impressed if their picture showed a piece of wood  cut parallel to the grain being made transparent. The piece of wood shown being prepared is cut across the xylem, meaning there are channels for the chemicals to be carried into the wood. 1 cm depth is pretty impressive, but less so when you consider the ease of diffusing along the wood fibers and through xylem channels rather than across them. Such a piece would have very limited structural integrity, making its transparency less relevant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend told me about a bar in Cancun where there were lots of monkeys in the trees above the deck. There were lots and lots of signs about not feeding the monkeys, but sure enough somebody in their group gave a monkey that came to the table some of his fries. The monkey loved them and kept asking for more. Finally the guy figured he was going eat his meal, turned away from the monkey and started eating the fries himself. The monkey jumped on his head and started pulling his hair out while screeching and baring his teeth at the other patrons. Everyone jumped back from the table, leaving their meals. Monkeys swarmed out of the trees, grabbing everyone's meals and running off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put this also in perspective for the lead up to the invasion of Iraq which the neocons in the Bush administration had been pushing since even before 9/11. The US needed staging for the invasion. While I disagree with some others in this thread that the 9/11 attacks were official policy of the Saudi government, one needs to understand how thoroughly compromised the Saudi governmental organizations are with religious extremists.  The suppression of the 28 pages and termination of follow up investigations into the Saudi officials who provided logistical support for the attacks was almost certainly a quid pro quo for permission to make limited use of the Saudi bases in the Iraq invasion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing how this is getting played. Pedestrian ramps on curbs were put there for a reason: largely for handicap access to and from the street. It can be argued that they're not just for handicap access, but a way to prevent complete blockage of sidewalk to street access. Any reasonable "common law" interpretation of a car parking to block one of these access points would be "That's illegal, blocking a pedestrian access". The thing that made this not illegal was apparently some local pol in NYC having his constituents say, "there's not enough parking and we have to give up 3 fucking feet of potential parking space for all those goddamn ramps for cripples!" So, the result was to pass a law saying it wasn't a legal pedestrian access point unless there's a crosswalk painted on the pavement. Probably a lot of them originally did have crosswalks, but with the constrained budgets, you repave the road, not enough money to go restripe the cross walk. I personally am glad every one of those people who were ticketed, got those tickets. I am glad anyone who paid those tickets, won't get their money back. I hope some police, especially the ones who know those pedestrian access points are used and needed by some people will continue to write those tickets even though some slimy politician has slipped a loop hole in ADA access in NYC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens everyday in every jurisdiction. People who know people will get favors done.  

It is also against the law, and in having the ticket dropped, indicts the credibility of the original issuing officer: the implication is the ticket was improperly issued. If this was the case, then anyone else issued a ticket by the same officer can very well claim there is evidence of incompetence or malfeasance by the same officer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly this is a case for Boss Hogg to mediate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 13:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story of the Russian mig pilot who flew his plane to Japan in the late 70s or early 80s was I think a lot more compelling. He still believed a lot of the ussr's propaganda about conditions in the west when he defected. Brought to Washington, D.C. And shown a supermarket, he refused to believe it wasn't a show prepared for him specially. Driving around the beltway, he demanded that his handlers pull off at random exits and then drive until they found a supermarket which he'd run into to "surprise" the staff. Seeing the produce in the front, he'd rush to back trying to catch them suddenly putting out meat and dry goods that weren't there before he came into the store. Apparent it took 5 or 6 different, randomly selected stores before he believed that this was the norm across the whole usa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to IMDB it was St. Moritz, Kanton Graubnden, Switzerland  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 19:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are theories that features like the Mare on the Moon and the Tharsis Bulge on Mars were caused by the convergence of shock waves from a large impact on the opposite side of the planetary body. Recent research has also quantified the characteristics of an earthquake shock necessary to trigger volcanic eruptions in nearby magma chambers. Is there any evidence that the Chicxulub impact caused a shock effect on the opposite side of the earth, or triggered distant volcanic eruptions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 18:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the actual jump off the cliff is [Mount Asgard](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/73/Mount_Asgard_3_2001-07-25.jpg). The rest of the skiing sequence had to be filmed elsewhere. I'd put my money on the French Alps, but would believe Tahoe if there was evidence  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 02:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bumblebee not a honeybee, very small amount of honey produced, can sting lots o times without dying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 02:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beats the shit out of Cape Horn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have your ever cosplayed using your forehead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course psychotropic drugs come from the same sources, the fungus ergot which grows on rye grain is the source of LSD. There is some speculation that the French revolution was brought on by widespread psychotic episodes among the french peasants due to an outbreak of ergot fungus at the time of the revolution  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 21:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From some fictionalized account of the Black Death in England, it would appear entire regions were completely depopulated. Other areas had mortality rates approaching 50 percent. What kinds of social change occurred in the aftermath of this level of death? Were there former peasants who set themselves up as lords afterwards? Were there migrations of populations into the depopulated areas from less hard hit areas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 21:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to say, many of these ramps look like they could be critical access points for disabled. Seems like the law allowing parking blocking wheelchair accessible street crossing ramps should have instead created a requirement for  crosswalks to be painted where they were obviously intended to be placed. It's not like vandals went out, jackhammering curbs, and recasting concrete ramps. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 16:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I was waiting in the jetbridge to board my flight yesterday three women executives from some company were talking about Banner Ads. One of them was saying, the revenue being driven from banner ads has really dropped over the past year. Another one says, client says they're getting a lot of feedback from their customers indicating they're offended by banner ads on the site, it creates a negative customer experience. Third one says, we need something to replace banner ads before we pull them off the site. I could see the evil racoon rubbing his hands. What new nefarious scheme will they hatch to modify consumer behavior through their eyeballs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the wording of the headline strangely protective of the oil sands industry. The source of the cancer causing dust is from piles of sand and rock which has already been processed to have the bitumen removed and processed into oil. In the rest of the world, we call those piles "industrial waste heaps". A bunch of crude oil in tanks waiting to go to the refinery is a "stockpile". The sludge that is left over from refining after all the useful products have been processed out is waste, usually highly toxic waste. Call it for what is and this headline becomes a DUH moment: Dust from oil sands toxic waste heaps very likely the source of cancer causing pollutant found throughout the northern Alberta region.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America named after Richard Amerike of Bristol, of whom no one has ever heard. That's rich, giggle snort snort.  The claim that the American flag stars and stripes derives from his coat of arms claimed in the same article has the same flavor of ridiculousness. 

In [this piece by scholars at SUNY](http://www.uhmc.sunysb.edu/surgery/america.html), they trace the naming to some German scholars who latinize Amerigo's name, then converted it to the feminine form because both Europa and Asia, in Ptolemy's geography had been taken from women's names. The geography they were issuing in 1507 was updating Ptolemy's geography with the recent discovery of a 4th part of the world, adding to the 3 known parts of Europa, Asia and Africa   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper explores several different possibilities, but they have demonstrated the viability and explanation of what is considered a major anomaly of our solar system as compared to exo-planetary systems that have been studied: The vast majority of other planetary systems include a "Super-Earth" in the inner system. Our solar system doesn't have one. We also have solar system evolution models to explain the orbits of our currently known planets (the Nice Model) which has Jupiter, Saturn and Uranus moving pretty far from their formation positions, and interacting with each other in gravitational resonances to enhance those movements. Those same resonances could also result in an additional planet involved in the mix getting a very big gravitational boost to put it into a much higher and eccentric orbit than the major planets of the solar system. The important finding of this paper is that this is indeed a viable scenario given the current state of the solar system's planets. The also looked at other scenarios of an exoplanet capture, but my reading of the article is that these are considered to be possible, but much lower probability than the inner system planet ejection theory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tartarus - in ancient Greek mythology, is the deep abyss that is used as a dungeon of torment and suffering for the wicked and as the prison for the Titans. As far below Hades as the earth is below the heavens  

Tartarus would seem to be a fitting name for a planet so far in the deeps of space we still haven't been able to find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America was named for Amerigo Vespucci.  
Why not call it Vespuccia instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deep upwellings are known to cause algal blooms, and these are, I thought, considered to be "good" occurrences that drive a productive oceanic food chain. What makes algal blooms "go bad", where oxygen is depleted from the water column and toxins are released into water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheeseburgers are on average fattier
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walking my pitbull mix recently, we ran into a couple walking their bully breed. Brief interchange asking whether it is ok for the dogs to say hello, they said "sure". Dogs approach each other, making eye contact, then both lunge toward the other's butt to sniff. The woman in the couple says to me "We taught him to sniff butts". For a moment I'm speechless, then crack "That must have been tough to do". She's embarrassed for a moment then explains its something the dog whisperer on TV says - don't put the dogs in a situation where they're staring face to face. It's an aggression stance. Instead, encourage them to get to know each other nose to tail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you discuss the role of  animal waste as fertilizer on farm fields in triggering algal blooms. It is my understanding there are federal limits on phosphate fertilizer application to farm fields, but these limits can be bypassed by directly utilizing animal manure. Is this an accurate representation? Are you modeling animal manure runoff as part of your algal bloom predictions? What does the current wet spring in the US Mid-Atlantic predict for algal blooms in the Chesapeake Bay, Delaware Bay, North Carolina sounds and New Jersey beaches this summer?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 18:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing says love like a whole body wag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 13:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would fapping be a separate counter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd ask how much money that guy has made off that cat, but I am afraid it might kill it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enron had branched into non-energy business areas before their total collapse. I work for a large IT / computer services company. In the weeks before their collapse I was responding to an RFP and had meetings at the Enron building Houston over their plan to broker online storage services. We were going to build an internet accessible storage system - e.g. Amazon S3  like capability. Enron had specifications for 100 GB blocks of storage (no small volume in the mid 1990's) that would be purchased for 1 month terms of service. They had some pretty onerous terms of service but it was basically a "Buy Low, Sell High" strategy. They wanted to setup a brokerage for storage services that mirrored the electrical energy they were already offering (and manipulating the energy market in some areas like California). We understood they were moving this some business area in numerous other areas. In many ways it was the cloud that AWS, Google, Microsoft etc all operate today, except Enron had no intention of actually setting up any of the cloud services. Instead they wanted to set themselves up as the exclusive provider that everyone had to go through to contract for those services. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 17:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TLDR  explanation is simple: no contact frition between wheels and rail/road surface to overcome. A maglev train is essentially sliding on a friction free surface. This is an oversimplification as there are electromagnetic effects analogous to friction but they have no where near the magnitude of true physical friction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A passport asserts the citizenship of the owner by the issuing government. The country being entered can decide whether or not they recognize the issuing government, or not. Pretty funny that the Paks think they can tell the Jews not to recognize it. It should better say "this man is the proud son of the great country of Pakistan, unless you reading this are a filthy Jew, in which case he is a worthless son of a dog and should be beaten for trying to enter your non-country which does not exist" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mainly just sit there manning a tip jar. There's a shit load of stuff on the counter: bottles of mouthwash, cologne, breath mints, condoms and other personal hygiene items. The guy makes eye contact and nods at you, appearing to suggest that just using the sink is sufficient service provided that you should put money in his jar. My wife confirms there are similar people and additional crap (hair gel, makeup, etc) in the women's restroom. The question we have is , are these people being paid or is this just a sort of institutionalized beggar/sundry items peddler  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what's with the restroom attendants in Charlotte airport? It's like a throwback to 1940s when you have to connect through there. Is this a common practice throughout the city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'd do it with a traffic cone. Smoker lays on the floor, put a towel around their face, then the cone on the towel so the face is looking up into the cone. Your bro's blow smoke into the cone filling it up, then put their hand over the top and squeeze the sides, inflating your lungs and driving all that smokey air into them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wrapper on a tampon makes nice rolling paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically yes an Xray, but today what we'd call a fluoroscope. Relatively low level xray delivered continuously to a fluorescent screen. My mother and her sister used to go down to the shoe store and try on shoes almost every day just so they could watch their toe bones wiggle in the shoes. Neither of them has come down with bone cancer or anything, so the dose must not have been too horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar experience with mercury in high school. Teacher took out bottle of mercury and played with the beads and droplets on the benchtop. We could all go touch if we wanted. Next year I took an independent study lab and accidentally spilled that mercury in a lab room. Clean up as much as I could but about 1/3 of it, say 1 tablespoon was still missing in the end. A few years ago a local high school was closed for fucking month and a half when some kids broke the mercury switch from an old thermostat in the hall way. There was maybe 1/4 tsp of mercury in that switch. They had a hazmat team in there and special chemical spill cleanup contractor before they'd let kids back into the school. I think about that when I'm back in my home town. That school where I spilled a 1/4 cup of mercury is still there, hundreds of kids graduating every year in what would be called a mercury contaminated building, if they only knew.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's she holding with her other hand? It looks like she could be holding the barrel of shotgun or large bore rifle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm - I remember the Magic the Gathering photoset. It came out around the time I first started lurking on Reddit and gave me a good chuckle at the time (having escorted my elementary school aged son to a couple Magic the Gathering hotel ballroom tournaments). However, when I go look at /u/OB1FBM's record on Reddit. He has only 14K in link karma and 46K in comment karma. Don't see how this could be the 4th highest post of all time on Reddit unless there was some excess karma profit tax levied on the Reddit karma 1%'ers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 22:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wailing Wales Winds Up On Wexford </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be interested in the 1980 protocol for incendiary weapons addition to the [Geneva Conventions](http://www.weaponslaw.org/assets/downloads/1980_CCW_Prot_III.pdf).  

It has the following definitions and explicit exclusions. I've annotated some elements such as the exclusion of smoke, tracer and signaling systems. Also annotated the section regarding weapons that contain incendiary material but are not designed to explicitly burn individual humans.  

1. "Incendiary weapon" means any weapon or munition 
which is primarily designed to set fire to objects 
or to cause burn injury to persons through the action
 of flame, heat, or combination thereof, produced 
by a chemical reaction of a subs
tance delivered on the target.   
 
(a)
Incendiary weapons can take the form of, for example, flame throwers, fougasses, shells, rockets, 
grenades, mines, bombs and other containers of incendiary substances.  
 
(b)
Incendiary weapons **do not** include: 
(i) Munitions which may have incidental incendiary effects, such as **illuminants, tracers, smoke or signalling systems;** 
(ii) Munitions designed to combine penetration, blast or fragmentation effects with an additional incendiary effect, such as armour-piercing projectiles, fragmentation shells, explosive bombs and similar combined-effects munitions **in which the incendiary effect is not specifically designed to cause burn injury to persons,** but to be used against military objectives, such as armoured vehicles, aircraft and installations or facilities.   

In the battle for faluja in Iraq, the UK's Guardian newspaper made a claim similar to yours above - that phosphorus munitions were banned by the geneva convention. This is not the case. Munitions design to burn people are banned, but munitions that have phosphorus in them, design for illumination or as explosives against military installations are not banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've attended a military exercise sitting in grandstands where jet fighters (F-4 phantoms) flew attack profiles on the grandstands, in one case pulling up only a few hundred feet over the crowd. There was a pretty intense jetwash, people's hats blew off; but nobody was knocked off their seat. The worst part was the heat of the jetwash. It was already 90/90 Florida heat. Add to that another 50 degrees of hot air blowing down, there wasn't a dry shirt in the crowd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly he did have a lot descendents period, but we can't trace the daughters because of the intermixing of  chromosome contributions from mothers and fathers. Y chromosomes on the other hand are handed down father to son through the generations. If you find a particular marker that you know is unique to a particular individual or very small clan that becomes extremely widespread, you can make the assumption that he, or one of his sons was pretty prolific in boy factory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you think that's one shot of the moon surface and one completely different shot of the Earth photoshopped into one photo, then it's kinda fake, yes.

So there are two different ways that scenario could play out, one of which I would call "fake", another I would not. 

If there was a picture of the Earth, taken from a completely different point in time and location in orbit from a picture of the moon's surface from a low light angle; and these two photos were merged to make it appear as if it was an Earthrise moment on the Moon's terminator, then yes I would call this photo fake. On the other hand, if the LRO was taking a series of photos covering the low light angle landscape on the moon, then took more images of the earth above the horizon at a different exposure, this would be a valid representation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U Parkee U Tickee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An acquaintance just buried her husband. He wanted a completely natural burial, no embalming or cosmetic fixups, no casket, just buried in the ground for the worms to eat. She actually had the body wrapped in a sheet (all cotton) but otherwise it was au naturale. Only two graveyards in her state allowed such burials. She had to obtain numerous state permits and licenses allowing the burial too. She said it cost more than if she would have had a funeral in a funeral home and a moderately nice casket.   

-- EDIT --  
My mom feeds the fish and crabs off her dock food scraps from her kitchen. She calls them her "pets". I've joked with her about feeding her to them when she passes. She's not that committed to her pets yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 22:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What other meat flavors are a combination of two or more meats? If I mix guinea pig  and iguana, do I get llama flavored sausage? Rabbit   Duck to get Fudd Flavor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 21:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even more so, the article seems to be describing a simulated, not actually built design. Another ludicrously sensationalized scientific claim published on Phys.Org. I used to think it was Physics but see now that it is just a marketing "Fizz" publicity rag for people probably looking to get funding to develop something with a fraction of the claimed capability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A relative worked on [this project](http://www.healio.com/orthotics-prosthetics/health-care-updates/news/print/o-and-p-news/%7B3a16d723-9a1a-44b8-b4f8-7a566ba291a2%7D/university-of-houston-professor-develops-mind-controlled-exoskeleton) at the University of Houston. They already have patients coming in to use the nerve induction control harness to walk with the exoskeleton. Although the control at this point is crude, in many cases the psychological benefits of just being able to control their own locomotion is incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tanker of (incredibly strong) coffee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save this picture on your phone for the next time someone says there's no difference between the parties.  To some extent they play to same games, but there is a level of immorality to the GOP that you don't see with Dems. I was a life long registered republican but switched parties last year largely due to shit like this. At lot of Dems are sanctimonious pricks, but at least they are generally not evil shits. This is evil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the curiously curling insulators on the high power lines around the roof line of the leftmost truck. Compare them to the power line insulators on the other power pylons which are all arrow straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although the comments already here are accurate --e.g. lack of tectonic plate movement means eruptions over time are in the same place and low rate of erosion means the mountains stay high instead of being worn down -- there is another factor to consider. If you measure mountains not in terms of their absolute height but instead with the height expressed as a ratio of the planetary diameter, Olympus Mons is not the highest mountain in the solar system. It actually comes in 9th, behind three volcanoes on Mars, Ahuna Mons on Ceres, and the peaks on several of Saturn's moons, most of which were created by large impacts relative to the size of the body being hit. The list of the tallest mountains in the solar system is [here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_tallest_mountains_in_the_Solar_System) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 16:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny to hear you say that. I grew up in the area but moved away before they built the Truman Show set where you live. I think it's kind of interesting when I go visit, but my folks bitch about it being a bunch of damned northeasterners. In the 70's there was so much nothing out there, it was where all people would go for nude sunbathing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 15:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tasty Panda Hot Bowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it's a cool video, not sure why this is posted in science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A taxonomy of Chinese Restaurant names </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true. In high school I moved to Northern Fla from out west.  Majority of my classmates were looking at attending colleges in Alabama. I attended UF, in Florida's "middle kingdom" between the Redneck North and Cuban/ New York-Jersey Jewish South.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to question the bias, intended or unconscious, embodied in what is being classified as an 'IS Terror Attack". Note for example the UK does not appear in the list of countries with casualties, but can think of two incidents off the top of my head which were either IS directed or IS inspired attacks: Beheading of Lee Rigby and the Leytonstone tube station knife attacks. One might claim there is tenuous proof of IS involvement in both these cases, but looking at the claimed 42 casualties in the US, it is easy to see some of these are the people killed at shot by the San Bernadino couple, but 42? Who else are you counting? Maybe the two guys who tried to shoot up the Mohammed cartoon contest in Dallas and were themselves killed? Another apparent "message" of the statistics is one of "look how bad Iraq has it". So 3633 killed in Iraq but only 609 in Syria? Really? Deaths alone in Syria are over 100,000 never mind injuries,  from all sides. How can you say only 609 directly attributable to IS? If you're saying, oh but in Syria, it is really a civil war and therefore not a "Terror" attack, then how do you justify your Iraq numbers? There are just too many inconsistencies and apparent "messaging" in this graphic to take it seriously as valid data analysis presentation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And every time they go, the homophobe employees say "That damn dyke is using the women's restroom again". If the altercations are being initiated by the Macdonalds management or staff, then it is a filing a false police report to say they're calling a disturbance. Instead it is the Macdonald's staff attacking a patron. Don't know if you have those laws in the UK, but it should be the girl calling the police and filing a hate crime harassment report </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say the space station is directly above you.  

While you don't say how far above you, Larry Niven had a great mnemonic for non-technicals living in a weightless orbiting environment ("The Smoke Ring"):  

East takes you Out, Out takes you West, West takes you In, In takes you East  

Basically, if you're in a lower orbit than the space station, it is above you, but would be falling behind you because your lower orbit means you're moving fasting. By throwing a rock behind you along your line of orbit, it would increase your velocity toward the East which orbital mechanics would immediately convert into a higher, but slower orbit. Throw enough rocks, you'd rise the space station's orbital altitude, but likely not at the same point along the orbit as the space station. If you threw a few more rocks, you could rise above the space station's orbit and let it catch up with you. Then throw a rock forward along your orbital vector (pushing you to the West) to lower your orbit down to the space station. All this presumes you and the station are in orbits with same eccentricity and inclination AND none of your rock throwing velocity vectors changed them. Otherwise you could get yourself completely out of sync with the station and likely only rarely seeing each other. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a couple aspects to the problem. One is sensory and the other is perceptual. In a sense we have already created numerous machines that allow people to "see" new and different colors. Radiologists reading xray and CT images are "seeing" the effect of xrays passing through tissue or other matter. MRIs - they're seeing the radiowaves emitted by tissues stimulated with magnetic resonance. Nuc Med Gamma camera images, they're "seeing" gamma rays, PET scan images they're "seeing" 511 keV photons characteristic of matter/antimatter annilation (not even sure what that part of the spectrum is called). In all these cases, humans are able to "see" these colors by shifting them into the visible light spectrum in which our visual system operates. A similar process goes on in most of those beautiful Hubble spaceporn images everyone loves.    

As /u/Karmaslapp indicates, there are also some people who have a genetic variation giving them sensory apparatus in the eye to see additional frequencies of higher than the blue pigment sensor most of us see. The end result is that they can distinguish a great granularity of shades of blue and purple when test images are shown to an experimental population; but conceptually are they really seeing a new color? 

Color perception, like sound, like smell, like taste are all artifacts of our conscious or unconscious minds.  You can do objective tests to determine whether two different people continue to see graduations of the color purple as higher frequency hues are added; but we have no way of knowing whether at some point they see something that is no longer purple but is a new color as different from purple as say, green. This would be mental construct. Unless there's some way to communicate mind to mind, we have only our agreed upon language to say  "That color is purple", "ooh look thatone is an even deeper hue of purple"   

-- EDIT ---Autocorrect and spelling errors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To add insult to injury, those giant silverbacks only have a 3-4 cm penis  

Saw an essay some years ago projecting the King Kong's penis size proportionally from his giant size as compared to current mountain gorillas. The answer was something like 12 or 13 inches, proving that Kong and Fay Wray were physically compatible. Her affection for the beast by the end of the movie can therefore be summed up in the well known saying  

"Once you go Kong, you never go wrong"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 20:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One suspects OP's question was directed along the lines of "Can concrete be recycled back into powdered form which can be mixed and cast into new structures". Considering concrete is made from an energy intensive process which produces copious quantities of CO2 driven off from the raw materials; AND, the process of setting concrete is an exothermic reaction that releases significant heat energy, one suspects the answer to my restated version of the question is "Not without significant input of energy and additional chemical reagents to reverse the chemical processes that occurred in setting the concrete originally. Even with these caveats, it is unclear whether there is in fact a reversible process which could restore old concrete to it's status as a raw material for pouring new concrete. Can you comment on this aspect of concrete recycling?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a pastafarian I am completely disgusted by you fucking gluten free freaks. Gluten is salve of my savior, the noodley one. I shall not sell you gasoline, nor make your wedding cake, nor cut your unclean hair. Go away you eater of buckwheat and rice slime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 00:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firecrackers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I don't and am a bit out of date. I worked in medical imaging and consulted in a number of government funded healthcare countries. Advanced medical imaging is capital intensive that doesn't work well with government allocated funding acquisition processes (as compared to market economy healthcare). Britain and Canada in particular were far behind in the number of advanced technology imaging machines per capita compared to countries like the US. Yes the imaging in the UK is free but if it takes you 2 months to get the exam, is it really serving your needs. I don't have specific individual stories, but did have statistics on waiting times for exams. These ranged from 4 to 9 weeks in the UK about 9 years ago. Given the cuts in the NHS recently, I can't imagine the situation has gotten any better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, try getting a MRI in the UK in nongeologic time. Hope that tumor isn't growing aggressively  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 19:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer adding the suffix "Dome" after every scandal in reference to the Teapot Dome. This would make scandals sound more like Mad Max than the Beaver Cleaver sound of anything "Gate".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  do people just believe that cops start their day thinking that they are going to go out and find any reason to kill someone?

No, but people do believe that cops decide to kill people during arrests, not in self defense, but in anger at defiance of their authority. Cops who beat unresisting suspects while shouting "stop resisting" are showing premeditation for the assault crime they are committing. Cops who step into the path of a car speeding away from a scene even as they start firing through the windshield and claim self defense against a vehicle used as a deadly weapon are demonstrating a willful intent to use deadly force rather than allowing a criminal to escape from a $17 waffle house bill. Cops who use tasers are on hand cuffed suspects laying on the ground are committing torture in retaliation for verbal or physical abuse the suspects dealt to them or their colleagues.   

Do I believe you go out looking for someone to kill every day? No, but I think you lack the social constraints that normally inhibits people in society from using physical violence and lethal force for what you perceive to defiance. The fact that there are violent criminals out there who will hurt police officers seems to the be the entire justification for police officers torturing or killing people for minor crimes. It is not that we think police officers shouldn't be allowed to defend themselves. Instead it is your belief that you can kill someone you encounter who shows the slightest resistance arrest, often for minor crimes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a very intense pre-surgical planning phase for liver transplants both for the donor and recipient. The liver has a very complex network of both blood vessels and billiary ducts. While it just looks a really big lump in the simplistic major organ charts, the liver actually consists of multiple separate lobes interconnected in a branching tree structure similar to the structure people often visualize for the branching bronchial tubes within the lungs. The liver typically consists of three or four separate lobes, with common connection point pretty close to the bottom of the tree trunk base. Here's a [link to an image](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4176786/figure/F10/)  from surgical planning system that is being used to map the internal vascular structure of a donors liver. The surgeons will identify one lobe that they will remove from the donor at the base of it's major trunk and plan where they have to suture off the connecting passages and vessels.  This whole lobe will then be transplanted, connecting it up the recipient's blood vessels and billiary tracts. The donor will grow a new lobe or increase the sizes of his remaining lobes. The recipient will do something similar with their new healthy lobe transplanted in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
