<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick Frost's character in **Hot Fuzz** (2007) was obsessed with **Bad Boys II** (2003). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow.  Sad news but somewhat expected.  Inland Empire was eleven years ago after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mr. Trumps toothless action is the inevitable consequence of years spent scaring white evangelicals with faux outrages. A problem with no victims requires nothing more than a solution with no substance. All Mr. Trump had to do was host some religious leaders in his garden, listen politely to some Christian contemporary music, repeat some religious-right talking points about how free speech doesnt end at the steps of a cathedral and voil! He becomes the savior of American Christianity.

Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yet even as Mr. Trump spoke in the Rose Garden on Thursday, the reaction in the conservative Christian world was one of disappointment. Total weak sauce, fumed David French at National Review. The evangelical pastor Skye Jethani tweeted, A whole lot of nothing; a symbolic act to please his base without any real change in policy or law. Robert George, a conservative Catholic intellectual, called the order a betrayal.

 Thats because the executive order changes absolutely nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clergy Members Aren't Being Persecuted for Their Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a model Roman scholar-athlete-citzen eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this it completely true.  Check for upcoming town halls all around the United States on https://townhallproject.com/ to see for yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to enjoy getting stoned and going to the batting cages . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day of shame . . . and BUD LIGHT!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear hear!!

90% of these Trump is getting impeached articles make up about 80% of this sub.

This is like the **Sex Panther** of Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  an audio tape of President Donald Trump attempting to shut down the investigation into his alleged ties to Russia exists

Um . . . Cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why all this fuss about the wall not being in this budget?

You should be bitching that the wall isn't in **Mexico's** budget instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna have to "call b.s." on this one, however funny and eye-catching this piece may be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it does sound like an Onion article doesn't it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven Reasons the Left Is Losing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Many of the people interviewed appear to have made their choices almost purely based on personal appeal rather than on the politicians stated issue positions.

I'm not a political expert, but that quote pretty much sums up what I have believed about voters for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently this Page fellow replied to their request with some juvenile snippiness. Not smart.

Why doesn't this joker just get an attorney to handle this stuff in a diplomatic and professional manner? An attorney can stonewall as well without being inflammatory about it.

Of course, this Page cat could just be a rampant narcissist. Or nuttier than a fruitcake.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently this Page fellow replied to their request with some juvenile snippiness. Not smart.

Why doesn't this joker just get an attorney to handle this stuff in a diplomatic and professional manner? An attorney can stonewall as well without being inflammatory about it.

Of course, this Page cat could just be a rampant narcissist.  Or nuttier than a fruitcake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo, true, but how is this news exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way that Trump is personally making money by all this?  Like billing the U.S. government for these stays, food, etc.?

Isn't that a bit shady?  Nickel and dime shady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so what's the next move?  More Dick Cheney growling about an act of war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I heard about that!  Very interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also in favor of universal guaranteed income.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, thanks for your honesty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, with education a mostly local nearly-precinct-level matter, and with a substantial proportion of the elite sending their children to private schools, how is this possible in practical terms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Record level?

They actually keep stats and records on such things?  Interesting!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why officials within the executive branch need to constrain Trump's leeway in "making choices."  Narrow his options and control the information he gets.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
