<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1055</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 01:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, but that's to be expected from most films about music in which actors that aren't trained musicians are used. I don't think it's fair to say that it isn't accurate to "real life drumming" based on that - I think that's more of a technical mess up. Everyone saying it's not accurate to drumming made me think that the techniques being played (by the overdub or not) and the general sound of the drums were not jazzy or "good" in the eyes of drummers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 16:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, what about the movie isn't accurate to real life drumming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 19:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh and Zach. Fuck. That's a rhythm section right there. 

And this is some of the most genuine emotion I've heard in Claudio in a Coheed song, and so different from them too. Love it!

edit: Oh my god. I've just finished it and I got emotional at that last chorus. This is incredible. I already know this is going to probably be in my top 5 Coheed songs. I'm so happy and I can't wait for the rest of the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the preview for a new BMTH song called "Oh No" is pretty much straight up radio pop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 02:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 07:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 07:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 07:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asked around and found a copy, thanks for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 07:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! I just hope I actually can fix this. I'm genuinely very worried that it might not be possible considering how ingrained in my brain the previous, wrong way of doing it is, but I'll certainly give it my best shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fingers get extremely tense and stick out when I bounce on the stick/ do doubles. Tips on how to fix this? (pics of what it looks like in text if that helps) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 16:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](http://imgur.com/a/efAdg) what my fingers look like when I play doubles. Whenever I go from a single stroke roll to a double stroke roll, my fingers just start sticking straight out and if I try to play the double stroke roll without the fingers out, the stick goes everywhere and nearly falls out of my hand. I've been playing for 6 years and pretty much been doing that with my doubles the whole time, so I'm sure it will take some work but I want to fix this. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 15:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man, why couldn't you have said this first?! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 06:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the kind of thing - for me - that took a pretty long time to get, but once I did, it sort of clicked and everything fell into place and it was really satisfying and stuff. So basically I said that to say don't get discouraged because I did lots. 

What I did was I played a basic beat for two bars, then two bars of just R-L-K followed by an empty beat, followed by R-L-K. Then the next two bars would be R-L-K, R-L-K etc., 8 times in total. I started very very slow, and when I could play that whole thing perfectly (I think) 8 times, I bumped it up 5 bpm. After a while it just clicked and now it's pretty much easy to get it down at any (rational) tempo. Good luck!

edit; just remembered, one great beat for incorporating this early on in learning it is [Dave Grohl's post chorus groove from Teen Spirit](https://youtu.be/KoQC3gGwqro?t=100). It's just one quick burst of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 06:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I've been looking up the basics and I'm going to dedicate tomorrow at least to getting them down and see how I feel then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 06:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP; Ignore this asshole. He's leaving pointless negativity on everyone's posts. You're not J.K. Simmons from Whiplash, dude. You're on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 06:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. You want the real TL;DR? 

'Should I follow my current urges to learn and master to the best of my ability jazz drumming, or instead put all of that time towards my strengths I already have to avoid spreading myself too thin, and is it possible to reach these goals considering how used to my comfortable genres I am?'

Don't have to be an asshole, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 05:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, I know. I'm always terrible for typing way too much, apologies. I guess the title is the TL;DR for the TL;DR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been drumming for 6 years, playing mostly more technical rock, and a tiny bit of metal and funk. I could never stay dedicated to learning jazz properly, but recently have the urge stronger than ever. Is it too late to start learning in the hopes of getting as good at it as the other genres? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 05:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 18 and start college next week (I'm so excited :D) to study drums for four years. I'm nervous because many of the students and teachers adore jazz and it will be a big part of the course; but I could never stick to it. I always felt a little bad about that, because my drum teacher I had for five years is a pretty prominent jazz drummer here in Ireland, and lives and breathes it; he did his college thesis on Max Roach for god's sake, so the fact I couldn't get into it made me feel awful. 

That's not the only reason I want to get better, of course, but it has been on my mind. I recently just have an urge to finally put my head down and stay dedicated, but honestly rock and general heavier styles are so ingrained in me that I don't know if I could even get moderately proficient at it any time in the next year or so. Whenever I try to play **trad grip**, I just.... can't. It just doesn't work. I don't know why. I'm the same with **finger technique**. I've tried all the drumeo exercises, everything, but my hand still insists on playing the fast, swung ride patters with the wrist, and it sounds awful and robotic. It's the same whenever I do any shuffle (particularly something like the Purdie shuffle. I know it's not really jazz but it's the finger technique). It's honestly infuriating and makes me feel like I have no soul as a player (that sounds very dramatic but I mean more feel and stuff), and that I'm just a brainless rock guy. I want to learn and I want to be able to do these things naturally. Whenever I see one of my drummer friends post a video of them playing even the simplest jazz pattern, and their wrist is working so beautifully and naturally with their fingers to produce that clean, satisfying swung ride pattern, I honestly feel terrible because I can't do it, despite my best efforts. 

Sorry to get so rambly. Basically, I just want to know if, based on what I've said there, I should dedicated my time to learning all these things. I most definitely want to learn, and want to get good at jazz drumming, but at the same time it could take a very, very long time; time that could be used to further my current strengths and become my own player in that realm. 

**TL;DR:**

**I'm currently at a very basic level of jazz drumming, but I really, really want to get better. Should I dedicate myself to learning jazz (and potentially spend a huge chunk of practice time in the coming months or years doing so) at the possible expense of furthering my current strengths?**

**Finger technique and traditional grip still, after trying quite a lot, feel very unnatural and as if I'll just never be able to do it because using matched grip and just my wrists is so heavily ingrained in my brain. How can I finally learn? Can I learn, will it actually work after all this time?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 21:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the first time in the last few years I've seen Will Smith actually look somewhere close to his age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love some of their songs, but honestly the majority of their lyrics seem to be different ways of phrasing "hang on/ I'm hurting too/ you can make it/ #believeinyoself". That's great in small doses, but when it's done so frequently by one band it just starts to seem pandering and disingenuous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 04:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the FB comments;
 "Please crowdfund a remaster"- fan

 "Step ahead of you bud." - PTH page

**HOLY SHIT YES OH MY GOD HEARING ALL THOSE SONGS AGAIN BUT WITH THE PRODUCTION OF VOLITION WILL BE INCREDIBLE OH LORD** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 17:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Throw me to the wolves" line is definitely back tracked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 07:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't seen it that time. Nothing wrong with a healthy repost now and then for the people that didn't catch it the first time around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 03:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the message to Aidan I typed out; 

"Hey look, I haven't wanted to say this because it'll inevitably cause awkwardness or maybe tension or something, and also because I wouldn't put it past myself to be imagining things and dramatizing everything (as usual), but is everything alright? Like, with us? With the band? With me being a part of the band, or being a friend of yours and Lucas's in general? Like I don't want to sound confrontational but seriously it's tearing me up and I can't stop thinking about it. I just feel like you and Lucas have some huge problem with me and aren't saying it. Forgive me if I'm just being dramatic and imagining things, but I'm definitely not imagining the fact that things are way different between all of us now than before, or how I'd hoped they'd be at this stage. I know Lucas probably has a huge problem with me based on how he's treated me in the last few months (the exact same way [*two other friends who basically dropped us all this time last year*] treated us that Lucas loved to complain about), but I thought you and I were ok, and I don't know lately. I can't tell. I keep flipping between thinking that Lucas is constantly complaining about me to you when ye hang out and that I need to grow up and get over it because it's probably nothing. But honestly, it's all I think about when I hear that you and him are hanging out and didn't think to invite me or anything, and that's not me saying "how could you not include me in everything omg??", it's just that we did say we'd do lots of stuff over summer, and you told me that you consider Lucas and I to be your best friends, and seeing you two hang out after practice and generally so much kind of hurts. I know the obvious thing to say to that is to ask why I haven't invited ye to do things with me, but I've spoken to Lucas about this so much - I can't invite people to do things. I know it's childish and pathetic and I need to get over it but I just can't. I become an anxious wreck when I do because I instantly feel that I'll be wasting the person's time. I just have to know. I'm not angry at you, I'm just confused and need to know. That's why I'm hard to be around at practice sometimes, I can just tell that Lucas is in a constant state of being annoyed by my presence and I can't help but feel bitter towards him for how he's let me down lately. I know you won't agree with that because Lucas is your best friend and everything, but I'm just saying what I think is the case. I know that you and Lucas probably see me as overly sensitive anyway, and this is just adding to that, but you have to understand that I have so much time alone with myself that my mind does nothing but think about things like this, and I need to just put a stop to it. Please understand. If it's nothing I'll forget about it and move on." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like my two best friends have a huge problem with me, but there's been no specific incidents and I don't know if I'm imagining things; I wouldn't put it past myself. But something has certainly changed for the worse. Should I risk awkwardness by confronting, or just wait and see if it passes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Apologies in advance for the long post, I think it's all necessary though for the advice I need. I won't use real names.)

This has been going on for the past 6 months or so. I'll try not to bore you with all the details (see the TLDR if it's too much), but basically my best friend of six years (let's call him Lucas) has, in recent months, stopped talking to me and inviting me to do things. There are a lot of potential reasons for this, but I think it's mainly because he's got a pretty good social life now, when before he had little to none, and that he thinks I have feelings for his girlfriend. I didn't have any social life either, and that's why we got close; we were both socially isolated in different secondary (high) schools, but we were socially isolated together. Last December Lucas started going out with this girl who I was really, really crazy about. I'm pretty sure I was in love with her (because I'm an idiot and fall for people way before I truly know them on any deep level (I'm working on it)), but she rejected me when I told her I liked her. I didn't tell her I was in love with her or anything, just told her after we'd been talking non stop for a couple of weeks that I like her and that maybe it'd be cool to hang out more. Long story short, she really liked Lucas all along, despite the fact that she denied it, and asked him out the day after my 18th birthday. Lucas didn't even like her that way at the time, she just liked him and decided to go for it. The day after my 18th, probably the first time I'd felt real happiness in months, of all days. They've been in a relationship since. He has a good social life now because he's started hanging out with her friends. 

I think Lucas thinks I still have feelings for her, and so might be trying to keep me at a distance. I don't, but I'd be lying if I said I wasn't a little envious and bitter about my best friend going out with someone I felt so strongly for, who rejected me. Whatever the reason for his blocking me out, it's been seriously tearing me up to see him grow so much socially and never invite me to do anything, especially considering we'd promised each other many times in the past that if either of us get to a better place socially, we'd help the other out. 

My other best friend, let's call him Aidan, had gotten really close to me only in the last year, and we always had really meaningful conversations and felt close, but in the last two months, he's been doing pretty much the same as Lucas, but not as much. They've been hanging out together a lot and never inviting me, despite Aidan telling me so many times that we'd hang out loads over summer and help each other out. My guess is that Lucas has been talking to Aidan about me, a lot. I have been cold around Lucas lately at band practice (literally the only times I see him lately, because he has to see me), very cold at times, but only because I feel like if I'm nice and warm towards him, it'll let him think that it's ok that he's blocking me out and that he can continue to do it. 

Lucas ignored my last message to him last week, but used to message me every single day. Aidan has been responding, but just barely, saying yes or no or literally just "you'll be fine" if I tell him anything that's bothering me, or "I'm grand" if I ask him how he's doing. This is weird because of how deep our conversations were before and how honest we were with each other. 

It's tearing me up and I need to know. I've spoken about it to my counsellor but he keeps urging me to take the "path I most see fit" and all this. I need to know because I don't really hang out with anyone else, except a couple of people from school occasionally, and I have too much time on my hands to keep thinking about this and driving myself insane. I have a long message typed out to Aidan but I can't decide whether to send it or not. 

Any help at all will be appreciated so much. Thank you. 

**TL;DR: My best friend of six years has been blocking me out and ignoring me, and my other best friend has been doing the same but hanging out way more with friend 1, and I think they have a huge problem with me but aren't saying anything. Do I confront one of them, risking the reaction of "you're imagining things" and the inevitable awkwardness, but also possibly resulting in honesty and a resolve to all of this, or do I just try to wait and see if it passes with time?**

edits: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 00:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much, it's really nice to have something so personal complimented so thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 00:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a week I think? Honestly it was a very strange time that I don't recall much of. I just spent hours on end sometimes doing it bit by bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 19:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 19:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](http://imgur.com/a/foJcK) an album with a few more pictures, if anyone's interested in seeing some more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 19:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually found a compass (mathematical instrument, not the navigational instrument) with a really long and sharp point, and I just started going at it with no real image of what I wanted it to end up looking like in mind. I wanted it to be sort of unique and different I guess, and eventually that design just took shape. I sanded off the wood then and just tried to make the whole thing smoother. [This](https://a1-images6.static-thomann.de/pics/prod/322896.jpg) is what it looked like before I did the carving and stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 16:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say invest in a Zoom H1 - they're cheap and sound amazing. I use mine to record all my music, and if you set the input level to 18 and place it a few feet away from the kit, at about the height level of your crash cymbal - you'll get a great sound. Just make sure to EQ it a little bit when you put the track into the mixing/production software you use. I just put up the treble and bass a little bit so it pops and add a little bit of reverb sometimes. [This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dN05vJtCE9I) is a good example! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 07:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you man, I'll check them all out. It's cool to have a proper goal with this open hand stuff now, practice had gotten a bit stale for a little while there tbh, cheers dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 06:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my favourite post on this sub ever, oh my. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 05:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for the detailed response! I didn't even think of the potential benefit of being able to switch between the two, or even just being as proficient with ghost notes in the right hand as with the left. I've been really interested in possibly trying to play open handed for a while, because my two favourite drummers play open handed (Ilan and Josh Eppard from Coheed and Cambria), but I just figured everything was so drilled in it would take too much work. But your comment makes me think it's actually worth a shot. I'm 18 so I mean I'm still relatively early in my drumming "life" or whatever it would be called, and about to start studying music in college, so now would definitely be the time! Cheers for that, man. (also, fuckin' sweet playing in that cover) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 04:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't competing though. He was the guest performer, I believe! I think he actually won it already, or at least competed and made it far, at a very young age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Fender CD-140SCE Mahogany acoustic being all deep by a river (custom carved design) [3264x2448] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 04:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 04:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guitar is on display at the music library in Cork City, I'm in there all the time! I can't think of another guitar with this much character and personality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this! This will be great for getting my single foot double bass drum strokes down (hopefully) really well too. Two birds with one stone and all that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 03:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out him [playing with Nine Inch Nails](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LBC3NXnN8y4) on their Tension tour, he brings a really exciting energy to all the songs. He even plays keys and guitar on some stuff in the show too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 03:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you start playing open handed early on in your drumming? Or had you been playing traditionally for a long time, and had to reconfigure (can't think of a better word) everything that you'd already learned that was related to left hand/right hand stuff to fit the open hand style, if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 20:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He definitely was just using it as an exaggerated metaphor, but still, there would no doubt be many servers in restaurants reading that status. That must have hurt after possible feeling a bit uplifted from what he'd written previously in the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 20:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been my favourite drummer for the last year or so, his style is so unique and I can't think of many other drummers whose personality shines through in their playing so much. If there was no video you'd still know it's Ilan playing after a second or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ilan Rubin - Guitar Center Drum Off 2011 Part 1. He is ridiculously entertaining to watch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 20:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 01:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this, but god, that autotune is hard to get past. It's disappointing considering how much Matt has talked up how far his singing has come along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 04:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem at all :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glen Hansard - Say It To Me Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 04:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed, but I didn't mean I like how his voice sounds in a technical sense, as in hitting the notes perfectly. I just meant the emotion and tone and delivery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 02:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? I was blown away. Draiman's voice sounds genuinely fantastic and like he's really feeling the emotion. The deep piano too. Man, it's all just great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disturbed - The Sound Of Silence (It's surprisingly really, really good) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wouldn't have helped him as much as you think. People in the industry are interested in making money, not doing people favors. Higher ups in the film business probably share the mindset of most of the internet, that mindset being "he's the son of someone who's respected and has had success in film, what an asshole, he doesn't deserve success".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 22:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair enough, but his Sheffield accent doesn't come out in his singing voice, so it just sounds wrong out of context, and the majority of their audience from all around the world won't know he's from Sheffield. I think he should have just said "were". But idk it doesn't really matter a whole lot either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. Though a lot of the lyrics in their earlier work certainly appealed to a younger "angry emo kid" audience, I don't think it was *made* for them, or pandering at all. I think it was still very much a personal and genuine thing for Oli, writing lyrics. He just happened to be something of an "angry emo kid" himself for a lot of that time. 

Like a song like Suicide Season is so personal and nearly specific in its lyrics, there's no way Oli just pulled it out of his ass because he thought it was what people wanted to hear. And they had so many songs about addiction, not every angry emo kid, or member of a general younger audience, has a serious addiction to something dangerous, to my knowledge. The subject matter on the songs we've heard so far from TTS seem to just be about literally being sad or angry with life or at someone, with nothing deeper at all going on. There's no mystery. I don't mean to let on like I think they were ever the most lyrically complex or amazing band ever, they never were, but this is still weak by the standards of their previous work imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was known about too. Plenty of people who knew the victim(s) had been tweeting the Neck Deep guys casually occasionally about it over the last couple of years. [This is just one example](https://twitter.com/HeavyHevd/status/635217286803161088) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like some of Oli's lyrics though. I absolutely love the lyrics to Blessed With A Curse, despite them being relatively simple. They're especially powerful in retrospect, knowing that he was hooked on ketamine at the time. It makes many of the lyrics make a lot more sense. All of the new stuff seems to just be pandering to the younger audience they seem to be aiming at lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just annoying because surely at least one person in the band or production of the album would have noticed that it was just bad grammar? Like do they think it adds to the image of the band or something? Oli's always been a bit lacking in terms of eloquence in interviews or his posts on social media, but I always thought some of his lyrics went against that in a good way. This is just disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 22:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it a lot! Caught me by surprise at parts definitely. I really, really think the lyrics are pretty weak though, they just seem unimaginative and bland. The "forest for the trees" line, "lots of nerve, not a lot of spine", "I'll forget but I'll never forgive you", "you broke my heart". And come on, "You can run, but you cant hide"? Seriously? Oli sounds great and the music is cool and I really like the main synth line because it sounds really original and fresh in this genre, but those lyrics just do nothing for me. Also, the chorus, "If I was you" just sounds a little childish, and maybe I'm just being a dick, but I surely it should be "If I were you"? I don't know. I'm a picky bastard when I'm tired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the Dark Side Of Me Video been pulled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 02:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to look it up a couple of months ago and it wasn't there, but I didn't really think much, and I really wanted to watch it again today for some visual inspiration for a thing I'm working on (I really liked how it looked and stuff), but I can't find it. I tried following the link from when it was posted on the original sub /r/coheedandcambria, but it says the video is private. 

Does anyone know if it's been reuploaded onto a different channel? All I can guess is that this has something to do with Coheed's recent move to 300 as their record label.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 23:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, is it? I was just looking at all the local cinemas I could find and their listings and I guess jumped to the conclusion that it wouldn't be released here since there was nothing in now or no mention of it. I momentarily forgot about the fact that a lot of movies release later over here! I am not smart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 23:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see it here in Cork, Ireland. I keep seeing Max's tweets and what people are saying about it, and it's legitimately been annoying me all day that it's not showing because I'm pretty sure I'd adore it. bleh (I know it's odd/silly that the first comment in a discussion thread is about how I haven't seen it but I thought I'd say something even if it contributes literally nothing yap) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 20:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that your comment is getting so downvoted really bugs me. I don't agree, but it's an opinion, and clearly contributing to the discussion based on the responses, creating debate and generating talk. Isn't that what comments on news like this are meant to be? Ugh, reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 02:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my theory. Just copied someone else's here for discussion's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 01:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Here's a cool explanation that Matt retweeted:**

This video is extremely weird but I think it has a meaning and I might know what it is. Let's break this down.

-The Old People Playing The Song: I believe this section, as well as the whole video represents what some Trivium fans think whenever the band comes out with new stuff. So many people have been saying that they "miss the old Trivium" and that's exactly what this video provides; an old Trivium.

-The Old People Dancing: These people represent these very same fans. The people who sit around and complain about how Trivium's new music is bad and prefer to jam out to the old Trivium. Old people often have trouble accepting new things, especially music.

-The Weird Dude Hugging The Picture Of Washington: I believe this also represents the inability to let go of the past. He's hugging the picture and seems to be very happy with it. He probably wouldn't be very happy if someone was to take it from him and give him a new one.

-The Arm Wrestling: This could represent the overcoming of obstacles that others cannot. The big guy represents Matt Heafy's intensity; his screaming that people miss so much. The other guys can't get over him but Matt managed to beat him.

-The Real Trivium: The real Trivium is seen preforming random activities instead of playing. This could show that they don't care about the backlash and would much rather do what they want instead of the traditional things that people expect from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 07:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emotional abuse. Granted, it's not physical, but some of the things that were said (and hugely supported) were despicable and ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 06:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could appreciate the attempts to recreate an early Experience-style sound with the new music they had to make for the performance parts, but I just found it cringy. It was really obvious that it was music made in a conscious effort to just sound like Jimi - and not music made by Jimi himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brand New - You Won't Know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 03:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The drummer for the post-hardcore band As Cities Burn had a serious anxiety attack in the middle of a show a few days ago. He wrote a blog post about what it was like and how he got through it and managed to pull through and play one of his best shows the next day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 20:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was key for me to remember that I'm worth saving.

Yes, this! That's exactly what I'm trying to say but put better; you can't hope to positively reshape yourself if you don't feel like you even deserve to get better in anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm not saying to necessarily "wait to feel better about yourself" first. I'm saying put the work that you would put into losing weight, into feeling better about yourself - seeing a doctor, a therapist, opening up to friends, making more of an effort to be sociable, whatever. This post was aimed at people who literally cannot stand the sight of themselves without a shirt on and devote huge amounts of thought to how disgusting they are physically, which is what I was for a very long time. My point is that if you have the capacity to hate one aspect of yourself that much, that "capacity to hate" will definitely stay after you lose the weight. It'll just spill to other areas. So for that reason, I think it's best to work on yourself emotionally and mentally before anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not telling anyone to just pull a better mindset out of their ass. I'm telling people to avoid using whatever negative mindset they have as motivation for weight loss. All I'm saying is that you should work on being in a better place mentally and emotionally setting out to be in a better place physically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I disagree - something similar happened to me after a long time of trying to motivate myself with self hatred and bitterness - eventually I was able to keep going because I just needed to change my view of myself so badly, and lost a lot of weight, and then I felt a lot better because people were giving me compliments all the time. And then after about a month, after that wore off, all the negativity from before came back and just found a place in other areas of myself, and if anything it was stronger because of the disappointment that losing weight didn't make me actually like myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't work for me, it didn't work for many people I know. My post doesn't add "nothing of value". If you disagree with it, you don't have to be an asshole about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said that you should accept who you are, and what weight you are, while *also* accepting that it needs to change. I don't mean accept your current or "before" weight in a loving way, I just mean to tolerate it. Accept it to the point where you won't feel a flood of bitterness towards yourself everytime you pass a mirror when you're wearing no shirt, accept it to the point where you won't be constantly aware of how "bad" you look, and how others might be perceiving you. 

I just mean to tolerate your current weight, while accepting that you need to work hard to change it to a weight that you can accept in a different way, a more loving way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a mindset of pure self resentment over your body and image when you start trying to lose weight is as bad, if not worse, than having a mindset that you're just trying it out and you don't ultimately care if it really makes any difference because, really, you're content with being overweight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 02:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just something I have to tell myself over and over again; 

Hating yourself to the point where you feel like you can use this hate to run faster than, lift more weights than, and just work harder in general than those who have "healthy" or "normal" motivation will most likely result in swift failure, and further self hatred. If you do slip up (binging on food after three days of basically starving, not doing any exercise for two days etc.), you will just detest yourself more than when you started, and those negative thoughts and feelings will weigh you down mentally and physically to the point where you will find it nearly impossible to lift them enough to even get out the door for a run. 

Please, please, if you're about to start losing weight, or have just started, have a healthy mindset. I'm not saying to love your current "before" weight by any means - there wouldn't be much point in trying to lose weight at all if you were 100% satisfied with your it - I'm just saying that it would best to accept who you are now, physically and mentally, while also accepting that you need to change your weight and that you will have to be disciplined and work hard for it. 

Sorry for the very negative post, it's just something I don't hear that many people say too often that I really needed to hear a lot when I started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably an odd thing to pick out in a sea of new cymbals and drums, but that throne is really cool looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my, I would love to see this so so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, it really can't hurt at all to bring it. Odd question, but will any carpet do? Are there ones that are better suited to drums in terms of material or thickness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was so good to read after the first comment! Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean too much physically - just taking a small gig a bit too seriously maybe. I know I'm probably coming across like I don't take every gig seriously and the immediate response would be "treat every gig, big or small, as seriously as each other" or something along those lines. I misunderstood his comment though, I thought he literally meant bring the carpet and two separate blocks of wood, and actually nail them into the stage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, I'll definitely try to bring one in future so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 20:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, thanks, I'll take note of that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okkkkkkkkk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aric is an incredible drummer, I love his style so much. So unique and exciting to watch. I hope he gets more exposure in future, but he seems like he's definitely getting there! Everyone should watch his Guitar Centre drum off performance if they haven't already, so good. Also, Loniel Robinson, yes! He's one of my favourite drummers at the moment, so underrated. His interpretations of the letlive. tracks he didn't play on (which is most of them) live are amazing and so much fun to watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh, that actually makes a lot of sense! It'd completely eliminate the need to constantly go around behind the kit after setting up something from the front to see if it looks ok from your actual playing POV. I think I'll definitely start doing that, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 18:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, but surely for smaller gigs (like I'm doing at the moment), in bars and such, that would be a little much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, cool. Cheers for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
