<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4010</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies that you thought were good but critics hated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 10:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First that comes to my mind is Transcendence, the Mummy trilogy and the Resident Evil series. Was surprised when I noticed they got a low rating when I enjoyed them so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they would just be accused of whitewashing the movie since John Stewart wouldn't be in it :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HA, for all we know he may actually be planning [this](http://vignette2.wikia.nocookie.net/fightclub/images/4/42/Project_Mayhem_01.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20111003084908) in the near future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 22:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder what the next thing we'll hear Jared has done to fit into the role </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 01:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe JJ should get going on the Half-Life/Portal movie soon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman looks so done with this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 19:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> figured out the problem, apparently after re-downloading it for the third time fixed the problem o.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 14:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually managed to play it? The camera keeps looking upwards and makes it insanely hard and irritating to play it for me :L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one that thought the woman was kicked off the plane when it was in the air instead of at the ground? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 16:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they probably proceed with punishing the users that doesn't exploit the glitch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's awesome, was just thinking that if you try to forget something you automatically think of the thing you want to forget. That was the idea anyway so I thought I'd submit it ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried forgetting something without violence or sickness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is impossible to manually forget something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did it go down? They had just fixed it so why f*ck it up again.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 15:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the really going for the homecoming title?... it seems so bad and the way it looked looked like it was made by someone in grade school.. Hope they pull the 'captain america serpent society' thing they did under the phase 3 reveal. cant wait to see what Keatons role in this would be tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a sequel to the last godzilla movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allot of events listed up here, allot of them revolving around a large portion of people dying. Tbh I think the destruction of the library of Alexandria is pretty bad, history wise at least.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 11:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will never get any movies like this in the future. The film industry barely make any movies that has the same quality as the ones made in the early 2000s, and by quality is mean that new films nowadays have way too much CGI and high quality resolution. I feel like when I watch a movie that came out today they have too much hd, contrast,lensflares(jj) for it too feel realistic. Movies like Fight Club, Lord of the Rings or even the Matrix didn't feel like they where overly abused with contrast or hd. Same goes fro tv series, shows like supernatural felt gritty, real and a little contrast. Now the series can barely be distinguished from a men's clothing commercial with the cast looking like models for f*cks sake...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 10:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/InGameShowerThoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 10:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every game I've played has run alright on Win10 so far, and I've had it since July last year. Only thing I'm not a fan of is the style and setup of basically everything, it took a while to get used to. Went online to find a few tips on how to change a couple of things to make it more similar Win7 and it makes it more bearable. So if you love the look and feel of Win7 and don't like too much changes, don't upgrade to Win10. On the other hand I think that everyone HAS to upgrade to Win10 at some point either they want to or not, just to play the new games that are coming out. Most likely more and more games will stop supporting Win7 and start using Win10

TL;DR Afraid of changes? Don't change. Don't mind them? Upgrade, eventually you'll have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 11:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gore movies, literally can't watch them at all for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Ainsley Harriot Cooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 21:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Ainsley Harriott Cooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 20:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Ainsley Harriott Cooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're going for the red hood storyline in the next solo batman movie, and that both Jason Todd and Dick Grayson is going to be in it. No idea who I'd want for Dick tho but I would love to see Jensen Ackles as Jason/Red Hood, loved him in the animated movie and I think he could fit perfectly as Jason. Agewise and fitness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it's set in the same universe as the last mummy films I think? If it is they should definitely bring Brendan Fraser in for a cameo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 12:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 11:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they remade this game for next gen consoles and perhaps launch it on pc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Praise the sun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 09:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I really liked the way they did the opening, how they just made the title small and focusing on what happened in the background instead of filling the whole screen with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 23:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I was one of the few who didn't have many glitches throughout the game, or maybe didn't focus/care so much if or when it happened. The game was awesome overall anyway but I see how people can get pissed at it. I remember being pissed cause I couldn't get to the last riddler  trophy in origins due to a glitch so I know how that feels like.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one that didn't have a problem with the PC version of the game? Like, no problems? I remember people had issues with using a controller instead of keyboard and mouse but that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 21:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of movies being adapted from games suck because there hasn't really been anyone really trying to make it right. The Silent Hill wasn't good but not bad either, somewhere in-between. So I get why you're saying that but when you get a great director, cast members and a compelling story the movie instantly get a bigger chance of becoming a good/great movie. Like the upcoming Assassin's Creed movie or Warcraft movie, both have great cast members and directors AND the difference from the other video game adaptations is that these are actually made by the companies that made the games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 09:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do people get this game? I've seen GIF's all over about this game but apparently it's still not out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 17:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a virgin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 17:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call of Duty franchise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite after credits scene in any movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is the scene after The Wolverine, with Ian McKellen and Patrick Stewart reprising their roles as Magneto and Xavier, just the reaction Wolverine gets seeing Charles after such a long time is awesome. (Also this just doesn't apply to Marvel movies) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus... What does it take to get you guys overseas to finally realize that this guy is no good..... (not saying all of you don't) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 09:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark souls and Amnesia, Dark Amnesia? *Dear god..* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] I need help with finding the right controller board for my laptop screen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 09:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My last computer was just laying there taking space so when I saw [this](http://imgur.com/a/Sqdeh#0) post I wanted to do the same. My laptop is an ASUS G75VW and the screen is in prestine condition. Here's the model number: [Model Number](http://i.imgur.com/aedp2G6.jpg)
So what I'm wondering about is what controller board should I get for the screen, every board I've found on Ebay all look the same so, which one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 19:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get the toy parts? I've only found the head and body but the arms and legs are no where </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] I need help with finding the right controller board for my laptop screen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be awesome just to see half of his face and having a line or two where the voicebox goes from his real voice to JEJ's voice, he's got the pissed off look done so that ain't a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
