<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4819</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 00:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got that, if anything most mainstream porn, especially American porn (but all the other ones as well) is incredibly homoerotic, and I never could understand how guys masterbate to that. It's like half the video is devoted to seeing a guy jerk into a girl's mouth ie blowjob, and I sit there thinking is the majority of American men really into watching another dude masturbate while a girl's face is in the background? I would much rather see a video of the girl getting off, rather than the guy. As a matter of fact most porn is TOO male centric and not enough focus on the woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 00:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe yeah. I was just remarking on how just last year, I was lamenting about getting asmr immunity, but since then in the last year and a half so many unique takes on asmr and unorthodox video have retriggered my asmr sensations by doing something unexpected instead of just the generic whispering or obnoxious tapping. It's so amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much good asmr, so little time. [Discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 11:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe this has now actually become a problem for me. So many new and unique asmrtists are coming out and making their own unique videos, and there's simply just not any time to watch them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much good asmr, so little time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 00:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HP Envy 5530 won't copy entire A4 page, the tip of the top is always cut off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried unplugging it from the power cord and plugging it back in but still doesn't copy a document properly, why does it do this? Any tips? I've tried going in settings but can't find something specific to copying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 10:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac and Dennis break up. 

Aka the origins of the dynamic duo, gruesome twosome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? That's what I  immediately thought. But I could type your ear off over some of the... shall we say idiosyncrasies of the Arab world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Men's portrayal of antiquated gender roles would actually be welcome... and it has aired here before. On the women's channel, to be even more ironic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I don't understand some of the people saying the Luke thing is cringe, it was hilarious for an older lady to be "going after" a young man, total sitcom material, A+ ! I mean sure they're kinda out of stories it seems for Luke. Hell they seem to not know what to do with Alex either; after another user stated how she just enters a scene to yell and then leave, I can't stop seeing it, with her just getting angry in every scene and literally scowling in the background, like that's all she's doing now, scowling as if that's her entire character. 

But I digress, I otherwise thought the episode like all of them was okay. 

What actually bothers me though, is Rainer's daughter. Are they seriously going to have us suspend our disbelief enough and pretend that this 6 foot tall, clearly 19+ year old girl  is 14? Come on son. That's bottom tier quality for an ABC show like Modern Family.


But otherwise, I don't get all the "creepy" posts, do some even know what it means? Also comedy is always about pushing boundaries into the uncomfortable zone, that's what makes things funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As someone from the stifling, freedom restricting Arab World, it's always HILARIOUS when they try to localize TV shows like The Simpsons and Modern Family. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you are unaware, this region of the world is predominantly Muslim so things like alcohol and premarital sex are not just taboo, but also grounds for capital punishment (extreme I know)

So for example, when they tried to localize something like The Simpsons, instead of beer, Homer's signature drink, they had him drink Pepsi, which is hilarious. Obviously it was heavily criticized and the show flopped because of the changes.

An even more hilarious one is Modern Family, which prominently features a homosexual couple, who have adopted a baby and are living together and everything. Now I need not state the prejudice that same sex couples might encounter in the West, but in Arabia they outright do not stand for it, and it's punished by physical violence, either torture or capital punishment. So when they tried to localize Modern Family, they either cut out most of Cam and Mitch's scenes, or edited them greatly, so a normally 20 minute show becomes what, 14 or 15 minute?

Just thought I'd share some of the frustratingly facepalming moments of this region and hope to garner some solidarity about how annoying it can be living in such a restrictive region of the world. You kind of have to be here to fully grasp some of the situation's stupidities, but nevertheless I just thought I'd show what life is like from the television medium aspect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 23:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All her twittery/social media photos do involve food and her eating some thing or other so I mean it was bound to happen. Burgers upon burgers upon all manner of fast food will eventually take their toll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the life of me I can't find the full video of Anny Aurora where she fucks in a garage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 23:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://picsee.net/upload/2015-03-06/39b2875f0b07.jpeg

I know it's from MyDirtyHobby, but I can't find the full complete video, it's like it disappeared from the internet and only a few 1 minute snippets remain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my GOD Taissia Shanti is so hot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically he was in a movie a few years ago with Jake Johnson who plays Nick on New Girl, so I always found that tidbit funny (not so much the movie itself). But yeah I'm a bit miffed he left since season 4 was such a sweet spot that balanced the entire cast perfectly (although season 6 while retreading a lot of ground, has been a step up from s5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hotspot Shield hasn't been working for the past... like, year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, in fact it's because he wanted to be doing more movies and felt that he was too big a star to be on a tv show, and wanted the silver screen instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok. No I'm saving it for a rainy day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 08:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The post was clearly talking about Hamlet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 07:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing. Absolutely beautiful and engaging, you feel captivated by every scene.

As for dialogue, I don't really know what Macbeth is like to compare it to, but it's Shakespeare. The lines are lifted verbatim from the play. 

But for the stuff that matters, I think you'll find it pretty easy to understand, like the one scene with "to thine own self be true" or Hamlet's constant indecisiveness and later transformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 07:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks and acts at least 11-13. Can't believe she was born as early as 2007, I feel so old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lol remember Winston's girlfriend Bertie from season 3? Who made the cream based soups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 23:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't even bother writing her out or giving a passing mention that Winston and her broke up, they just kind of... forgot about her.

Rewatching season 3 makes me remember how much they dialed Winston's crazy up to 11. Wasn't a great time, wasn't great... glad they found their sweet spot in season 4.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone noticed how tall Lily has gotten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like someone has been using the taffy puller from Willy Wonka on her or something. Maybe it's just camera angles and perspective, I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Always Sunny did it/said it first in The Gang Tries Desperately To Win An Award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When shows have not one "token black character" but two! And it's like, hallelujah what a game changer. But then... one of them leaves as if the only 1 token black character rule HAS to be applied. Eerie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever wonder why that is? Back in season 4 of New Girl we had both Coach (Damon Wayans jr) and Winston (Lamorne Morris) and it was a great season, and the entire cast had great chemistry even if it was bizarre to have 5 people living in one tiny loft. But then Coach left and it was back to one...

Same thing with Agents of Shield. First we had Trip join the agents and it was cool, and then the season after we got Mac, and it was like whoah! Two black characters on a show instead of just one token cast member, that's great! 

Up until... well you know. And there are many times that tv and movies have parodied the token minority character thing, like in that "not another teen movie" scene which always cracked me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh wow. Charlie's whole "all calico cats are female" is actually somewhat true. Sorry for doubting you Charlie __ . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a definitive version of Macbeth or film that has all the lines like 1996's Hamlet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 09:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the 2015 version with fassbender and marion since I love both these actors.

But I kinda am wondering if there's a version of Macbeth that's like Kenneth Branaugh's Hamlet with all the lines of the play and as beautifully decorated and shot. 

Also I hear the 2015 version takes some liberties with the story and I just want a movie that really tells me what Macbeth is, since like Hamlet it's a Shakespeare story I never got the opportunity to read and I'd like to experience it through film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hell yeah I love when someone posts a NEW tracy scops comic. Thanks so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hell yeah I love when someone posts a NEW tracy scops comic. Thanks so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you obsessively watch all these teasers, trailers, and news stories, then you've basically watched the gist of the entire movie and ruined it for yourself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 11:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now sure if you don't care about being spoiled that's one thing, but finding out every little tidbit about the movie just makes it a whole lot less fun and potentially sets you up for disappointment so... I can't understand that need to consume every single little bit of media, even if you're not part of the internet generation.

I enjoy discussing a movie obsessively after it comes out and I've seen it, but I'd rather the experience stay fresh before I go to see it instead of know what x actor did x thing for x scene in the movie. But hey that's just me. I know from experience that consuming every little bit of media is exhausting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my gosh yes exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know exactly what triggers this drive to stuff my face whenever I get depressed. It's very complicated, tying in to the whole not having any friends and feeling depressed about life and finding the cathartic release in just sitting in my room eating and watching media to dull my mind and not think about how unhappy I am. But appreciate the kind words, a little goes a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always forget how to find my computer's specs. I'm not really a computer person like most people here, heck the only other game I have on steam is portal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I don't have an xbox controller, any alternatives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to try Psychonauts for the first time what with all the praise, but just want to be sure I can run it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I eat like 50 cereal and milk bars a day. That's the worst kind of sugar addiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each bar has 8 grams of sugar. That's 400 grams of sugar A DAY. So I'm eating an entire pound of sugar every day, and I really can't stop myself when I'm in this rut, until the actual grocery stores run out of the product, that's how bad I am with this. 

I can't tell you how terrifying it is when I get tingling sensations in my toes and feet but I. Just. Can't. Stop. I'm insane. Just a crazy idiot person quite frankly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I should clarify by saying election moreso than political. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Political" episodes in sitcoms are always the absolute worst, not to mention forever dating the show and/or those specific episodes. Why do shows do them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not funny, they definitely don't appeal to an international audience (ie people like me) and they just make the show seem dated many years from now, so the unfunny jokes become more cringey in just a few years' time. 

For example, I love 30 Rock; its first 3 seasons are absolutely comedy gold, some of the best comedy on TV. However they wasted almost the entirety of their final season, season 7 (which was already only half a season with 12 episodes instead of the standard 20-24 episodes) on the stupid american political debate thing with... whoever the hell was running against Obama back in 2012 (I mean I don't even remember, that's how dated it is) and it just seems like a terrible idea to waste the final season of the show on a political debate that literally no one would remember after the fact. 

And I was recently watching a New Girl episode that featured this recent election with the 2 horrible candidates and it was, if possible, even worse than the 5-6 episodes of 30 Rock that were devoted to the politics. 

There are probably more examples but these are the 2 that come to mind in recent memory. What are your thoughts on election/political type episodes? Especially if they're heavy handed in an otherwise comedy show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is no one watching New Girl anymore? Its individual sub is so damn dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened? The show is still pretty funny and enjoyable. Sure last season had the blight of megan plastic-face fox who is a horrible horrible actress that brought down the already weak season 5, but still the show as a whole is pretty enjoyable, and season 6 has been shaping up to look pretty good. 

Yet there are no individual episode discussions and the topics are spaced like months apart, for a still ongoing show. Television fans, is no one watching New Girl anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/search?q=The+best+Jerry oq=The+best+Jerry aqs=chrome..69i57j69i64l3j69i60 sourceid=chrome ie=UTF-8

It's a quote from this tv show that released in the 80s and was popular in then 90s of the country known as usa, on the american broadcasting channel known as nbc. The show was called seinfeld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love incase. I mean... this guy's the only artist who basically made me read gay porn and I didn't immediately exit the tab, all because I actually got invested in the story of Alfie. 

And goddamn. It's like at first the comic is quite erotic but now it's just constantly giving me THEM FEELS. It's too emotional. I just want a happy ending for everyone, I've become so invested in all of their lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I hope you're serious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a more Buffy/Firefly vibe, which is why I actually love the first few episodes before the Hydra storyline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 3 blows season 5 out of the water, and while I disliked it a bit when it aired I find that the hate for season 3 is entirely unjustified as there are still hilarious moments in the episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will we ever see the teases they built up in season 1 like gravitron? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember thinking the HIVE stone slab was supposed to be the gravitonium which would have been an amazing throwback to tie season 1 even further. 

But it turned out to be something else entirely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So far I'm liking this season more than last, so that's good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could have done without the stupid Reagan relationship though, it's pretty sad to try and make an offscreen relationship. Not that I want to actually see megan plastic-face fox,  I'd rather nick and jess get together if nothing else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So why are American porn guys so empty during the cumshot compared to Japanese porn guys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In American porn the guy's moneyshot is almost like sterile or cumming dust, while in Japanese porn the creampie shot or cumshot always has plenty of semen all over or inside the woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best scene in Blade. The best Jerry. Blade Spoilers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 11:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Val Kilmer was hottest Batman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://img.buzzfeed.com/buzzfeed-static/static/2015-01/20/17/enhanced/webdr05/grid-cell-7566-1421794689-14.jpg

No one ever mentions this in discussions, why? I thought he was really good looking, always wondered why he didn't return for shoemaker's other batman movie.

In Batman Forever I actually thought he was really good in maintaining a dark side especially when they delved into the whole psychology of Bruce Wayne and that speech he gave to Robin about revenge was also really good. 

I feel like he's an underrated Batman/Bruce that no one mentions in discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 08:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right? I love that about this place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I would like to recommend to you another unknown series with Ken Marino that while not as hilarious as party down, is still pretty damn funny: burning love. I just found out about this show and it's cracking me up, even though I've never seen the shows it parodies. Ken Marino is awesome in damn near everything, I love his guest stars on shows like veronica mars and happy endings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ken Marino is by far the best new captain they got for the precinct. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong I like Dennis Duffy, even if his jerkitude is amped up by 11, but Ken Marino is damn awesome.

"Uh oh Captain Stentley, am I in trouble?"

"No, you're *our* boss"

"Oh right, right"

I damn nearly blew a gasket from laughing so hard at that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and let's not forget just how much Ryan Reynolds put into this role, he's a HUGE part of what makes this movie great. There are so few actors who were born to play characters, and RR as Deadpool is just... beautiful. Amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the hell did Batman: Mask of the Phantasm underperform at the box office back in 1993? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People back then should be ashamed of themselves for not going to see it, how is that even possible? I still remember my parents taking me and my baby brother to the movie, and it was amazing. 

Although what's actually amazing is that you appreciate the movie way more as an adult, and catch a lot more dialogue and implications in scenes. Joker, Batman, the phantasm... my god this movie is so 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did Deadpool make so much money at the box office, and how can we use that tactic for other amazing movies to make as much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this stuff going against it:

- R rated superhero movie

- Obscure comic book character that only internet nerds know about

- Released in **February**

- *Actually good*

I mean... it had all this stuff going against it, and yet it pulled so much money at the box office, like insane numbers on the budget it had.

Is it thanks to girls that the movie made so much money, that it released on valentine's day so had a lot of the female audience going to see it? If you'll recall the female audience is usually where the money is, eg twilight and frozen and 50 shades of grey. Could that account for how it made so much money? 

I mean who would have ever thought we'd ever get such an amazing Deadpool movie, or even a Deadpool movie at all, in this timeline. We need to harness this power and use it for future movies of obscure comic book characters and less mainstream characters that are not batman/superman/spiderman (ie the big 3)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone watch the New Girl and Brooklyn Nine Nine crossover episodes? I'm so hyped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was watching New Girl when *all of a sudden Jake Peralta shows up!* I nearly blew a gasket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's always the case though isn't it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About Koba (ape with scar on his eye) Dawn and Rise of the planet of the apes spoilers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else totally get a Scar from the Lion King vibe from him, especially with his whole manipulating of the apes clan and Caesar's son?

And anyone else find Koba's demise in Dawn of the Planet of the Apes really ironic?

In Rise, Jacobs is hanging for his life in a crashed helicopter, and Koba mercilessly pushes it over the edge. 

In Dawn, Koba is hanging for his life on the tower edge. Caesar doesn't help him and lets him fall.

Looks like karma came to bite him in the ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate it guys thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barbershop: The Next Cut was rather topical wasn't it? Preachy too. But very good movie, and possibly needed to be. Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I especially don't get agree with most of the things the characters are saying regarding attraction and saying things like "this is what ALL men want" and "this is what ALL women like"

Otherwise I think I kind of like it. It's weirdly a lot more heartfelt than I would expect from Ice Cube and a sequel that's a whopping 14 years after the original. Enjoyed seeing characters like Eve  keeping it tight for a 14 year age different since Barbershop 1. And while I really don't like that singer niki minaj with her incredibly plastic appearance, I found her character here surprisingly funny in that "person you want to hate" kinda way.

Rest of the cast is shaping up nicely. Common is keeping it real. Winston from New Girl is a fantastic addition. The kid actors are... passable. There presence serves its purpose in the message the movie is trying to send and I like it too. 

All in all I'm surprised it's nearly 2 hours, it feels much shorter since it's such a seemingly simple plot that has a lot of heart thanks to the performances and the character interactions. Almost just like the first in that way isn't it. 

Really didn't expect it to be as good as it was. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever notice how so many tv characters go by their last names? I wonder why that is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e.g. cartman, fry, quagmire, kramer, etc.
 
A lot, like Schmidt from New Girl, have the trope of creating an air of mystery over what the character's "real name" or first name actually is.

What's really weird is that on Scrubs, Carla calls her husband by his last name, Turk. I mean maybe I could understand JD calling him Turk, but it just sounds weird for the wife to address her husband by his last name instead of first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time in my life I think I'm actually considering the whole "build your own pc" concept. Or at the very least... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  maybe try to find one of those places that build the pc for you but with all the best parts and the most rams, I have no problem paying extra.

This prebuilt all in one desktop pc that I bought last year... it's a piece of crap. Straight out of the box it was giving me blue screens of death. I took care of that eventually, but it still has always had terrible specs, is rather laggy, can't handle a bunch of programs open at once, and just really makes me regret spending so much on it.

Games are not really important, I just for once want a pc that has a very high processing power, can handle several tabs especially youtube videos and etc, adobe acrobat and reader, my email, and can do a comprehensive scan to boot. Basically the works. 

I wouldn't want to buy another prebuilt pc since they all come with Windows 10 now. I mean 8.1 is no picnic but I think I'd be comfortable with it since I'm mostly used to the OS for better or worse. 

Is there a specific website people go to for pc building? A shopping site that puts parts all together? An actual brick and mortar store that you go to where they'll just assemble the parts together for you? 

And is it just the desktop that people build when talking about pc building, while they buy any monitor or do pc gamer build the monitor too? Just wonder since All-in-one PCs don't seem to be the lifesaver I thought they would be in saving me space on my desk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean breastfeeding pretty much gets rid of a majority of the weight women gain during pregnancy, at least any weight gain during the second or third trimester. Any weight before that stays on. I'm just surprised she wasn't hassled by the studio about it, that's surprising of a giant conglomerate like CBS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, let's just say nearly, or almost. I mean what must that even be like for the actress? I was under the impression that tv producers and the like put a lot of pressure on actresses to be thin and conform to typical Western expectations of female beauty, so I wonder if this was ever brought up to the actress by the studio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King of Queens might be the only sitcom where the hot wife of the fat guy becomes also fat like her husband. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As is a common staple of sitcoms, cartoon or live action in America, the morbidly obese fat guy seems to always have a stellar hot wife who would never actually be with this slob in real life as JD's Scrubs would put it. 

Now in this case I think she may have been pregnant and just gained a little bit of weight so it's not exactly the same thing, but near the end of King of Queens run I happened to catch an episode of one of the later seasons and was shocked at how big Carrie became. It almost seemed like her husband's bad eating habits and diet had started to affect her so she was just as big as Kevin James was. Almost seemed like the effect of a bad influence (Kevin James) on a person, can't explain why I felt that way when I was younger but that's what it felt like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manipulating Triple Triad rules in FF 8 is such a headache. Any tips? Spoilers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many more seasons do you think it's always sunny in Philadelphia has left in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what are your thoughts on the recent seasons, especially 11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well considering modern family is an amazing abc comedy and not a garbage CBS show that inexplicably get millions of viewers, that goes without saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 09:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird that I deleted that,  I usually only delete stuff that don't get any posts so I can resubmit them again and hopefully generate discussion. 

Anyway fair enough, just wanted to see if this website uses America's laughably hypocritical laws in regards to this stuff or if it is a more international website, with users from different parts of the globe like me that don't adhere to your or Americans' upbringing in that kinda stuff. 

But don't assume anything, I don't do "sneaky" or whatever nonsense you're inferring, I come from a culture where if I want something I demand it outright and am *very* specific about its criteria. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At your last sentence: Um what???!

No seriously what are you even talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah revenge isn't exactly a reason. A non germaphobic person wouldn't get naked in a public place and sit in a car, there's absolutely no way sheldon would. 

I guess it's the kind of nitpicking Sheldon himself would do if he happened to watch tbbt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How young is allowed on here? Is it going by only America's over 18 ruling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol totally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sheldon's OCDNess is incredibly inconsistent in The Big Bang Theory. Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As well as just his general personality and characteristics.

For example, he goes diving in a children's ballpit area and really immerses himself in it. Um gross? Literally everyone is aware of the fact that ballpits are giant germ infected areas filled with the poops and pees of thousands of kids. They're an infection magnet even regardless of that. And yet Sheldon dives into one? Yeah right. Dude throws away his entire food container if someone takes out like one fry.

Then there's the time he literally got naked in the college campus parking lot and sat in Howard's car, like completely naked and in another person's car. The dude who has a specific spot on the couch to sit in and won't allow any compromise of the location. 

It just doesn't make any sense, and that kind of inconsistency is jarring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hell WAS vanilla sky all about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 13:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty young when I saw this movie so understood none of it, and haven't seen it since it came out.

I know it's a remake of a Spanish movie, has anyone seen both and can give me their interpretation and impressions of the plot? It's really quite a mind whirl, and I was always confused by what was real or a dream state or whatever the heck was going on in that movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the bbc miniseries the cartoon? Because I remember watching the lion the witch and the wardrobe as a kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chronicles of Narnia movies were trying SO hard to be the next lord of the rings. Disney was trying so hard to push them as such. Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney gave up after the second one hehe and gave the franchise to Fox for the 3rd one. 

Thing is, I kinda liked some scenes in the first 2 movies. I especially thought Prince Caspian had a ton of potential to be what disney were trying to market as "epic" and there were particularly scenes that I thought were great, particularly the cameo of the Witch. 

I think they were held back by being like, pg rated or something, especially prince Caspian which had a lot more adult themes of betrayal and bloodshed. I mean you can't have a pg war, it just doesn't work. So disney at the time didn't realize they couldn't have it both ways, be for children and dark/epic for adults at the same time. 

But I liked the first 2 for the most part. I did happen to catch the 3rd one a few months ago... wasn't a fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 10:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you even talking about,  who said anything about dofp being about wolverine?  The criticism  is aimed at it being about mystique  because that no talent hack jlaw somehow became this big star for some reason,  so studios were so obviously milking that   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyfall was praised, Spectre was criticized. Days of Future Past was praised, Apocalypse was criticized. But... both Skyfall and DoFP were as bad as their sequels. I never got why they were critically lauded. Many spoilers for all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 08:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many things about Skyfall I disliked, from the sudden jump in time where Bond who *just* got his 00 license is now apparently too old, abandoning the plot/secret organization that Casino Royale and Quantum of Solace (which everyone hates but I felt was a good resolution to the vesper storyline, one of the best aspects of the reboot) set up, and a joker ripoff of a villain who totally copies the "planned to get caught" nonsense again and didn't pull it off nearly as well. Where the hell did the train come from. Oh and I'm not even going to get into that home alone finale. The fact that this movie made a billion dollars is just... I mean with **that** finale... I just can't even. 

Then we have DoFP. Oh boy I don't even know where to start with this movie, we'll be here forever. Remember when we were getting tired of Wolverine being center stage for every single xmen movie, to the point where they literally made a show called wolverine and the xmen? Yeah I now miss that, because anything is better than the mystique show. Christ not only is jlaw a terrible actress (at least Hugh Jackman is a great one and really made wolverine work) but their extreme focus on her inconsistent character is just completely misguided. It's what brought down first class, which was an amazing return to form and a shame they killed off all the characters there off screen (really, the powerful emma is killed off? How does that work exactly). I mean I could criticize every aspect of this movie (besides the rather cool quicksilver scene which singer literally just did again for Apocalypse) but let's just say that I would have much rather just watched an entire movie with the future segments and how all these cool new xmen with barely any dialogue met up. THAT would have made for a much better movie than this recent decade hopping trend the crappy xmen series has been doing. 

It's just weird how Skyfall and DoFP were praised when they share the exact same flaws their sequels do, and it's as if it took the sequels for people to finally notice the flaws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you 2 and the cowardly down voters who haven't shown  their face are terrible  people. I bet you thought dexter's ending was great as well right? I hope you don't represent the attitude of this forum because that would be horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you 2 and the cowardly down voters who haven't shown  their face are terrible  people. I bet you thought dexter's ending was great as well right? I hope you don't represent the attitude of this forum because that would be horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lol yeah that came out of nowhere. Boy dexter was terrible at deciding what to do with all the side characters and subplots wasn't it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... you thought what season 2 did with trying to build up some kinda romance with penny and Dave was a *good* idea?  Every other fan of  the show that I know of hated that and thought it was terribly forced in an otherwise amazing season of happy endings (so many abc shows that got canceled,  this and suburgatory and the Grand daddy Mac of them all,  better of ted) that  unfairly  got cancelled  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god you reminded me of how much I hate Lost, a show I was completely in love with and invested in up until season 5. That whole Sawyer Juliet thing was part of it. Not least because it was lazily done offscreen. God this show makes me so mad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really? Tell me more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the op I meant ones that haven't  been  built up,  and are like just friends or casual  acquaintances for a couple of seasons and then bam all of a sudden  are sleeping  together  and/or in love. Or at least dating. It feels  like  Friends is the only show  that did this  and I'm trying to remember  other shows that  did  something  similar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Other shows that did what FRIENDS did with Monica and Chandler? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make 2 main established   characters that didn't have a will they/won't  they setup,  hook up out of the blue and  then end up  pronouncing  their undying love for each other, potentially  getting married  (but not necessarily  for this comparison) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I meant, it was saccharine in that old school 1960s way and I really liked it, actually feel it's timeless otherwise and not dated like some other critically lauded children's movies. 

Find myself singing the tunes often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *have* always thought they're awfully catty  and snippy with each other at times  throughout  the seasons... thought it was just me  who was thinking that   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm... why do you think Cam and Mitch would divorce?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw 1968's Oliver! Wow that was really good, I definitely recommend it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The musical numbers just keep coming, it's really fast paced. And they're incredibly catchy, I recognize some of them even though I've never seen that movie, they're really iconic. 

I'm just surprised by how much I like it.

I love Ron Moody as Fagin and all his numbers are probably my favorite, like pick a pocket or two and reviewing the situation. 

All in all, I think this is the kind of movie that I'd watch again. As someone who's read the book I really thought this musical was a great adaptation of the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know how hentai has a lot of talking during sex? I kinda want that with some live action porn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the girl saying stuff like how her pussy ridges are squeezing down on the guy's shaft, and she wants to feel his cum inside her. Really dirty stuff like that but none of the boring stuff like just saying "fuck" and "yeah" like mainstream American porn does. Something a bit more erotic for dirty talk than those two words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 13:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so when shopping should I look for a water resistant type label? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds great for me since I tend to get cold feet anyway. 

But out of curiosity what are fast drying shoes? Do you have any examples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waterproof running shoes for flat footed individuals? For running in the rain and having dry socks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine was showing me how his feet were very dry and he was wearing salomon shoes. My shoes on the other hand were soaked. 

Ideally I'd like the shoes to also have some arch support until I can get some good arches of my own. But yeah I tried wearing the brand salomon shoes but they're too uncomfortable for my flat feet. 

Just wondering if anyone has experience with waterproof shoes since it rains a lot and while I don't mind the rain at all, I do want shows that can withstand the rain so I don't get soggy socks and basically ruin the shoe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This new show called Humans, any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw an ad for it and just curious. Has anyone here been watching it, and give some impressions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh coolio. Yeah she's amazing. Here's another one of hers:

https://www.reddit.com/r/JavDownloadCenter/comments/4cmoyw/new_updated_link_caribbean121815453_1080p/

Hell I'll just link you to her sub:

https://www.reddit.com/r/ai_uehara/

Enjoy ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you fish out a topic from 4 months ago? Anyway I think it's PLA-045 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the fact that they both came out the same year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have they made an adblock yet for youtube's inhouse app and chrome browser for non-rooted phones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How to repel flies from the outside patio that we eat on? Does lavender really work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 08:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to repel flies from the outside patio that we eat on? Does lavender really work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 08:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... how long will the show go on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think we'll get to see Lily go to college? You think we'll get to... seeing Joe go to college??!!!

Just curious how long the show will last. I feel it's been pretty consistent in amazing quality these past 7 and now 8 seasons. Though I do feel sad about Andy being put on a bus, I really felt he was a permanent member of the cast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is she? Unbelievably hot scene. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=ph5744dce867ab0

I damn well came twice when she basically screamed for the guy to cum in her. Hoping to find more of her with a guy who can actually stay hard for this lovely lady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone find porn with a lot of kissing, a lot of erotic talking, and ending in creampie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love stuff like the girl saying how her vagina is fitted just for this penis, and how it's reaching every part of her. And then telling the guy to cum in her. It's the best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have E319's BTS? I'd love to see it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... it's good for you? Tell me more, I'm interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So cooking with coconut oil is clearly bad for you right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been debating this with a friend. I would have thought it was well known that coconut oil is super unhealthy fatty and the least best oil to cook with for the whole polyunsaturated fats vs saturated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So cooking with coconut oil is clearly bad for you right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been debating this with a friend. I would have thought it was well known that coconut oil is super unhealthy fatty and the least best oil to cook with for the whole polyunsaturated fats vs saturated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That comic makes me think Hive was Marvel's version of DC's Starro. That eye in the middle reminded me of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fucking shit... you're a genius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the heck did they have Ward dressed like Neo from The Matrix sequels last season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... someone in wardrobe HAD to have noticed that... 

Actually,  now that I think about it he kind of acted like Neo from The Matrix sequels as well didn't he. Wonder if it was intentional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow man excellent list, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have an imgur gallery of all the recent tracy scops comics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 07:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kaylee from x-art. Video is called "first love" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This does make sense.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This all makes a lot of sense thanks for the read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm yes I definitely understand the religion/cult like aspect, I can definitely see it from that point of view.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just don't get season 3 Hydra and Malick's motivation for bringing the creature back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sane person would want to invite this sort of thing back to Earth?  I mean why intentionally bring a bigger fish into your own pond? Did they think it will share its powers with Hydra? That they could control it or use it as a weapon to control the world? With evil beings that's rarely ever the case. Doesn't seem like many if anyone would benefit from it's return besides Hive itself. So you just signed up to make yourself and everyone you know it's bitch, not something a multi-billionaire powerful man would be ready to do, powerful men simply don't become subservient. 

I just felt that entire aspect last season was weak sauce. A multi billionaire couldn't see that this creature will clearly betray him and could eat him alive? Literally!

Another thing I don't get, why does Hive say he needs a Malick by his side? After killing Gideon's daughter he just up and kills Gideon the next episode. May as well have killed Gideon then before Gideon seemingly destroyed all Hydra operations out of revenge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait I'm confused about one of the openings of last season's finale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 23:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skye/Daisy and Coulson were in one of those containment boxes on a ravaged planet and Phil says "but Daisy... this is earth" but nowhere in the finale did a scene like that happen so I'm wondering if the event in question hasn't happened yet or if it was just meant to be a hallucination? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait I just realized: Mac who is gay played "that girl is poison" song while simulating fellatio on Dennis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the classic finale "the gang dances their asses off"

I never realized how deliberate that choice of song was lol. It definitely fits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His art is out of this world... just need him to do a more lovey dovey story line instead of, well, rape. Also needs more creampie instead of the typical mainstream american porn "moneyshot". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it comparable to ugly Betty in tone or humor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jane the Virgin? Has anyone watched this show? Is it any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 16:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you "accidentally" artificially inseminate someone??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's the age difference between Claire and Gloria in the show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 16:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious. Funny thing is Julie Bowen is actually 2 years older than Sofia, yet I kinda got the impression in the show that Gloria is a few years slightly older than Claire, but not by much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough I suppose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the simpsons is still popular and going on strong if it has similar view numbers to an amazing fantastic show like modern family, so hopefully it will make it to the 30th season for a landmark achievement. 

Not really that hard to figure out in the context of this topic and what I'm asking for. Incidentally, the downvotes by some of the users were particularly childish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 23:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked and one of the episodes last season actually had a whopping 8 million viewers! That's the same amount as modern family averages, goddamn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet that other poster above yours says that Liquid "just wanted his own country to live with his brothers" painting Liquid as a sympathetic nice character, as opposed to a anarchistic villain type person as you seem to describe him. Surprised that there are differing views on Liquid who we know so little about (beyond his obsession with dominant and recessive genes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how new venues of watching media like Netflix are factored in to Network executives. Are there ads on Netlfix? I wonder how they make money beyond the low subscription people pay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of curiosity does anyone know how many viewers the simpsons has? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to check ratings, has the simpsons had decreased viewers throughout the years, just wondering if the network executives have a way to find out the answer to all these questions. 

I'm just wondering if the simpsons will make it to their 30th season since that will be quite the landmark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In hindsight, why in the hell did Solidus, Ocelot, and Snake not work together? Series Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering they, you know, all wanted to defeat the patriots... hell even Liquid did. Literally all 4 of them, and all 3 Snakes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In hindsight, why in the hell did Solidus, Ocelot, and Snake not work together? Series Spoilers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering they, you know, all wanted to defeat the patriots... hell even Liquid did. Literally all 4 of them, and all 3 Snakes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 09:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a rule of thumb if there are quick cuts and edits instead of one long continuous shot, it's fake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the video in question is fake, if you'd read the other comments you'd know she doesn't do *real* creampie videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird how you fished out this topic from 2 months ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda doesn't, since I don't live in America :p . Appreciate the help though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 12:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm experiencing this right now. Can't find any of the episodes. There's 3 seasons and 14 episodes each right? Yeah I can't find most of them. Wonder what's causing such a lack of availability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 23:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's an understudy for Jeff. He has to wear a blond wig on top of his Chang hair, and a bald cap on top of that. There's no air getting through, he's literally dying.  

But you'll never hear his story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... they have billions of dollars. They even spent some of those billions buying stuff like tumblr (the dot-com website not that Nolan Batman vehicle) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched the first 5 minutes... immediately grinned. Think I'm gonna like this.

Also why is Ken Jeong (Chang from Community) playing a woman? I don't get it... otherwise, all the women candidates they've chosen are... well really attractive. Insanely so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The order is seriously confusing me/throwing me off.

Speaking of Children's Hospital that's another parody show I've always wanted to watch. I saw an episode like years ago but never was able to procure the entire series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone watched a show called Burning Love? Is it any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched Party Down before and it was a little known comedy on Starz that I actually found pretty funny.  Wondering if Burning Love is any good or funny. Wikipedia says it's a spoof of the bachelor shows of America, but since I'm neither American nor am familiar with these types of shows, I don't know if the humor would still suit me. I did like the "bachelor" inspired episode of Another Period, after being told what it was spoofing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I wasn't actually expecting to ever know the truth behind it, thank you! Appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What in the HELL, is a head-cha-la? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless I'm not hearing the lyrics correctly? Cha la, head cha la?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 10:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently watch angie t. Are you sure it's the same station as b99? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 08:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True... although I do find myself a little frustrated that all my favorite new comedies seem to be ones that you "either get it or you don't" like The Grinder, which I thought was hilarious but ended up being canceled :( . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 08:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity I wonder what possessed you to type a comment like that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So did anyone watch Another Period season 2? It is hilarious, I love this show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing a little notification for a show called Another Period last year on tv, and thinking "huh this looks interesting" and by god it was hilarious. 

It's one of the best comedies on tv that no one is watching. It's chock full of satire, crassness and humor that's done so well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I've always wondered about How To Train Your Dragon 2... (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 18:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did Drago even get control of an alpha dragon? I mean the damn thing can just squish him, why is it remotely afraid of him? This is something I've always wondered especially since he's the reason for causing toothless to kill Hiccup's dad. That made me so sad, and it's especially sad because hiccup *just* got to know his mother, only to lose his father...

I had heard that they were originally going to make his mother the villain of the story but there were some rewrites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I've always wondered about How To Train Your Dragon 2... (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 18:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool thanks. Do you have any of his others? Let me see if I can link to his amazon page with all his books, if some of them are as interesting as those 2 I'd like to read them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, do you have any of the ones on Amazon? Also was Neighborhood by him as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh I was just reading this the other week. Love this guy for actually having story in his work and actual characters, like people you sympathize with, that make you laugh, cry, basically *feel*.

Does anyone have his other stuff? He's done some other cool things as well. I do prefer creampies best in terms of the sex, which he does rarely so that's the one thing I'd change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best Anti-Virus on the market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 13:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throughout the years I've used the combo of AVG+Malwarebytes, Microsoft Security Essentials+Malwarebytes, and Avast+Malwarebytes. I've currently been using Avast for the past 3 or 4 years, ever since it was reported MSE was no longer as good as it was before. 

Just wondering if there's a best. I mean I'll probably never need it but always good to have, especially if people stick their flash drives in my pc's port for numerous reasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 08:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didn't isohunt go defunct? It was my go to place for the last 5 years after mininova and other such sites went defunct, especially since at the time I had an old computer with an older client that couldn't recognize magnet links, which tpb uses almost exclusively now. 

I got a new computer and qbittorrent in 2015 though, so magnet links no longer became a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know what that means, but luckily extratorrent's link worked! That was a major relief, appreciate the help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks yeah I'm testing it now, if the link works then it's all good, here's hoping. Will be using extratorrent from now as a backup. Always good to have one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... is there an alternative torrent site to tpb for a specific link that's not working on tpb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 12:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a torrent that has no seeders on thepiratebay so for days it's been either stalling or just simply sitting in qbittorrent idly without downloading anything at all. 

Was just curious if there are still any trust worthy sites left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 10:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. I do enjoy stir frying as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 10:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah cool thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not poultry or fish? How about beans, do they not have complete proteins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 17:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah interesting. Yeah I was just wondering if roasting crickets was a thing as opposed to frying. 

Also what regular foods contain  bcaas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 16:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... a little bit of both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post comes off as hostile. I wonder why you're acting that way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is eating insects all that healthy when most of these asian countries are frying them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is eating insects all that healthy when most of these east asian countries are deep frying them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... that kinda beats the point health wise, which for me would be the only reason to eat something like crickets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the best place on reddit to post about general things, like a social board? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 13:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That does make sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that does make sense, and I suppose for large scale corporations they would outsource it to a 3rd party... not too sure about small businesses though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 years later, I still don't know if George Clooney's profession in that movie Up in the Air was a real job. *safety spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The basic premise of the movie is George Clooney works for an agency that handles firing people for companies that are... too shy to do it themselves or something? Lol what. There's no room for shyness in the cutthroat business industry.

Especially since it's like... you're paying an outside company to fire employees that you're firing to save money? I love the movie, George Clooney and Anna Kendrick's performances knock it out of the park (as well as Vera Farmiga) but the premise is... to quote Aquaman, "outrageous" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's weird how rare balls deep creampies are. There needs to be more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 08:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the creampies have just the tip of the penis at the entrance of the vagina and worse, has the dude needing to jack himself off inside her. Gross. Creampies need to be balls deep, ideally with the guy and girl tongue kissing each other the moment it happens. 

Have any of you encountered a perfect porn scene like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No trust me they're definitely fake. Not that there's anything wrong with that, for me it's more about the believable performance even if it's fake, and the ones like bangbus are so poorly acted and cringey it makes me exit the tab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 08:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are all fake though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 09:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I love Boyle. He went from a bit of a creeper in his whole Rosa obsession to easily one of the best characters. 

Also while it's meant as a joke, I can totally see his point of view on sound. For example a lot of people get snacky and like to eat chips for that crunch sound. For a healthier alternative you can substitute it with apples and/or carrots for the similar satisfying crunch sound while simultaneously being healthy. So it's an actual thing hehe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you agree or disagree with the beast of a billion backs? Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 12:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in a "perfect" utopia where everyone is connected to each other, you think that was a good thing? Did you side with Bender when he came on his ship to infiltrate the world, or did you wish he'd just left well enough alone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok so... the whole Rosa and Adrian Pimento thing was weird right? Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 10:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought nick cannon was a weird choice to use for rosa's boyfriend since bnn is a fantastic show that's way out of his league acting wise. 

But then Adrian Pimento comes along and I recognize him from parks and rec so that made me smile. Then the whole silly flirtation thing with him and Rosa Diaz made me laugh. 

But then... in the next episode rosa wants to marry him? That was... kinda fast. Even in the context of a few months, that did seem wildly out of character. 

Also this: "You guys, I can't *wait* to spend my life with Adrian Pimento."

That statement alone, I couldn't help feeling that came out of left field from rosa's mouth. Didn't she break up with nick cannon because she wasn't sure if she was ready for that kinda next step?

I dunno. I do like that actor from his parks and rec role, but I can't help feeling this whole romance was rather rushed. So I didn't feel *as* invested as I could have in the whole attempted assassination and him having to leave and/or written out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 09:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice find! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't seen finding dory, I do hope it's good though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I do like a simple story, like what they did Inside Out. So that's not to say I don't also appreciate  something more grounded in some ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess since I come from a somewhat more collectivist society than an American/western one that celebrates individualism, we don't really have what the west has with old people being alone and/or put in homes, since it's a very family oriented society. 

I *can* understand everyone you've ever known dying and you being the only one left, but still... old curmudgeony man that's literally the "get off my lawn!" stereotype of cartoons and such? Very poor compared to an idea as wonderfully original as say, Ratatouille.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
