<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9525</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to abandon a game because of valve's bullshit server gave me a 2.7k ms ping. Now I'm in low priority. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Volvo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 08:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how no one has selected support. Very realistic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 08:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Same goes for me. Only stacking camps requires you to know about timings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about a build that has no cool downs? 
Boots, Aquila, sny, skadi, crit. You'll deal 2x damage in fights and still have enough damage to push when needed. Battle warden is what Volvo wants, hence the nerfs. Also, I guess midas is still good if you sync up the cd's on hero and tempest double  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the sabre on a core doom with infernal blade. 1st hit ministun and damage, 2nd hit slow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enigma seems like a good option but the black hole disable does not count. So, I had to do it with malifice in a 110 minute game. And I got it done just as we destroyed the enemy ancient. So, not recommended  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 05:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's around the x:27 or x:54. But I prefer to pull that camp without looking at the clock. You stand in vision of the neutrals and pull just as the wave is reaching the tier 1. Feels easier that way for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 07:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ubisoft had said that the story will not feature anything from the video games released so far and that they will create a different story line seperate from Desmond Miles and what's-his-face from Black Flag. So, it was either the Spanish inquisition, or ancient Egypt or some other important time in mankind's history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 07:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the lane is pushed, you can always pull it back with the hard camp pull  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question to that is since sunray does max hp % based damage, will the spirits do more damage in the early game?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the total damage from the fire spirits  birdlaser earlier on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skill build on Phoenix support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 19:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen Fly do 1-1-2, kuro 1-2-1. How to decide when to go for which one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 08:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try maxing poison touch before heal. Watch the world burn. ZFreek did this yesterday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 08:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just played a game where I picked enigma and then my team went on to pick PA, wind, troll and slark. And kept asking me for wards and kept asking me to gank at level 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 08:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But his base damage is so low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 07:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just thinking on the lines of set up for the egg, mate. And the draft would benefit more from a support duo who can set up each other instead of a void or ds in the core line up + insane amount of sustenance. Sure, they will lack a bit in the disable department but once the laning phase is done, there are hardly any core heroes who will keep farming (except maybe spectre, but haunt so...) and because the supports are self sufficient in ensuring a good team fight, core picks can be more damage or push oriented instead of more team fight. Imagine this lineup: ck, Dp, treant, tide, Phoenix. 
You got the crowd control from tide, pushing power and team fight from Dp as well ck, sustain from bird laser, living armour. And they have plenty of catch from ck stun, Dp silence, tide gush.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 13:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what you mean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 13:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CC element can be easily brought in from the cores, and the tree ult doesn't have that high a CD as compared to other team fight ults. Also, his ability to heal towers would go along really well with the current style of play of fighting, going for objectives and repeating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 12:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As we saw with fly Phoenix yesterday, Phoenix doesn't always need to be as greedy as an offlane Phoenix is.  He just needs to be active on the map. 
Treant can get away with being greedy in that case. Also, ppd is the one who plays treant on EG (the one team I'm expecting it from). And he doesn't play greedily at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 08:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 07:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said he's THE shit. Not just shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who wants a treant from EG at the least since Phoenix support is the shit right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 07:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they'll lose. They're up against players who actually have an impact on the game unlike bulba and aui.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are getting better...at getting away from Dota. Live your life man, play casually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 07:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can almost taste the salt between fear and artour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 08:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From all the potms I've played with or against, I'm pretty sure at this point that arrows are for farming creeps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 07:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Nintendo employee has probably read this and now he/she will take all the credit for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 07:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that's what it actually was, a slideshow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
