<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 14:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's fairly straightforward. I believe I started aristocratic, and then took quality third. Something like that. And yeah, I westernized while I was allied to France. You probably don't need to westernize if you just want to go for Winged Hussars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 03:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case someone wanted to see how it all (basically) ended. 

A couple more images:
Opinion of Europe: http://imgur.com/6TH7LI2
NA: http://imgur.com/a/SRqlR
Achievements: http://imgur.com/a/yrKe9

I got the three Polish based achievements in this run. Nothing that special, but I was pretty proud of finally tempering my impatience in incorporating all the countries around Poland without imploding. I give this playthrough a B+, with an extra bonus of Swedish USA and the most passive rival giant France this world has ever seen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, Hello, I'm the guy who sold his soul to Baguette and became the One Polish Federal Republic of Winged Hussars that can into space to rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 03:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice. I didn't know if Wikipedia would be enough without having finished the book yet. I think you're right, it should be sufficient. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got Foucault's Pendulum shelved for my own personal endeavor in the future!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running a Book Club Discussion on The Name of the Rose, Need Help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 17:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, I'm going to be heading a discussion for my library's book club on The Name of the Rose, by Umberto Eco. I think my group will like the the underlying murder mystery story, but will certainly be confused by  heavy mention of the feud going on between the pope, the emperor, and the various monastic orders and their branch sects. Hell, even I'm a little lost, finding myself re-reading sections to get a firm grip on the situation. 

I would like to be able to provide a primer of sorts for the group, the month before they begin reading, to prepare them for what's important and try and clarify some of the history before they go in blindly. I'd look online, but as I haven't actually finished the book myself yet, I didn't want to spoil the plot. Basically, I'm asking for those of you who have read the book to provide the most essential bits of this whole historical context, in the frame of not ruining any part of the actual plotline, so that I can give my group a quick lesson on what's important for them to know to give them a fuller understanding the story. For example, I know I'll need to explain the relationship between the Franciscan/Benedictine orders as I'm sensing the significance it will have on the conflicting ideologies of William and the other monks.

As much as I would love to do a comprehensive history lesson, teaching my group about the complexities of 14th century secular vs. religious powers in Europe, it'll simply be too much. They typically only want to read CJ Box stories, so this whole literary historical murder mystery is a bit ambitious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CLG's individual infographic is the same link for G2. What are you trying to say, OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It breaks my heart to always see this happen to the Netherlands. It doesn't stop me from denying support/refusing to ally with them, but it does make me feel bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was allied to Bohemia, Sweden, and France, making GB, Spain, Russia, and the Ottomans rival me. GB only recently formed actually, like 50 years ago due to France messing up their island substantially. Sweden became the Protestant leader during the League War and has forever rivaled me since. France ate up the Bohemian throne and then broke my alliance to team up with Russia. My only friend had been Portugal for a century or so until Spain realized that I wasn't worth rivaling anymore. 

I don't really know how I can fight France at this point, and I probably won't even try. Their rise to power is on me, and I must suffer the consequences. Luckily, they won't rival me and don't seem to be inclined to go to war with me. Maybe we can just coexist (   ) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allied with France and facilitated their dominance over Europe. They got a PU over Austria, now over Bohemia, vassalized Hungary, become HRE, and then broke their alliance with me.

But...I got Constantinople! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes, to remove Kebab you must sell your soul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Austrian.
Slovakia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's possible, but you'll be cutting it close. Hopefully someone who's done the MN run themselves can weigh, because I'm not a particularly advanced player either. 

What you've got going for you is a huge army. England seems to be pretty weakened, so taking London won't be difficult. If you can take all of Italy by 1600 and then spend the next 200 years or so grabbing all that coast line, it seems possible. 

What seems worrisome is that your aggressive expansion has pissed off a lot of people. The trick is going to be how well you can manipulate alliances, manage AE, and deter any kind of a meaningful coalitions from forming.

In regard to Kebab, they'll lose their potency later in the game. If you can ally PLC or Russia or even a strong Sweden/Scandanavia, you should be able to take what you need from them. I would think Kebab will be your final boss for the game. 

Make sure you're grabbing those other weird provinces like Zeeland and Vienna and whatever else the Roman Empire requires. If you go for it, share some pictures of the process! Good luck, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My strategy involved allying France immediately, and using their provinces as collateral whenever things went wrong. Oh. Spain and Burgundy and Austria feel I'm aggressively expanding a bit too much? Here, take Gascoigne. Or maybe Berry. Champagne? Sure. I'll just be keeping London, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a strange temporary bug. Came back to it later and all was well again. As if to reward me for my patience, EU4 granted me a nice, juicy Austrian PU. 

Thanks for the attempts to solve this issue everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I would receive a stab hit if I declared. Tried restarting and same issue. I shouldn't have a truce since they formed from Serbia and Bosnia releasing them (I had no part in it). Even still, my claim should still be visible in the declare screen, as I should just get a penalty for breaking the truce.

First Lithuania breaks my PU, then a coalition fires and forces me into greater debt and the loss of lands, and now this. It's starting to look as if Poland cannot into space after all...


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't I have a Casus Belli on Nitra? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/q1eWX

The first picture shows that I have no actual claims as Poland to start the war, but the second shows that there is a Polish claim to the province of Spis, which is part of Nitra. 

Am I just tired and missing something obvious here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 07:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, fuck the elitist Habsburg schnitzel-whores. 

YOUR DYNASTY HAS NO CLAIM TO OUR LANDS. +50% HOSTILE CORE CREATION MOTHERFUCKERS.

But yeah, those succession war tool tips are really confusing at first glance. I think bbqftw is correct in his interpretation. Royal marriage mechanics aren't super transparent. They do need some kind of clarity update one of these days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
