<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump ruined hired a bunch of movement conservatives who think hes a sucker and keep manipulating him to make stupid and embarrassing decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump ruined hired a bunch of movement conservatives who think hes a sucker and keep manipulating him to make stupid and embarrassing decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump ruined everything by hiring a bunch of movement conservatives who think hes a sucker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he will not label China currency manipulator, reversing campaign promise: trump lied again and broke another campaign promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he will not label China currency manipulator, reversing campaign promise: trump lied again and broke another campaign promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he will not label China currency manipulator, reversing campaign promise: trump lied again and broke another campaign promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he will not label China currency manipulator, reversing campaign promise: trump lied again and broke another campaign promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he will not label China currency manipulator, reversing campaign promise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our economy is a hellscape for consumers. The United flier is the latest victim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond United: How oligopolies hurt Americans pocketbooks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our economy is a hellscape for consumers. The United flier is the latest victim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing nothing is better than what gop  does  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, you saying fact before your opinion doesn't make your opinion fact. If you want career services enroll in a 1 hour noncredit  course. It will save you lots of money. 

Your new argument is basically

*I admit the boot camp won't teach you much or has any value but you get career services unrelated to the bootcamp. That is worth thousands and thousands of dollars you pay* 

Kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. This is great. 

First you make shady claims and demand proof of common knowledge. When it is pointed out that is in fact your claim that has no proof you source yourself saying your opinion is proof. When that fails you source promotional material the boot camp itself. When that fails you resort to name calling and cyber stalking. You sure are a butthurt loser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can improve his ratings by pursuing progressive policies. If he abandons all his bad positions and takes up smart ones to be popular I don't see problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the moron who blindly believes marketing material with no proof. You can't be this dumb, nobody is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol your source is the gw boot camp that gw is marketing. Classic. 

You my friend are not smart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His approval rating is plummeting. It is historically low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, you mentioning something is not proof. Did I mention my magic beans earlier? Want to buy them? Per your logic my mention of them is proof they work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol the claim was boot camps in the advice was good advice. I said that isn't proven. You took offense. 

If you aren't willing to back it up we can agree to agree there is no peoven benefit to bootcamps.

If you disagree you can provide proof. If not you can quit showing you admit you can't show that bootcamps provide value. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the region. 

It is highly dysfunctional and has been for some time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, you are the one who can't show any real benefit to these bootcamps. You are proving my point. You know what paying lots of money for something that doesn't have any proven benefit is called?

You want to buy magic beans from me? Only $15k. They will get you a job and cure cancer. Sure they aren't proven to work but it assumed they work until you prove they dont. 

/discussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because reaganism  became religion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The irony is that the president and the gop  are threatening a shutdown when they are in control. This is so stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What don't you get?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know. That is why they voted for trump. Now they realize trump duped them too but that is not relevant to our discussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a historic first the president is going to purposely shutdown the government: Trump threatens a government shutdown if he doesn't get his way with Congress that his own party controls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gw wasn't duped. They are the one doing the duping. 

And the burden of proof is on you. You have to show boot camp are beneficial in most cases and not a ripoff i don't have to disprove something that has no proof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a historic first the president is going to purposely shutdown the government: Trump threatens a government shutdown if he doesn't get his way with Congress that his own party controls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a historic first the president is going to purposely shutdown the government: Trump threatens a government shutdown if he doesn't get his way with Congress that his own party controls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House loses it over sanctuary cities: Team Trump threatens a government shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duped by the gop. That is why they voted in trump. Trump duped them too but that wasn't the point I'm making now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the one with some bias here. You are right hundreds of people are placed in entry level jobs out of the thousands and thousands who attend bootcamps. In most cases they could have gotten the jobs without the boot camp and they gave lots of money to these scams when they could have gotten the same result for free. 

Your arguments are all weak and you are the one with bias. I have nothing against bootcamps. I'm just telling the truth that you can get the same result 99% of the time without forking over money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure they are, they want to make easy money. 

Sure the people taking these boot camps are paying lots of money for a very small leg up  but hey whatever. 

The fact remains employers don't care about boot camp. It is not a replacement for an actual degree, work experience, or an actual portfolio made on your own. If you are willing to do none of these things above than a boot camp is slightly better than nothing and may get someone an entry level job if they network really hard and are lucky. 

If I ran a school and wanted easy money I'd make one too. You are looking at this wrong. Boot camp is great if you are the one collecting the money. They aren't great if you are the one paying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The citation is their support for trump. There is a reason they hate *cuckservatives* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boot camps aren't real schools. They are a way to make lots of money of stuff that is free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be deported to russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A free online guide literally teaches it too for free. The only way to really learn is actually work in not go to a class, but you can *learn* about it for free. Your marketing for them is dishonest. From a career perspective employers are not impressed by these expensive boot camp certificates. 

What you want is a degree from a real school, actual work experience or a portfolio. Not some for profit certificate from a 6 week course. 

If you can't be bothered to learn on your own and build a portfolio than sure a boot camp will give you a small leg up for a very high price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't hyberbole. It is the truth. The altright  is basically honest gop  base. The gop heartland used to be the biggest supports of new deal type programs and welfare. They turned against it during civil rights when black people started to get it too. The gop exploited resentment of funds going to support non-whites to gut programs that poor white people mostly used. The language against welfare used by say Reagan *welfare queena, young bucks eating tbones  and driving cadillacs* was meant to tie government to supporting black people. The gop said these white people were winners and didn't need these programs but if they did need them they deserved it because they weren't lazy dark skinned people but honest god fearing Americans. They bought it up to spite black people, and other people they didn't like. 

The end result was the rich gutted them. In the same way the rich gutted black people in inner cities in the late 60s through the 80s the rich gutted lower and middle class white people in rural areas, and to a lesser extent suburbs.  The little wealth these people had trickled up to the elite. 

The altright realizes they have been duped. Make no mistake they never wanted to gut welfare for themselves just to nonwhites. They weren't honest about this in the past because it made them sound bad but that was the result of gop policy. However gop policy affected them too equally and now they are pissed. So now they are honest and want a redo. They want the welfare state of old but just for them, no non-christian and non-whites, and only Christian whites who hold their view should get benefits. That is always what they wanted they are just honest about it. 

Look at spencer. He supports say universal healthcare. Just in his white identity ethnonationalism way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> School doesn't teach you about working in agile either, you need to work in one. They just give you text on it, you can get that free online too. 

You can make a creative portfolio on your own. These programs basically charge a lot for what is essentially free online. For the price some charge you can get a masters or a cc degree. All they do is give you a program and a little guidance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they need to learn a lesson. If you add 1 they will start a war over it. They fight dirty and it is time we stop accepting it. I'd add a justice every few days. Let it swell, it isn't good if a few people have this much control. 50 ne justices is a good start but I'd want more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically the altright  is for universal healthcare, pensions, etc. Just for white people. The Republican base was never against welfare, just darker skinned people getting it. 

The rich realized this and used the gop to cut benefits for all which poor racist whites supported until the cuts destroyed them too leaving them as badly off as the dark skinned people they hate. 

Now they are just being honest and saying they want welfare but just for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Howard Dean was warning people about the opioid crisis a decade ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't be more fucked  up than American gov </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Code academy is a good start but not enough. 

Learn the basics and build something. Stackoverflow and Google is all you need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Trumps pick for drug czar: A punisher of addicts and poor people in developing countries: trump plans to use drugs to launch a class war against the poor including his base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Trumps pick for drug czar: A punisher of addicts and poor people in developing countries: trump plans to use drugs to launch a class war against the poor including his base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Trumps pick for drug czar: A punisher of addicts and poor people in developing countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump voters realize the hard way that the president cant follow through: he broke every promise to them and did the opposite of what he said he would do and his base his turning against him rapidly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump voters realize the hard way that the president cant follow through: he broke every promise to them and did the opposite of what he said he would do and his base his turning against him rapidly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump voters realize the hard way that the president cant follow through: he broke every promise to them and did the opposite of what he said he would do and his base his turning against him rapidly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is coming for your Social Security: How the GOP plans a bait-and-switch to cut taxes  and pensions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is coming for your Social Security: How the GOP plans a bait-and-switch to cut taxes  and pensions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is coming for your Social Security: How the GOP plans a bait-and-switch to cut taxes  and pensions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That they want to make coal cost competitive. 

When it is only source of power it is competitive with regulation.  It just lowers the profits. Without regulation it still can't compete. 

You were mostly right but the coal of king coal is not to make coal cost competitive as it doesn't and can't compete. Rather before it dies they want to maximize their revenue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got here because coal was viable in the past. There was a time when it was a good option. Now it isnt. Even with no regulation coal is not viable now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes we can. His trickle down economics and policies carried over for decades. There is a reason he is brought up so much. When reagan brought up his policies economist said in a few decades it would destroy the middle class and the middle class did not listen. Here we are. 

Reagan may have died but we have not escaped reaganism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have nothing to gain either. You sound like an Appalachian bud fanboy and that is fine but the truth is the stuff they grow in that area is average at best so I dont understand. 

The reason we are here is you claimed Appalachia has some of the best soil for growing bud. That is untrue, the soil is actually pretty bad, that is fact. But ill make you a deal find me a scientific source that shows the soil is actually pretty good and ill accept it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://addictinginfo.org/2015/12/21/republican-poverty-93-of-the-poorest-100-counties-in-america-are-in-red-states/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not seeing they make shit product. I am saying the climate and soil are not optimal for growing outdoors. It is so-so at best. There is nothing special about what is going on in Appalachia. It certainly cant compete with what is grown outdoors at west, the quality and the price is much lower. 

If it were fully legalized Appalachia would be at a disadvantage for outdoor growing. Indoor is different, I guess you could turn coal mines into giant indoor farms if you could heat them. 

but the soil is not great. I am from Appalachia too. The weed is shit there compared to the stuff out West. I love Appalachia but you are wrong. 

Cannabis is prevalent in many states and is the number one cash crop in many states.

https://www.drugscience.org/Archive/bcr2/cashcrops.html

Appalachian bud is not renowned, it wasnt thought of highly even in Appalachia. You can grow good stuff sure, but it isnt on the map. You are the first and only person I have heard making this claim. it sounds more like undeserved regional pride to me. Growers out west would laugh at your claims, and even these *mountain boys* dont make the claims you do.  

Drugs are very prevalent in Appalachia and have been ingrained in the culture for some time. They are often overpriced and low quality. I guess it is good because if these people had the same quality and lower price you could get in east/west urban corridors they would be dying in much greater numbers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I was in the military and good luck getting them to do anything. Every tuition payment was hours of battles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good luck finding a coal mining job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why bring kids into this world? 

I would like to have one, but I cant justify bringing life into this fucked up situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is all Reagan's fault. 

People worship him but this is his trickle down. The wealth trickles up and the shit trickles down. We reaped what we sowed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But hey we got nice cul-de-sacs and strip malls. Totally worth it. Who doesnt love Applebees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is depressing. We are a failure as a country. We had it all and threw it away to benefit a few rich people. Maybe we can turn things around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like she is toxic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, get a job? Just get a job? Why dont I strap on my job helmet and squeeze down into a job cannon and fire off into job land, where jobs grow on jobbies?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is conservatives for you. They enjoy the misfortune of others, although increasingly the misfortune is on them. 

We are a failure as a society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the suffering our generation breaks my heart man. I see my fellow millennial in debt slavery to undeserving boomers who had benefits handed to them on a golden spoon while denying us what they had. 

Dont give up man. Resist.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they are right in that white middle class and working class support of the GOP has resulted in poor outcomes. Rural areas are the new inner city, with mass unemployment, broken families, and addiction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most conservatives are poor and on government assistance. They feel their own welfare use is justified but other people are not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is what happens when they hit 25 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just learn on your own. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people spent that much and such stupid things in the late 80s? 

I thought this was a new thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sure they can grow it but I doubt it is best soil. 

If you look at optimal climates Appalachia doesnt meet the requirements

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cannabis_cultivation

It isnt awful, but it isnt that great. You want somewhere that is warm all year, but not too hot. Where this the right amount of water but not much. You wants nutrients in the soil, and Appalachia has bad soil, that is why it isnt a big farm area. 

Yes, you can grow it there and even get good results, but there is much better areas for growing. It is prevalent in Appalachia due to poverty and a drug culture, not because it has good soil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Appalachia not anymore. Coal miners travel all over the place now. No single community can rely on coal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ancestors were feudal serfs. I should aspire to continue that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. 

Jewish people, Chinese people, East Asians, and lots of immigrants all did this and still do this. They mostly started off with shit jobs and worked hard and really pushed their kids to succeed in school.

The book tiger mom identifies cultures that do this. They realize in life you have to work hard and push yourself. 

Lots of white people did this too, all those people in silicon valley or in NYC working finance at some point their relatives worked in labor. They did better and now the working class who didnt push themselves and was content with an easy situation hate them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. 

The owners know coal isnt competitive. Some people dont have an alternative yet as all they is coal plants. They know eventually it will be replaced. Environmental regulations lower their profits, which are still high. They want more profit. The coal miners will see very little benefit to decreased regulation maybe a small decrease in the decrease of coal jobs and a small increase in pay and benefits, but the owners of the capital will see tens of millions if not billions in profits before their company goes under.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even without those barriers coal is dead. There are cheaper alternatives that pollute less. 

The only reason they have a job is legacy coal plants. Some areas havent built better newer power plants yet, and still need coal. The lack of demand for coal is not due to environmental regulation. The companies hate it because it makes them less profit and they want to squeeze all they can out of coal before it is fazed out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, it no longer has a sense of community. Maybe in the past. Now it is all heroin and dysfunction. Rural areas are collapsing the same way inner city blacka reas did in the 60s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it isnt that. They cant adapt to outside culture. Appalachia is mostly small bubbles and they are out of touch with the rest of the country and the world. They are unsophisticated and often ignorant and dont fit in. They feel like they are looked down upon, and they largely are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is sad when you look back at Dubya and think he was pretty awesome for a Republican. I hated him at the time, but he is better than 90% of the GOP today, it isnt because he was good but because they have gotten so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true they love welfare. And they love infrastructure investments for the small rural roads they drive on. They dont love other people getting these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote GOP if you believe that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, the soil is pretty shit for growing in general. Lots of clay and highly acidic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. WV has very few coal jobs left. It also has natural gas, and there is fracking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was *good enough*. They got so little but they could afford a small house, truck, and tv. Meanwhile the corporation made billions of them. 

They asked for nothing, willingly got exploited. and got nothing, and now are angry. There was a time when coalminers fought against the companies, and won. After winning once they gave up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people in kentucky arent coal miners. They arent even voting to save jobs or get jobs, but based off the image they have of themselves. They see themselves as hard working coal miners even if few of them are, and these few will all soon lose their jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EC system is rigged. It is all rotten. Trump will have one positive benefit he will destroy this rotten system with his failures and maybe it will get better when a revolution comes, but probably not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Millenials do vote, but we live mainly in urban areas and blue states. GOP wins by capturing rural voters whose vote counts more due to EC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why stop at 11? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why bother? They fuck over their voters year after year and somehow still thrive. Going full retard has worked for them for decades. Sure it is destroying America, but since when did they care about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, im a millenial and I live in DC, I can vote for a non-voting senator and house rep with no power. Explain to me why I should vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]North Koreans of Reddit, how did they teach you about the existence of South Korea in School when you were young? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this was always the case. It is definetly something I noticed in last 2 or 3 years. 

Seems like when it got popular it started to attract douchey types. I don't think it's the haircut itself but rather people devoid of personality who just do what is popular and trendy at the moment. If mullets became cool they would sport them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't my state. It is just a very high percentage of people with that haircut that I have met, at least 75% and probably much higher, prove themselves to be douches very quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tend to cluster around certain haircuts at different times. That haircut is a generic douche stamp now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have just said *we are at peace with eurasia* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universal healthcare supporters see their chance: 'Theres never been more support' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tops Obama, Bush and Clinton in Golfing: After years of criticizing former President Barack Obama for playing golf and going on private getaways, President Trump has already done more of both in his first 81 days than Mr. Obama, as well as former Presidents George W. Bush and Bill Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tops Obama, Bush and Clinton in Golfing: After years of criticizing former President Barack Obama for playing golf and going on private getaways, President Trump has already done more of both in his first 81 days than Mr. Obama, as well as former Presidents George W. Bush and Bill Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tops Obama, Bush and Clinton in Golfing: After years of criticizing former President Barack Obama for playing golf and going on private getaways, President Trump has already done more of both in his first 81 days than Mr. Obama, as well as former Presidents George W. Bush and Bill Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tops Obama, Bush and Clinton in Golfing: After years of criticizing former President Barack Obama for playing golf and going on private getaways, President Trump has already done more of both in his first 81 days than Mr. Obama, as well as former Presidents George W. Bush and Bill Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tops Obama, Bush and Clinton in Golfing and Private Getaways So Far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Monarchy: The Trumps long-running campaign to promote nepotism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Monarchy: The Trumps long-running campaign to promote nepotism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Monarchy: The Trumps long-running campaign to promote nepotism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Monarchy: The Trumps long-running campaign to promote nepotism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A beautiful thing: The Trumps long-running campaign to promote nepotism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am. You are using race to try and deny reality. *he is black so therefore he is not a trumpet*. You ignore statistics based off race. Killing people because you are angry is trump supporter 101.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because briebart  is mostly not altright. A lot of middle age and older white people who are angry and bitter like briebart because it is antiimmigrant  and somewhat antigop. They are who trump is stealing. The nazis are toxic and trump knows that but he wants to steal poor and middle class whites. 

Fbi is investigating briebart for Russian ties. It will be shut down or Bannon will take fall for Russia gate and be replaced by a trumpet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are loyal to trump not Bannon
 Mindlessly so. Trump betrays everyone. Before he was in politics he would betray his investors, lendors, and employees. Politically He first betrayed America, then he betrayed russia who funded him and supported him. Now he is betraying the alright. He just uses people for his own ends and has never paid for it. 

Trump will steal the altright  from Bannon just like he stole the gop base  from ryan. Next he will probably try to use liberals, democrats, and progressives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> global elites cucked trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> global elites cucked trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSI justice: Jeff Sessions joins the war on science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because they are black they can't support trump? On top of stupid you are racist. Nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global Elites Cucked Trump: How Trump turned into a cuckservative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> global elites cucked trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global elites strike back: global elites cucked trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global elites strike back: Have Jared and Ivanka defeated Bannon  and turned Trump into a cuckservative? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the undercut has been the generic douchey bro haircut for awhile now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cant develop a coherent domestic policy, or even give a coherent speech, so I think you are asking for too much. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not worried about impossible events. If and when is a bridge we will cross when we get there similar to if and when aliens attack us. The real question is what will you do when even breibart admits I am right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make whatever excuse you want  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's statistics not statistic. A statistic is a single statistic. Statistics is the plural of statistic and is the name for a type of applied math that deals in probability. Not that you understand this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is on trump's failures and events under trump. 

Trump clearly doesn't care about the people in Syria.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give trump credit for what? A little fireworks display? Obama is irrelevant to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the one who doesn't get it snowflake. The facts are what they are. You can get triggered and butch about them but it won't change them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be worse, I could be an altright  trumpet who shoots up schools or a snowflake like you who gets triggered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistics are not assumptions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a bummer to you how stupid you are snowflake but the rest of us don't care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was never any doubt you were altright. Your inability to accept reality while being triggered by it gave you away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowflake you can grasp all the alternate facts you want. Source is reality. Accept it or fuck  off. Just don't see kids because reality doesn't agree with you like the alright trumpet who did this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how triggering snowflakes like you with facts waste her time. If you want we can schedule a 3 way call with your mom to discuss this issue you have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know they are an altright trumpet but we don't know their name or how fat they are, as trump supporters are fat. And that is your cause of butthurt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that is why people are angry at trump and people in the altright. I just don't see why you are so angry right now and not at trump and the altright </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source is submission and statistics . If you can't accept that snowflake you can fuck  off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes yes every failure of trump or everything bad that happens because of trump is Obama's fault or Clinton's fault. We get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You not accepting reality is your own personal problem snowflake. 

I assure you nobody scores points when alright trumpets murder kids  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you triggered snowflake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reality is what it is not some form of capitalization. 

I gain nothing when alright trumpets murder a bunch of kids. We all lose, especially you since you find the actions of alright trumpets so disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So trump's hypocrisy is Obama's fault. Let's add this to the long list of failures of trump that are all to be blamed on obama.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ones who lack decency are the altright nazi snowflakes who shoot at kids and vote for trump. I realize pointing this out violates your safe space but reality is what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Altright trump supporter shoots up elementary school to MAGA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sessions orders Justice Dept. to end forensic science commission, suspend review policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump wants to get his war on with Syria, have him send his own kids first </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump wants to get his war on with Syria, have him send his own kids first </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the nuclear apocalypse happens, point to Donald Trump putting nukes in South Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the nuclear apocalypse happens, point to Donald Trump putting nukes in South Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the nuclear apocalypse happens, point to Donald Trump putting nukes in South Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump was OK with assad using chemical weapons in the past,  killing 200k of his own people, displacing millions, and he banned these same kids he pretends to care about from coming to the us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democracy Has Stood Up to Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democracy Has Stood Up to Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump actions risk 'millions dying on Korean Peninsula' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump actions risk 'millions dying on Korean Peninsula' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump actions risk 'millions dying on Korean Peninsula' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump actions risk 'millions dying on Korean Peninsula' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps flagrant hypocrisy: Suddenly the mean-spirited clown-king cares about Syrian children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps flagrant hypocrisy: Suddenly the mean-spirited clown-king cares about Syrian children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps flagrant hypocrisy: Suddenly the mean-spirited clown-king cares about Syrian children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps flagrant hypocrisy: Suddenly the mean-spirited clown-king cares about Syrian children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-wing fascism vs. one-percent oligarchy: In the war between Bannon and Kushner, Trump agrees with both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-wing fascism vs. one-percent oligarchy: In the war between Bannon and Kushner, Trump agrees with both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-wing fascism vs. one-percent oligarchy: In the war between Bannon and Kushner, Trump agrees with both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-wing fascism vs. one-percent oligarchy: In the war between Bannon and Kushner, Trump agrees with both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-wing nationalism vs. one-percent oligarchy: In the war between Bannon and Kushner, Trump agrees with both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballad of a sad little man: Pity Bill OReilly, for he will never experience great sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> opposite actually. It just shows congress, which i cant vote on, can run DC and overturn any law they want and make any local official powerless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could give examples for days, ill just settle for the first thing I can find on google

https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/dc-politics/is-dcs-local-government-in-the-fight-of-its-life/2017/02/04/61fe338c-e7dd-11e6-bf6f-301b6b443624_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Syria is already weakened. It will take decades to get back to where it was just in 2011. 

Also NATO could cut off Russia from Medi with Turkey. 

US policy in Syria makes no sense and constantly changes. It is clear nobody has a clue what they want. They just react to events and have no real plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont see why Trump is suddenly pretending to care. He was ok with Assad killing 200k civilians and supported the guy, and suddenly he kills 200 with Sarin and he cares? Yeah Sarin is horrible and I dont support Assad using it but isnt worse than all the past stuff he did. I certainly dont have faith in Trump to lead during a crisis like this. 

It is obviously a distract to cast doubt on Russiagate and all the money and support Putin gave him. Maybe Putin is in on this maybe it is a betrayal. Either way Russia will regret supporting Trump as he is unpredictable, cant be controlled or reasoned with, and is vindictive.

So either Putin is going to have diffuse the mess he made or we are going to have wwiii because Trump wont diffuse this, and he wont be restrained.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually yes the US did lose standing when Obama made a red line and then didnt honor it, and later late Russia ride in. 

Now Putin lost a little, but I doubt Trump is serious about doing anything else, although he is unpredictable, so I doubt Putin will lose much more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dignity is all Russia lost. Really these strikes were pointless but Russia is pissed because it makes Putin look weak and impotent. 

Im guessing though Russia is secretly ok with them since they need to cast doubt on their ties to trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> id upvote a picture of hitler at disney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for foreigners disney was a big deal, still is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now you see why I dont bother. In many ways it is good, it just dispels the illusion of how our system works and allows me to see it for what it is. My vote is symbolic but pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most people would prefer living in US than NK and would prefer getting stung by a bee than a harpoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in both cases one is preferable to the other even though they all suck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same as voting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they is something called extent. If a bee strings you and a harpoon is shot through your face in both cases an object pierced you. The extent is different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they get overridden by congress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like Sith lord and apprentice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no tools. I threw nothing away but the illusion of choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no local races where I live, and ballot initiatives are overridden by congress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They dont need to surpress the vote in most places, only in a few swing areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at my username. I dont have voting senator or congressmen... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. We might be better than NK but being than NK is not a high standard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The outcome will be a certain way. That is point of EC, we dont have a real democracy. 90% less people could have voted where I lived now and the outcome would have been the same. My vote has never gone to the candidate I voted for and has always gone to the candidate I am against due to EC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it wont be. Our democracy is fake . 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> problem is EC system. I did not vote, but my vote would not have mattered since where I am from heavily went against Trump. In fact in no election ever has my voted ever really made a difference, ive lived in several different states both blue and red and each time the state swings a certain way regardless of vote. EC is terrible system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump has no strategy, no beliefs, and no principles: Hes a simple, vulgar person who makes decisions for vulgar reasons. There is no strategy There is no grand plan There is no moral, ethical, or philosophical calculation Theres only Trump and how he feels from one moment to the next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump has no strategy, no beliefs, and no principles: Hes a simple, vulgar person who makes decisions for vulgar reasons. There is no strategy There is no grand plan There is no moral, ethical, or philosophical calculation Theres only Trump and how he feels from one moment to the next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump has no strategy, no beliefs, and no principles: Hes a simple, vulgar person who makes decisions for vulgar reasons. There is no strategy There is no grand plan There is no moral, ethical, or philosophical calculation Theres only Trump and how he feels from one moment to the next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump has no strategy, no beliefs, and no principles: Hes a simple, vulgar person who makes decisions for vulgar reasons. There is no strategy There is no grand plan There is no moral, ethical, or philosophical calculation Theres only Trump and how he feels from one moment to the next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump has no strategy, no beliefs, and no principles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump administration is ill-prepared for a global pandemic, experts warn: High-level health vacancies and budget cuts could leave the United States extra susceptible to the threat of infectious disease which will likely lead to the deaths of Millions of Americans all from Trump's incompetence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
