<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject513</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tank glitch in Conquest is ridiculous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played far too many games of conquest at this point that have been completely ruined by this glitch. One team will have 4 tanks and the other will have 1 or none. And before one of you clever guys tells me "they probably stole your teams tanks", they are all tanker classes in the scoreboard so no they didn't, they spawned into tanks. 

Dice really needs to fix this because there isn't a damn thing you can do when the other team has 4 tanks that instantly spawn back upon destruction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its alright man remember that sports don't effect your life in any real way. There is always next year and the falcons are looking like a good team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always get an "NFC champion" tattoo instead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still think so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the heartbreak of an entire city fuels me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHAHA OH THE UNFATHOMABLE PAIN ATLANTA FANS MUST BE FEELING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finish this Pats. Finish this and deny Atlanta yet another championship  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atlanta fans, how angry will you be when Tom Brady throws for 500 yards and completes this comeback?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the 28-3 memes will be glorious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this New England. This is the super bowl I wanted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots might do it but Atlanta has Jones and Matty Ice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could become the best superbowl of all time. I can't believe it but I'm totally rooting for the Patriots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let OT happen. This game deserves it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT

This is fucking crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT THAT FUCKING CATCH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Falcons could have the most epic choke in superbowl history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots gonna patriot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STRANGER THINGS HYPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that my one jackass falcons fan friend is ruining my enjoyment of the Patriot blowout  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be the game we all look back on when we ask "what happened to the Patriots?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I thought Thermo was ok. I have Product Safety to work on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate super bowl blowouts TBH. I always want to watch a classic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I may as well go do my homework at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NE is done after that drive TBH. Don't think they can fix this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can think about are those fake youtube chevy commercials when I see this.

"Its the poop emoji because its shit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots receivers only play like this in the super bowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even notice until you pointed it out, thats a heads up play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh goodie is this the part where Atlanta plays conservative AF and lets New England score 21 unanswered points?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have given some viewers a heart attack haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No political statements for all those attacking Gaga before the show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great halftime show. Imagine if she drops that ball haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like I'm being transferred back to highschool with all this old Lady Gaga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4 Gaga gives a great halftime show completely devoid of political statements and old people everywhere don't know what to complain about  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So where's the political statement Gaga? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I just don't feel like dealing with trump shitheads while I watch football </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave that shit at the door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else feels that historic comeback in their loins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who gets the ball next half? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4 Pats somehow still win and the words "21-0" haunt Atlanta forever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy I still don't quite buy New England's death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a feeling this game would be a blow out I was just wrong about the team on the receiving end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alabama and New England go down in the championship in the same season. What a time to be alive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously who the fuck is this team and what have they done with the Patriots?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is rigged by illegal Patriot referees. SAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear lord all these holds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm amazed by how long Atlanta managed to fly under near everyone's radar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't count the Patriots out yet. Those guys find a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mechanical Engineering. South Carolina is ranked higher in Mechanical Engineering than Clemson. Or at least that is whats spread around the department. 

I'll never change my fandom. I've been a Clemson fan since childhood and I'm more than capable of separating the football team from my academic choices. I would have gone to Clemson had I been able to afford it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you've got me; a Clemson fan at South Carolina for engineering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably goes to one school and grew up a fan of the other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as one of them is South Carolina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting someone with a history of hateful rulings and this guy has a couple things I disagree with but I don't think he's doing anything ridiculous like establishing dictator trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dude doesn't seem that bad after some research considering the kind of loony toon I was expecting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see y'alls argument I just don't agree with it. If the SACS is putting you on probation too then that should be more than enough proof for the NCAA about the nature of that class. I wouldn't mind the NCAA waiting for the SACS rulings then bringing the hammer down if that is the precedent to be set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why shouldn't the NCAA have the authority to impose penalties on a school that had fake classes and sullied the name "student athlete"? What is your logic?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well of course all the North Carolina fans are going to think that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bringing State Troopers to a basketball game is pretty ridiculous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you hear that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will take Thomas too and put an end to this minor crowing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you guys beat us I'll just go with the "who cares won the natty" method  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean that would be as crazy as the Citadel beating South Carolina! ^^twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a mod, what was the logic behind the year rule because it seems very silly to deny us information like that in the title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ever consider with that little pea brain that people dont get to choose where they are born and could have a very big problem with their countries policies? Refugees are trying to escape this shit and you're no better than the dicks that turned away Jews in the 30s to their deaths in Germany. 

Go ahead and keep spewing that bile. The history books will remember this as the president elected by bigotry and hate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you're the bigot for showing hatred towards people that want to get out of some terrible situations and assuming they all must believe that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, you're a goddamn bigot you happier with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not racist to ban Muslims and give priority to Christians? You people are disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just assume every top recruit in the country must want to play for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could but they'd be screwed if they ever lost power again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That woman is a liar and she deserves it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That L slapped sense into the team and turned them into monsters all the way to the natty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people want to pretend like Creationism belongs on equal ground in education with Science then they can enjoy failing out of any reputable college after they leave their fake charter school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're an atheist then I'd hope you would see the problem with injecting religion into our education system.

So you're a "my tax dollars and guns" type conservative. Congratulations, that type is slightly more bearable than the "backwards religious" conservatives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, now all the conservative kids will go to religious schools that teach them creationism instead of real facts. A whole generation of conservatives will be even less educated than usual if this woman has her way.


Also can't help but notice you paid no mind to the president lying about some truly irrelevant shit. We can't oppose the great leader Trump after all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it not bother you to have a president that lies about things as small as crowd size on his first day in office? A president who clearly has no idea what he is doing putting people like DeVos in charge of education?

This man is taking our country down a dark path but I'm sure youll be happy as long as you get to keep your precious tax dollars and guns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so we should only follow traditions when they benefit us, ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah at the dickhead who wouldn't release his tax returns like every other modern president. Not at all Republicans unless they all also want to be shady dickheads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They patched that one I believe. I used it before I'll admit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think we will see 30 million people protest something unless things are truly going to hell. Thats 9% of the US population. the 1% of the country that protested  is about as impressive as protests get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats an unfair comparison given something like 30 million Women voted. If 30 million people protested it would cause some massive problems infrastructure wise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey only one of those things is true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Todd is too clever for the QB sneak  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow what shit playcalling. Disgusting. Todd is too fucking fancy to use our massive QB on a sneak at the 6 inch line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't teams qb sneak in that situation. Like wtf are you doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commercials are fucking ludicrous tonight. I frequently wonder if "official timeouts" are occasionally taken by the league to fit a couple more commercials in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may as well blitz every 3rd down since Brady is guaranteed a 10+ yard pass if we don't sack him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pats are the worst man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't we defend a fucking third down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fade me motherfuckers you can't bring me down, my college team won the natty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I hate ~~Bama~~ New England  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Packers are the Ohio State of the final four playoff teams  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cook doesn't even give a fuck with those drops. It's completely over  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP cheesemen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it that makes some offenses 3x better on 3rd down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green bay is so terrible on 3rd down its ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Packers have to get points or its almost a guaranteed L with how Atlanta's offense looks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greenbay needs to take that secondary out behind the woodshed at half at put em down for their own good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god that secondary is a steaming pile of garbage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that had been called a safety it would be the cheapest most tick tacky call in the playoffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like the Packers won't make the Falcons punt all game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way in shit hell they go back and call that a safety  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could just feel the last bit of air leave the packers sails on that turnover  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not a safety chill out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when is the part where Aaron Rodgers crushes the hope he has allowed to build in the enemy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Initial impressions: I may have been too high on GB and too low on ATL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame one of my friends is an insufferable prick about the falcons or I'd enjoy watching this offense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No chance we could beat bama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9 out of 10 times is pretty shit odds for this sort of thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the laziest excuses I've seen getting passed around. If it mattered a lot to people they would take off work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can be reviewed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If South Carolina could make a 3 pointer this might be a real close game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any video review in basketball?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
