<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 15:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at the bottom :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Independence Day Resurgence Box Office Prediction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 15:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Worldwide] June Summer Movies Box Office Predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 13:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 05:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You people forget how big wow is in china.

https://media.giphy.com/media/cfL8a1rB1przO/giphy.gif lol in all honesty, though, I think X-Men and Alice Through the Looking Glass will still have legs in China.  However, I think you're right to an extent - WoW is huge in china and the movie will fare well over there and in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, great job!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk if this is where I should post this, but please feel free to let me know if this is the wrong place.  Also, if you can please let me know where I can post it, that would be awesome.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My warcraft movie box office prediction - it's the second one down - feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My box office prediction for Finding Dory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for letting me know!  I'll stop with the posts :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 01:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry i just don't know where to promote - this is my original music though and I would like to hear feedback as I am a musician.  Do you have any suggestions as to where I can post my music for promotion?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry that's my fault - I just updated it and fixed that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to let me know what you think! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> June Summer Movies Box Office Predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> June Summer Movies Box Office Predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Does the third act (when the Batman v Superman fight begins) take place in Gotham or Metropolis?

My version?  Gotham.  The actual film - probably still Gotham, but idk now that I think about it.

 Superman knows next to nothing about Batman

In Man of Steel, he's 33 so in BvS he's 35.  He was 15 when Batman stopped appearing and he grew up on a farm in Smallville, Kansas.  Idk if he should have heard of Batman.

 In your write-up, it sounds like Gotham (with the Bat signal) and Metropolis (with the Daily Planet and Luthor estate) are both the same city.

The fight between Bruce and Clark is in Gotham, but the Bruce/Lex fight is outside of Metropolis (in a rural area - Lex's estate).

Hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 12:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to give credit to the owner of the pictures - otherwise things could get a bit messy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Movies/TV] I rewrote Batman v Superman - Feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 05:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that Snyder did a different interpretation: however that character for that particular movie felt off - Lex was a crazy person for no apparent reason at all.  I couldn't even understand what Eisenberg was saying half the time because he said it too fast and quiet.

People hate Snyder's interpretation because of the same way you hate mine: they think it's "wrong and doesn't fit the character of the comics."  That mentality is limiting and hinders creative character design.

 you probably have only seen the Donner films as reference for superman

Yeah those, Brian Singer's, and Man of Steel - what other live action films for Superman do you want me to see?  Before you ask, yes, I did see a ton of animated Superman films.  I have seen the animated TV shows for both Superman and Batman and I've seen the animated Justice League show.

Bottom line: I think people hate on Snyder because they could be butt-hurt comic fans who think it's cool to be in the loop of comics knowledge and so they like to express it anytime a comic book film comes out that is meant to attract general viewers so they can "correct the people who liked the film."  I'm not saying this is a fact - it's just what I think so don't get all rallied up because to me you seem like one of those people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my interpretation of Lex: it's hypothetical - I don't have to go with a by the numbers Lex Luthor doing by the numbers real estate things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I respect that and everything - it was definitely a movie made for fans of DC comics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but have Bruce become Joe Chill just to really hammer that point home visually without any heavy-handed dialogue.

Ooh I really like that idea actually - nice!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I just finished reading Part 3 and I honestly have no idea what to say!  It's hands down amazing!  Dude, you should like contact Warner Bros or something and show the company this!  I really liked everyone's motives.  This was very much a fix of Batman v Superman because it doesn't really digress from the overall plot, but it fixes specifics and that's awesome - really liked what you did with Lex Luthor and Superman!

One thing though: i just think this version of the movie would have a really long runtime (3 and a half hours - like LOTR runtime), but maybe that's just because your articles were extremely detailed.  Anyway fantastic job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay yeah that's kinda sad that no one falls for it anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, man, I appreciate it!  Thanks so much for the input like it must have taken you forever to write that idk what to say! 

 Sorry, but no. Lex is ruthless   evil.

I can make Lex however I want him to be because it's my hypothetical plot - heck, Chris Terrio did it in the actual film!

 I would've rather Snyder cut-out anything to do with Congress

Point taken actually - I like that more now that I think about it - saves screen time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, thanks so much!  Secondly, the sonic trap sounds like a pretty awesome way to make them matched!  Like how cool would that be in a movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't kill Superman - he just appears dead because he has kryptonite lodged in his chest from Batman's knuckles.  I wrote that he's dead because that's what the audience is supposed to think and that's what makes Batman change his viewpoint.  Superman comes back if you read the whole thing you'd know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate it :)
Yeah, I do think that DC should take a little step back with introducing a ton of characters.  Hopefully Justice League Part 1 won't feel as cluttered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rewrote Batman v Superman - feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   they don't fit in with the arc you're going for.

Point taken.  I appreciate the input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, I just finished reading part 1 your version and it's fantastic!  I really like Superman's character and in your version he's more than just a threat who says only 40 lines of dialogue.  He's really fleshed out.  I also like the Luthor character switch so he just doesn't seem evil in public.  I just started reading part 2 and I'll let u know what I think!  So far, like i said before, its actually really good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a bunch!!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 12:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I just think that's a problem with movies today.  Whenever a character dies in a superhero movie, it isn't believable because everyone is all like, "When are they gonna bring him/her back?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 12:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I really appreciate it :)
Yeah it would be kinda hard to see Jesse Eisenberg in a mech suit - "First rule of magic, always be the smartest uy in the room." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 06:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Did you post this up before? It seems familiar.

I posted up segments of this before, but this is the complete and final version

 As I see it, your story also devotes too much space to Lex Luthor who doesn't need as much screen time here. All that needs to be established is that he's Metropolis' Bruce Wayne and he's the bad guy. It doesn't even need to establish his strong hatred of Superman at this point.

I actually agree.  However, I only skip over the Batman versus Superman fight because it worked really well in the movie.  I spent a ton of time talking about Lex because I just thought his character was really done wrong from a filmmaking aspect (not a comic book aspect because a ton of people are derailing me on that) and that it needed a ton of tweaking.  I know he's a bad guy, but I think we need to see that he's a person because I think we're gonna be spending a lot with Lex over the next few movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it in parts so two separate days - overall probably a little over 3 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol the Stuckmann script :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rewrote Batman v Superman - feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fool's errand.  You aren't "fixing" anything,

Agreed.  I'm not fixing anything - I'm just posting to my blog and I thought it would be nice to share it just like you would like to post whatever you want.  It has a nice ring to it: Plot Fix so I'll keep it.

 purely hypothetical

Wow... wow... wooooooooooooooow... what a revelation, Einstein.

 aren't much better than the film as it is.

that's an opinion - I wrote in the bottom that my post is also an opinion - it's neither right nor wrong.

 /r/fixingmovies

didn't actually know about that - Thanks, I appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry I'm trying to start a series based on just that: take bad movies and attempt to fix them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I thought Chris Stuckmann's script was solely about the two Superheroes meeting each other for the first time before the battle.  I only have 2 sentences on that.

That's a holocaust of a rewrite

Mine or Stuckmann's?  (Personally I kind of liked Stuckmann's script and idk why) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  what I thought "no!" at the most reading this- "This has to be Christopher Reeve's Superman."

lol yeah that was sort of a joke (it would have been hilarious if that was Henry Cavill doing a Reeve impression).  What I meant was I think Cavill's Superman can be a little lighthearted.  I appreciate the comment though because a lot of people are telling me that I got Lex wrong.  What do you think about the Batman in this article, though?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rewrote Batman v Superman - feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rewrote Batman v Superman - feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rewrote Batman v Superman - feel free to let me know what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice Full Plot Fix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> part 2's up btw: https://blugger.wordpress.com/2016/04/25/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-plot-fix-part-2/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok I see what you mean and it makes perfect sense.  Yeah I guess I messed up on that one (part 2's out btw so idk if it changes anything: https://blugger.wordpress.com/2016/04/25/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-plot-fix-part-2/).
What I don't understand is how the actual BvS version showed a power hungry Lex - he just seemed like a lunatic for the whole film and I didn't get what he was trying to do - if you could clarify what his motives in the movie were, that would be awesome because I was trying to figure that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to let me know what you think! Also, if you haven't read part 1, here you go: https://blugger.wordpress.com/2016/04/20/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-plot-fix-part-1/ Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman v Superman Plot Fix Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down Poe Dameron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point taken.  I'm trying to do this with more movies that didn't live up to the hype and I'll try to get better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to let me know what you think! Also, if you haven't read part 1, here you go: https://blugger.wordpress.com/2016/04/20/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-plot-fix-part-1/
Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman v Superman Plot Fix Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to let me know what you think! Also, if you haven't read part 1, here you go: https://blugger.wordpress.com/2016/04/20/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-plot-fix-part-1/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice Plot Fix Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to let me know what you think! Also, if you haven't read part 1, here you go: https://blugger.wordpress.com/2016/04/20/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-plot-fix-part-1/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman v Superman Fix Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
