<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8593</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 16:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, thank you so, so much for your kind words! /hugs to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 16:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your compliments! It means so much to me to know that other people enjoy them as much as I enjoy creating them! :)

Custom bunnies start at 24 for a short upright eared bunny and 25 for a lop eared bunny. These are for standard bunnies like the ones in the pictures with printed fabric inside their ears, solid minky bodies and ribbons and bows. All in your own choice of colours. Extra markings and any printed fabrics I have to order for the bunny (say if you would like certain theme that I don't already stock) have a small added cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 15:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your compliments, they mean the world to me!  

Honestly, for me it was all just about perseverance. I had never sewn anything other than a button before (and terribly at that!) so I had absolutely zero knowledge of what I was doing when I first took up the hobby! My first attempts were awful, haha. But I stuck with it because the process of making something from nothing, something physical that I could hold and feel, made me feel great, no matter how bad the plush turned out!

I'm sure of it's possible for me to make something out of nothing by just using pure determination, then other people can do it too! 

I wish I could give you a hug too! And I hope that you eventually find the project that inspires you enough to stick with it, like sewing did with me. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 15:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I hope I can inspire other people who are in a similar position to what I was, and just show that there really is an end to darkness but you really do have to look for it yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I wish you luck on getting better! :) I have three bunnies and they definitely help to keep me motivated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 15:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, hugs to you too! Thank you for your compliments!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 15:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) If you want to contact me through etsy and let me know if you'd like a standing or beanie pony, I can give you a price quote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're very welcome! I only wish I had a magic wand that could teach everyone to sew! I didn't have a sewing machine for the first year, I would stitch everything by hand (usually while sitting in bed all day hah). Then last Christmas my boyfriend bought me a lovely sewing machine as he was sick of seeing me struggling to keep up with the sudden demand for my bunnies. I couldn't hand sew anything fast enough! 

The machine he bought me is a fantastic machine for both beginners and the experienced. He got it from amazon: http://www.amazon.co.uk/Janome-J3-18-Sewing-Machine/dp/B0036UODH2/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8 qid=1405696476 sr=8-3 keywords=janome+sewing+machines

It's super easy to use and isn't too heavy or too loud. I would definitely recommend a Janome machine for a good combination of cheap price and good quality, and wouldn't recommend getting one priced any lower.

I was actually bought an unbranded machine that was half the price of that one (and pink!) for my birthday last year by my grandparents and never touched it. I was a complete novice (had never touched a machine before) but even I could tell that it wasn't sewing straight, couldn't turn corners and was maddeningly LOUD! Hah. 

So yeah, always get the machine that you can just about afford, rather than the cheapest. You'll be so glad that you did when you get it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm glad you like the ponies, the beanie ones are the ones I'm most proud of out of all my plushies. :) And I definitely will not! I've come this far, there is absolutely nothing that is going to push me back down again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your compliments! I sell them at my etsy shop: https://www.etsy.com/shop/thetinyteaparty

They've actually allowed me to quit my horrible retail job that was making my depression worse. While the income isn't entirely stable or even making minimum wage, I'm happier than I've ever been. :)

I would love to see your bunny quilts when they're finished! They sound adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I do. I have a little shop here: https://www.etsy.com/shop/thetinyteaparty

I also take custom orders for bunnies in your own choice of fabrics/colours. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diagnosed with severe depression and anxiety a year and a half ago, I took up sewing cute plushies to help me through. Here's some of the little creations that saved my life! (Was told to x-post from /crafts, 'cos BUNNIES!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thank you! I'm hoping to make a matching terriermon when I have a bit of free time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Do you have pictures of your jewellery? I would love to see them, if you're up for sharing! Deciding to sell on Etsy is a scary step, I was filled with so much doubt in the beginning: Will it sell? Will people even like it? What's the point? etc. But there's really nothing to be afraid of. 

You should definitely give Etsy a go! It costs $0.20 to list an item for a few months (or until it sells). And generally the more items you have in your shop the more you will sell. And hey, what's the worst that can happen? Things don't sell. Nevermind! You haven't lost out on anything. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I'm so glad I was able to make someone else smile!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your lovely compliments! All the words of support here are going to make me cry! You're too nice. :) 

And it really is true! You don't really believe it at the time, and that's often the biggest hurdle, but you start to see progress very slowly over the months and then it gets easier from there on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Thank you! The compliments means so much more when they're coming from someone who's not in my usual target audience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
