<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New brain imaging technology allows tumors to be easily distinguished from normal tissue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insights into The Economist's social strategy for journalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 14:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 17:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's [a link to her research papers and publications](http://www.people.fas.harvard.edu/~banaji/research/publications/publications.html), in case you were looking to dig more into her studies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 13:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to [their research in British Medical Journal](http://www.bmj.com/content/347/bmj.f5001). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter makes protected tweets searchable for private users and their approved followers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 13:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds that eating more whole fruits, particularly blueberries, grapes, and apples, was significantly associated with a lower risk of type 2 diabetes -- but greater consumption of fruit juices was associated with a higher risk of type 2 diabetes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 13:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geochemist argues that seeds of life originated on Mars and were blasted to Earth by meteorites or volcanoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 03:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undocumented migrants in U.S. gaining improved access to higher education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 14:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's her [TEDxAtlanta talk](http://youtu.be/XD6N8bsjOEE). Worth watching, if you're interested in the article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find that the same genetic mutation responsible for red hair also triggers a cancer-promoting pathway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 14:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At the height of the last ice age, Earth was dramatically more covered with ice than scientists previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 18:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 17:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russell House Tavern has great small plates, pizzas, and sandwiches. Can't miss with their dinner menu either.

Crema Cafe gets really busy around lunch, but has some good sandwiches. Try the House Roasted Turkey   Jicama Slaw or Spinach Artichoke Grilled Chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the talk:

Amy Cuddy: Your body language shapes who you are: http://www.ted.com/talks/amy_cuddy_your_body_language_shapes_who_you_are.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly released court documents provide gruesome details of the injuries that alleged Boston Marathon bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev suffered before his capture, including a skull fracture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 17:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bizarre history of White House pets, starring Calvin Coolidge's pygmy hippo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 17:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a study, nearly all participants  including highly trained musicians  were better able to identify the winners of classical music competitions by watching silent video clips than by listening to audio recordings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 14:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard-themed "Three Lies" sneaker draws collectors from around the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 21:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers testing a mammary gland progenitor marker say it may soon be possible to gauge individual risk for breast cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 12:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to research in the journal Cell Stem Cell: http://www.cell.com/cell-stem-cell/abstract/S1934-5909%2813%2900197-5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing catch to end Wiffle Ball tournament at mini Fenway Park replica in Vermont </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 16:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Fenway wiffle ball fundraiser ends with incredible catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 16:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard Law School Library digitizes law student notebooks from 200 years ago, giving readers a glimpse at legal education in the young U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 16:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with long commutes have a 40% higher risk of separating from their spouses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 14:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rarely Seen Maps From San Franciscos Quirkiest Hidden Library </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 15:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It takes takes just 30 minutes for a Facebook post to get 50% of its global reach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 15:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard Business School course uses works of literature instead of case studies to teach leadership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 15:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Direct link to the study](http://www.jci.org/articles/view/69098) in the Journal of Clinical Investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Novel treatment boosted selective immune attack on leukemia cells in post-transplant patients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 14:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rise of Google Glass and other wearables offer those with disabilities a little more independence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 14:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at the Harvard School of Engineering and Applied Sciences (SEAS) have developed a way for photographers to create a 3-D image through a single lens, without moving the camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 14:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why spending money on new experiences yields more happiness than spending it on new products </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 19:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 15:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the Natick Mall (in MA) for the first time this weekend and was surprised to see a Tesla store, right there, inside the mall. There was only room for a couple cars in there, but the place was packed with 20-30 people. Info: http://www.teslamotors.com/natick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter wears Google Glass to Pelosi press conference, she immediately questions him about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 18:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Postal Service eyes alcohol deliveries to raise revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 18:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bioinspired microfluidic circulatory system for windows developed by researchers at Harvard University could save energy and cut cooling costs dramatically </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 17:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why its so hard to stop college cost inflation in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 14:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers develop new type of endoscopy that can produce 3D images of the surface of the colon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 20:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maps of Unrealized City Plans Reveal What Might Have Been: 1945 Boston Subway Expansion (among others) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 14:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stem cell researchers produce a new model of leukemia development, which could influence the effectiveness of bone marrow transplants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 12:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New EPA administrator Gina McCarthy gives her first policy speech at Harvard Law School, discusses climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 14:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rapidly-deployable airborne communications network could transform communications during disasters, say researchers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 17:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economist finds that people are living to older ages and adding healthy years, not debilitated ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 17:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have solved the mystery of why type 2 diabetes sometimes disappears after gastric bypass surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 15:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In-depth analysis examines how articles perform when shared from the Boston Globe Facebook Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 15:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard researchers identify a pair of genes that appear to be responsible for allowing a specific strain of bacteria to break down a widely prescribed cardiac drug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 15:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 03:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think it was possible to hold a cringe for 3:38. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We will have to produce more food in the next 40 years than we have had to for the past 8,000 years: Hacking into plants to make photosynthesis more efficient. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 18:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 15:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 14:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. The reason I included '*appears* to reduce the risk..' in the title too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 13:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA:

Caffeine not only stimulates the central nervous system but may act as a mild antidepressant by boosting production of certain neurotransmitters in the brain, including serotonin, dopamine, and noradrenaline. This could explain the lower risk of depression among coffee drinkers that had been found in past epidemiological studies, the researchers reported.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 12:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to their [study in The World Journal of Biological Psychiatry](http://informahealthcare.com/doi/abs/10.3109/15622975.2013.795243). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drinking several cups of coffee daily appears to reduce the risk of suicide in men and women by about 50%, with caffeines impact on brain chemicals playing key role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 12:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 12:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for featuring /r/highereducation as the subreddit of the day. Really appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers track brain tumors by searching for evidence of mutations in cerebrospinal fluid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 18:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter fakes real users tweets to promote ad platform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 18:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analyzing language in Twitter: Tweets reveal a lot about community well-being </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 22:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research from Harvard scientists explains how gut microbes can inactivate cardiac drugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 21:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Controlling genes with light: New technique can rapidly turn genes on and off, helping scientists better understand their function </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 19:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tablets to Become Irrelevant in Five Years, Claims BlackBerry CEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 14:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Zuckerberg was secretly filmed with spy glasses for "Terms and Conditions May Apply," a documentary about internet privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 14:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers estimate that the amount of gold produced during the collision and merger of two neutron stars may be as large as 10 moon masses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 12:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That robot that did a perfect quadruple backflip? Here's the blooper compilation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 02:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> License plate scanners are the dark horse of the surveillance world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 22:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvards Houghton Library recently uncovered documents from 1767 that foreshadow the American Revolution: eight sheets of signatures  more than 650 in all  protesting Colonial taxation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 16:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eavesdropping on endangered species with iPods and machine learning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard researchers have generated long-lasting blood vessels from reprogrammed human cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 14:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 14:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great segment - heard it on the radio when it aired. I didn't realize Dilla's medical bills ballooned so much at the end because of insurance issues. Sad to hear his mother talking about spending every penny just to have more time with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at the Broad Institute of Harvard and the MIT are tapping the human genome mapped by its founders, hoping to create effective treatments for vexing afflictions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 13:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study from the University of Chicago found that elevated stress hormones can help give your athletic performance a tangible boost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 14:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alarming Research Shows the Sorry State of US Higher Ed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 14:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 14:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to their research in Nature: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature12291.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social psychologist Daniel M. Wegner, most famous for his experiments on thought suppression, passes away at 65. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 14:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spurred by increasing levels of atmospheric carbon dioxide, forests over the past two decades have become dramatically more efficient in how they use water, a Harvard study has found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 14:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 18:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the abstract](http://jeb.biologists.org/content/early/2013/06/27/jeb.087809.abstract) in the The Journal of Experimental Biology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted. Just did a quick search on the URL and didn't see anything submitted to r/WTF, so I posted. Must have missed it when it hit front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Service Illustrates the Gorgeous Spiderweb of Retweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 16:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research enables high-speed customization of novel nanoparticles for drug delivery and other uses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 200-Year-Old Fish Caught Off Alaska: Centuries-old Shortraker Rock-fish may be the oldest of its species ever landed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 19:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there such a thing as food addiction? A study using brain imaging suggests that high-glycemic foods may trigger the same brain mechanism as substance abuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 17:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers examine why humans are so uniquely good at throwing, while all other creatures, including our chimpanzee cousins, are not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sochi 2014 Olympic Committee plans to send the Olympic torch to the International Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 14:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High-performance, transparent, and stretchable electrodes using graphenemetal nanowire hybrid structures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 14:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 03:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A statement from Jack Reardon at Harvard   video on Harry Parker: http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2013/06/statement-on-passing-of-harry-parker/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 15:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to the study: http://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/1206187/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exposure to high pollution levels during pregnancy may increase risk of having child with autism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous hacks North Korean websites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 14:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Air pollution may have had a major soothing influence on storm cycles in the North Atlantic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 14:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study suggests that the body posture inherent in operating everyday gadgets affects not only your back, but your behavior. Operating a relatively large device inspires more assertive behavior than working on a small one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 15:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Bing for Schools' will strip out all ads, beef up privacy protections and adult content filtering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 14:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Powerful gene-editing tool appears to cause off-target mutations in human cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 22:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 15:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit goes to the article's writer, but thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphin dies after idiots make it pose for too many photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 15:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Throwing shade: how Pixar changed the way light works for 'Monsters University' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 21:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online games offer trove of brain data: Study of 35 million users of brain-training software finds alcohol and sleep linked to cognitive performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 20:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microfluidics Will Put 'Lab on a Chip' on Future Robotic Spacecraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 20:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3D printing tiny batteries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 20:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 18:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost (already submitted this): http://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/1gr4k0/mit_study_finds_that_a_gene_associated_with/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian scientist studies swarming behavior of locusts, finds new insights into the causes of obesity epidemic in humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT study finds that a gene associated with longevity also regulates the bodys circadian clock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 23:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered the chemical that makes naked mole rats cancer-proof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 16:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to know if someone's lying to you? Telltale signs may include running of the mouth, an excessive use of third-person pronouns, and an increase in profanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 14:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low doses of silver make bacteria more susceptible to antibiotic attack, paving the way for new therapies for drug-resistant and recurrent infections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 23:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that a 2009 study described the smell of old books to be "a combination of grassy notes with a tang of acids and a hint of vanilla over an underlying mustiness." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Materials scientists have 3D printed fully functional lithium-ion batteries the size of a grain of sand [x-post from r/science] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil Gaiman and book designer Chip Kidd discussed their collaboration on Make Good Art and challenges and opportunities for artists today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 13:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wired science writer breaks down the physics of detecting a "flop" in the NBA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 16:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 15:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vladimir needs to stop Putin things in his pocket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 21:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't realize that it was behind a paywall. Tried to follow your rules:
 a direct link to or a summary of peer reviewed research with appropriate citations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook reportedly in talks with US government to reveal secret data requests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 19:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 19:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a blog post from NYT that describes the research: http://economix.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/06/13/how-money-affects-morality/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find that mere exposure to money can trigger unethical intentions and behavior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 15:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers analyze edX course page views, clickstreams and discussion threads for clues to how students learn online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 15:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17 of the oldest man-made structures on Earth still in use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 20:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research revealeds distinct sets of itch-generating neurons that explain why current itch therapies often fail and suggest new ways to selectively silence itch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 14:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former FCC chairman, Harvard scholar make a pitch for private networks to aid public safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 20:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outrage over professor's Twitter post on obese students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 19:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A design student creates a graphic novel for the sight-impaired that tells a simple story through touch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 15:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More info on their research is available at: http://www.heb.fas.harvard.edu/Press4/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers use barium levels in fossil teeth to show how breast-feeding behavior changed among Neanderthals and early humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 14:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Differences in unemployment and earnings based on major for BA and graduate degree holders [study] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 15:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Immigrants (including those in the country illegally) contributed $115 billion more to the Medicare system than they received in benefits, while the American-born received $28 billion more than they contributed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 14:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eat a Password Vitamin Daily to Log In: Motorola presents idea for a vitamin authentication pill one could take daily </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 22:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Boston: A tilt-shift film [3:12] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 22:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A first step turned x-rays emitted by the binary system of EX Hydrae into sounds. A second step made these sounds into music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 16:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oprah Winfrey's Commencement speech at Harvard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 01:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 15:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be great to see NPR Music folks get more involved in reddit. Bring some musicians to reddit for AMAs, take requests from the reddit community before live performances, reddit user suggestions for reviewing new music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 15:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper wasn't linked in any of the news articles about the study. Did some digging, I think this is it: http://learnmem.cshlp.org/content/19/9/423

Edit: better version of link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that infantile amnesia may be due to the rapid growth of nerve cells in the hippocampus, the brain region responsible for filing new experiences into long-term memory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 22:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Harvard's Houghton Library contains a book bound in human skin. In the 1880s, Arsne Houssaye presented his book 'Des destinees de lame', to Dr. Ludovic Bouland. Bouland bound the book with skin from the unclaimed body of a female mental patient who had died of a stroke. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 16:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds that female college students exceed alcohol guidelines more frequently than male college students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 17:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 16:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate that - thanks! I feel that a lot of web designers also dabble in development, and vice versa. This is just the subreddit I gravitate to whenever I want to share/read about what's new in web dev or design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 16:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pull-to-refresh is a common UI element, thought it was relevant to this crowd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
