<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1780</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a scary event to watch unfold. Can't say I blame you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She isn't so bad, to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the idea. You have a 50/50 chance of being right, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest candidate! But she still falls into our pay spectrum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll see tonight. Hopefully the popular vote aligns with our plans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are *a lot* closer than you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rough day, man. Rough day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 100% true. I wouldn't risk putting myself out there just to lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You severely underestimate the power the government has over you. Do you not think that we can keep your televisions on? You wouldn't be able to mute if there was a nuclear disaster, I can promise you that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but we do have control over the parent company that hosts their site! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddy, no one should go back to Australia. Everything there wants to kill you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one step ahead. Don't you worry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything on nosleep is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to go *that* far, but maybe just having a plan in place would do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we took care of you people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What video...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your birthday is on Inauguration Day? Talk about a bad day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd vote for a Hugh Mungus/Bone ticket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just say there's certain things that can be done to manipulate people through audio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I wouldn't recommend it. Do so at your own risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it interesting that there's a few of you leaning that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be surprised how much we own/run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I upvoted your comment before reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, you still have plenty of reasons to be terrified.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really?! I guess I've been so consumed with our internal workings that I haven't paid much attention to foreign affairs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably one of the more clever theories we've heard! Nice job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably do. But Snowden took a chance, and he enlightened the world to a lot of things. I felt like it was my duty to do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree - since I'll probably be living there one day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plead the fifth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50/50 chance of my candidate getting elected. It's quite the lovely system, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course! You guys have been our greatest allies for decades. Plus, you never do anything wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I needed to share this info, but yea...if I gave away who I work for there would be harsh consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been waiting a long time as well. Stay informed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't confirm any reptilian reports, but you're right - we essentially are just toys to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has definitely been a...strange election cycle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a good chance our candidate will be elected. Be wary of all speeches and questionable actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say. I wish I could, but I have a family to consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful who you vote for. Be informed. Look for the signs. That's really all I can say on the subject. It's ultimately your choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election Day: 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a high-profile, unfavored candidate who has a chance of receiving your vote today. Due to what I'm about to tell you, I can't reveal who it is. Non-disclosures and such - I'm sure you can understand. What I can tell you is that there's more to this election than what some doctored tax records and planted emails can tell you. 


Wait. You don't actually *believe* any of those documents are legitimate, do you? 


Our campaign staff had those made and spread.


We **own** /r/politics.


We **own** /r/The_Donald. 


We **own** the mainstream media.


Every. Single. Fact you think you know - that you think you can believe - has been manufactured by our staff. Wikileaks is a farce. Sanders was a lie. Johnson was...well, Gary Johnson was a plan that went sour. We fixed that, though.


Now that we've gotten that out of the way, I would like to move onto the more pertinent information that may alter the election depending on who sees this. 


Our candidate is dangerous. Not in your "nuclear codes pressing - causing a war with Russia" kind of way. This candidate has killed people...many people, to get to the position they're in. Countries full of people have died for no reason other than their cravings for ultimate power and control. It's been covered up well and, for the most part, supported by the powers that run this country. Lately, though, we can't control it. Since the primaries began, our candidate has been getting increasingly more violent and unstable. 


It began in 1945. 


The idea came up that instead of leaving the election and fate of the country in the hands of the public and a few "wisely chosen" politicians, we could create the perfect presidents. Test tube babies, if you will. They could be raised and groomed in secret at Camp David in the presence of all of the greatest powers this country had ever seen. They would learn all of the secrets and ideologies...and then be put to sleep. Rather, a hypnotic sleep that would keep them from being able to access their memories and training until given seats of power. 


The issue was with the available technology at the time. While most conspiracy theorists were correct in believing we had technology available that the public wasn't aware of, it wasn't near what there is today in 2016. 


The manufactured young were a success. They were born healthy - free from defects and racial abnormalities. As they grew, they learned at an amazingly accelerated rate. The professors kept at the camp were some of the best in their fields and yet by the teen years, our premade candidates were stumping them at every logical fallacy. The problems were in the containment facilities. We...couldn't keep them locked in.


They began fleeing one by one, immersing themselves into the public and out of our reach. Some even began dabbling in politics, which made it incredibly hard to deal with them (See: JFK).


One stayed, however. Just one. Almost like it wanted to.


Needless to say, once the rest of them had escaped, most of our attention and funding was turned towards this one candidate. Our last hope, at least until the next batch were done incubating. We taught it everything it needed. We gave it the best upbringing Ive ever heard of. Hell, we spoiled the shit out of that thing. It got pretty much anything it wanted, whenever it wanted. It always got its way. We thought it was completely content being our little puppet, happy even. Until a few years ago, we really thought we had it completely under control. 


It did everything we told it to, played all its card right. Climbed the political ladder (with the help of its family members), made connections, made promiseseven instigated a few carefully chosen scandals, to appear more fallible. Not even the American public is stupid enough to trust a perfect candidate. You need your president to have *some* kind of personality. Even if that personality includes some less-than-savory aspects. 


In fact, you really like the scandals, dont you? That dirty underbelly keeps you watching, even while you scoff at the shitshow this election year has turned into. You keep crawling back for more, digging deeper, wanting to see what other skeletons your national leaders have in their closets. At your core, you want to be reassured that despite all their power, theyre humans. Just like you.


Thing is, with this candidate, the skeletons arent figurative. With this one, if you had the misfortune of seeing its true face, youd have nightmares for the rest of your life. I know from experience. It showed me what it really looked like, once. And let me assure you, despite all appearances, that thing is not human.


It manifests on the weaknesses of the human race. Sustains itself on the blood of the innocent victims of wars. The candidate had a hunger, and in our desperation, we gave in. Thousands of people killed just to be used as nourishment for this goddamn beast. You've heard of the bombings. All a cover-up for it. I know it's wrong. I get it. But I'm just a pawn in this operation - for now. I don't know how much longer I'll be involved after today.  


Honestly, we should have known, when the rest of them escaped, that they couldnt be controlled as easily as we thought they could. When this candidate stayed behind, passive and submissive, I guess we just kind of assumed the hypnosis took. All that MKUltra had to be good for something, right? We knew what we were doing - were part of the fucking US government, right? And now something seventy years in the making would finally come to fruition - wed be the ones holding the reigns when it finally rose to power. 


None of us knew that it wasnt sleeping. It had never been sleeping. None of us knew that it knew what it really was. For years, *years*, it sat under our noses, pretending to be the perfect obedient child, while really practicing its abilities, growing stronger by the day. 


But we know now, and it's too late. We made a single assassination attempt. The storm we dealt with after previous attempts was hard, and we still deal with it today, but we knew we needed to do something. 


One sniper. One bullet. 


The agent had a clear shot while the candidate was in the backyard of it's home. He took it - and it was a clear, definite hit in the chest. The candidate (according to the video transcript from the helmet cam) fell to the ground immediately and was visually confirmed by the agent to be killed. The conference room exploded in the most contained celebration you could ever imagine. 


The agent moved in to remove the body - per protocol - so it could be replaced with a body double. As he approched the body, and knelt next to it to feel for a pulse, the candidate said something to him. The audio isn't clear, but some analysts believe it may have been older Russian. The agent began to seize upon hearing the words. At that moment, the candidate sprung to life and grabbed the agent by the neck, squeezing harder and harder until there was a clear snapping of bones. Then it began to feast. 


The recovery team only found the camera, gun, some personal memorabilia, and the upper third of his body. 


If this thing gets elected - if it gets the chance to stand there and speak with the entire countrys eyes upon it - youll know, too.


Honestly, however it goes today - whoever you vote for - I have a feeling our baby will be the next president. Like I said, it always gets its way. And when it does, I suggest you play it safe. I suggest you avoid all television screens in general on January 20, 2017. But, even if you cant manage that, definitely do *not* to tune into its Inaugural Address.


Because I happen to know, that is when its going to shed its skin.

**Edit:**

Now we wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just all in quality, man.

*Quality* title that makes people click on your story.

*Quality* story that makes people want to finish it and read more.

*Quality* reader engagement that stimulates growth in the comment section.

*Quality Quality Quality*

(Last point is subjective)

I've beaten out a big author before, and I'm relatively unknown in comparison. The authors that attract large amounts of upvotes are really fucking good and they earn it. Fan base would be a minimal influence, at best. 

For example, the "I Dared My Best Friend" series  was written under a throwaway and was a **massive** hit. Those Search and Rescue stories - unknown user, biggest stories on the entire sub. 

It doesn't boil down to author's credibility. It's being good. The names you're seeing all the time are simply good writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, removing who posts a thread is more of a sitewide Reddit thing. But is it all that bad? You could just not look.

Just like /u/Gallowboob posting literally everything - it doesn't change the content by knowing it's him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Essentially my month of NaNoWriMo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine that they're quite common. Even boiling down to specific neighborhoods. 

There's always that weird neighbor, or that creepy house, or the historic building. Kids will always talk and make up stories about anything. I can think of like four or five about where I grew up off hand. If anything, I would imagine that more rural areas would have less stories because there isn't as much around. 

Um. Popcorn chicken is fucking tasty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Podcast and desire to write aside, I don't believe there would be much of a difference between urban and rural "legend" stories, aside from the obvious (setting, character, etc.). Stories like those spread through word of mouth and - in these days - internet/social media. Regardless of where you live, the method of them becoming "urban legends" is going to be the same. 

Does that answer your question? I had a hard time extracting what you wanted to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mistaken Identity  /r/shortscarystories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maximum Malcontent  /r/ShortSadStories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you don't laugh, I'll kill you  /r/nosleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a story of mine gets removed by a mod, 9.8/10 I'd just fix what they ask me to and then ask them if I can repost it. The only reason I wouldn't do that is if the entire story needs reworking. Then I'd probably just move it to a different sub, tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/DrStrangelove4242 wrote this beautifully fucked up piece about a drug that I had a hard time with. It got removed, but trust me - it was disturbing. I winced so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 12:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, you're right. I was hoping this story would maybe draw some more people to my shows. Attendence has been down a bit lately.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 11:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, there's a rule that specfically states that your submission must be a story. Poems aren't necessarily stories **but** I don't know with 100% certainty if you could do it or not. For a clear, correct answer I would like to summon /u/kneeod, who can answer you and use the word "fuck" four times in a tasteful way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 02:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Will do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 02:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's half the battle! Fuel for these trucks just gets so expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 02:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ba dum tch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't ask for anything more. Well, I could. But I'd need more help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be useful for some states that Dougie can't reach.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Maybe we can arrange something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your style. I think you'd enjoy my shows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're masterpieces, duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could I interest you in some free tickets..? I'm in Tuscon tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is! Very expensive, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you want to open up for me sometime? I think our crowds would be in for a treat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been known to throw some subtle references into my acts ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your style. [This](http://www.funnymeme.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Funny-memes-kid-handcuffed-to-cart-walmart-484x720.jpg) is how we can shop :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely!! What kind of skills do you have? Any experience in the entertainment industry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a couple I thought of just now. They aren't great, but could be viable options. 

The Stairs in the Woods. Search and Rescue. Stay Off the Stairs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddy, you're a clever one. I don't have any plans to come across the pond anytime soon. If I do though, I'll get you on the VIP list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got to work hard to get famous. Sometimes that means doing things that people might not agree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So delish, man. Super easy to make! The pain is just cooking everything before baking. Lots of dishes and prep time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll fucking murder bitches in hopscotch. I've got legs 4 dayz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya know, fake laughs are almost worse than not laughing at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But. But. Friendship bracelets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand! I would probably avoid any comedians with seven letters in their names, then. Just to be safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll totally braid yours!  [But..](http://i.imgur.com/VDo9X2g.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I would be *so* pissed if that happened to me! Thanks for the tip. That's one thing I've managed to be good with. What I do is buy everything I plan to give him, and then just divide it up between myself, Santa, and birthday. Lots of wrapping paper and bags though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, that's great! I might use that in my next show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. Did we just become best friends? I think we did. 

Baked Lays work? The grocery store tossed out a bunch of expired bags last week and that's how I've been sustaining myself. I have like 50. Minus the two I use as pillows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessssss. Does that mean I can crash on your couch for a couple weeks...? They have to delouse my place. My crabs got out of control.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh..how is it having a birthday so close to Christmas? My son's is the 27th, and I don't really know what to expect when he gets older.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh campy - yes, that fits way better. I also loved that it was self-aware. If they tried to ay it off as a 100% serious movie then I think it would have flopped (in terms of reception, not box office). Moronic decisions though...so much yes. It also made me want to punch a child. Those kids were dicks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
With the same argumentation as the "clickbait titles are more believable" one might discuss the believability of the fact that who the hell would post to reddit while dangerous things are going on. That would remove 99 out of a 100 stories on here. 

Perfect point. I don't even have anything to add to this. I just wanted to agree with you in a more eloquent way instead of saying yes.

I am also very happy with the new rules. I can see the title rule resulting in a lot more exposure for stories that normally wouldn't be given a chance because of a "creative" title. Now people will actually have to read stories - damn!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a god among common men. 

Or a really cool dude. You can pick. 

Thanks for the list! Also, I'm totally writing a banger for Christmas. Crossing my fingers that you'll love it ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *loved* Krampus. It was so perfectly shitty. It reminded me of a high-budget Troma movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still eat the noms - don't you worry. 

An old, fat man giving kids presents sounds a bit...rapey. But it can totally be a solid horror story, as long as he doesn't say rapey stuff like "Come reach in my sack, Susie." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty good! Probably super unhealthy, but tasty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you don't laugh, I'll kill you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ma always told me that I had wanted to be an entertainer ever since I was old enough to stand up. She said I would walk into a group of people and start chatting away until they started laughing. Then, once I got them going, I would feed off of it - changing my routine to keep everyone laughing as long as possible. It was my talent. 

Ma knew I would be a comedian.

I didn't really see it, if I'm being honest with you all. When Ma passed in 2009 though, I felt like I needed to do something to pay my respects. 

There was a small club in my hometown just outside of Jersey called McKinnion's. Nothing spectacular there. When the washed up, D-List comedians would get booked they *might* draw in about fifty people to sit at their sticky tables. However, they booked anyone who could guarantee ten people. Desperate for business, much?

It took zero effort to get a gig there. Pauly Shore was coming through town on a Saturday and the guy at McKinnion's didn't even hesitate about giving me a twenty minute opening slot. 

Twenty minutes, though. How was I supposed to fill twenty minutes?! 

I spent the next week staying up late writing out my routine. It wasn't spectacular, but I managed to avoid cliche one-liners. Most of the routine consisted of jokes about having no clue how to perform stand-up comedy. I watched a few videos on YouTube and that seemed to be a solid starting point. 

Honestly, I was nervous to tell the guys at the job site. They were a bunch of macho construction workers and, while they always included me, I was the runt of the group. Much to my surprise the guys thought it was the greatest thing ever, and were pumped about coming to the show! It was bliss, if I've ever felt it. I was gonna tell my family, but I figured it could wait until I see if I was any good or not. My wife was a bitch - she'd never let me live it down if I ate dick.

The nerves didn't bother me the entire time leading up to the show...until about ten minutes before I was supposed to go on. The guys spared no expense to come show support. They brought their gals, buddies, and some family. Pauly said that in all of the times he played McKinnion's, that was the most packed he had ever seen it. 

The minutes turned to seconds in the blink of an eye. 

My breathing was heavy. My heart was pounding. Sweat was pooling in places I don't even wanna mention. Then the owner of the club came up to me. 

"Hey kid, I'm givin' ya an extra ten minutes. You earned it." He said to me with a grin and a pat on the back. 

Thirty minutes?! I barely had enough material to cover twenty! There wasn't any time to argue, though. It was already 9:01 and I had to get out there. Pauly rubbed my shoulders and wished me luck, and with that I walked out onto the stage to roars of clapping and cheers.

When I got up to the mic, I didn't hesitate at all to dive into my routine. It kind of came naturally to me...just like Ma always thought it would.

I started out strong, but toward the middle of my set things started to die out. I began losing confidence in my jokes. My voice started cracking every few words, and I started stuttering when it didn't even make sense. The club was getting quieter by the second.

"Listen, if you guys are gonna act like zombies and not laugh - I'm just gonna kill ya!"

I don't know where that line came from, and I don't particularly care because it slayed them. The entire joint *erupted* with laughter. I even saw Pauly cracking up on the side of the stage. Maybe it was the fact that I was a scrawny, light-skinned Italian guy threatening a gang of huge construction workers. Maybe it was them thinking my routine falling apart was hilarious. Either way, it doesn't matter. 

My routine was a hit.

McKinnion's kept inviting me back time after time after time. They started advertising me as "The Comedy Killer" and even gave me headlining spots from time to time! Each show brought in a slightly bigger crowd and my pay started getting a pretty hefty bump. At my peak there, I was bringing in about $800 a show. For perspective, Pauly only got $1,200 in cash on my first night.

After about a year and a half of performing exclusively at McKinnion's, a promoter for a comedy agency reached out to me. He was in charge of booking talent and had a 45 minute slot coming up at a gala event. If the show went well, I was promised a contract *that night.* I said yes, obviously.

I'll admit, before I went out on stage for that show my nerves were considerably more shot than my first night at the old club. I was standing behind a giant purple curtain on the stage in the basement of a mansion. The gala was a cancer benefit hosted by some internet millionaire, and to cut costs and maximize donations, he put on the entire thing at his house with his staff. I was used to the slum that graced the dirty walls and slippery floors of McKinnion's, not rich people eating fish eggs and sipping wine. 

My set started out alright - I got some good laughs and applause. It didn't turn south until I went to my trademark bit about killing everyone the audience. I won't list the nasty things that were yelled to me by hecklers, but I will say that it's apparently in poor taste to make jokes about death at a cancer benefit. I wasn't even allowed to finish my set or stay after I was taken off stage. 

I blew it. 

Getting escorted out by security did something to me. It evoked something I hadn't felt before. It was rage, but with a thirst. I felt like a man in a desert and my rage needed to be fulfilled. 

I called up Dougie, one of the guys from work. Dougie had been my closest friend for years. He was actually the one who landed me the job with the company. I needed someone to vent to - to get all of that anger off of my soul. I told him what happened, how my killing joke basically cost me a real career in comedy. I couldn't help but cry a bit. 

"Why don't you kill em then, bro?" He laughed. "Sorry man, I've gotta get Alaina to bed. Stop by tomorrow we'll grab some beers, yeah?"

"Kill em." It resonated with me. I mean, that was the entire part of my routine that got me to this gala in the first place. Maybe that's what I needed to pass my boundaries as a comedian. To get people to take me seriously.

I retreated to my car until the event had long since passed. I sat there for hours holding my glock, contemplating eternity. 

On one hand, if I killed someone, I'm a criminal. I get caught and I go to prison. 

On the other hand, this could cement myself as a legend: "The Comedy Killer."

Before I had enough time to come to a thought-out decision, the promoter walked out to his car. Before he got in, I got out and asked him if he wouldn't mind helping me change a flat to which he gladly obliged. Nice guy.

As we were digging in the trunk to loosen up the spare, he apologized to me profusely. He said he should have given me a heads up about the situation, and that he would make sure to get me another shot. 

I pulled the trigger against the back of his head and he collapsed into the trunk. 

I sped to Dougie's house. I didn't know who else to turn to. I had just killed a man, for Christ's sake!

I called him up and told him I was parked on the street. He came out, got in the car, and we drove off. I think he knew something was up. Maybe it was the blood on my arms. But he didn't ask any questions or make any comments. Dougie told me to drive to the building site and those were all the words we exchanged until we got there. That's when he told me his plan:

Cement Truck.

We carried the body to the back lot, and somehow managed to get him in the barrel. Dougie took care of the rest. The dull thuds I heard every couple of rotations made me sick to my stomach. 

Dougie called someone and told them to wipe the cameras. That was the end of it.

It's been seven years since I started comedy, and my career is pretty damn good. I quit the construction company to be able to tour year-round, but I'm still in good with Dougie. He has contacts in most states. The ones I book my shows in, conveniently.

Attendence has been booming, too. Although, I'm no longer sure if it's because I'm genuinely funny or if it's the legend surrounding my shows. According to what Dougie tells me, it's all over the internet that one person goes missing after every one of my shows and they're never heard from again. Before you wonder, yes - I've had plenty of conversations with cops, the FBI, all of them. 

The thing is, they'd have to tear down entire buildings to stop [me](https://twitter.com/knutsonwrites?s=09). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more of a pretend sous chef in my girlfriend's kitchen. But! I make a *killer* chili ramekin potato bowl thing.

It's essentially homemade chili topped with a layer of mashed potatoes, topped with a layer of cheese, topped with a layer of crispy hash browns, topped with a layer of cheese and Italian seasoning. Then you bake it to make it crispy on top. I drew a [diagram](http://i.imgur.com/EWZ8ArN.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas and Horror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm Mikey.

You might know me from such stories as ["How I Became a Donut Farmer,"](https://youtu.be/LLpIMRowndg) or ["I'll Kill You All If You Don't Laugh at My Jokes."](https://youtu.be/MGTIWr6aixE)

I'm one of those people that skips Thanksgiving in favor of Christmas. It's a recent thing for me - I used to hate Christmas. Now, I think I'm compensating for years lost (long story). 

I want to know if anyone has some favorite NoSleep Christmas-themed stories they'd like to share! Also, how do you feel about combining the happiest, most innocent holiday with horror? Is it cheap? Does it remind you that you hate Nightmare Before Christmas merchandise? Talk to me, I'm needy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool, but did it kill Frieza? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya know, I don't really have an answer for that. I don't get creeped out by my own works, nor do I read something I wrote and think "that's terrifying." I'm immune to myself, I guess. 

What makes something scary is totally subjective. I mean, there's definitely common tropes and guidelines but that doesn't define what is or is not scary. 

You definitely stimulated my brain with this. Now I'm wondering about how I write (as I'm taking a day off of Nano and writing a NS story). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, after reading all of the comments discussing this, I think I have something to say about the argument of believability.

I've read quite a few comments saying that the clickbait titles make stories seem more realistic (or at least implying that point) and that creative titles would come across as more fiction than anything. I don't believe this is the case.

Look at it as if you were at a campfire late at night in the middle of the woods. Cliche scary story setting. Someone telling a story isn't going to say "Guys, I have this story about a park ranger and the creepiest stuff happened to him one time." That would be silly. 

However, campfire stories tend to leave you wondering whether or not they're true, no? That's kind of like nosleep - its just a story...but what if it isn't? Writing will dictate that more so than a title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with Grind, that title is radical, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 11:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a kid on Christmas! Okay, maybe not that excited. But this sounds like a good addition to the rules for each sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 11:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't going to go over very well.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have six tattoos so far. Not a ton, but a decent amount. All of them mean something to me and represent important aspects of my life except for one. 

Guess what? I hate that tattoo. 

My advice to you would be to not get a tattoo just for the sake of getting a tattoo. It might be all cool and sexy for a few years, but who's to say you'll still like it when you're older?

Tattoo removal is expensive, friend.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I'm in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 12:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sci-fi noir...? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 12:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dabbled a bit with some sci-fi stories and I absolutely *had* to keep a little piece of paper that had all of my terms defined. My favorite short story clocks in at just over 3k words - I can't imagine doing something larger without a "dictionary." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, but you guys still blew a 3-1 lead with the "unanimous" MVP after having the best season since the Bulls. You're the OGs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Disclaimer: I don't know a lot of the proper terms for the different sexualities, and what is considered the proper way to speak on something. Sorry if I somehow offend someone - it's just lack of knowledge.*

Hmm. I just finished the story - you did a really nice job with it. I can see why someone might consider the story as "de-legitmizing" trans people in a way, but only because it seems to be a genuine story about transsexuality that turns into that ending. It might cause some more sensitive people to be upset that it wasn't what they wanted from a story. Emotional backlash is what I'm saying, I guess. 

However, I feel that there's a greater meaning (?) with the transsexual MC. Even though it turns out he isn't (spoiler) human, it's still a being struggling with it's sexuality and going through the issues associated with that. On the surface, it might seem like it's just a horror story using transexuality as an attention grabber, but that just isn't the case. You wrote - in my opinion - a very well thought out piece that incorporated a clever dual-adaptation of the word trans.

I hope all of that makes sense. I think I said what I meant to, but sometimes I miss the mark.

On the topic of inclusion of different sexualities in stories - I feel it's important to be open to the inclusion, but only if it makes sense to the overall plot of the story. 

Similar to gore, if you can take it out and the story still is perfectly fine then I don't necessarily believe it should be forced. I mean that in regards to all things involving sexuality and gender. If telling us your character is straight, gay, bi, trans, etc makes no difference to the story, then I don't see the need for it. 

With that, I also would like to see more usage of identities in stories. I can't speak for everyone, but I know I tend to naturally gravitate towards a straight character and, to be honest, it's kind of boring. When done correctly, I feel like sexuality can add beautiful amounts of depth to a character that might just get left out of a typical straight character's background. 

Again, I think I adequately conveyed what I wanted to say, but I might have missed a point or two. Let me know if I can explain myself any better! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 11:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was only able to watch about 2/3 of it on mu way to work, but the connections it makes are interesting. Especially how the make a point to mention that stories would go nowhere without a strong community. As everyone on NS knows, that's entirely true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think that [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/55pali/love_the_record_keeper/) one that I wrote has a happy ending. Not a conventional one. But happy for the narrator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying it for the first time this year. I'm writing a web of stories that surrounds one person. More of a straight thriller style than anything else. Same username, if you want to add me. I'm starting up tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats - you've done an excellent job with everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fuck yes. The moment I've been waiting about twenty minutes for!

**Stories Written:** 31

**Number of Subs Posted In:** 11

**Word Count:** 14,424

**Average Words per Story:** 465

**Total Upvotes:** 1,855

**Average Upvotes per Story:** 59.8

**Average Percentage:** 93.03%

**Lowest Upvoted Stories:** [Fired (1) - 10/16](https://m.reddit.com/r/ShortSeriousStories/comments/57us3z/fired/) and [Snapclap (1) - 10/28](https://m.reddit.com/r/ShortSillyStories/comments/59yt6n/snapclap/) (both tied at a single upvote)

**Lowest Rated Story (by percentage):** [Drink and Walk (64%) - 10/7](https://m.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/56fexd/drink_and_walk/)

**Highest Upvoted Story:** [I tried confronting a clown (1,416) - 10/6](https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/565abv/i_tried_confronting_a_clown/)

**Highest Rated Stories (by percentage):** 15 tied at 100% (counting single upvote stories)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I gave kids some olives my house would get egged and my pumpkins would get smashed. Well, probably not. But there's a chance because 'Murica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Is. Amazing. And you're an amaizng person for doing it. Nice job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a call from some strange number I didn't recognize. If it can even be called a number - there were only like three or four digits. I didn't answer, but it left a voicemail. When I listened back it was a monotone beep for about ten seconds followed by a distorted woman's voice laughing.

Weird as fuck, but I debunked it as a scam call and whoever dialed just didn't realize their receiver wasn't hung up or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mistaken Identity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The concern is mostly in the ingredients. I wouldn't go as far as to say that we've mislead anyone with our advertisements, product description, or ingredient lists. I mean, in accordance with the FDA, meat doesn't have to be labeled in plain-term. The ingredient in question does use it's "proper" name and is clearly listed in the third line of the list. Any consumer could easily type the words into Bing or Google and learn what it is. 

We can't be blamed that they don't. It isn't hidden.

The handling and ethics of obtaining the ingredient is what creates so much concern. But, honestly, we're selling cat treats - how can ethics really be a serious question for us? Our hands don't even get dirty!

Take for example, this past Halloween. We have a team of "retrievers" in place around the country. Their purpose is to find the locations of the bodies, extract them, and get them on ice to be shipped to our processing facilities. We're cleaning up the messes from all of those stupid satanic rituals, people! We don't harm them. We don't kill them. All our company does is retrieve them and repurpose the waste. Dogs love the flavor, and the public gets a kick out of the flavor gimmick.

Our sales have never been higher! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. Really...? Mostly commenting to see where this goes. But also just in case.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maximum Malcontent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never questioned her love. Ever. 

Not when her phone would go off constantly, at all hours of the day. Or even when she would have to run errands that didn't make any sense. I mean, who needs to hand deliver a check to the gas company in 2016? 

I wanted so badly to believe that he was just a friend. I did, actually. For months. Jealously is a common factor in driving people away from each other. I didn't want to drive her away. 

One day, though, I had to know. I went through her phone and found all the proof I needed. 

She avoided me for a month before leaving me for him.

"The only reason I'm still with you is because I don't want to hurt you anymore." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ that's terrifying. Yet, I'm intrigued that you can scream that loud. That sounds like some crazy hidden talent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silent Hill. Resident Evil: Nemesis is a close second. I also thoroughly loved Outlast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem - you're in for a treat# </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know that sub existed?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Gambling Problem  /r/ShortSadStories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Digs [Part Three]  /r/cryosleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, it's a requirement. However, you might have some success with that over on /r/cryosleep or another similar sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
