<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3447</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Steven Gerrard and Rio Ferdinand celebrating Barcelona's 6th goal live on TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Mascherano admitting that he fouled Di Maria and was lucky that the ref did not whistle! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSG coach Unai Emery after Barcelona's sixth goal by Sergi Roberto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIDEO: Luis Enrique celebrating Barcelona's 6th goal against PSG. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WhatsApp, the Facebook-owned messaging service used by more than 1 billion people worldwide, is testing a system that would let businesses talk directly to WhatsApp users for the first time, according to communications about the project seen by Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can Grow Potatoes On Mars - Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brain activity may continue after heart stops beating - A new study reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brain activity may continue after heart stops beating - A new study reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii sues US president Donald Trump over travel ban, says ban will harm its Muslim population </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Jason... How are you? Have you contemplated it before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii sues US president Donald Trump over travel ban, says ban will harm its Muslim population </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian police answering thousands of calls for help from battered women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. open to dialogue with North Korea, but Pyongyang must take steps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The British economy has outperformed expectations since last years vote to leave the European Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. intelligence and law enforcement officials said on Wednesday they have been aware since the end of last year of a security breach at the CIA and were focusing on contractors as the likeliest source of documents being passed on to anti-secrecy group WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kosovo signaled on Wednesday it would turn its security force into a national army, in plans opposed by its ethnic Serb minority that drew immediate criticism from NATO and the territory's biggest foreign supporter, the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There were angry scenes in Israel's parliament on Wednesday as preliminary approval was given to a bill that would restrict the use of outdoor loudspeakers by religious institutions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 19 people have been found dead at the scene of a fire in a shelter for children near Guatemala City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. general says Russia deploys cruise missile, threatens NATO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand. I just hope someday, we can find answers to all the "WHYs" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China posts first monthly trade deficit in three years as imports soar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey has launched a complaint at the World Trade Organization to challenge U.S. anti-subsidy duties on Turkish pipe and tube products, the WTO said on Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spending more than 2 hours on social media per day could make you feel isolated, New research says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sophie Gregoire Trudeau, who is married to Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, is taking heat over an International Women's Day post asking people to "celebrate the boys and men in our lives who encourage us to be who we truly are, who treat girls   women with respect" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CIA had a special programme allowing it to trick people into thinking they had been hacked by other countries, according to WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany 'must decide if Turkey is a friend or not', Turkish foreign minister says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland has marked International Womens Day 2017 by requiring companies to prove they offer equal pay regardless of gender, ethnicity, sexuality and nationality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek farmers clashed with police in central Athens on Wednesday when a protest against tax and pension reforms mandated by the country's multi-billion-euro bailout turned violent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man claiming to be the son of the slain, estranged half brother of North Korea's leader said he was lying low with his mother and sister, in a video posted online by a group that said it helped rescue them following the murder a month ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines Foreign Minister Yasay booted from post amid US citizenship row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyclone slams into Madasgacar, at least three dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States and North Korea are heading for a collision like "two accelerating trains with neither side willing to give way," Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi told reporters Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Africa has officially revoked its withdrawal from the International Criminal Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am so sorry to hear that. Comfort and peace to you and the rest of the family  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lake on the outskirts in southern Australia has turned a shade of pink because of a strange natural phenomenon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Donald Trump is to nominate Washington lawyer Noel Francisco for the position of solicitor general, the government's top advocate before the U.S. Supreme Court, according to two sources familiar with the hiring process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is probably in love with me, says Arnold Schwarzenegger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Depressed Man Commits Suicide After Announcing it on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Canadian government is weighing the chances of a potential surge in asylum seekers illegally crossing into Canada from the United States as the weather improves, a government minister said on Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Panamanian dictator Manuel Noriega suffered a hemorrhage after surgery Tuesday to remove a benign brain tumor and was in critical condition, his daughters reported </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of Egyptians protested across the country on Tuesday because they were unable to get their share of subsidised bread, police said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Depressed Man Commits Suicide After Announcing it on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese telecom equipment maker ZTE has agreed to pay $892 million and plead guilty to criminal charges for violating U.S. laws that restrict the sale of American-made technology to Iran and North Korea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea warns of 'actual war' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico has canceled existing sugar export permits to the United States in a dispute over the pace of shipments, according to a letter seen by Reuters, in a flare-up industry sources said could temporarily disrupt supplies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber looking for chief operating officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber looking for chief operating officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifty young people have been detained in France for allegedly throwing stones at police cars, setting fires and lobbing smoke bombs into a school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Hassan Rouhani should apologize to the Iranian people if he cannot show that the economy has improved, one of Iran's most prominent hardliners said on Tuesday, setting a battle line for a presidential election in May </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest WikiLeaks document dump about the CIAs computer hacking tools is being viewed in Washington as just the most recent skirmish in a struggle between US and Russian intelligence services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks has released a huge set of files that it calls "Year Zero" and which mark the biggest exposure of CIA spying secrets ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana and prescription painkillers are flooding into the Gaza Strip as never before, prompting officials from the ruling Islamist group Hamas to seek tougher punishments for smuggling drugs into the blockaded territory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The military chiefs of staff of Turkey, Russia and the United States held talks on Tuesday in the southern Turkish city of Antalya to discuss regional issues, including Iraq and Syria, the Turkish army said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China has warned it will take "necessary measures" in response to the US acceleration of plans to set up a missile defence system in South Korea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea barred Malaysians from leaving the country on Tuesday, sparking tit-for-tat action by Malaysia, as police investigating the murder of Kim Jong Nam in Kuala Lumpur sought to question up to three men hiding in the North Korean embassy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half of all new cars in Norway are now electric or hybrid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nurse fired for abusing President Zuma and wife on facebook after the first lady was admitted at hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moscow is seriously worried about North Korea's latest missile drills, which saw Pyongyang fire four ballistic missiles into the sea off Japan's northwest, Kremlin spokesman Dmitry Peskov said on Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia has banned its football team from playing in North Korea citing security threats amid a diplomatic row over the death of Kim Jong-Nam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of Nigerian women forced from their homes by Boko Haram jihadists held a protest on Sunday to demand better conditions as UN Security Council envoys visited their camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian scientists have successfully tested a cancer-killing drug in space, which can fight all kinds and stages of malignant tumors in the human body, the local newspaper Izvestia cited a professor as saying on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian scientists have successfully tested a cancer-killing drug in space, which can fight all kinds and stages of malignant tumors in the human body, the local newspaper Izvestia cited a professor as saying on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian scientists have successfully tested a cancer-killing drug in space, which can fight all kinds and stages of malignant tumors in the human body, the local newspaper Izvestia cited a professor as saying on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian scientists have successfully tested a cancer-killing drug in space, which can fight all kinds and stages of malignant tumors in the human body, the local newspaper Izvestia cited a professor as saying on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian scientists have successfully tested a cancer-killing drug in space, which can fight all kinds and stages of malignant tumors in the human body, the local newspaper Izvestia cited a professor as saying on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia has stepped up security checks at all border crossings to stop North Koreans linked to the murder of the estranged half-brother to North Korean leader Kim Jung Un from leaving the country, Malaysia's police chief told Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korean firms are being squeezed in China, in suspected retaliation for Seoul's deployment of a U.S. missile defence system, highlighting the tools China can deploy to hit back at the corporate interests of trade partners it disagrees with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim-Americans offer to stand guard at Jewish sites across US to prevent vandalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German town that cancelled Turkish event receives bomb threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three suspected suicide bombers have been killed after one of them detonated an explosive device by a parked fuel tanker early Friday morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU Threatens Member States With Fines Over Failure To Accept 160,000 Syrian Refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new Bangladeshi law that lets under-age girls marry their rapists for the greater good of the adolescent may put more children at risk of sexual abuse, child rights groups said on Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computers and cellphones seized during a deadly Special Operations raid in Yemen in January offer clues about attacks Al Qaeda could carry out in the future, including insights into new types of hidden explosives the group is making and new training tactics for militants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered what might end up being the oldest fossils ever found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered what might end up being the oldest fossils ever found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim students send flowers to Jewish organisations and synagogues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea and the United States agreed on Thursday to strengthen cooperation on financial sanctions against North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which of these Server should I go for? LiquidWeb VS OVH </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently using a servr from Unihost.com who I found out are reselling for OVH. I notice my sites has been slow and search traffic going down too consistently.

So I got an offer from LiquidWeb. I need your opinionon which Server is better.


Here is the one from LIquidWeb:


Processor: Intel Xeon E3-1271 v3 Quad-Core
RAM: 32GB DDR3 SDRAM
HD1: 2 x SSD Software RAID 1 (+250GB Crucial SSD (MLC))
HD2: SATA Backup Drive (+1 TB SATA (7,200 rpm))
GUARD: Guardian Data Protection Special 500G (+500GB Storage) (+MySQL Plugin) (+Guardian cPanel PlugIn) (+Continuous Backup Schedule) (+No Disk Safe Data Encryption Required)
SERVERCHASSIS: Standard - Single PSU - No Hot Swap Bays
OS: Linux OS (+CentOs 7 - 64Bit) (+Apache)
ControlPanel: cPanel/ Web Host Manager - Fully Managed (+Softaculous) (+Server Secure)
DDOSProtection: Standard DDoS Attack Protection (up to 2gbps)
ExtraIp: Public IP Addresses (+1 Public IP Address)
Bandwidth: 5 TB Outbound Bandwidth (+100M Uplink Port)
SetupFee: No setup fee
Monthly Fee: $239.00 /mo


From Unihost reselling OVH

Panel/WHM - 37.187.73.229 (22/02/2017 - 21/03/2017) $39.95USD
IP : 37.187.73.229
Intel Xeon E3 1245v2 - Abel Abel (22/02/2017 - 21/03/2017) $67.00USD
RAM: 32 GB DDR3
IPMI: no
Operating System: CentOS 6.7 x64
Guaranteed Bandwidth / Traffic: 250 Mbps / Unlimited
HDD: 2 x 2 TB SATA SoftRAID
Additional IP v4 (1 is already included. Up to 129 IP on server): no
Location: France
Backup Storage: 100 GB
------------------------------------------------------
Sub Total: $106.95USD




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full Inaugural Speech of Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
