<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 10:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't here for S3 so out of curiosity, what was the assassin trio? I'm guessing Zed, Kha and someone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 06:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a handful of characters who have gay undertones in their interaction and lore, and can easily be interpreted as such, Diana/Leona (this one I believe IronStylus even outright confirmed Diana was in love with Leona in an AMA iirc), Vi/Cait ("Cupcake"), the latest story about TF/Graves was pretty gay (or I, a straight man mind you, interpreted it as such, and yes I know TF was previously with Evelynn but it's completely possible for someone to be be attracted to both sexes and that's even less represented). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 17:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut down used to feel more satisfying but now it plays for any guy whos picked up two consecutive kills it feels meaningless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the new champ select, being "first pick" will be the least desirable position. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 04:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note, this isn't a complaint thread, just me noting what will be an interesting shift from the current state of things where getting stuck being last pick repeatedly is generally the least desired position. 

Going into the new champ select, Riot decided to give the bans to the last three picks (3, 4, 5) with the intention of making champ select fairer but thinking about it, with how roles are now going to be decided before anyone even enters champ select there's no longer going to be much advantage to being an early pick in ranked - first pick no longer gives you the benefit of role selection (as you'd have already chosen your role) or bans and instead the earlier you pick the more likely you're forced to blind pick your matchup and are going to end up getting countered. The only advantage I can think of is you may get a chance to first pick an OP champ but this is something I rarely see done in solo queue at present and people tend to just ban away OPs anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 14:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still delaying your powerspike somewhat going for hydra over ghostblade, on a champion like Zed who thrives on getting fed off his mid-game spike you don't want to sacrifice that just to get some lifesteal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 15:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the person. For some people it passes on its own, for some it passes with therapy and treatment (which in itself varies from person to person. As he said maybe the meds/psychiatrists he's seen weren't right for him, and there's one that'll work out for him out there), for some it just never gets better and lasts forever. For some once it's gone it's gone, for others it goes for a bit and then comes back. But regardless (and this is speaking as someone who did suffer it in high school and from talking to others who've been through the same) when you have depression you genuinely feel like it's going to be there forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
