<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7338</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Drives the Gender Gap? An Analysis Using Sexual Orientation (gays/lesbians) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 20:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soft paternalist policies that are manipulative collide consumer sovereignty, reflective sovereignty, and citizen sovereignty (new research) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fully agree (if the study is correct). But there are still even better alternatives. They suggest for example that "Achieve universal access to sexual and reproductive health [...] will return $120 for every dollar spent." 

All this stuff rather makes me think why no private investors try to do the job if the return is that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research on discrimination in the credit market... Analyzing access to financial capital among selfemployed immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 10:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 10:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cost-benefit analysis gives very different pictures. It is not enough to say that you get $16 per $1 invested... you need to compare it to other alternatives too... This is done by the Compenhagen Consensus, for example: http://www.copenhagenconsensus.com/post-2015-consensus/nobel-laureates-guide-smarter-global-targets-2030 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research on Immigration: "Decomposing Welfare Wedges: An Analysis of Welfare Dependence of Immigrants and Natives in Europe" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 10:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary of article:
Anecdotal evidence suggests that people migrate to avoid air pollution. In this paper, we empirically examine the extent to which air pollution is a push factor for international migration. We allow air pollution to affect migrants differently according to their educational attainment as well as their gender. We also instrument for the level of pollution. Results generally show that air pollution is positively associated with emigration for higher educated individuals but less so for those with less educational attainment. Gender differences are less pronounced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research: Air pollution affects international migration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary

Models of political competition portray political candidates as seeking the support of the median voter to win elections by majority voting. In practice, political candidates seek supermajorities, rather than majorities based on support of the median voter. We study the political benefits of supermajorities using data from Bavaria, the largest German state. Members of the Bavarian parliament had been permitted to hire relatives as office employees, but in the year 2000 the practice was prohibited, with exceptions that allowed continuation of employment of previously hired relatives. The circumstances provide an informative setting to relate political behavior to protection of incumbency. Our results show that the likelihood of politicians hiring relatives increased with the margin of the majority for the incumbent in the previous election. When the majority increased by one percentage point, the likelihood of hiring relatives increased by about one percentage point. Supermajorities thus facilitated political rent extraction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supermajorities and Political Rent Extraction in Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 13:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the abstract: This paper investigates whether financial cooperatives are crowded out by commercial banks in the process of financial sector development. We use a self-constructed database based on World Council of Credit Unions data for the years 1990-2011 of cooperatives in 55 developing countries. Our empirical results are threefold. First, financial cooperatives tend to reach more members in countries where the commercial banking sector is weak. This validates their role as a banking market failure solution. Second, in the process of commercial bank expansion, financial cooperatives run the risk of being crowded out. Third, the relationship is actually complex, since financial cooperatives seem to benefit from some kind of bank presence, especially as far as savings mobilization is concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Financial Cooperatives Crowded out by Commercial Banks in the Process of Financial Sector Development? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 13:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research Article on "The Long Shadows of Spanish and French Colonial Education" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 13:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
