<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject573</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, to spread awareness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Publish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racism and sexism in comments is actually against DC policy and will result in your comment being deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the car have camera built-in? The car probably saves at least the last few minutes before a crash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Volvos driving consumers today? Have they had someone injured while the self driving mechanism was engaged? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 09:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The middle driver was not right. You can't swerve into some other vehicle. But, the PT did nothing wrong (other than being a PT), so your first sentence is just blowhard bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying it was clever. I'm not sure it was completely voluntary.

Voluntary would have been telling us right after the accident happened.

Also, according to the blog post, Tesla learned of the investigation yesterday. They could have posted something this morning, before NHTSA announcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 04:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 04:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the PT corrected too sharply and lost control for a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do not want to die/crash/be injured, then yes, it does become your responsibility when all others are negligent and you are on a visible crash-course with another vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The black suv/truck to the right is to blame. Looks like it starts to speed off after the accident too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I cannot even read the page: http://imgur.com/2tK42eD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thus limiting the supply of such devices. Excellent work Apple! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This blog post is only reporting on the accident almost two months after the accident occurred.

It was also posted after market close on the last day of many fiscal years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if the Tesla was accelerating?

If not, definitely the trailer is at fault for turning when it did. The driver/autopilot is also at fault for not seeing and reacting to a giant vehicle crossing its path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the vehicle were turned slightly, it might have hit a wheel, or the truck body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Clinton emails released, including some she deleted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just tried to submit it, but someone beat me by an hour:

https://www.reddit.com/r/hillaryclinton/comments/4qn4mj/more_clinton_emails_released_including_some_she/

Edit: Oh, I can't find that one in the new section. I submitted again:

https://www.reddit.com/r/hillaryclinton/comments/4qnr3l/more_clinton_emails_released_including_some_she/

Edit2: Hmm, mine doesn't show up in the new section either. I messaged the mods about the problem, hopefully it will be there soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you posted this article there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 18:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So even in the face of hard data, your response is that personally you find it to be a "little woo woo" and don't have a single shred of evidence to back your stance up?
 
You seem to have trouble comprehending.

I said:


*MBTI depends on a written, English questionnaire*, so it already starts out terribly confounded.

*It also regularly categorizes me into two different groups.* There may be some vague concept of personality that can be discussed, but I'd guess those are cultural (eg. daughters taught to seek a husband or sons taught how to fight). I don't think anyone has or can give a scientifically understandable concept of personality. They are largely subjective theories interpreted by their adherents.

What more data do you want?

Holy shit, I don't even know why I attempted to engage in intellectual discussion with you. Stay classy and never change. God knows no amount of reality is gonna change your opinion anyway. 

Yes. Classy.

Keep trollin' bro
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...you cannot supply a definition for your primary term (personality)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I find claims about personality to seem a little woo woo.

MBTI depends on a written, English questionnaire, so it already starts out terribly confounded.

It also regularly categorizes me into two different groups. There may be some vague concept of personality that can be discussed, but I'd guess those are cultural (eg. daughters taught to seek a husband or sins taught how to fight). I don't think anyone has or can give a scientifically understandable concept of personality. They are largely subjective theories interpreted by their adherents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their upvotes now outweight their downvotes.

I don't see how the contents of the article or your comments were missed. Their comment *directly* addresses your claim.

Any two people will not perform identically, so your crazy thought is redundant. We can already know that two interviewees will not be identical, without even having to consider their gender (which means, even same-gendered pairs will not be identical). So, gender's not "all there is to it". In fact, what seems to be "to it" is simply that you are comparing two different individuals.


Saying 'no there's no gender differences, there's only PEOPLE differences' is beyond stupid and ignores evidence that all sides of this debate agree on

I don't see anyone here that said that.

The topic of this discussion is precisely that that are gender differences. That's an indisputable fact even if there's disagreement on where those differences come from.

You have me curious now, what are the differences (besides definitional: chromosomes, genitalia, etc)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 21:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy, scary thought: you are being downvoted for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Here's a crazy thought, ~~men and women~~individuals don't perform identically

Neither men and men nor women and women perform identically.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 11:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have just been an overextension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy Atkins most likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 01:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but Typescript doesn't add modules, classes, or literals; those are part of ECMAScript. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 05:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like left arm broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The measure says board members won't be paid, but will be reimbursed for actual incurred expenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vague generationist comment is made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it is called, "fraudulent inducement of employment". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The front man is already doing so by forcibly jacking up the vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Coinbase will cash your merchant wallet out to a checking account daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The machine could be better tracking the vehicle as it comes in, reducing the time to stop.

I can even imagine machines that could service the vehicle while in motion. The vehicle could transfer its momentum on to a rail or suspension system for the brief moments it would take to change out the tires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, make a machine that can adjust. Or, you just force the car into the right spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 19:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily.


You cannot regularly sell fraudulent debt on a large scale and not get found out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 06:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, only that there were two distinct phases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 06:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 18:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure?

It binds to the deploy phase by default and uploads all of the applications dependencies to S3 individually. On paper this actually makes the build slower, but the trick is that it only needs to do this if the dependency doesnt already exist in S3. And since our applications dependencies dont change very often, this step is usually a no-op.

Granted, I don't know if the dependencies come from a JAR or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what are you saying?

The folder is being passed and differential copies can be made from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 21:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A JAR is a compressed folder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 22:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I want to use DAO contracts if they can just be reverted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 20:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conspiring to empty the DAO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 07:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a minor point, but yes, such a set doesn't really *exist*. You cannot write down the set of all integers. If it were possible, you'd simply need to produce it as a counter-example to prove me wrong.

More to the point, I don't see why TMs wouldn't form some topological space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 05:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say "nothing to do", but yes, you cannot show the set of all integers either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the little l libertarianism, whose key feature, I believe, is non-violence.

A private individual depriving another of their freedoms is not compatible with non-violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violence should not be privatized. How can one be a libertarian and support private prisons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does one need more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 21:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not my analogy. I think you are confusing identities here.

Countability is irrelevant. I just don't think you can show the set of all Turing machines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 20:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not studied the code, but my understanding is that it should support a continuous deformation from the source to a common representation. I assume that the compiler is actually implemented as such a deformation.

I don't think the set of all Turing machines exists. There are too many of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 19:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general, certainly not a new finding. The particular stream of instructions might be.

Intuitively, it does seem to display a homeomorphism among all Turing machines,  though (which it should already be known exists in some form). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coins apparently joined a proposal whose seven days had already elapsed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 17:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The compiler *is* made to produce the same assembly for all programs (though, there is a large data chunk to go along with each) and you'll notice that there is only one jmp and it is to a constant label. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain what the use case is, here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but if it was run through a simulator first, it would have probably been noticed that it would consume a large portion of ETH? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be able to do pretty much anything you want. You get full arithmetic with logic and guaranteed termination. So, no bizarre loops that drain a fifth of the ecosystem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there no contract simulator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 22:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The limitation of Bitcoin scripts is that they must provably terminate, otherwise you can do pretty much whatever you want (I'm sure there is a hard cap on instruction length in a single transaction).

The current attack on DAO is not possible under Bitcoin as recursion is not available.

If you want to program your own:
https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 22:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever script someone puts into a transaction.

Here is a language reference: https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 21:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitcoin is already a smart contract that executes scripts. What does Ethereum add? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 21:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, now we have a Die Hard episode on our hands.

I thought I read that there are only 27 days of embargo (has anyone checked the embargo code?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 21:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard it will be forked and come back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At some point you run out of room in the tortilla. My last one was more like a giant taco and would definitely not have benefited from thick slices of jerk chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hmm. All programs reduce to the same instruction stream. Left, AES; right, Minesweeper. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starches, tubers, and roots are all pretty much the same thing.

Try some beans and grains. Here is an extremely satisfying dish:


    Mashed (refried) black beans (salt)
    Wild rice (cumin, chili, tomato)

    Saute:
    Cooked lentils
    Cooked green garbanzo beans
    Tomato
    Oil

    Make salsa:
    Tomato
    Onion
    Garlic
    Cilantro
    Lime
    Chili pepper
    Salt
    Pepper

    Warm a tortilla, then stuff it full of the above and some sliced avocado. You can add some cheese if you'd like. Eat with chips and salsa, and fruit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The faster speed through water doesn't matter. You can triangulate positions using multiple microphones in air as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearby shelter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 03:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably some corrections have been made to provide a reasonable sampling; otherwise, this graphic doesn't mean much without more description of what it is actually depicting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 01:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume average world temperature would mean a uniform sampling across the entire surface (water or land). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 00:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the image couldn't be using average annual temp within months because then all summer months would show hotter than average and vice versa for winter months.

Summer? The globe doesn't go on summer all at once. (ie. "summer" months are also "winter" months) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 23:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you zoom into the scale, you will see that the scale extends at least four pixels past the +1 marker.

The scale I suggest would put the center of the gradient equidistant from the lowest and highest temperature differences being represented.

As is, the spectrum is weighted to the yellow side simply as an artifact if how the data was handled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on how the average is calculated, it would matter.

The "dictionary definition" of average is mean, median, or mode. Though, I'd say other functions could be called an average as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scale does not have equal distance on both sides. You'll note that -1 is missing and the scale extends beyond +1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The image doesn't provide enough information to say what exactly is being shown.

I guess the mean is calculated for each column, then a cell is assigned a color based on the row's deviation from the column (month) average? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would matter for calculating a total mean though; which, I think is what the image is trying to use.

For example, the mean temperature for the year cannot be calculated just by adding up the mean temperatures for each month and dividing by twelve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the scale/coloring is very misleading.

I'd like to see a scale based on ````(max - min) / 2````.

Can you explain what you mean with "maintain constant lengths"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct usage? Where is that defined?

Even saying "mean" is not really sufficient. How was each point weighted? By month? They are of unequal sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mean? Median?

I would have expected the average temperature to fall in the middle of the scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the scale really not go to -1? What average function was used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 03:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know he was talking about a timed exclusive. I don't closely follow all of the technical details of the various VR devices, their platforms, and developer contracts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 22:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I believe that is the comment. I haven't seen any evidence that the person who started the self thread is/was a Serious Sam developer.

The developer also didn't say the offer was timed-exclusive, and I'd argue that it was implied that FB/Oculus was offering to buy the game outright, or at least for indefinite exclusivity.

That said, timed-exclusive is still exclusive.

I'm curious to know more specs on the shitton of money that FB/Oculus offered for six months of exclusivity. How do they they think that helps anyone?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't the door already open? How do you close a closed door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 22:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you trust the website, which is selling you to said third parties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The there is no way to guarantee that, short of forcing someone's eyelids open while your ad fills their entire field of view -- which you would certainly need to pay more for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hardest part would be collecting a catalog of DNA from the voters, and that wouldn't be too difficult.

The secondary handlers are well known and their DNA would be distributed over all the ballots, so they would be easy to filter out. Your DNA wouldn't be very likely to transfer to other ballots and I'd guess that you'd see a very clear signal for most ballots pointing to who cast it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you handled the ballot there may be recoverable DNA on it that could be used to make a guess at whose ballot is whose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can verify my vote is recorded accurately, any manipulation would be easily detectable, wouldn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 19:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that, exactly, "fronting the cash"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 19:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have that in my industry. I work in advanced automated industrial technology, so basically factories can *get rid of all employees*....

If the machine stops for whatever reason during the night (usually something tripping the light curtain safeties) it will text, email, or *call an employee* so they know they have to go in and fix/restart it.

Where does the fixer/restarter employee come from?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm...can you write something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 23:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, you must have a different definition of objective than I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 23:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did. Evola is dead.

Julius seemed quite confused. Do you know of a succinct definition if his claimed (by you) objective morality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 16:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, can you define objective morality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 15:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Objective morality is scary as fuck given that we can know all is subjective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 16:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, an industry veteran. What lab? Do you have a chemical engineering doctorate?

You'll note that I never claimed it to be easy to modify chain lengths (even though chain cracking *is* a key process in crude oil refinement).

I only claim that describing oil for plastic and fuel as having many different components is a bit misleading as the components are all substantially similar (compare to, e.g., milk).

*I don't consider my explanation to be particularly technical. A high school level understanding of chemistry should be sufficient to understand my claim.*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually pretty much all the same thing: chains of carbon atoms, saturated with hydrogen atoms. The only difference is the length of the carbon chains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *[civil]

*degree~~s~~

/nobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 05:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need are hydrocarbons, whose two raw materials are plentiful in earth's atmosphere and on its surface.

Exxon CEO probably is not even aware of this fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for contributing your opinion, sis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vested stock options are not a severance package, they are standard compensation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 23:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reply did not come until after this thread. Also, the offending comment is still offending and still receiving upvotes.

No one has yet been able to describe how such a goof could be made. Literally the easiest thing to answer the question is to hit [twitter.com/lea](http://twitter.com/lea), yet somehow we got an answer that shit on business insider and their editors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think npm is anyone's favorite tool. I think most are just waiting for a viable replacement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you mix them up? You'd have to somehow seek out some other person (instead of looking at the twitter account) and then not even do a cursory check to see if the person you sought out was the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 08:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA: Was contractor at Facebook, not employee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you think that was the same person? There are probably many people named Lea[h] Goldman.

I think the correction was in line with your judgmental tone and margin of error.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 05:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a standard REST discovery and client generation mechanism? I know SOAP could do it, but I thought REST was roll your own (ie. for programmers [internet users]). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 05:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to define lots of redirects. You just need a fall-through to your current rules if there isn't anything at the new URL. Or, alternatively, you can leave your current rules in place, but seal them so that no more can be added. If you want to reuse the slug, you will have to lose the reference to the old content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 03:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is easy. His post is evidence of itself. The information is factually incorrect and is thus synonymous with made up shit. How else do you think it formed? Shit does not spontaneously assemble AFAIK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 03:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you provide any evidence to back up your assertion?

The Tweet in question appears to have been an honest mistake as I cannot even find it. I've only seen cropped screenshots, so, presumably, @lea thinks it was a mistake and consequently unpublished it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 03:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not according to the rules of this sub.

Mmm. The guy acted as an authority on a question which he obviously knew shit about, which created a mistaken impression that it was actually the case that twitter has verified the account of the assistant management[sic] editor at business insider (they haven't) *AND* that business insider editors would publish something like this, in addition to just being flat wrong about the identity of the hypocrite. As you can see further down in the thread that people continue to relish in the bullshit instead of spending the 5 seconds it takes to read a bio.

Edit: If my post is not bullshit calling, then the GallowBoob posting is certainly not bullshit calling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 03:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, publicly firing some flavored information off the top of your head that incorrectly maligns entire swaths of people, when all it took to verify that your information was bad, was to read a few words on a twitter bio, is bullshit, and should be quit.

Worse, in this case, is that many other people ate up this bullshit and propagated it further. I don't think the thread has recovered even yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
