<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8864</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder when it's also legal to punch people in the face?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you like about boxing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 20:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I pick myself back up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 09:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 26, bisexual.  i've tried dating for 2 years, but got rejected by everyone and haven't gotten a date.  It's damaged my self esteem and confidence a lot.  Now I've decided to concentrate on myself.  I've decided to stop watching porn, change my appearance, and work out.  I feel like I'm not manly enough.  I'm a nerdy bookworm that's very quiet.  I can't find the energy to do anything anymore.  My passion for life has disappeared.  I 'm slowly feeling better after talking to people on 7 cups of tea.  I've started doing what I wanted, like reading, writing my book.  The next difficult habit i need to maintain is exercise, but I can't even do that.  How do I pick myself back up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a manly friend for mentorship and advice. Where do I find him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 05:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 03:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in, I abstained for two days, then I continued to fap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 03:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend also went through depression.  She said counseling and drugs did little to help.   Only exercise got her out of her rut.  I'm also  hesitant to take pills because of the lack of research with long term effects.  I'm also living with my parents, and I don't want to go through therapy because they might know.  Plus, my insurance doesn't cover mental health issues, and paying out of pocket is too expensive for an unemployed grad student like me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 02:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea, I can sleep on the hard floor.  I have thin thatch mattress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 02:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried nofap.  It didn't work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've started to try to do things for myself, like reading good books and writing my book.  I've also tried exercising, but when I get out of bed and start lifting in my room, I get bored and crawl back to bed.  It's like all the energy from myself is just gone, and I go day to day barely functioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been a month of trying to improve myself, and I feel just as miserable as I did before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help me, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boxing and commitment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 22:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While boxing is fun, I realize that the ones being pro really put in the work at the gym.  I'm a full time grad student, and my priorities are in school first.  I admire the ones who put in the time and effort to be the best at boxing.  Kudos to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Personal Blog Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 02:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been writing a blog about Chinese literature and Chinese art commentary for the past two years on blogger. I haven't been getting many views and I felt no one was reading it, so I stopped posting on my blog. Do you guys have any tips to improve? Should I pander to my audience with my writing? Should I use a different host? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant should I write something thing that I think would be popular? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Personal Blog Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 20:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been writing a blog about Chinese literature and Chinese art commentary for the past two years on blogger.  I haven't been getting many views and I felt no one was reading it, so I stopped posting on my blog.  Do you guys have any tips to improve?  Should I pander to my audience with my writing?  Should I use a different host? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 07:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only decided to do so.  I was researching methods and mental mindsets that would be best for a beginner to be consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 03:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, I did not know this subreddit existed. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you find the motivation to change myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried dating for 2 years, but got rejected by everyone and haven't gotten a date.  It's damaged my self esteem and confidence a lot.  Now I've decided to concentrate on myself.  I've decided to stop watching porn, change my appearance, and work out.  I feel like I'm not manly enough.  I'm a nerdy bookworm that's very quiet with a very doughy body.  I can't find the energy to do anything anymore.  My passion for life has disappeared.  How do you get it back?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 18:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really busy yesterday, so I didn't have time to wallow in self-pity.  Which is a good thing I guess.   At least something is happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 04:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right.  Like junk food to the body, porn is junk food to the mind.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
